<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="https://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Exchange4media</title>
    <link>https://www.exchange4media.com</link>
    <description>At Exchange4media, read the latest news and updates on advertising agencies, marketing, print, radio, digital, television, media, events and happenings in India.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 08:30:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Our purpose is to bring value, not kill competition: Bhaskar Bhat, MD, Titan</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing/our-purpose-is-to-bring-value-not-kill-competition-bhaskar-bhat-md-titan-93389.html</link>
      <guid>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing/our-purpose-is-to-bring-value-not-kill-competition-bhaskar-bhat-md-titan-93389.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>content@exchange4media.com (exchange4media News Service)</author>
      <description>At the launch of Taneira’s first flagship store, Bhaskar Bhat, Managing Director, Titan Company Limited, spoke about Titan’s new offering and the changing retail landscape in the country.</description>
      <content:encoded>
        <html lang="en" prefix="op: http://media.facebook.com/op#">
          <head><link rel="canonical" href="https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing/our-purpose-is-to-bring-value-not-kill-competition-bhaskar-bhat-md-titan_93389.html">
                    <meta property="op:markup_version" content="v1.0">
                    <meta charset="utf-8">
                    <meta property="op:markup_version" content="v1.0"></head>
          <body>
            <article>
              <header><time class="op-published" datetime="Tue, 11 Dec 18 18:30:00 +0000">Tue, 11 Dec 18 18:30:00 +0000</time></header>
              <figure><image><img src="93389-BhaskarBhat.jpg" alt="Smiley face" height="470" width="870"></image></figure>
              <p><p>Titan Company Ltd, which has successfully launched many lifestyle brands over the years-- Titan, Tanishq, Fastrack, Xylys, Raga, Skinn (fragrances), has now entered the textile category with its new offering Taneira.</p>

<p>The company might be a late entrant in the category, but it plans to draw on its strong brand appeal to build its presence across the country.</p>

<p>At the launch of Taneira&rsquo;s first flagship store, Bhaskar Bhat, Managing Director, Titan Company Limited, spoke about Titan&rsquo;s new offering and the changing retail landscape in the country.</p>

<p>Excerpts:</p>

<p><strong>What was the thought behind launching this new category?</strong></p>

<p>See where I sit,&nbsp;which is as the head of the company,&nbsp;it has to be a combination of&nbsp;inspiration and business sense.&nbsp;We have what is known as a sandbox,&nbsp;it&#39;s called the Titan hexagon,&nbsp;which we apply to look at the future.&nbsp;One of the important sides of this hexagon is the under-served and underpenetrated&nbsp;and under-organized.&nbsp;Any category which has two out of three of these,&nbsp;we would like to explore.</p>

<p>So in that process, we found this (Taneira) as one, and we have several others.&nbsp;And as we explored more and more, we realized&nbsp;that it has&nbsp;a significant proportion of unorganized. We also realized that this is a category where we can bring more value,&nbsp;and it is a very big category.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>

<p>Looking at the size of this category and given our ability to transform the category combined with our strong retail play is a big strength that we have. Also, branding in this category has not happened so often in the past, and branding is something we bring to the table&nbsp;apart from retail expertise.&nbsp;</p>

<p><strong>In a world which is betting big on digital and considers mobile as the future, how would you contextualize this big investment in offline retail?</strong></p>

<p>I don&#39;t think offline will ever go away for categories where&nbsp;standardization is not the driver of the demand.&nbsp;Anything which has touched and feel has a very strong offline component.&nbsp;&nbsp;But&nbsp;the marriage of the two is what we do,&nbsp;which is called Omni, and we are doing that very well, for example in the eyewear category.</p>

<p><strong>Would you call yourself a late entrant in this category? How do you plan to take on players who have been in this business for a long time?</strong></p>

<p>Our impulse is never to compete, our impulse is to serve. I&#39;m not saying this in any philosophical manner. We have found great value and inspiration in being&nbsp;totally driven by the consumers.&nbsp;So consumer insight is a very important function&nbsp;in the company.</p>

<p>In every store, we listen to our customers and&nbsp;we are driven by the customers. That is what has brought us size and scale,&nbsp;and what happens to the competitors&nbsp;in a way is not our problem. Our purpose is not to kill the competition; our purpose is to bring value. I believe we will create so much value&nbsp;that people would want to come to us.&nbsp;</p>

<p><strong>You have </strong><strong>helmed</strong><strong> the success of Titan across categories, what would you call the enablers of this success story?</strong></p>

<p>Fundamentally, customer-centricity; we are driven by the customers;&nbsp;fantastic people orientation in the company. We have a theory about people-- which is unconditional positive regard.&nbsp;It means people first before any other stakeholder. So we are totally people focused. The other factor is design.&nbsp;</p>

<p><strong>How do you see the future of retail panning out in India over the next few years?</strong></p>

<p>I think it will be Omni&nbsp;and the relevance of&nbsp;brick and mortar stores will continue.&nbsp;As I said,&nbsp;for standard products and technology led products,&nbsp;it will&nbsp;become less and less relevant&nbsp;but there will be flagship stores,&nbsp;which will be less for sales and more for showcasing.</p></p>
              <footer><aside>@2018</aside></footer>
            </article>
          </body>
        </html>
      </content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning a thing or two from the Mumbai Police about upping the Social Media game</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital/learning-a-thing-or-two-from-the-mumbai-police-about-upping-the-social-media-game-93403.html</link>
      <guid>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital/learning-a-thing-or-two-from-the-mumbai-police-about-upping-the-social-media-game-93403.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>content@exchange4media.com (exchange4media News Service)</author>
      <description>Sunchika Pandey Group Director, Citizen Initiatives & Government division, Gozoop, tells us how she built the social profile for the Mumbai Police Department step by step</description>
      <content:encoded>
        <html lang="en" prefix="op: http://media.facebook.com/op#">
          <head><link rel="canonical" href="https://www.exchange4media.com/digital/learning-a-thing-or-two-from-the-mumbai-police-about-upping-the-social-media-game_93403.html">
                    <meta property="op:markup_version" content="v1.0">
                    <meta charset="utf-8">
                    <meta property="op:markup_version" content="v1.0"></head>
          <body>
            <article>
              <header><time class="op-published" datetime="Tue, 11 Dec 18 18:30:00 +0000">Tue, 11 Dec 18 18:30:00 +0000</time></header>
              <figure><image><img src="93403-mumbaipolice.jpg" alt="Smiley face" height="470" width="870"></image></figure>
              <p><p>Lately, the woman behind the famed Mumbai Police department&rsquo;s Twitter handle (@MumbaiPolice) finds herself catching up on the latest binge-worthy shows, viral memes and Twitter trends whenever she finds the time.&nbsp;</p>

<p>From Game of Thrones and Stranger Things to Twitter memes like GharSeNikalTeHi, Sunchika Pandey and her team is thinking content round the clock and tries to never miss a social media opportunity for the Mumbai Police. Over the last three years, the Mumbai Police Department&rsquo;s Twitter handle has become every Mumbaikar&rsquo;s go-to channel for latest updates on law and order related happenings in the city, to register complaints, all while being treated to social media memes on the side. The social media strategy is a prime example for consumer facing brands that are trying to establish a strong social media presence.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>

<p><strong>Seeing Content Everywhere</strong><br />
&nbsp;<br />
Content has become a state of mind for the Mumbai Police social media team. &quot;If I see a glass lying around on the table, I wonder how to use it as content!&quot; she says. But she is not cued into all the millenial themes and trends, so she&nbsp;generally gets all her&nbsp;references checked with her&nbsp;team of youngsters.&nbsp;&quot;But now I am also watching all the popular shows,&rdquo; confesses Pandey, who is&nbsp;the Group Director of its Citizen Initiatives &amp; Government division at independent digital agency, Gozoop.&nbsp;</p>

<p>It&rsquo;s not just Pandey, even the policemen who run the Twitter operations for the department have begun looking at the world around them through the lens of &ldquo;content.&rdquo; This is the result of the Mumbai Police department&rsquo;s innovative attempt at reaching out to the citizens of Mumbai through the micro-blogging platform three years ago.&nbsp;</p>

<p>Every brand is talking the language of content, and there is no reason&nbsp;the Mumbai Police should be found lagging. &ldquo;What ticks with the readers now-a-days is content. Content that is quirky, trendy, timeless, resonating...&nbsp;the list goes on. Mumbai Police has ticked all the boxes.&nbsp;Messages about safety, social &amp; traffic discipline, celebration, respect for martyrs, cyber security, and all such occasions are so very well weaved into different engaging formats of content. By default you end up consuming these pieces and the point is driven home,&rdquo; says Shekhar Mhaskar, EVP Isobar India, decoding the success of the Mumbai Police&#39;s social media game.</p>

<p>&ldquo;The first tweet we ever put out was : Why should the police station be the only place where we meet? Let&rsquo;s meet here every day,&rdquo; recollects Pandey. Hers and her&nbsp;team&rsquo;s efforts to make the police department more approachable and less fearful for&nbsp;the citizens has earned the department the moniker Meme-bai Police and Amul of Government departments.</p>

<p><strong>Response Engenders Trust&nbsp;</strong></p>

<p>Hidden under the satirical content and prompt informative responses from the department is a lesson for all marketers who are trying to create a social media persona for their brands. To Pandey the lesson is very simple: a clear vision plus knowledge of target audience complemented by fulfilment of brand promise = success.&nbsp;</p>

<p>Even Pandey knows this is easier said than done. Social media handles of most consumer facing companies are inundated with complaints from disgruntled consumers every day. These complaints are mostly met with automated responses that only irk consumers further.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;There are instances when a disgruntled consumer feels a loss of trust with the brand because of a negative experience and cannot be assuaged by following documented response matrices. This is where a brand can elevate itself to the next level of sophistication &ndash; with their ability to humanise interactions and setting up of strong internal processes that speak with different departments to effectively act upon their customer commitments,&rdquo; says Sakshi Arora, Strategy Director, Digitas India.&nbsp;</p>

<p>Anticipating the citizen outpouring, at least eight policemen and two senior police officers monitor the Mumbai Police and Police Commissioner&rsquo;s Twitter handles at any given point. The policemen monitor the tweets and direct messages sent to these two handles until 3-4am every day. &ldquo;The clear mandate when we started out was that we must respond to every single tweet,&rdquo; Pandey says.&nbsp;</p>

<p><strong>Kidding, but seriously...</strong></p>

<p>The mission of the Mumbai Police was to utilise Twitter as yet another touchpoint where the department could interact with the citizens. &ldquo;It was not in our plan to make it iconic in the way that it has become,&rdquo; says Pandey with humility.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We wanted to make people smile and that&rsquo;s how we thought about using humour in our posts.&rdquo; At the same time as the Twitter handle of the police department the content had to always adhere to a certain high moral and ethical code. &ldquo;As Mumbai Police we needed to maintain the dignity of the officers and the uniform. That is why we chose satire.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Mumbai Police has resonated with the citizens of Mumbai by &ldquo;challenging the status quo on the type of online personality an administrative body should have,&rdquo; says Arora. This dark humour coupled with healthy engagement with citizens gives Mumbai Police its clutter breaking social presence and huge organic following.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Brands typically monitor their social media handles but worry that saying something edgy will get them trolled. Typically BFSI, healthcare, and B2B brands are uncomfortable about using humour on social channels. But the Mumbai Police is okay with taking a stance and even responding to citizens. Now the mental impression of Mumbai Police has improved because of the social media presence of the department,&rdquo; says Siddharth Hegde, MD &amp; Founder, Ethinos Digital Marketing.&nbsp;</p>

<p>All of these factors have made Mumbai Police a social media case study that other police departments across the country have begun to emulate. The Bangalore and Kolkata City Police engage with their citizens on social media very successfully. &quot;Even the UP Police has launched a Twitter account and that has helped the department improve its image,&quot; quips Pandey. As the&nbsp;&nbsp;Group Director of its Citizen Initiatives &amp; Government division at Gozoop, Pandey wishes to work with more government bodies, helping them engage in a healthy manner with citizens.&nbsp;</p></p>
              <footer><aside>@2018</aside></footer>
            </article>
          </body>
        </html>
      </content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delivery boy eating customers' food: Will the viral video brew trouble for Zomato?</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing/delivery-boy-eating-customers-food-will-the-viral-video-brew-trouble-for-zomato-93408.html</link>
      <guid>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing/delivery-boy-eating-customers-food-will-the-viral-video-brew-trouble-for-zomato-93408.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>content@exchange4media.com (exchange4media News Service)</author>
      <description>Industry experts signal that the incident is a big hit to not just Zomato but also other players in the category</description>
      <content:encoded>
        <html lang="en" prefix="op: http://media.facebook.com/op#">
          <head><link rel="canonical" href="https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing/delivery-boy-eating-customers-food-will-the-viral-video-brew-trouble-for-zomato_93408.html">
                    <meta property="op:markup_version" content="v1.0">
                    <meta charset="utf-8">
                    <meta property="op:markup_version" content="v1.0"></head>
          <body>
            <article>
              <header><time class="op-published" datetime="Tue, 11 Dec 18 18:30:00 +0000">Tue, 11 Dec 18 18:30:00 +0000</time></header>
              <figure><image><img src="93408-zomato.jpg" alt="Smiley face" height="470" width="870"></image></figure>
              <p><p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif"><span style="background:white"><span style="color:black">Online food ordering and restaurant reservation platform Zomato found itself at the receiving end of public ire after a video showing one of its delivery boys consuming food out of its boxed orders appeared on social media. In the two-minute video, the boy was then seen re-sealing the packages, which were likely to be delivered, and putting them back into the delivery bag. </span></span></span></span></p>

<p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif"><span style="background:white"><span style="color:black">The video has gone viral and has </span></span><span style="color:#222222">prompted widespread outrage on social media, with people questioning the brand and its credibility. </span></span></span></p>

<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-lang="en">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><a href="https://twitter.com/deepigoyal?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@deepigoyal</a> Hope you are doing something to repose the trust on your brand <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Zomato?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Zomato</a> <a href="https://t.co/Z6LuSL3cGW">pic.twitter.com/Z6LuSL3cGW</a></p>
&mdash; Samrat Ghosh (@SamratYokel) <a href="https://twitter.com/SamratYokel/status/1072381186125774849?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 11, 2018</a></blockquote>
<script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>

<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-lang="en">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">What is this <a href="https://twitter.com/Zomato?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@Zomato</a> I just placed an order, should I cancel it? <a href="https://t.co/L6izWHajpO">pic.twitter.com/L6izWHajpO</a></p>
&mdash; Ankita (@Miss_Takken) <a href="https://twitter.com/Miss_Takken/status/1072150302592253952?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 10, 2018</a></blockquote>
<script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>

<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-lang="en">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">It&#39;s not fault of employee but it is d biggest mistake of Brand name <a href="https://twitter.com/Zomato?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@Zomato</a> who made it&#39;s packing so that employee can unpack it thn repack it <a href="https://t.co/yLlIi16uWz">https://t.co/yLlIi16uWz</a></p>
&mdash; ONK (@omkak55) <a href="https://twitter.com/omkak55/status/1072212529575645184?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 10, 2018</a></blockquote>
<script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>

<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-lang="en">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><a href="https://twitter.com/Zomato?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@Zomato</a> Here is what I received on Whatsapp!! Please attend to it or it can damage the Brand really badly. <a href="https://t.co/fpoLk49iLW">pic.twitter.com/fpoLk49iLW</a></p>
&mdash; Ajay Sharma (@itz_aj) <a href="https://twitter.com/itz_aj/status/1072207501901381632?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 10, 2018</a></blockquote>
<script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>

<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-lang="en">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><a href="https://twitter.com/Zomato?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@Zomato</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/ZomatoIN?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@ZomatoIN</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/zomatocare?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@zomatocare</a><br />
<br />
What the heck is this .. Customers trust the brand blindly and this is what we get in return . Cant dare to believe that we are being served such kind of food . ?? <a href="https://t.co/4O85PEz6nb">pic.twitter.com/4O85PEz6nb</a></p>
&mdash; James Chacko (@JamesChacko1984) <a href="https://twitter.com/JamesChacko1984/status/1072196597658894336?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 10, 2018</a></blockquote>
<script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>

<p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif">The question that now arises is will the brand be impacted due to this? What&rsquo;s interesting is that Zomato&rsquo;s competitor Swiggy recently rolled an ad communication asking consumers to empathise with delivery partners, as they, like each one of us, have a name and unique identity that they would like everybody to acknowledge. Will this incident then jeopardize Zomato&rsquo;s image and give its competitors an edge over it? Or will Zomato be able to reclaim itself just right post the fiasco?</span></span></p>

<p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif">Kiran Khalap, Co-founder &amp; Managing Director, Chlorophyll&nbsp;Brand &amp; Communications, calls this a </span></span></p>

<p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif">classic crisis and contends that besides sacking the delivery boy, the brand will have to engage directly with the end-consumer to explain putting into place processes that will prevent recurrence of such incidents. </span></span></p>

<p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm">&nbsp;</p>

<p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif">&ldquo;Hopefully Zomato has a crisis management manual. It is the same with the Cadbury&rsquo;s or the Nestle Maggi crisis: telling the truth always helps! It is difficult, but it can be done. And if done well, Zomato will regain its lost goodwill,&rdquo; reasons Khalap. </span></span></p>

<p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm">&nbsp;</p>

<p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif">Brand expert Gaurav Gulati opines that the video has surely damaged the brand reputation and is a lesson that even others in the category should pay heed to. &ldquo;This surely is going to create a lot of trouble for the brand. Moreover, people might start poking the brand and Zomato delivery boys with sarcasm and prefer to use the services of their competitors instead. But it is high time for all these brands to take food tampering and hygiene very seriously.&rdquo; </span></span></p>

<p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif">Gulati adds that Zomato recently raised fresh funding of $210 million from Alibaba&rsquo;s Ant Financials for payment solution, but as things have changed, they should probably utilise most of the funds on image building and fixing brand reputation. After all, it&rsquo;s the matter of existence now.</span></span></p>

<p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif">Harish Bijoor, brand guru &amp; founder of Harish Bijoor Consults Inc, remarks that pulling one delivery boy off roster does nothing and is a big hit not only to Zomato in terms of &nbsp;consumer-imagery and impression, but to the entire food and beverage delivery category altogether. &ldquo;When a brand outsources literally everything it does, issues such as these are bound to be a constant bother. It is important to make food handling and delivery totally tamper-proof. Packaging can play a crucial role here,&rdquo; says Bijoor.</span></span></p>

<p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif"><span style="background:white"><span style="color:black">Meanwhile, responding to the criticism, Z</span></span><span style="color:#222222">omato released an official statement, saying that it will soon introduce tamper-proof packaging.</span></span></span></p>

<p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif"><span style="color:#222222">&quot;In our commitment towards mitigating any possibility of tampering with food,&nbsp;Zomato will soon introduce tamper-proof tapes and other precautionary measures to ensure we safeguard against any chances of tampering of food. Zomato has a zero tolerance policy for tampering of food.&rdquo; </span></span></span></p>

<p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif"><span style="color:#222222">&ldquo;We have found that the video was shot in Madurai. The person in the video is a delivery partner on our fleet. We have spoken to him at length - and while we understand that this was a human error in judgement, we have taken him off the platform. This incident only makes our commitment to fleet training, scheduling and process even stronger. We stand behind our extensive fleet who do the right thing across many hours of the day,&rdquo; the statement said further.</span></span></span></p></p>
              <footer><aside>@2018</aside></footer>
            </article>
          </body>
        </html>
      </content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thanthi TV Editor-in-Chief Rangaraj Pandey steps down</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/media-tv/thanthi-tv-editor-in-chief-rangaraj-pandey-steps-down-93410.html</link>
      <guid>https://www.exchange4media.com/media-tv/thanthi-tv-editor-in-chief-rangaraj-pandey-steps-down-93410.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>content@exchange4media.com (exchange4media News Service)</author>
      <description>Rangaraj Pandey said he wanted a break from his daily routine and also give opportunity to next generation of journalists.</description>
      <content:encoded>
        <html lang="en" prefix="op: http://media.facebook.com/op#">
          <head><link rel="canonical" href="https://www.exchange4media.com/media-tv/thanthi-tv-editor-in-chief-rangaraj-pandey-steps-down_93410.html">
                    <meta property="op:markup_version" content="v1.0">
                    <meta charset="utf-8">
                    <meta property="op:markup_version" content="v1.0"></head>
          <body>
            <article>
              <header><time class="op-published" datetime="Tue, 11 Dec 18 18:30:00 +0000">Tue, 11 Dec 18 18:30:00 +0000</time></header>
              <figure><image><img src="93410-Pandey.jpg" alt="Smiley face" height="470" width="870"></image></figure>
              <p><p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif">Rangaraj Pandey, who was the Editor-in-Chief of Thanthi TV, has quit from his post, with effect from Monday. Pandey announced his decision to step down in an emotional video, where he thanked the viewers and said that he wanted a break from his daily routine. He added that he also wanted to give space and opportunity to the next generation of journalists. </span></span></p>

<p><iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/c0KWyKkSznY" width="560"></iframe></p>

<p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif"><span style="background:white">Pandey, who has 22 years of experience in journalism, began his career with Tamil newspaper Dinamalar. <span style="color:#222222">He started the well-known satire column &ldquo;Doubtu Dhanabalu&rdquo;, a fictional character who mocks the day-to-day political discourse in Tamil Nadu and pan-India.</span></span></span></span></p>

<p style="margin-top:6.0pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:6.0pt; margin-left:0cm; text-align:start; -webkit-text-stroke-width:0px"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif"><span style="background:white"><span style="color:#222222"><span style="line-height:inherit"><span style="font-variant-ligatures:normal"><span style="font-variant-caps:normal"><span style="orphans:2"><span style="widows:2"><span style="text-decoration-style:initial"><span style="text-decoration-color:initial"><span style="word-spacing:0px">His interviews with famous personalities made him a popular television face. He hosts talk show &ldquo;Kelvikku Enna Badhil&rdquo; (What is the answer to the question?). Pandey also hosted a prime-time news debate programme &lsquo;Ayutha Ezhuthu&lsquo;. He is renowned for his simple and spontaneous questioning style. Pandey, who hails from North India, is a post graduate in Tamil from Madurai Kamaraj University. </span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></p>

<p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif">&nbsp;</span></span></p></p>
              <footer><aside>@2018</aside></footer>
            </article>
          </body>
        </html>
      </content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2019 will be the year of regional content: Tarun Katial, ZEE5</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital/2019-will-be-the-year-of-regional-content-tarun-katial-zee5-93411.html</link>
      <guid>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital/2019-will-be-the-year-of-regional-content-tarun-katial-zee5-93411.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>content@exchange4media.com (exchange4media News Service)</author>
      <description>The CEO on the consumption drivers, reception towards region-specific subscription packs in 2018, partnerships and how 2019 will only get bigger</description>
      <content:encoded>
        <html lang="en" prefix="op: http://media.facebook.com/op#">
          <head><link rel="canonical" href="https://www.exchange4media.com/digital/2019-will-be-the-year-of-regional-content-tarun-katial-zee5_93411.html">
                    <meta property="op:markup_version" content="v1.0">
                    <meta charset="utf-8">
                    <meta property="op:markup_version" content="v1.0"></head>
          <body>
            <article>
              <header><time class="op-published" datetime="Tue, 11 Dec 18 18:30:00 +0000">Tue, 11 Dec 18 18:30:00 +0000</time></header>
              <figure><image><img src="1526893051_UNDgGs_Tarun-Katial.jpg" alt="Smiley face" height="470" width="870"></image></figure>
              <p><p style="margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="background:white"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif"><span style="font-size:11.0pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,&quot;sans-serif&quot;"><span style="color:#222222">2018 has been a rather action-packed year for ZEE5 and the upcoming year or two will only see things getting bigger and better for ZEEL&rsquo;s OTT platform with more investments being pushed in that direction. Punit Goenka, MD &amp; CEO of ZEEL, had mentioned earlier in one of his interviews that the streaming service is their next big bet when it comes to investment and cornering incremental and additional viewers. With increasing investment he is expecting the business to break even in three to five years.</span></span></span></span></span></span></p>

<p style="margin-bottom:8.0pt; text-align:start; -webkit-text-stroke-width:0px; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="background:white"><span style="font-variant-ligatures:normal"><span style="font-variant-caps:normal"><span style="orphans:2"><span style="widows:2"><span style="text-decoration-style:initial"><span style="text-decoration-color:initial"><span style="word-spacing:0px"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif"><span style="font-size:11.0pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,&quot;sans-serif&quot;"><span style="color:#222222">Tarun Katial, CEO, ZEE5, talks to e4m about the future plans and how the past year has been for the OTT platform, including the reception, region specific subscription pack and original content. Excerpts:</span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></p>

<p style="text-align:start; -webkit-text-stroke-width:0px; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="background:white"><span style="font-variant-ligatures:normal"><span style="font-variant-caps:normal"><span style="orphans:2"><span style="widows:2"><span style="text-decoration-style:initial"><span style="text-decoration-color:initial"><span style="word-spacing:0px"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif"><strong><span style="font-size:11.0pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,&quot;sans-serif&quot;"><span style="color:#222222">Innovative pricing</span></span></span></strong><br />
<span style="font-size:11.0pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,&quot;sans-serif&quot;"><span style="color:#222222">Apart from bringing in regional content, ZEE5 played around with the pricing and introduced special subscription packs for Tamil, Telugu and Kannada audience. This enables users to access premium language content at half the price (Rs 49/month).<br />
Katial shared that the reception to these region specific packs has been &lsquo;great&rsquo; as they are offering live TV, regional original content, digital movie premieres and early access to regional shows even before TV. &ldquo;So it&rsquo;s a healthy bouquet of content with lot of depth for Tamil, Telugu and Kannada consumers. After South, we will take a break for a quarter and go East,&rdquo; revealed Katial. &nbsp;<br />
2018 saw original regional content really taking off with OTT players eyeing growth from tier II and III cities. But that, says Katial, was just the tip of the iceberg. &ldquo;2019 will be the actual year of language (regional) content, the big proliferation of original content and digital movies in India. The uptake of original content will move 3-4 times,&rdquo; he said.</span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></p>

<p style="margin-bottom:12.0pt; text-align:start; -webkit-text-stroke-width:0px; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="background:white"><span style="font-variant-ligatures:normal"><span style="font-variant-caps:normal"><span style="orphans:2"><span style="widows:2"><span style="text-decoration-style:initial"><span style="text-decoration-color:initial"><span style="word-spacing:0px"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif"><span style="font-size:11.0pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,&quot;sans-serif&quot;"><span style="color:#222222">Katial also mentioned the launch of a premium brand around ZEE5. &quot;It&rsquo;s in the process of being created. SVOD section will be branded separately. It&rsquo;s a different experience than AVOD subset. Several features will be added to it.&quot;</span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></p>

<p style="text-align:start; -webkit-text-stroke-width:0px; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="background:white"><span style="font-variant-ligatures:normal"><span style="font-variant-caps:normal"><span style="orphans:2"><span style="widows:2"><span style="text-decoration-style:initial"><span style="text-decoration-color:initial"><span style="word-spacing:0px"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif"><strong><span style="font-size:11.0pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,&quot;sans-serif&quot;"><span style="color:#222222">Content game strong</span></span></span></strong></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></p>

<p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="background:white"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif"><span style="font-size:11.0pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,&quot;sans-serif&quot;"><span style="color:#222222">Right from its launch, ZEE5 has kept its content game strong especially for originals and movie acquisition. It came out with 15 originals across six languages including the big-budget &lsquo;Karenjit Kaur&rsquo; and big digital premieres of popular titles such as Mulk, Parmanu, Stree and Veere Di Wedding. The strategy of movie premieres particularly worked as it was one of the major consumption drivers. &nbsp;<br />
It&rsquo;s now looking to launch over 90 originals in FY2019 and reach 150+ digital premiers in the next 18 months. Katial mentioned that audience sees value in original content as it&rsquo;s a big differentiator. This explains the deep investment. &ldquo;Original movies did well, case in point being &lsquo;Tiger&rsquo; (Emraan Hashmi) We have &lsquo;Rangbaaz&rsquo; coming up next month with Saqib Saleem which is as big as &lsquo;Karenjit Kaur&rsquo; for us. Then there will be big original shows in Tamil, Telugu, Bengali and Marathi. We will amp up in 2019. A slate of 40-50 big shows will come up over the next two quarters,&rdquo; Katial added.<br />
AVOD is not getting overshadowed as Katial sees TV shows and their characters being big drivers. &ldquo;We have content beyond the general shows like character journeys and best scenes. Lot of content is created outside the core content. We will continue to invest behind that as well.&rdquo;</span></span></span></span></span></span></p>

<p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="background:white"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif"><span style="font-size:11.0pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,&quot;sans-serif&quot;"><span style="color:#222222">&quot;Language original content, shows around specific themes and relevant topics will continue to resonate well with Indian consumers. You will see off-take in subscription,&quot; says Katial.</span></span></span></span></span></span></p>

<p style="text-align:start; -webkit-text-stroke-width:0px; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="background:white"><span style="font-variant-ligatures:normal"><span style="font-variant-caps:normal"><span style="orphans:2"><span style="widows:2"><span style="text-decoration-style:initial"><span style="text-decoration-color:initial"><span style="word-spacing:0px"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif"><strong><span style="font-size:11.0pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,&quot;sans-serif&quot;"><span style="color:#222222">Distribution</span></span></span></strong><br />
<span style="font-size:11.0pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,&quot;sans-serif&quot;"><span style="color:#222222">Like any other OTT streaming platform, ZEE5 hasn&rsquo;t left any stone unturned to reach the consumer.&nbsp; This goes beyond the regular tie-ups with telecom service providers, digital wallets and smart TVs. For instance, for travel start-up RailYatri customers, ZEE5 had introduced a sachet subscription which gets bundled with the bookings. Similar partnerships with Oyo, MakeMyTrip and RedBus among others are aimed at travel-loving consumers by offering them discounts. &ldquo;Sachet consumers come for a short period of time and want entertainment on the go.&rdquo;</span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></p>

<p style="text-align:start; -webkit-text-stroke-width:0px; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="background:white"><span style="font-variant-ligatures:normal"><span style="font-variant-caps:normal"><span style="orphans:2"><span style="widows:2"><span style="text-decoration-style:initial"><span style="text-decoration-color:initial"><span style="word-spacing:0px"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif"><span style="font-size:11.0pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,&quot;sans-serif&quot;"><span style="color:#222222">All this and more is definitely working as the ZEE5 app garnered 41.3 million Monthly Active Users in Sep&rsquo;18, a whopping 190% growth since Apr&rsquo;18, according to data provided by ZEE5. And they have just about begun.</span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></p>

<p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm">&nbsp;</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p></p>
              <footer><aside>@2018</aside></footer>
            </article>
          </body>
        </html>
      </content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WPP takes on new identity to push its ‘radical evolution’ plan</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements/wpp-takes-on-new-identity-to-push-its-radical-evolution-plan-93412.html</link>
      <guid>https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements/wpp-takes-on-new-identity-to-push-its-radical-evolution-plan-93412.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>content@exchange4media.com (exchange4media News Service)</author>
      <description>Superunion and Landor have collaborated to create the new identity for WPP</description>
      <content:encoded>
        <html lang="en" prefix="op: http://media.facebook.com/op#">
          <head><link rel="canonical" href="https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements/wpp-takes-on-new-identity-to-push-its-radical-evolution-plan_93412.html">
                    <meta property="op:markup_version" content="v1.0">
                    <meta charset="utf-8">
                    <meta property="op:markup_version" content="v1.0"></head>
          <body>
            <article>
              <header><time class="op-published" datetime="Tue, 11 Dec 18 18:30:00 +0000">Tue, 11 Dec 18 18:30:00 +0000</time></header>
              <figure><image><img src="93412-WPP.jpg" alt="Smiley face" height="470" width="870"></image></figure>
              <p><p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"><span style="font-size:11pt"><span style="line-height:107%"><span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif">WPP CEO Mark Read on Tuesday announced a three-year plan for &ldquo;radical evolution&rdquo; of the company to deliver improved performance. To reflect the new strategic direction of the company, WPP has launched an evolution of its brand identity.</span></span></span></p>

<p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"><span style="font-size:11pt"><span style="line-height:107%"><span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif">Superunion and Landor have collaborated to create the new identity which represents WPP as a creative transformation company that is dynamic, connected and organised around the needs of its clients, according to information available on the agency&rsquo;s site.</span></span></span></p>

<p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"><span style="font-size:11pt"><span style="line-height:107%"><span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif">The logo is made up of many parts that combine to form the whole &ndash; a representation of WPP&rsquo;s people, agencies, capabilities and markets that work together as one for clients. </span></span></span></p>

<p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"><span style="font-size:11pt"><span style="line-height:107%"><span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif">On-screen, the logo is designed to have a continuously changing form and colour, symbolising creative transformation in itself. </span></span></span></p>

<p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"><span style="font-size:11pt"><span style="line-height:107%"><span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif">Talking about the idea behind the new logo, Jim Prior, Global CEO, Superunion, said, &ldquo;Our ambition was to present WPP with the same energy and creativity that we offer to our clients right across the company. There&rsquo;s a lot of pride and ambition in WPP that is now united under a strong and dynamic brand identity.&rdquo;</span></span></span></p>

<p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"><span style="font-size:11pt"><span style="line-height:107%"><span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif">Jane Geraghty, Global CEO of Landor, said, &ldquo;WPP has always been transformative &ndash; bringing together the best people and ideas to meet the needs of our clients. We now have an evolved brand and expression of purpose that better reflects who we are as a company, our collective capabilities, and what we offer.&rdquo;</span></span></span></p>

<p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"><span style="font-size:11pt"><span style="line-height:107%"><span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif">According to WPP, the Superunion/Landor team worked alongside WPP&rsquo;s central team on the new positioning as a dynamic, forward-thinking company with creativity and technology at its heart, and the core purpose of creating better futures for its clients and people.</span></span></span></p></p>
              <footer><aside>@2018</aside></footer>
            </article>
          </body>
        </html>
      </content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We aim to be in top 3 brands in the water heater category by 2020: Rakesh Kaul, HSIL Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing/we-aim-to-be-in-top-3-brands-in-the-water-heater-category-by-2020-rakesh-kaul-hsil-ltd-93413.html</link>
      <guid>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing/we-aim-to-be-in-top-3-brands-in-the-water-heater-category-by-2020-rakesh-kaul-hsil-ltd-93413.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>content@exchange4media.com (exchange4media News Service)</author>
      <description>Rakesh Kaul, President and Chief Executive, Consumer Products Division & CEO EVOK Retail, HSIL Limited spoke to us about the first-ever TVC for their water heater brand Hindware Atlantic, and more</description>
      <content:encoded>
        <html lang="en" prefix="op: http://media.facebook.com/op#">
          <head><link rel="canonical" href="https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing/we-aim-to-be-in-top-3-brands-in-the-water-heater-category-by-2020-rakesh-kaul-hsil-ltd_93413.html">
                    <meta property="op:markup_version" content="v1.0">
                    <meta charset="utf-8">
                    <meta property="op:markup_version" content="v1.0"></head>
          <body>
            <article>
              <header><time class="op-published" datetime="Tue, 11 Dec 18 18:30:00 +0000">Tue, 11 Dec 18 18:30:00 +0000</time></header>
              <figure><image><img src="93413-RakeshKaul.jpg" alt="Smiley face" height="470" width="870"></image></figure>
              <p><p>Water heater brand Hindware Atlantic, part of the sanitaryware company HSIL, recently released its first TVC campaign for the Ondeo Series &lsquo;Fresh Hot Water Saalon Saal&rsquo;. The TVC highlights the industry-first and Patented O&#39;Pro Protection Technology and Titanium Core Shield of the Ondeo range which prevents internal corrosion, thereby enhancing the life of water heaters. In 2015, HSIL had entered the home appliances segment with a collaboration with Groupe Atlantic of France.</p>

<p>Commenting on the insight&nbsp;behind the TVC for its water heater brand Hindware Atlantic, Rakesh Kaul, President and Chief Executive, Consumer Products Division &amp; CEO EVOK Retail, HSIL Limited says, &ldquo;We wanted to bring a campaign to help consumers understand what is happening inside their water heaters as they are not aware of the corrosion and dirt deposits that are formed inside the tank over the years. Thus the first ad campaign focuses on our water heaters equipped with the Patented O&#39;Pro Protection Technology and its Titanium Core Shield helps protect the tank longer from corrosion. The &lsquo;Fresh Hot Water&nbsp;Saalon&nbsp;Sal&rsquo; campaign emphasizes the prolonged life of Hindware Atlantic water heaters as compared to any other ordinary water heaters.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Conceptualized and created by DDB Mudra, the film captures how corrosion and dirty deposits impact the longevity of a water-heater in a light-hearted neo-mythological format. Speaking on the brief given to the creative agency, Kaul says, &ldquo;Our brief to the agency was to voice the aforementioned insight in a humorous and light-hearted manner. Hindware Atlantic Ondeo series comes with patented technology which prolongs the life of the product,&nbsp;our&nbsp;ask from the agency was to keep this messaging at the heart of the commercial while creating an ad that is not just engaging but also entertaining.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Hindware has taken a multi-pronged marketing approach for the commercial through various platforms such as Electronic and Digital. For a wider reach, the TVC is being aired on key regional channels in languages like Bengali, Kannada, Tamil, and Telugu including prominent Movies and News channels. Kaul says, &ldquo;We&#39;ve kept a sizable budget for the TV&nbsp;campaign&nbsp;so that it&#39;s well tailored to reach out to our target audience.&rdquo; Talking about ad-spends he says, &ldquo;We will spend up to Rs 50 crores this financial year on marketing to build our brands across categories. The majority of the spends will be on digital marketing and advertising during festival season.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Speaking about the company&rsquo;s growth Kaul says, &ldquo;We have grown phenomenally in all the categories we are present in over the years. In the chimney segment, we are already among the Top 3 players with a 15-16% market share. Our water heaters category is doing extremely well and in a span of 24 months, we have grown 165% more than last year and currently have 6-6.5% market share in this category.&rdquo; Looking ahead he adds, &ldquo;We aim to be amongst the top 3 brands in the category of water heaters by end 2020 and similarly be amongst the top 3 in the water purifiers category in next 5 years and are working to extend our distribution and retailer network, after sales network and introduce tech led variants in the categories to ensure we achieve our target.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Campaign video:</p>

<p><iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/0K5lDBjI5l4" width="560"></iframe></p></p>
              <footer><aside>@2018</aside></footer>
            </article>
          </body>
        </html>
      </content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WPP to cut 3,500 jobs as part of restructuring</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing/wpp-to-cut-3500-jobs-as-part-of-restructuring-93414.html</link>
      <guid>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing/wpp-to-cut-3500-jobs-as-part-of-restructuring-93414.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>content@exchange4media.com (exchange4media News Service)</author>
      <description>CEO Mark Read said WPP will not take up more mergers of companies. He was speaking at the company's Investor Day presentation</description>
      <content:encoded>
        <html lang="en" prefix="op: http://media.facebook.com/op#">
          <head><link rel="canonical" href="https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing/wpp-to-cut-3500-jobs-as-part-of-restructuring_93414.html">
                    <meta property="op:markup_version" content="v1.0">
                    <meta charset="utf-8">
                    <meta property="op:markup_version" content="v1.0"></head>
          <body>
            <article>
              <header><time class="op-published" datetime="Tue, 11 Dec 18 18:30:00 +0000">Tue, 11 Dec 18 18:30:00 +0000</time></header>
              <figure><image><img src="93414-read.jpg" alt="Smiley face" height="470" width="870"></image></figure>
              <p><p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif">WPP&rsquo;s radical evolution plan laid down at the Investor Day on Tuesday indicates that following the hiring freeze, the network will be cutting jobs globally. It was revealed that WPP&rsquo;s restructuring will include shutting 80 offices globally and combining operations of a further 100 in locations where business is slow.</span></span></p>

<p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif">&ldquo;Fewer businesses make it easier to manage, but unfortunately there will be job losses from bringing businesses together,&rdquo; said Mark Read, CEO, WPP, during his presentation. The company is said to cut 3,500 of its 1,34,000 global workforce. WPP has 400 ad businesses in more than 3,000 offices in 112 countries.&nbsp;</span></span></p>

<p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif">Responding to a question from an analyst about further consolidation in the WPP group of companies, Read clarified that WPP will not be looking at more mergers for now. </span></span></p>

<p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif">Over the last three months, WPP has reviewed and restructured agencies that make up for 23 per cent of its revenue. Read called the mergers of VML with Y&amp;R and Wunderman with JWT &ldquo;tough choices&rdquo; and added that the merged companies should be able to provide more integrated solutions to clients. </span></span></p>

<p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif">&ldquo;There is nothing worse than running a company in a so-called traditional area that is doomed forever to the client,&rdquo; he said.&nbsp;</span></span></p>

<p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif">In this new radical phase of WPP, Read said, he is banning the use of the word &ldquo;digital&rdquo; and veering more towards technology. WPP is positioning itself as a &ldquo;creative transformation company&rdquo; that uses &ldquo;creativity as differentiator and technology as growth engine,&rdquo; Read said. </span></span></p>

<p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif">&ldquo;Any company that is not deeply investing in technology will not be successful in the next 5 or 10 or 25 years. I think it is incumbent on us to do that in the right way,&rdquo; he added.&nbsp;</span></span></p>

<p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif">Talking about the mergers that WPP has undertaken recently, Read said the artificial difference between analog and digital is not helpful in understanding the world. &ldquo;Removing those distinctions helps you get to the answer better,&rdquo; he said. &nbsp;</span></span></p>

<p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif">Making a reference to ex-CEO Sir Martin Sorrell&rsquo;s reference to Google and Facebook as frenemies, Read said those companies should be treated as &ldquo;technology partners not as frenemies; as partners and also increasingly and interestingly as clients.&rdquo;&nbsp;</span></span></p>

<p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif">He further said that WPP&rsquo;s technology strategy is to become a developer of technology and not just an integrator. &ldquo;We cannot compete with Google or Adobe in terms of technology, but we can leverage the spend of many large partners and stitch their systems together to give us what we need.&quot;</span></span></p>

<p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm">&nbsp;</p></p>
              <footer><aside>@2018</aside></footer>
            </article>
          </body>
        </html>
      </content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data richness makes India an ideal market to experiment: Kaushal Kurapati, Oracle</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital/data-richness-makes-india-an-ideal-market-to-experiment-kaushal-kurapati-oracle-93299.html</link>
      <guid>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital/data-richness-makes-india-an-ideal-market-to-experiment-kaushal-kurapati-oracle-93299.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>content@exchange4media.com (exchange4media News Service)</author>
      <description>Group Vice President Product Management at Oracle on how marketing technology has heralded a new era for the domain</description>
      <content:encoded>
        <html lang="en" prefix="op: http://media.facebook.com/op#">
          <head><link rel="canonical" href="https://www.exchange4media.com/digital/data-richness-makes-india-an-ideal-market-to-experiment-kaushal-kurapati-oracle_93299.html">
                    <meta property="op:markup_version" content="v1.0">
                    <meta charset="utf-8">
                    <meta property="op:markup_version" content="v1.0"></head>
          <body>
            <article>
              <header><time class="op-published" datetime="Mon, 10 Dec 18 18:30:00 +0000">Mon, 10 Dec 18 18:30:00 +0000</time></header>
              <figure><image><img src="93299-KaushalOracle.jpg" alt="Smiley face" height="470" width="870"></image></figure>
              <p><p>Technology is enabling a new marketing dynamic which is making the task for marketers more insightful and efficient while also retaining its own set of complexities.</p>

<p>Sharing the impact and correlation between new marketing technology and brand communication, Kaushal Kurapati, Group Vice President Product Management at Oracle strongly believes that marketing technology has heralded a new era for the domain.</p>

<p>&ldquo;Over the years print has given way to TV and TV now holds a big sway of advertising dollars. &nbsp;Also, the advent of performance marketing, internet and smartphones has unleashed new form factors and new ways of targeting consumers. All of this is primarily because technology is driving consumer behaviour to change. Now marketers have to understand this difference in consumer behaviour and be able to target appropriately. &nbsp;Otherwise they will be missing a big opportunity,&rdquo; said Kurapati.</p>

<p>Underling the difference between big data vs. quality data and the need to give precedence to the latter, Kurapati&nbsp;believes that this issue is not unique to the Indian market but a global phenomenon.</p>

<p>&ldquo;I think that struggle is world over and not just in India. If the data going in is noisy then your prediction and your estimation and all of those factors will be bad as well. Smart businesses or smart organisations have to take care while considering data and I think a lot of people miss that point. So, it is not just about the amount of data but also the quality of data that is important.&rdquo;</p>

<p>When asked to define the most popular technology solutions that brands are seeking from technology providers, Kurapati&nbsp;explained, &ldquo;Many brands would like to monitor what is going on in the social media space and how people are talking about the brand in terms of the positive or negative sentiment.&rdquo;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Also when it comes to mobile apps, they want to understand what happens to the customer journey as they come and navigate the site and also to understand the overall digital foot print,&rdquo; he further added.</p>

<p>With growing concerns about data privacy and the implementation of General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) in mature data markets, regulatory concerns may pose challenge to big data usage in the coming time.</p>

<p>When asked to explain the role of technology providers in such a scenario, Kurapati&nbsp;said, &ldquo;GDPR is having a big impact not just in the European context but also technology solutions are getting compliant that way. Big countries like India want data jurisdiction within their borders, it is happening in the payment space, it will happen in the consumer behaviour space too. It is the question of when not if in my view, and it will require some change on part of the technology providers too.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Sharing his thoughts about the future of marketing technology, Kurapati&nbsp;added, &ldquo;We will see a unified data picture because there is still data in silos even in the advanced data markets. &nbsp;Figuring out what to recommend as a product based on what you already purchased would become more strategic.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Explaining the critical role that India is poised to play as the centre of big data, Kurapati&nbsp;said, &ldquo;India over the years has become one of the lowest data rate markets in the world. &nbsp;This has led to a change in the consumer behaviour and an explosion in terms of spending time on the mobile phone. This consumer behaviour change has made India a data rich market, and because of that data richness I think it is quickly becoming an ideal market to experiment and try out different things.&rdquo;<br />
&nbsp;</p></p>
              <footer><aside>@2018</aside></footer>
            </article>
          </body>
        </html>
      </content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most viewed videos of 2018</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital/most-viewed-videos-of-2018-93300.html</link>
      <guid>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital/most-viewed-videos-of-2018-93300.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>content@exchange4media.com (exchange4media News Service)</author>
      <description>From Priya Prakash Varrier's wink, to a daily wager discovered by singer Shankar Mahadevan, here's a list of people whose videos went viral making them overnight social media superstars</description>
      <content:encoded>
        <html lang="en" prefix="op: http://media.facebook.com/op#">
          <head><link rel="canonical" href="https://www.exchange4media.com/digital/most-viewed-videos-of-2018_93300.html">
                    <meta property="op:markup_version" content="v1.0">
                    <meta charset="utf-8">
                    <meta property="op:markup_version" content="v1.0"></head>
          <body>
            <article>
              <header><time class="op-published" datetime="Mon, 10 Dec 18 18:30:00 +0000">Mon, 10 Dec 18 18:30:00 +0000</time></header>
              <figure><image><img src="93300-PriyaVarrier.jpg" alt="Smiley face" height="470" width="870"></image></figure>
              <p><p>The power of social media is so huge that it requires no time to make one become famous. It recognises true and unrecognised talents and has given them a platform to display their unique skills. The year 2018 witnessed a bunch of videos going viral making the person depicted in it, famous. From winking girl to daily wager, who is a singing sensation, the list of people who became famous through social media never ends.<br />
Let&rsquo;s take a look at some of the videos that went viral in the&nbsp;year 2018.</p>

<p><strong>The Winking Girl</strong></p>

<p>Priya Prakash Varrier took the internet by storm by a wink. The 19-year model-actress from Kerala was seen winking in a 30 second clip from a song from the movie &lsquo;Oru Adaar Love&rsquo;. It didn&rsquo;t take much time for Varrier to become global sensation. Meltwater, the global media intelligence company, tracked and analysed mentions of the film and of Varrier across online, editorial and social media. According to reports, &lsquo;Oru Adaar Love&rsquo; and Varrier were mentioned 2,723 times on editorial media and 89,785 times on social media globally, in the second week of February.</p>

<p>Varrier has around 6.5 M + followers on Instagram and 6 lakh+ followers on Facebook. The song has garnered 82 +Million views on YouTube. She was signed for Nestle Munch advertisement and a South Indian shopping mall, even before her first movie release.</p>

<p><iframe allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/W0fKl43QmIE?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" width="100%"></iframe></p>

<p><strong>Dancing Uncle</strong></p>

<p>Sanjeev Shrivastava fondly known as Dancing Uncle became a sensation overnight with his &lsquo;Govinda&rsquo; dance moves. A video of Shrivastava dancing at a wedding has gone viral in the month of June.<br />
Bajaj Allianz Life Insurance capitalised on Shrivastava&rsquo;s popularity and quickly roped him for their latest announcement of a one-time special bonus for their policyholders. The video saw him dancing to Bajaj Allianz Life&rsquo;s new jingle &lsquo;Samjho Ho Gaya&rsquo; that captures the essence of the brand&rsquo;s new philosophy &lsquo;Life Goals. DONE&rsquo;.&nbsp;</p>

<p>His Twitter account @Dabbuthe dancer has 8.2K followers.</p>

<p><iframe allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/dvQb76sRR2E?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" width="100%"></iframe></p>

<p><strong>Singing Baby from Andhra Pradesh</strong></p>

<p>In the month of November, Baby, a native of East Godavari district of Andhra Pradesh &nbsp;was seen in a viral video singing &lsquo;O Cheliya&rsquo; from the movie Premikudu, Telugu version of A R Rahman&rsquo;s popular song &lsquo;Ennavale&rsquo; from the movie Kadhalan. Rahman himself shared the video captioned &lsquo;unknown, anonymous, beautiful voice&rsquo;. The video got millions of shares and likes in no time. She has got her Tollywood break in the&nbsp;movie &#39;Palasa 1978&#39;.</p>

<p><iframe frameborder="0" height="476" rel="nofollow" scrolling="no" src="https://www.facebook.com/plugins/video.php?href=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.facebook.com%2Farrahman%2Fvideos%2F524106481413224%2F&amp;show_text=0&amp;" style="border:none;overflow:hidden" width="261"></iframe></p>

<p><strong>The daily wager who caught Shankar Mahadevan&rsquo;s attention</strong></p>

<p>In the month of July a daily wager went viral with his song &lsquo;Unai Kaanadhu Naan Indru Naal Illaye&rsquo; from actor Kamal Haasan starrer film &lsquo;Vishwaroopam&rsquo;. The video was shared by singer Shankar Mahadevan who sang the original song asking people to help him to identify the singer in the video. The person was identified as Rakesh Unni, a daily wager from Kerala who sang during break from his work has met Kamal Hassan and sang for the actor. &nbsp;Unni is soon to get a break in play back singing.</p>

<p><iframe allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/ZzRqbwiC914?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" width="100%"></iframe></p></p>
              <footer><aside>@2018</aside></footer>
            </article>
          </body>
        </html>
      </content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook and Twitter’s public policy experts root for addressing digital addiction</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital/facebook-and-twitters-public-policy-experts-root-for-addressing-digital-addiction-93361.html</link>
      <guid>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital/facebook-and-twitters-public-policy-experts-root-for-addressing-digital-addiction-93361.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>content@exchange4media.com (exchange4media News Service)</author>
      <description>Ankhi Das of Facebook  and Mahima Kaul of Twitter India spoke about the issue of digital revolution and social challenges at a recent event in New Delhi.</description>
      <content:encoded>
        <html lang="en" prefix="op: http://media.facebook.com/op#">
          <head><link rel="canonical" href="https://www.exchange4media.com/digital/facebook-and-twitters-public-policy-experts-root-for-addressing-digital-addiction_93361.html">
                    <meta property="op:markup_version" content="v1.0">
                    <meta charset="utf-8">
                    <meta property="op:markup_version" content="v1.0"></head>
          <body>
            <article>
              <header><time class="op-published" datetime="Mon, 10 Dec 18 18:30:00 +0000">Mon, 10 Dec 18 18:30:00 +0000</time></header>
              <figure><image><img src="93361-Jagran-event-pic.jpg" alt="Smiley face" height="470" width="870"></image></figure>
              <p><p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:10.0pt; margin-left:0cm; text-align:justify"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif">While the rise of social media has given us countless benefits, the flip side of it is gradually becoming the new focus area. Issues such as trolls, data safety and digital addiction are being spoken about more vocally than before and social media platforms such as Facebook and Twitter are taking due cognizance to address these concerns.</span></span></p>

<p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:10.0pt; margin-left:0cm; text-align:justify"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif">At a recent event in New Delhi, Ankhi Das, Public Policy Director, Facebook -India, South &amp; Central Asia; and Mahima Kaul, Head, Public Policy &amp; Government Partnerships, Twitter India; spoke about the issue of &lsquo;digital revolution and social challenges&rsquo;.</span></span></p>

<p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:10.0pt; margin-left:0cm; text-align:justify"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif">Answering a question on the increasing addiction to social platforms like Facebook and the way to deal with it, Ankhi Das said, &ldquo;We are creating a &lsquo;time spent&rsquo; dashboard and it will&nbsp;help to self-regulate.&nbsp; Also I think it is the responsibility of all of us as a society&nbsp;to address it. We have created a network of safety partners and mental health&nbsp;experts,&nbsp;including institutions like Tata Institute of Social Sciences, to tackle it.&rdquo;</span></span></p>

<p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:10.0pt; margin-left:0cm; text-align:justify"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif">Das also spoke about Facebook&rsquo;s thrust on promoting regional languages and reaching out to people beyond the big cities.</span></span></p>

<p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:10.0pt; margin-left:0cm; text-align:justify"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif">&ldquo;Facebook has been upgraded to be available in 16 Indian languages. A lot of consumption is happening in the local languages. If you look at the way media is getting consumed, the patterns of consumption are changing in terms of being more visual and more towards video.&rdquo;</span></span></p>

<p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:10.0pt; margin-left:0cm; text-align:justify"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif">She also spoke about the collapse of information barriers, something that social media platforms like Facebook have enabled.</span></span></p>

<p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:10.0pt; margin-left:0cm; text-align:justify"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif">&ldquo;The way we access information has changed drastically.&nbsp; People, especially youngster students, don&#39;t have barriers to information today,&rdquo; said Das.</span></span></p>

<p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:10.0pt; margin-left:0cm; text-align:justify"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif">Mahima Kaul of Twitter spoke about the correct use of the micro blogging platform and how the government has made it an effective tool to reach out to public at large.</span></span></p>

<p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:10.0pt; margin-left:0cm; text-align:justify"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif">&quot;If you see, the government is using Twitter in the most efficient way. You can find all the ministries on this platform and they share important information through this platform&rdquo;.&nbsp;</span></span></p>

<p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:10.0pt; margin-left:0cm; text-align:justify"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif">Answering a question about the rampant issue of trolling and safety on social media platforms, Kaul said, &quot;There are many product features within the platform that can tackle these issues and most of the users don&#39;t know about them. And when they do, it becomes easier to&nbsp;deal with trolls and address other such concerns.&rdquo;</span></span></p>

<p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:10.0pt; margin-left:0cm; text-align:justify"><span style="font-size:12pt"><span style="font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif">The event was organised by&nbsp;Jagran Group.</span></span></p>

<p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm">&nbsp;</p></p>
              <footer><aside>@2018</aside></footer>
            </article>
          </body>
        </html>
      </content:encoded>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
