<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9" xmlns:image="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-image/1.1" xmlns:news="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-news/0.9">
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/account-news/kurl-on-awards-creative-mandate-to-fcb-ulka-93396.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>11/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Kurl-on awards creative mandate to FCB Ulka</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;FCB Ulka has partnered with&amp;nbsp;Kurl- on for their creative mandate. FCB Ulka will service the iconic brand from the Bangalore office. FCB Ulka was awarded the mandate following a multi-agency pitch. Kurl-on is India&amp;#39;s leading brand of mattresses, furniture and furnishing products in India. The company was founded in 1962 by Ramesh Pai. With state-of-the-art technology, Kurl-on endeavors to improve standards in the Indian mattress and furniture industry besides being in tune with the changing needs of the Indian consumer. The brand is available across India through 7000+ multi-brand outlets, 920+ franchise outlets, and 35 exclusive brand outlets across the country today.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The company manufactures mattresses in 126 different configurations. Pan-India, they have partnered with a network comprising more than 10,000+ dealers, 72 branch &amp;amp; stock points and 10 strategically located manufacturing facilities across Karnataka, Orissa, Madhya Pradesh, Uttaranchal and Gujarat. The company was formerly known as Karnataka Consumer Products Limited and changed its name to Kurl-on Limited in 1995.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking on the occasion, Ashutosh Vaidya, CMO, Kurlon, said, &amp;ldquo;Kurlon is a brand undergoing an immense transformation from being known as India&amp;rsquo;s largest selling mattress brand to becoming a leader in cutting edge technologically driven home comfort products. We wanted an agency that could understand this vision and work with us through the journey of achieving collaborative success. We met many agencies through a pitch process, but FCB Ulka stood out in their ability to translate our market ambitions with a clear strategy, differentiated creativity and a unique understanding of the digital ecosystem. We are confident of this partnership and look forward to meeting milestones together&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the win, Theresa Ronnie, Vice President, FCB Ulka- Bangalore said, Kurl-on is a great brand with an impressive presence in the Indian market. They wanted an agency partner who understood their business aspirations. We, in turn, were very impressed with their ability to understand and seek the differentiation that good creativity brings to brand growth. We are encouraged by the quality of the partnership thus far and hope to build a new chapter for Brand Kurl-on together&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Adding to this, Romit Nair, Creative Head, FCB Ulka- Bangalore, said, &amp;lsquo;&amp;rsquo;I believe this is the start of something big and beautiful. We are really excited to partner Kurl-on on the next phase of their journey and hope to create a strong relationship that leads to some beautiful work.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93396-KurlonFCBUlka.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/account-news/dvio-digital-awarded-creative-and-social-mandate-for-gaana-93306.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>06/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>DViO Digital awarded creative and social mandate for Gaana</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Gaana, one of India&amp;#39;s leading music streaming platforms has aligned themselves with DViO Digital, one of India&amp;rsquo;s largest integrated marketing companies, for the third year in a row. The account was won following a multi-agency pitch and DViO Digital came out the winner again.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The agency will be involved in user engagement, retention, acquisition and content discovery at its core. Additionally, DViO Digital will also be conducting large scale digital-first activations and engagement programs for brand loyalty with a focus on artists, occasions and new releases. Strengthening Gaana&amp;rsquo;s market share in North and West India, along with growth in the South is one of the focal points for the next few months.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking on the account win, CEO &amp;amp; Founder of DViO Digital, Sowmya Iyer said, &amp;ldquo;DViO is continually associated with the leading brands in the industry such as the &amp;lsquo;Star&amp;rsquo; entertainment group, Universal Music and Gaana.com and we are excited to strengthen and consolidate our position in the entertainment industry with our continued alliance with Gaana&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Manish Shrivastava, Vice President of Gaana commented on the alliance with DViO Digital, saying &amp;quot;We are pleased to keep DViO Digital on board for our creative and social duties. Their work for Gaana over the past three years has been par excellence and we can&amp;#39;t wait to see what our renewed partnership bring us&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93306-DViOGaana.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/account-news/storia-foods-awards-integrated-communications-mandate-to-publicis-beehive-93301.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>06/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Storia Foods awards integrated communications mandate to Publicis Beehive</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Storia Foods &amp;amp; Beverages, a budding entrepreneurial venture in the natural foods space, has set its sight on establishing a firm grip in the Indian food market with its multiple offerings. To give flight to its much-coveted dream, the company has roped in Publicis Beehive to manage its entire communications mandate.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The agency was shortlisted after a multi-agency pitch and will manage the entire communication mandate including advertising, brand activation, digital and media. The agency was chosen for articulating a sharp and forward-looking communication plan that seeks to establish Storia Foods as the go-to brand for its multiple natural offerings.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;A relatively new entrant in the natural foods arena, what makes Storia Foods a brand to watch out for is its commitment to creating products that are natural, full of goodness and promote a healthy lifestyle. It is driven by the philosophy that food is much more than a means to sustain life; it is a means of sharing, caring and bringing people together. Storia finds its roots in celebrating these moments of togetherness and turning moments into bonds of a lifetime.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/VishalShah.jpg" style="width: 300px; height: 300px;" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Vishal Shah &amp;ndash; Founder &amp;amp; Managing Partner, Storia Foods &amp;amp; Beverages&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Sharing his viewpoint on his plans for the Indian market and also on appointing Publicis Beehive as its communications partner, Vishal Shah &amp;ndash; Founder &amp;amp; Managing Partner, Storia Foods &amp;amp; Beverages said: &amp;ldquo;It is important that we have a deep understanding of our consumers, how we want our consumers to perceive us and what feeling we want to leave them with. Today&amp;rsquo;s society is moving rapidly and brands have a small window to interact with their consumers and create an impact through their products and communication. It was thus important for Storia to invest in a partner who could communicate these brand values and create a feeling of belonging for our consumers and Publicis Beehive fit the bill seamlessly. They understand our brand vision and culture and there is immense trust that they will nurture our brand as well as we do.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/ParitoshSrivastava.jpg" style="width: 300px; height: 300px;" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Paritosh Srivastava, COO &amp;ndash; Publicis Beehive&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Expressing a similar sentiment, Paritosh Srivastava, COO &amp;ndash; Publicis Beehive said: &amp;ldquo;Partnering an upcoming and entrepreneurial brand like Storia Foods &amp;amp; Beverages presents both an opportunity as well as a challenge. Opportunity lies in leveraging our integrated strength to put our best foot forward in terms of creative, media, digital and activation. The challenge is the trust and responsibility entrusted by Vishal and team upon us to make Storia a success in a tough environment. It&amp;rsquo;s a great product and we hope that together we will create memorable communication that will result in disproportionate trials and awareness.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;As a new-age brand, Storia lays great emphasis on making products that are healthy and natural. There are absolutely no artificial colours or artificial flavours added. Instead, all products are made in a way to keep them as close to their natural state as possible, while also ensuring that there is a minimum loss of nutrients in the process. What consumers end up with is a healthy, natural and wholesome product that they are better together with.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The agency is currently working on the first communication message which will be rolled out shortly.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93301-PublicisStoria.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/account-news/makani-acquires-the-integrated-mandate-for-traworld-luggage-93264.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>04/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Makani acquires the integrated mandate for Traworld Luggage</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Makani bags the integrated mandate for Traworld, the premium luggage brand from the house of High Spirit Commercial Ventures. Having recently launched the &amp;lsquo;World is Your Ramp&amp;rsquo; campaign, the agency will be handling the brand&amp;rsquo;s ATL, BTL, brand collateral&amp;rsquo;s among other creative duties. The agency&amp;rsquo;s digital wing will be handling the entire digital mandate. Bollywood actor&amp;nbsp;Sonam Kapoor Ahuja has been featured as the face of the brand.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking on the association,&amp;nbsp;Sameer Makani, Director, Makani Creative said,&amp;nbsp;&amp;ldquo;Fashion and travel is an imperative aspect of most people lives and to travel fashionably has become a norm. The idea was to break the clutter of the luggage industry and position the brand as high fashion travel gear. Sonam Kapoor as the brand&amp;rsquo;s ambassador personifies the brand perfectly&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the win, Tushar Jain, Founder, and Managing Director, High Spirit Commercial Ventures said, &amp;quot;Traworld is a premium luggage brand for the modern globetrotter. We aim to meet all their requirements innovatively and stylishly. &amp;ldquo;The World is Your Ramp&amp;rdquo; campaign aptly positions the brand as fashionable and aspirational. The campaign aims at introducing the brand to a premium and fashion savvy target audience. Makani as an agency has done a great job in positioning our brand and elevating it to another level&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Traworld is the latest addition to Makani&amp;rsquo;s pool of clients, which includes brands like Nilkamal, Panasonic TV &amp;amp; Smart Phones, Mahindra Logistics, Tata Motors, @home, Pepe, Lavie, Metro Shoes, Mochi, Siyarams, Vishal Sarees, Neeru&amp;rsquo;s, DCTEX , Killer Jeans, Dixcy Scott, Image Eyewear, Idee Eyewear, JBL and Epic Channel to name a few. A fully integrated advertising agency, Makani Creatives has team strength of over 100 talented individuals.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93264-MakaniTraworld.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/account-news/zenith-wins-global-media-mandate-for-lactalis-93255.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>04/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Zenith wins global media mandate for Lactalis</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Zenith has won the global pitch for the consolidated media business of dairy products corporation Lactalis. Zenith has been appointed Master Agency Partner, commanding 75% of Lactalis&amp;rsquo; markets.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The win sees Zenith retain all its existing markets in EMEA, APAC and Latin America, and take on 11 new ones, including Canada, UK and USA. Lactalis is a global leader within the dairy industry, with leading local dairy brands in each of its markets. The group is the number one cheese manufacturer in the world and the European leader in milk consumption, butter and cream.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;As Master Agency Partner, Zenith will have lead media communications responsibility, with global coordination run from Zenith&amp;rsquo;s HQ in London. Zenith will now work with Lactalis both centrally and locally to deliver against the company&amp;rsquo;s growth targets.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking about the win, Vittorio Bonori, Global Brand President, Zenith, said: &amp;ldquo;We are absolutely delighted to become Lactalis&amp;rsquo; Master Agency Partner. This is a testament to our strong relationship with Lactalis and to Zenith&amp;rsquo;s approach to driving business growth as the ROI agency.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93254-zenithlogo.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/account-news/social-kinnect-wins-digital-mandate-for-zee-jaipur-literature-festival-2019-93147.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>27/11/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Social Kinnect wins digital mandate for ZEE Jaipur Literature Festival 2019</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Social Kinnect has won the digital mandate for the &amp;lsquo;Greatest Literary Show on Earth&amp;rsquo;, the ZEE Jaipur Literature Festival 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Set against the backdrop of Rajasthan&amp;rsquo;s stunning cultural heritage, this esteemed festival has hosted nearly 2,000 speakers in the past decade.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Social Kinnect is delighted to come on board as the digital agency for the Literature Festival this year from amongst the multiple agencies that pitched for the prestigious account. The Festival brings together a diverse mix of the world&amp;rsquo;s greatest writers, thinkers, humanitarians, politicians, business leaders, sports people, and entertainers on one stage to champion the freedom to express and engage in thoughtful debate and dialogue.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Its core values to serve as a democratic, non-aligned platform offering free and fair access remain unchanged even today. Having welcomed people from across the globe, the Festival has transformed into a global literary phenomenon and is known worldwide for its sumptuous feast of ideas. The mandate includes duties of Digital Marketing Strategy, Media Planning &amp;amp; Execution, as well as Online Reputation Management, the same will be managed from Social Kinnect&amp;rsquo;s Delhi branch.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking on the partnership, Preeta Singh, President -Teamwork Arts said,&amp;nbsp;&amp;ldquo;ZEE Jaipur Literature Festival has transformed into a global literary phenomenon that hosts nearly 200 speakers and attracts people from across India and the globe. Given our commitment to a renewed experience every year, it is crucial for us to work with an agency that specialises in effective digital solutions. Social Kinnect has a strong legacy in digital marketing and understands a business&amp;#39;s need to balance strategic insights with creative campaigns. Their strategic approach and strong creative framework will enable us to develop universal resonance, as well as reach out to the desired digitally forward audiences. We are thrilled to partner with Social Kinnect!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the win, Rohan Mehta, CEO of Social Kinnect said, &amp;ldquo;We at Social Kinnect are extremely excited about the opportunity to work for the renowned ZEE Jaipur Literature Festival 2019. With the prestigious mandate, we have a huge responsibility to manage the sensitivities attached to the Festival and the profile of delegates and audience members. We believe that handling the digital mandate for an event of such repute will be instrumental in taking Social Kinnect to a much higher pedestal and carve us a niche.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;ZEE Jaipur Literature Festival will take place from 24th till 28th January 2019.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93147-ZEEJaipurLiteratureFestival2019.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/account-news/navneet-education-limited-appoints-pitchfork-partners-as-pr-consultants-93130.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>26/11/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Navneet Education Limited appoints Pitchfork Partners as PR consultants</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Navneet Education Limited, one of India&amp;rsquo;s oldest and most trusted brands in the educational products space, has signed on Pitchfork Partners Strategic Consulting LLP to advise on communication initiatives. The mandate will include internal and external communications which will extend across their stationery brands, Youva, HQ, and the Kids Book division.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Youva is a stationery brand crafted for youngsters, while HQ is the formal stationery brand for office-goers. The Kids Book division is the dominant player in the children&amp;rsquo;s books space. Youva from Navneet Stationery recently appointed Prithvi Shaw, who has been the captain of the India U-19 cricket team as their Brand Ambassador.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Shailendra Gala, Director - Stationery Division, Navneet Education Limited, said: &amp;ldquo;Pitchfork Partners shares our beliefs and values, and we are delighted to partner with them. The stationery business in India is booming and we are proud to be pioneers in the sector. We see a huge opportunity for sustained growth and Pitchfork has the credentials to help us.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Jaideep Shergill, Co-Founder, Pitchfork Partners, added, &amp;ldquo;Navneet is an iconic Indian brand and we are extremely happy to partner with it. We will work closely with the Navneet team on internal communication, and provide strategic direction and analytics to aid its growth.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93130-NavneetPitchfork.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/account-news/glaxosmithkline-awards-15-billion-media-account-to-publicis-media-93075.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>22/11/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>GlaxoSmithKline awards $1.5 billion media account to Publicis Media</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Pharmaceutical giant GlaxoSmithKline (GSK) has awarded its $1.7 billion media business to Publicis Media, following a review which began in May this year, according to media reports.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;It has been reported that Publicis Media has created a dedicated unit to handle the account.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;According to reports, Scott Grenz,&amp;nbsp;VP of Consumer Healthcare and Global Head of Media, GlaxoSmithKline, said in an updated statement, &amp;quot;We ran a very thorough and competitive pitch process with strong presentations from all companies, but ultimately Publicis was the best fit for us. We&amp;rsquo;re excited about the new partnership and the potential of the platformGSK model as we continue to progress our marketing transformation program.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The &amp;#39;platformGSK&amp;#39; model will synergise various expertise from across Publicis Media in the areas of healthcare, consumer strategy and digital business transformation.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The review, which was handled by ID Comms, came less than three years after MediaCom won GSK&amp;#39;s European business, while PHD will handle the US media mandate. Both agencies had retained the accounts in 2015 following a global media review, after initially winning the account in 2013.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93075-collage_(59).jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/account-news/vmlyr-india-appointed-as-social-agency-of-record-for-kerastase-loreal-group-92931.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>13/11/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>VMLY&amp;R India appointed as Social Agency of Record for Kérastase, L’Oréal Group</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Following a multi-agency pitch K&amp;eacute;rastase, L&amp;rsquo;Or&amp;eacute;al Group has appointed VMLY&amp;amp;R India as their Social Agency of Record for a period of two years.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Part of the L&amp;rsquo;Or&amp;eacute;al Group, K&amp;eacute;rastase represents the finest in luxury hair-care. K&amp;eacute;rastase understands that every woman wants exceptional hair, but the solution is not the same for every woman. K&amp;eacute;rastase creates innovative products and bespoke rituals for flawless results.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Since 1964 L&amp;#39;Or&amp;eacute;al Advanced Research has selected its most advanced technology for the K&amp;eacute;rastase Collection. Its products are unique, avant-garde formulas with innovative ingredients. Women aspire to K&amp;eacute;rastase for the ultimate in hair care and the ultimate in beautiful hair.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;K&amp;eacute;rastase is focusing on key communication to relevant audiences, contextualising the brand for the Indian market and at the same time maintaining its global equity and standards. Creating awareness of the luxe brand and increasing salon footfall is also crucial on their agenda.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Brought on board as their Social Agency of Record, VMLY&amp;amp;R India will manage the digital strategy and communication for the entire K&amp;eacute;rastase&amp;rsquo;s portfolio across their Facebook, Twitter and Youtube channels. While the agency will dive head first into all the creative communication on social, it will also shepherd the brand through its overall digital strategy.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the partnership Rachit Mathur, GM K&amp;eacute;rastase India &amp;ldquo;We are excited to start this journey with VMLY&amp;amp;R India. The strength that they have shown to own content-driven social for their partners is indeed impressive. We look forward to this partnership with them and K&amp;eacute;rastase.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Adding to this, Udit Bhambri, Country Head, VMLY&amp;amp;R India said, &amp;ldquo;K&amp;eacute;rastase knows that every woman is unique and with ten haircare ranges designed for all different types of hair, every woman can benefit from a personalised beauty program designed by her specially-trained K&amp;eacute;rastase consultant. As VMLY&amp;amp;R India, we aim to bring alive digitally, this proposition of the brand and invite and welcome all women to the luxurious world of K&amp;eacute;rastase.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/92931-collage_(57).jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/account-news/ao-realty-appoints-fruitbowl-digital-as-its-aor-92915.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>12/11/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>A&amp;O Realty appoints Fruitbowl Digital as its AOR</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;A&amp;amp;O Realty, one of Mumbai&amp;#39;s leading real estate developers, that aims to redefine urban lifestyle and living, has entrusted its mandate to Fruitbowl Digital after a competitive multi-agency pitch.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The 360-degree directive will include site branding, creative and media strategy, social media, SEO, ORM, mobile and content marketing, and search engine marketing (SEM) across digital platforms, for existing and upcoming projects across Mumbai, including f.Residences Ghatkopar, f.Residences Malad, Bellevue, Palazzio, Excellent&amp;eacute; and Eminent&amp;eacute;.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the association, Rahul Patel, Director, A&amp;amp;O Realty said, &amp;ldquo;When they came to us, they brought some ideas that we had never even thought of, and the confidence to execute the ones that we already had in mind. Their fresh perspective towards what real estate communication can be, is definitely helping us stand out in an industry where the competition is never sparse.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;He added, &amp;ldquo;We want to have conversations beyond elevation, carpet size, and cost per square foot. We want future home-owners to see, imagine, and live the experiences that the brand promises and delivers time and again,&amp;rdquo; says, Dedeepya Reddy, Co-Founder, Fruitbowl Digital. &amp;ldquo;The average Indian homebuyer has evolved. In our current world of communication clutter, you can&amp;rsquo;t sell to them; you have to grab their attention. In the time that you read this article, at least 2 more real estate ads will have found a space in Mumbai. Our city is plastered with them but how many do you really remember?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/92915-collage_(56).jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/account-news/little-monk-digital-wins-digital-mandate-for-saaho-92909.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>12/11/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Little Monk Digital wins digital mandate for Saaho</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;After a series of high-level multi-agency pitches, UV Creations has chosen Mumbai based social media agency, Little Monk Digital to handle the digital mandate of their upcoming magnum opus, Saaho. The agency which has&amp;nbsp;experience in handling illustrious lists of clients in Bollywood including the likes of Vidya Balan, Boman Irani, Kangana Ranaut, Emraan Hashmi, Huma Qureshi, Junglee Pictures, Sony Pictures Networks, and many others are steadily marching ahead in becoming the most sought-after digital marketing firms in the country.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the latest development, Vaishnav Thaalla, Head of Marketing, UV Creations said, &amp;rdquo;We wanted only the best in the industry to work on Saaho which we&amp;#39;ve maintained from the beginning. For Saaho&amp;#39;s digital we interviewed close to 15 top agencies from the country and after grilling, multi-agency pitches choose Little Monk. What we liked about them were their zeal and enthusiasm and their ideas were mind-boggling. Which is, in our opinion, executed well, can be a game-changer in terms of campaigns done for movies in India.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking on the mandate win, Bishal Paul, CEO of Little Monk Digital said, &amp;quot;After the Baahubali franchise, Saaho is going to be Prabhas&amp;#39;s first film. It is not only going to have a humongous release across more than 7000 screens, the largest ever of any Indian film. But has tremendous expectations from both trade as well as audiences. That makes our work very challenging as we as an agency don&amp;#39;t believe in running a traditional campaign. My team is working around the clock to strategise a campaign which is unique and different in all aspects&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;He further added, &amp;quot;We have a great responsibility on our shoulders, but I&amp;#39;m confident that my team will be able to deliver. We&amp;#39;ll mount a campaign which will complement the grandness of the film and promise to surpass all expectations. For now, I can just say that it would be a campaign that everyone will look up to and will generate tremendous buzz.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/92909-LittleMonkCommunications.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/account-news/oriflame-india-awards-social-media-marketing-mandate-to-vmlyr-india-92705.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>25/10/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Oriflame India awards Social Media Marketing mandate to VMLY&amp;R India</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;VMLY&amp;amp;R India, a full-service digital marketing agency of WPP Group, has won the digital mandate for Oriflame India following a multi-agency pitch. The agency has been entrusted with the task of providing strategic, content and creative inputs across various platforms within the social and digital ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;VMLY&amp;amp;R will be in charge of building a strategic approach for Oriflame India through social media channels. It will also look into strategic planning, social media strategy, content creation for digital mediums, ORM, media planning and buying and working with influencers.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;VMLY&amp;amp;R will also be handling various product launches on digital for the brand in categories including skincare, wellness and more.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the partnership, Naveen Anand, Senior Director, Regional Marketing for South Asia, Oriflame said &amp;ldquo;Social media is a very important part of Oriflame&amp;rsquo;s strategy to continuously engage with the consultants as well as end consumers. We are happy to have VMLY&amp;amp;R on board with their understanding of our business, brand and community.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Oriflame&amp;rsquo;s vision is to become the #1 Beauty Company Selling Direct. The most important objective for social media is to build continuous engagement with the online community which consists of Oriflame&amp;rsquo;s consultants as well as the end consumers.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the association Amandeep Singh Kochar, Business Head, New Delhi, VMLY&amp;amp;R India, said, &amp;ldquo;Oriflame is an iconic brand and has established itself in a great way in the Indian market. Digital has a very big role to play in its marketing and communication strategy and we are excited to be associated with the brand.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/92705-collage_(53).jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/account-news/columbus-india-wins-search-duties-of-hdfc-life-insurance-92704.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>25/10/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Columbus India wins search duties of HDFC Life Insurance</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Columbus India, the data-driven digital marketing agency from Dentsu Aegis Network, has been appointed as the search agency for HDFC Life Insurance, one of India&amp;rsquo;s leading Private Life Insurance companies. The account was won following a multi-agency pitch and will be handled out of the agency&amp;rsquo;s Mumbai office.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;As part of the new mandate, the assignment will involve using Columbus India&amp;rsquo;s expertise in the digital ecosystem for managing the Search mandate (Paid &amp;amp; Earned) for HDFC Life Insurance.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the win, Vishal Subharwal, EVP &amp;ndash; eCommerce &amp;amp; Digital Marketing, HDFC Life Insurance said, &amp;ldquo;We are happy to partner with Columbus for both our SEO and SEM accounts. We look forward to working with their team of experts to fortify our market-leading position and help grow our revenues at the optimal cost in a highly competitive, online marketplace.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Nitin Sabharwal, Chief Business Officer, Columbus India added, &amp;ldquo;We are extremely happy to have HDFC life as our client enabling us to deploy our proprietary data-driven tech solutions for managing user engagement across search engine platforms. We look forward to helping HDFC Life insurance get maximum return on advertising spends.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Anurag Gupta, CEO &amp;ndash;Columbus India said, &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s an absolute privilege to have won the SEM &amp;amp; SEO directive for a leading brand like HDFC Life Insurance. With this engagement, we will try to ensure that HDFC Life gets the best of Columbus India&amp;rsquo;s digital solutions and expertise, enabling them to increase their customer base and stay ahead of the competition.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/92704-hdfclife.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/account-news/foxymoron-wins-digital-mandate-of-the-hershey-company-92604.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>18/10/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Foxymoron wins digital mandate of The Hershey Company</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;The Hershey Company has awarded the digital mandates of eight brands including Hershey&amp;rsquo;s Syrups, Hershey&amp;rsquo;s Milkshake, Hershey&amp;rsquo;s Spreads, Hershey&amp;rsquo;s Milk Booster, Sofit, Jolly Rancher, Brookside and Kisses to leading digital marketing solutions agency FoxyMoron. The account was won following a multi-agency pitch.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The mandate entails strengthening the brand&amp;rsquo;s digital presence by building a distinct online personality and highlighting product offerings. FoxyMoron will be involved in the strategy, content creation and design across all social media platforms, as well as website maintenance and search engine optimization. The agency is already working towards building affinity via brand advocacy on digital with a collaborative strategy focusing around topical and interactive content.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Commenting on this win, Pratik Gupta, Co-founder, FoxyMoron said, &amp;ldquo;This is most definitely a &amp;#39;sweet&amp;#39; win for us! To have the opportunity to be the one-stop digital agency for the entire group calls for a huge celebration. Each brand in the portfolio has a different challenge and each of them are at a varied stage in their digital lifecycle. Our team has already begun working on a range of things, including content creation, digital collaborations as well as amplifying the brand&amp;rsquo;s resonance with the consumer. The biggest proof of the pudding lies in the recent launch of Kisses; which has accounted for the most amount of our work and output on the brand. Looking forward to making many more &amp;#39;sweet&amp;#39; memories with the group.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/92604-collage4_(1).jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/account-news/social-kinnect-wins-digital-mandate-of-entire-indiabulls-group-92596.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>17/10/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Indiabulls Group awards social media mandate to Social Kinnect</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Social Kinnect, India&amp;#39;s foremost independent digital marketing agency, has been awarded the social media mandate of Indiabulls Group. The agency will be responsible for managing the social media platforms of the entire Indiabulls Group umbrella namely - Indiabulls Housing Finance Limited (IBHFL), Indiabulls Ventures (IVL), Indiabulls LED (IB LED), Indiabulls Real Estate (IBREL), and Indiabulls Pharmaceutical, Indiabulls Personal Loans, Indiabulls Asset Management Company (AMC), and Indiabulls Foundation.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Previously, Social Kinnect handled the mandate of Indiabulls Home Loans. Their result-driven media strategies and creative approach for the brand&amp;#39;s growth on digital, was the decisive factor for them winning the mandate for the entire Indiabulls Group. The agency will be responsible for driving and delivering the overall social media requirements of the group. The mandate includes creative strategy and execution, social media management, performance creative development, website development as well as influencer marketing.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Established in 1999, Indiabulls Group today has a net worth of over ₹ 22,608 crores and their market capitalization stands at over ₹ 75,838 crores. The group has a strong presence in the financial services, real estate, pharmaceuticals and LED sectors. It&amp;#39;s three main independently listed companies - Indiabulls Housing Finance Limited (IBHFL) ranked 13th largest Consumer Financial Services Company globally, Indiabulls Real Estate Limited (IBREL) is the 3rd largest real estate company by net worth and assets, and Indiabulls Ventures Limited (IBVL) has been rated BQ1 by CRISIL - highest for any brokerage in India.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the account win, Rohan Mehta - CEO, Social Kinnect said, &amp;ldquo;It has been a pleasure working with the Indiabulls team for over two years now. It&amp;#39;s great to see our relationship with them grow this way. Indiabulls is a challenger company that is evolving at a very fast pace, and we are excited for our onward journey of shaping the way the group will be perceived in the digital spectrum. Our endeavours will always be to ensure that we are pushing the boundaries on digital to drive great brand sentiment and devise effective digital strategies that make a business impact.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Ankit Banga (AGM &amp;ndash; Digital Marketing, Indiabulls Group) says &amp;lsquo;Consolidating our communication approach &amp;amp; strategy across Social Media allows us to showcase the entire gamut of our offerings, whilst maintaining a common narrative for the entire Indiabulls Group. In a little more two years, Social Kinnect has been a great partner for the Group&amp;rsquo;s flagship company Indiabulls Housing. Their diligence and support have been considerable in this time, and a deciding factor in this renewed association. We look forward to taking giant strides along with them as we synergise the Group&amp;rsquo;s efforts across social media.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/92596-SocialKinnect.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/account-news/dentsu-webchutney-wins-digital-mandate-for-big-fm-92551.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>16/10/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Dentsu Webchutney wins digital mandate for Big FM</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Dentsu Webchutney, the digital agency from Dentsu Aegis Network, has attained the digital duties for BIG FM. The account will operate out of the agency&amp;rsquo;s Mumbai office.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking on the partnership, Manoj Lalwani, Marketing Head, BIG FM commented, &amp;ldquo;Radio by its very nature is quite similar to digital. Both allow for interaction and a dialogue with people so going whole hog with digital is a natural extension of our brand strategy. Dentsu Webchutney is known for its out of the box thinking and we believe that their digital expertise and their understanding of platforms and culture will really do wonders for Big FM.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Harsh Shah, Vice President, Dentsu Webchutney added, &amp;ldquo;Big FM, with its wide network, is a content gold mine. When it comes to digital, nothing works better than content that is compelling, memorable and social. We&amp;rsquo;re very excited to see how such diverse content from Big FM can be put into play. We have some very interesting ideas lined up and can&amp;rsquo;t wait to put them into motion.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/92551-Colalge.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/account-news/starcom-wins-ola's-media-dutiesaccount-size-over-rs-200-crore-88728.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>06/03/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Starcom wins Ola's media duties, account size over Rs 200 crore</news:title>
      <news:description>Starcom India has been awarded the media duties of Ola, one of the world’s largest ride-sharing companies. Starcom will oversee the account's media planning and buying across both traditional and digital media. The business was won in a closely contested pitch, with various leading agencies in the fray.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As per sources, the account size is worth Rs 200 crore and the account has moved from Group M's Motivator.&amp;nbsp;The mandate is for India, as well as for upcoming international markets that Ola will operate in.&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="http://cms.exchange4media.com/files/1520305044_8rK04M_deepak.jpg" style="width:445px;height:240px"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When contacted for confirmation,&amp;nbsp;Deepak Sharma, Managing Director, Starcom North says, “Ola was impressed with our strategic planning skills, led by the Human Experience (HX) approach, as also with our strong data and analytics-led capabilities. They are on an incredibly exciting journey and we look forward to being a part of their growth and expansion plans.”&lt;br&gt;Mudit Shekhawat, Sr. Director, Marketing at Ola said, “We are excited to partner with Starcom. Their teams were able to demonstrate strong insights on the category and brought in fresh ideas and thinking on the brand. Their expertise in integrated communications strategies and smart execution will help in further consolidating our leadership in this industry. We are excited to work with them.”</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1513589969_FOURzY_big_(23).jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://www.exchange4media.com/industry-briefing-news/Adlabs-Imagica-rolls-out-extensive-360-mktg-campaign_50848.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>07/05/2013</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Adlabs Imagica rolls out extensive 360 mktg campaign</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;Keeping its core target audience in mind, Adlabs Imagica has launched a 360 degree marketing campaign, taking customer engagement to an all new level. With a strong media mix, including print, radio, digital, OOH, television and cinema, the campaign has been divided into the pre-launch, launch and sustenance phase to keep the momentum on-going. A clear role has been given to each media vehicle and various innovations have been implemented across media from time to time.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;Driving social conversations and education about a true international standard theme park is critical for the launch period. With an aim of building the recall for the trails of the park, the campaign revolved around good use of digital media in the form of social and innovative display &amp;amp; Search during the pre-launch phase to create hype and build up around Imagica. A co-branded contest with The Times of India Group across print and radio was initiated that offered an exclusive sneak peek preview at Imagica coined as &amp;lsquo;First of the Imagicans&amp;rsquo;. Additionally a unique web and mobile app was created for the visitors, &amp;lsquo;Imagicate your World&amp;rsquo;. This application allowed customers to create photos with captions using park characters in the frame. Going forward, the mobile app will further play the role of driving social loyalty, social share and e-commerce.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;The launch phase consisted of extensive print advertising campaign with close to 100 high impact and innovative print advertisement inserts spread over six weeks across Maharashtra, Gujarat and Delhi NCR. To add to this, the OOH campaign was spread over 500 sites across Mumbai, Pune and the Mumbai-Pune Expressway. A judicious mix of high impact hoardings for a short burst and bus shelters &amp;amp; pole kiosks to drive a 45-day long sustenance campaign was executed. Followed by this, television and cinema advertising campaigns will break with cinema catering to Maharashtra, Gujarat and Delhi NCR with a good mix of multiplexes and key single screen cinemas, the month-long television campaign will communicate to audiences pan India through a right channel mix across genres like GEC, music, kids, English movies and news.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;Amidst the mainstream ATL mediums, a strong viral campaign is also running on digital and radio to drive intrigue, awareness and constant recall amongst consumers. The viral campaign is around two key characters of the Park &amp;ndash; an Astronaut and a Dinosaur. A strong plot has been created around these characters, which will generate curiosity and interest amongst consumers and driving them to the social media handle.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/50848-default-story.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/account-news/airtel-moves-creative-business-to-jwt-39053.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>10/08/2010</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Airtel moves creative business to JWT</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p align=justify&gt;Putting all speculations to rest, Airtel has moved its creative business to JWT India. Senior sources close to the development have confirmed the news to exchange4media. With this, Airtel has ended its 15-year relationship with Rediffusion Y&amp;R. The Airtel account has been pegged at Rs 400 crore. &lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p align=justify&gt;It may be recalled that Bharti Airtel had awarded the creative duties of its DTH venture, Airtel Digital TV, to JWT in 2008.&#13;
</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/fs_39053.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/account-news/reliance-communications-splits-rs-400-cr-media-biz-between-mec-and-omd-38985.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>03/08/2010</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Reliance Communications splits Rs 400-cr media biz between MEC and OMD</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p align=justify&gt;In the wake of a multi-agency pitch, Reliance Communications has moved its media mandate to OMD and MEC. The wireless data and DTH part of the business has been awarded to OMD, while the wireless part, which includes voice and 3G, has been assigned to MEC. The incumbent on the business is Mudra Max. The total business is pegged at upwards of Rs 400 crore. &lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p align=justify&gt;The other agency in the fray besides the incumbent was MediaCom. &lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p align=justify&gt;Confirming the development to exchange4media, Sanjay Behl, CEO, Reliance Big TV and Group Head - Brand &amp; Marketing, Reliance Communications, said, “We have crafted a new vision for our brands, and we were looking for media partners that would enable us to achieve the vision, and hence this change.” &#13;
</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/fs_38985.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/account-news/maxus-to-handle-the-media-duties-for-neo-sports-38257.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>26/05/2010</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Maxus to handle the media duties for Neo Sports</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p align=justify&gt;Neo Sports has roped in Maxus as its media agency. Prior to this, MEC was handling the media duties. The creative duties continue to be with McCann Erickson. Industry sources peg the business in the region of Rs 20-25 crore. &lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p align=justify&gt;Prasana Krishnan, COO, Neo Sports, has confirmed the development to exchange4media. While both MEC and Maxus belong to GroupM, the change comes due to some internal restructuring. &lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p align=justify&gt;Sports and entertainment company Nimbus Communications had announced the launch of Neo Sports, a 24-hour cricket centric television channel in September 2006. The channel focuses on various cricket related programming, live coverage of both domestic and international cricket, interviews with top cricketers, analysis and sports entertainment. &lt;/p&gt;&#13;
		&#13;
		&#13;
		&#13;
		&#13;
		&#13;
		&#13;
</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/fs_38257.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/account-news/kingdom-of-dreams-awards-ad-duties-to-mud-piegcell-technologies-to-handle-digital-38254.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>26/05/2010</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Kingdom of Dreams awards ad duties to Mud Pie; Gcell Technologies to handle digital</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p align=justify&gt;Kingdom of Dreams, The Great Indian Nautanki Pvt Ltd venture situated in Gurgaon (Delhi/NCR), has brought in Mud Pie to handle its advertising duties. Gcell Technologies has been chosen as the digital agency. &lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p align=justify&gt;Speaking on the development, Viraf Sarkari, Director, Wizcraft, said, “Mud Pie will handle the creatives for Kingdom of Dreams, while Gcell Technologies will take over the digital marketing. Wizcraft is the in-house brand activation in-charge. The contractual period is for 6-12 months and work has already begun.” &lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p align=justify&gt;On being chosen for the business, Syed Usman, Founding Partner, Mud Pie, India, said, “I think they chose us because of our strategic thinking and they possibly identified with our passion towards work.” &lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p align=justify&gt;Since Kingdom of Dreams is a new concept for the people of India, advertising will play a crucial role. “Print will be playing a big role. But digital, outdoor, radio and, possibly the film medium later, will be important too. We are also looking at some unconventional ways to create impact,” informed Usman. &lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p align=justify&gt;He further said, “While digital will be a critical platform for us, the entire concept has to work as one, irrespective of the medium. So, not only the look, style and tone will be carried across, the basic brand idea and character will be the unifying thread across different vehicles.” &lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
Meanwhile, Mud Pie has already kickstarted the project in relation to practical purposes and the efforts will be evident as and when the launch date – tentatively mid-July – draws closer. &lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p align=justify&gt;Gcell Technologies will be taking charge of the complete online activities and implementations. On this, its Business Development Head, Ali Qadir, said, “We are doing the website design, development, implementation, digital marketing and 3D/ graphic designing.” &lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p align=justify&gt;The agency has already begun work on a website, which will be new in terms of content and feel. “We are currently working on developing a new website that will be a lot more informative, interactive and rich with content. The new website is being designed keeping the some key important factors in mind, that is, layout, usability, functionality and reporting. We are tying up with Bookmyshow.com so that people can book their tickets online too,” Qadir added. &lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p align=justify&gt;On being asked what all tools of digital marketing would be used in terms of reach, he replied, “Emails, SMS campaigns, online advertising on travel sites, social media sites, and PPC campaigns, to name a few.” &lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p align=justify&gt;Mud Pie, the advertising firm delivering clients and brands with creative solutions, has clients like Grohe, Acme, DeraMandawa and now Kingdom of Dreams in its kitty. On the other hand, Gcell Technologies is more inclined towards IT solutions and the main services are website designing, developments, digital marketing, digital publishing and software solutions. &lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p align=justify&gt;Kingdom of Dreams, situated in the golden triangle of Jaipur, Agra and Delhi, is an entertainment and lifestyle destination that will showcase and bring together India’s art, culture, heritage, crafts, cuisine and performing arts – empowered by new age technology. The lavish concept boasts of some spectacular zones such as Nautanki Mahal, Culture Gully and Showshaa Theatre. &lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
		&#13;
		&#13;
		&#13;
		&#13;
		&#13;
		&#13;
		&#13;
		&#13;
</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/fs_38254.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/account-news/parle-products-reviews-media-biz-of-entire-portfolio-38251.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>26/05/2010</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Parle Products reviews media biz of entire portfolio</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p align=justify&gt;It is learnt that Parle Products is reviewing the media duties for its complete portfolio and has invited media agencies to make presentations to get a fresh perspective on its media business. TME is the current media AOR on the business. &lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p align=justify&gt;Sources close to the development have confirmed the news, however, no official confirmation was available. Neither could the account spend be ascertained, but it is believed to be substantial. &lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p align=justify&gt;As per the sources, quite a few agencies have been invited to make their presentations on the basis of credentials. &lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p align=justify&gt;It may be recalled that very recently Digital Law &amp; Kenneth had bagged the entire Parle Products portfolio, including the confectionaries and savouries business. The brands include ParleG, Monaco, Hide &amp; Seek, Parle Marie, Melody, Kisme, Musst Bites and Musst Chips. Industry sources have pegged the account size at Rs 4 crore. The account had moved from BC Webwise. &lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p align=justify&gt;However, there shall be no changes in the creative side of business and the existing creative agencies on the roster will continue to handle the creative duties of Parle Products. &lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p align=justify&gt;Parle Products is one of India’s oldest biscuits and confectionery products companies. This move by the company is an effort to continue to engage with the youth, who are now more focused on digital platforms for their media consumption. &lt;/p&gt;&#13;
		&#13;
		&#13;
		&#13;
		&#13;
		&#13;
		&#13;
		&#13;
		&#13;
		&#13;
</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/fs_38251.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/account-news/uidai-pitchdentsuperceptconcept-shortlisted-for-the-final-round-38250.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>26/05/2010</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>UIDAI pitch: Dentsu, Percept, Concept shortlisted for the final round</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p align=justify&gt;Dentsu, Concept and Percept have been shortlisted for the final round of the pitch for the Unique Identification Authority of India (UIDAI) business. It may be recalled that UIDAI had called for a pitch earlier in May this year. Two agencies will be awarded the creative and media duties. Industry sources have pegged the account size at over Rs 100 crore. &lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p align=justify&gt;UIDAI, which had unveiled its new brand name – ‘Aadhaar’ – and logo last month, has been scouting for an agency to handle its creative and media duties. The pitch was called last week and reportedly agencies like Span Communications, Lowe, Concept, Rediffusion Y&amp;R, Dentsu and Percept were in the fray for the business. &lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p align=justify&gt;UIDAI is a committee set up by the Government of India to provide a Unique Identification Number to all residents in order to improve their lives and also cut down on the annual costs incurred in verifying identities. The project is headed by former Infosys Chairman Nandan Nilekani. &lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p align=justify&gt;Though it is targeted across sections of the society, the scheme is expected to benefit the poor the most, who are generally deprived of various benefits and schemes that the government offers and face a lot of barriers in accessing welfare related opportunities. &lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p align=justify&gt;Between August 2010 and February 2011, the UIDAI will begin issuing the first unique identification numbers (UIDs) to residents. The UID rollout presents a significant opportunity for Government, public and private agencies in India. &lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p align=justify&gt;Also read: &lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p align=justify&gt;&lt;a href=”http://www.exchange4media.com/e4m/news/fullstory.asp?section_id=45&amp;news_id=38120&amp;tag=3757&amp;search=y” target=_blank&gt;Span, Lowe, Rediffusion Y&amp;R, Dentsu, Percept among agencies in the fray for UIDAI biz&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p align=justify&gt;&lt;a href=”http://www.exchange4media.com/e4m/news/fullstory.asp?section_id=8&amp;news_id=37955&amp;tag=3539&amp;search=y” target=_blank&gt;UIDAI unveils brand name &amp; logo; communication strategy in next few months, says Nandan Nilekani&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;		&#13;
		&#13;
		&#13;
		&#13;
		&#13;
		&#13;
		&#13;
</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/fs_38250.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/account-news/mudra-connext-assigned-media-mandate-for-travelguruac-size-upwards-of-rs-10-cr-38178.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>17/05/2010</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Mudra Connext assigned media mandate for Travelguru; ac size upwards of Rs 10 cr</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p align=justify&gt;Mudra Connext, a unit of Mudra MAX (Integrated Communications Planning &amp; Implementation) has been chosen to handle the media mandate for travel portal Travelguru. The account size is estimated at upwards of Rs 10 crore and the operations will be carried out of the agency’s Mumbai office. &lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p align=justify&gt;On awarding the media business to Mudra Connext, Praveen Meloth, AVP-Marketing, Travelguru, said, “We were always in a hunt for an agency with the right approach, which accepts challenges and proves itself by way of its work. We look forward to Mudra Connext bringing innovative thinking and a strategic direction to the brand. We are confident that Connext, with their category experience and capabilities across all media formats, will help us optimally spread our message and reach out to our customers across the country.” &lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p align=justify&gt;On choosing Mudra Connext over other agencies, Meloth said, “The team at Mudra came across with some innovative thinking and strategies, they impressed with us with their understanding of the category as well.” &lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p align=justify&gt;When asked what new additions one would see on Travelguru in the coming months, he replied, “We have tied up with hotels for some great offers that are exclusive to Travelguru. Customers can look forward to benefiting form these hotels and holiday offers on our website.” &lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p align=justify&gt;Travelguru chose to remain tight-lipped about the names of the other agencies that had pitched for the account, but did inform that they weren’t looking for any other agency as of now. &lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p align=justify&gt;Commenting on the win, Manas Mishra, EVP &amp; Country Head, Mudra Connext, said, “It is an exciting category. Building awareness and identity for Travelguru, a hotels and resorts portal, would be a major task. We need to create a distinct identity for the brand as all travel portals are often dedicated to flight bookings.” &lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p align=justify&gt;Travelguru offers access to more than 4,000 hotels across 350 cities in India and over 72,000 hotels worldwide. It offers travellers the opportunity to plan and purchase their travel in a transparent, easy and customisable manner with instant hotel bookings and confirmations. &lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
		&#13;
		&#13;
</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/fs_38178.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
</urlset>
