<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9" xmlns:image="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-image/1.1" xmlns:news="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-news/0.9">
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/advertising-news/why-the-sudden-rise-in-ccos-quitting-and-switching-jobs-93390.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>11/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Why the sudden rise in CCOs quitting and switching jobs?</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;The last two weeks have witnessed a number of Chief Creative Officer (CCO) movements. Ajay Gahlaut recently quit as chief creative officer of Ogilvy North and deputy chief creative officer, Ogilvy India. Gahlaut is expected to&amp;nbsp;join Publicis, replacing Bobby Pawar who is slated&amp;nbsp;to join as Chairman of Havas Group, India&amp;nbsp;in January.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Ashish Chakravarty quit Contract India to join McCann India as creative head while Sagar Mahabalaleshwarkar has taken on Chakravarty&amp;rsquo;s place at Contract.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The question here is,&amp;nbsp;what has changed all of a sudden&amp;nbsp;to lead to such a large-scale churn? As per the owner of a manpower search agency specializing in ad and media hiring, &amp;ldquo;It is a result of ad firms trying to reinvent themselves to keep pace with the rise of digital, which have upended the marketing business.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;With digital coming in, creativity has become&amp;nbsp;far more complicated than it used to be. Agencies, regardless of their respective sizes, need to keep reviewing how they are coping (or not) with the digital wave.&amp;nbsp;Hence, overhauling existing creative teams is one of the priorities, points out a former CCO turned independent ad-man. &amp;ldquo;Digital has, of course, changed a lot. Agencies are now creating hundreds, if not thousands pieces of creative, a month. This rise of social media and platforms in general has meant that creativity is more targeted than ever. So most large agencies are constantly re-evaluating the positions and talent pool.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Sandeep Goyal, former President of Rediffusion and ex Chairman of Dentsu India remarks that there is paucity of talent at that level. &amp;quot;Most creative directors of certain seniority and stature set up creative shops of their own in recent years leaving fewer and fewer talent available for employment by agencies. &amp;quot; Goyal opines that the bigger problem is that these creative satraps also invariably carry some creative followers into their new agencies. So a lot of attrition and turmoil all around. &amp;quot;Network pressure today is simply how many global awards you pocket, how much new biz you win. Earlier it was not easy to quantity and compare. Now it is. Laggards are always under pressure. Quitting &amp;lsquo;for better prospects&amp;rsquo; is the easy way out,&amp;quot; he explains.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The job-list of a CCO entails&amp;nbsp;supervising the creative team, directing their output, developing design concepts that further the company&amp;rsquo;s identity to anticipating the future direction of the industry using research and insight and bringing the company in fore of that trajectory.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Industry sources share that one of the biggest shifts has been the network-pressures, which can also be attributed to the high churn rate. &amp;ldquo;Agencies today are angling to ingrain themselves deeper within client&amp;rsquo;s businesses, to centralize themselves closer to the bottom line. The revenue streams are being attacked on various fronts which does lead to cost-cutting. One being given the polite exit signal under a cost-cutting mission is the &amp;lsquo;new&amp;rsquo; normal in the business,&amp;rdquo; shared an ad-agency co-founder on condition of anonymity.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Another source argues that in case anything goes wrong, a CCO is one of the most visible heads. Besides, a CCO who merely handles ad campaigns and branding consistency is a missed opportunity. &amp;ldquo;CCOs today end up being easier scapegoats if the business isn&amp;#39;t doing too well. Infact, this person needs a seat at the table when executive business plans are being created and the leverage to present big interruptions and lead the team through strategic brainstorming too. This remains one reason they&amp;#39;re likely to want to quit or switch their work culture,&amp;quot; said the source.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93390-cco.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/advertising-news/taco-bell-introduces-new-chickstar-wrap-in-itsthenew-campaign-93383.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>10/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Taco Bell introduces new Chickstar Wrap in #ItsTheNew campaign</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;The #foodie millennial generation in India has been flocking to Taco Bell stores in India all year to relish new twists to their favourite food, such as the Naked Chicken Taco and the Crispy Potaco. For its third product launch in India, Taco Bell went bigger and bolder; and leveled up the customer&amp;rsquo;s food experience from the standardized fast food burgers, sandwiches and wraps.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Taco Bell announced the launch of its latest product innovation &amp;lsquo;Chickstar Wrap&amp;rsquo;, a unique form of star-shaped tortilla, filled with crispy chicken, delicious veggies and signature sauces from the house of Taco Bell. This new product innovation has already proved to be a hit with anyone who enjoys a good burger or sandwich.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The Chickstar Wrap is unique right from its shape to the taste to the ingredients, that it deserved a launch campaign that was unlike any other food type. The brand has joined their consumer base in facing the unshakeable personal small-talk question of &amp;ldquo;Aur bata, what&amp;rsquo;s new?&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The campaign was conceptualized by Taco Bell&amp;rsquo;s agency on record Ogilvy Delhi.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking on the campaign, Sidharth Shukla, Vice President &amp;amp; Head of Digital, Ogilvy Delhi said, &amp;quot;Our insight was based on the fact that for our target audience trying out experiences is essential. It comes out of a &amp;lsquo;want&amp;rsquo; to discover new things and equally from a realization that there is nevertheless a certain rut which has seeped into day-to-day life.&amp;nbsp; An embodiment of these feelings, we felt, was reflected in the numerous &amp;ldquo;What&amp;rsquo;s up?&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Aur Bata&amp;rdquo; questions that we receive&amp;nbsp;as we go about our day &amp;ndash; The Chickstar Wrap here is the symbolic answer, counter and come back to this question &amp;ndash; putting a new spin from both a format and a taste perspective to a food item which has largely remained unchanged since we have known it. &amp;nbsp;The film remains true to the Taco Bell style that we are now so familiar with &amp;ndash; slices of life, witty, young, all of which add to making it very relatable to the audience we wish to engage with&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Campaign video:&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/J2RvcpuyR00" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93383-TacoBellChickStarWrap.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/advertising-news/dentsu-webchutney-launches-30-films-for-platinum-days-of-loves-new-seasons-collection-93380.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>10/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Dentsu Webchutney launches 30 films for Platinum Days of Love’s new season’s collection</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Dentsu Webchutney, the digital agency from Dentsu Aegis Network, has launched Platinum Days of Love&amp;rsquo;s new season&amp;rsquo;s collection with the campaign #LoveSoRare, a series of 30 digital films inspired by the design story of the collection. The complimentary design of each pair of love bands is brought to life by 30 films that arise from the insight of togetherness amidst individuality.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;With evolving times, couple&amp;rsquo;s relationships and their expectations from love are also seeing a change. Modern relationships born out of this change now demand a better understanding of each other, respect for what each person brings to the dynamic, and a sense of individuality that doesn&amp;rsquo;t stop them from coming together. This ability to be oneself while being together is highly sought after and aspirational for young couples, but it isn&amp;rsquo;t easy to achieve. In fact, it&amp;rsquo;s rare.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Friends:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/z0bvHVABRC0" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Platinum Days of Love celebrates this very kind of modern love, one that is progressive, equal and rare, and their new collection is a reflection of this ethos.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;This kind of rare love brought alive through these 30 films, is seen in very relatable differences between couples. She&amp;rsquo;s an environmentalist, he likes to burst firecrackers; he&amp;rsquo;s watching his weight, she tempts him by bringing home delicious desserts. Will it come in the way of love? With wit and gentle humour, the 30 films of togetherness demonstrate how those who have a rare connection don&amp;rsquo;t see differences as something that comes in the way of love, they look at it positively. They know that despite the differences, what they share is rare.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Cat-Lover:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Uy9G21f_Oz8" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;To introduce this idea of rare love, the agency created a Love Score, a test that encouraged people to test their love based on their differences. Ultimately, it was revealed that these differences should be celebrated and will not push you and your partner apart when you share a #LoveSoRare. Once intrigue was built, the agency launched 30 films inspired by the 30 designs that symbolize rare love.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the campaign, Pravin Sutar, Executive Creative Director, Dentsu Webchutney said, &amp;ldquo;In a world where brands tend to look at relationships and love with rose-coloured lenses, it was refreshing to create a campaign that adds to the conversation in such a unique and honest way. Through #LoveSoRare, we&amp;rsquo;re asking viewers to rethink what makes their relationship truly unique.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Aalap Desai, Senior Creative Director, Dentsu Webchutney added, &amp;ldquo;Each pair of rings from the collection has a unique design story that that marks the rare bond between a couple. Our 30 days of togetherness is a perfect reflection of this very love.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Baby Conundrum:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/QFgoB4kIBs4" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Sujala Martis, Director- Consumer Marketing, Platinum Guild International said, &amp;ldquo;Today&amp;rsquo;s generation is very pragmatic, we can&amp;rsquo;t attempt to sell them a fairy tale that is removed from their reality. But working with today&amp;rsquo;s truths &amp;amp; creating a value system that is aspirational, progressive &amp;amp; yet differentiated is what we aim for. Love needs to be based on a true partnership with openness, honesty &amp;amp; real acceptance of each other&amp;rsquo;s individuality at the heart of it. Putting this into practice, however, is hard and rare to find. A rare love like that deserves an equally rare metal platinum.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Biryani War:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/X4GeYULqdbA" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;This campaign will also give couples an exciting opportunity to win a special dining experience or wedding photoshoot on a purchase of platinum in-store.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The series of 30 videos will be released daily, starting from November 23rd till December 23rd.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Hoarder:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/5BugUJ0z-qk" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93380-PlatinumDaysofLove.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/advertising-news/lowe-lintas-designs-campaign-to-position-veedols-take-off-as-a-youthful-brand-93379.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>10/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Lowe Lintas designs campaign to position Veedol's Take-Off as a youthful brand</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Veedol has launched a new campaign for its flagship brand Take-Off. Lowe Lintas Kolkata, the agency-on-record for Veedol, has conceived the advertising campaign. Take-Off specifically caters to 2-wheeler riders in the country.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;According to the Society of Indian Automobile Manufacturers (SIAM)&amp;#39;s report for FY2018, the Indian two-wheeler industry has crossed the 20-million unit sales milestone for the first time - registering a growth of approximately 15 per cent over the previous financial year. The road ahead for the two-wheeler industry looks very exciting and promising. Riding on the fast-growing two-wheeler industry, Veedol&amp;#39;s launch of a new campaign for Take-Off appears to be particularly opportune.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;The campaign film focuses on the innate characteristic of young Indians who challenge the status quo and set things right for the common good. The narrative is woven around these purposeful youth of today who see themselves as agents of change, with the inherent power, confidence and intent to make a difference to the society as a whole. Positioning Veedol as a modern, youthful brand, &amp;#39;For The Young Engines of India&amp;#39; acts not just as a new advertising slogan but celebrates India&amp;rsquo;s energetic youth who equitably represent the brand&amp;#39;s values.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Commenting on the campaign, R N Ghosal, Managing Director, Veedol India, said, &amp;ldquo;The campaign showcases Veedol&amp;rsquo;s full range of motorcycle and scooter engine oils in an upbeat, youthful ambience with an over-riding sense of purposeful action built into the narrative. This would go a long way in enhancing Veedol&amp;rsquo;s imagery, in step with several other brand interventions we have undertaken recently like the launch of the new international packaging. I believe that this campaign is an important milestone in positioning Veedol as a vibrant and youthful brand of choice for emerging consumers&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Janmenjoy Mohanty, Regional President, Lowe Lintas, said, &amp;ldquo;While tuning into the larger India story, we were looking for a youth truth that would suitably reflect the current dynamic. Our search led us to the fact that young people are self-starters, who will not wait for things to happen, but effect change themselves. That is what makes them the &amp;lsquo;young engines&amp;rsquo; of a fast-changing India. A belief we reflect in the new communication for Veedol.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;D K Guha, Executive Director, Lowe Lintas, added &amp;quot;Veedol&amp;rsquo;s new international packaging, as well as the introduction of high-performance oils, provided the perfect moment for launching the new campaign. Set against the backdrop of a young and restless India, the campaign captures the youthful energy and attitude of the millennials -&amp;nbsp;the driving force behind the nation.&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;The campaign is being actively promoted online and offline.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/-bArba_Id_Y" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;u&gt;CREDITS:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Agency: Lowe Lintas&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Creative: Janmenjoy Mohanty, Abhishek Deshwal, Surajit Chakraborty&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Account Management: DK Guha, Subhabrata Roy, Nibedita Ghosh&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Account Planning: Anurag Prasad, Punit Singh&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Production: Finger Print Films&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Director: Rajay Singh&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93379-veedol.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/advertising-news/lk-saatchi-saatchi-and-renault-india-reveal-who-are-indias-worst-drivers-93378.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>10/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>L&amp;K Saatchi &amp; Saatchi and Renault India reveal ‘Who are India’s worst drivers’</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;If you are living in any big megalopolis in India, the odds of you witnessing or even being subjected to rash driving or lawlessness on the roads is pretty high. Be it a two-wheeler or four or even the bulkier ones, each one seems to be in some hurry or the other to reach a destination of their choice with little regard to traffic rules and pedestrian safety. From jumping the red light, to ignoring traffic signs, to over-speeding and lane cutting, virtually every rule in the book is broken when it comes to driving across major roads in India.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;In a unique experiment, Renault India partnered with its creative agency Law &amp;amp; Kenneth Saatchi &amp;amp; Saatchi, and decided to monitor the driving habits of motorists across a few important locations. The team installed cameras across key sites and monitored the traffic violations that took place every hour. This experiment was limited to the cities of Mumbai and New Delhi, usually the hub when it comes to evaluating driving patterns of people on the roads.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Titled &amp;lsquo;Who are India&amp;rsquo;s Worst Drivers?&amp;rsquo;, the experiment throws the spotlight on a cross-section of vehicle owners spanning bikes, auto-rickshaws, taxis, buses, trucks, etc. Each owner is seen presenting their own assessment on who are the worst drivers on the road with hardly anyone pointing a finger to him/herself. The experiment threw up startling findings that showed there are almost 110 traffic violations per signal / per hour. The initiative further goes on to educate viewers to maintain road discipline and urges them to become agents of change via #RespectTheRoad.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the initiative, Virat Khullar, Vice President and Head of Marketing, Renault India said, &amp;ldquo;Renault stands for &amp;lsquo;Passion for life&amp;rsquo; which in a way means easy life for our customers. But for an easy life with cars, one important aspect is to follow the rules defined for driving these cars on road. In India we all face huge traffic issues and true to our nature, all externalise the fault. This campaign is an attempt to portray reality that the traffic situation can only improve if we change ourselves and respect the road.&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Sharing his views, Charles Victor, Executive Director, L&amp;amp;K Saatchi &amp;amp; Saatchi said, &amp;ldquo;This initiative - Driving Smiles, is a wonderful initiative by Renault where we try and give back to the world we sell to. From lighting up villages during Diwali to lighting up smiles at an orphanage during Christmas, the initiative has always tried to take a step towards change. What better change to expect than to change the way Indians drive. This little social experiment aimed at showing us that the change needs to begin with us.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;A two part series, the films have been launched only on the digital platform and serves as an educational tool. While the first film questions people on who are the traffic offenders, the second film goes on provide answers to the questions and how we all need to become agents of change.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CREDITS&lt;/strong&gt;:&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Client: Renault India&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Team: Virat Khullar, Hardik Shah, Kautuk Malviya&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Agency: L&amp;amp;K Saatchi &amp;amp; Saatchi&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Creative: Kartik Smetacek, Thomas George&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Client Servicing: Jay Mehta, Shazia Shaikh&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Planning: Snehasis Bose, Ankur Kapoor&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Production House: Prodigious&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Director: Gaurav Gandhi&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/myjf_g8LiSk" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/J0WaKAVuYBQ" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93378-collage2.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/advertising-news/rp-sanjiv-goenka-group-unveils-latest-too-yumm-karare-tvc-with-virat-kohli-93377.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>10/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>RP-Sanjiv Goenka Group unveils latest Too Yumm! Karare TVC with Virat Kohli</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Guiltfree Industries Limited, the FMCG division of the RP-Sanjiv Goenka Group, has launched its latest TVC showcasing the all-new Too Yumm! Karare. With an emphasis on health and without any compromise on taste, the brand has scored yet another sixer with its latest TVC aptly tagged as &amp;lsquo;Bahar se Tedha, Andhar se Seedha&amp;rsquo; starring Virat Kohli.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Conceptualized by Mullen Lintas, the 30-seconder features ace Indian Cricket Captain, youth icon and fitness enthusiast Virat Kohli. The opening scene of the TVC captures a lady walking into an airport lounge, where she notices Virat Kohli also waiting, and munching on a snack. She sits next to Virat Kohli, and opens her own packet of fried snacks and starts eating it. Each describe the taste of the snack they are eating as tasty and crunchy, this makes the lady slightly curious. Putting the suspense to rest, Virat finally reveals that his snack is the new Too Yumm! Karare exactly like hers, but not fried only baked.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/NoodleMasala.jpg" style="width: 400px; height: 482px;" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Too &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Yumm&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;! &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Karare&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;- Noodle Masala&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Anupam Bokey, VP Marketing (CMO) RP-SG FMCG said, &amp;ldquo;We are absolutely thrilled about the new Karare launch. This is the 6th innovative product from the house of Too Yumm, which effortlessly marries taste with health. Consumers are more receptive to products that they can relate to. This has driven us to introduce Karare, where we have pushed the taste to a higher level, while still staying true to the core promise of Too Yumm! which is &amp;lsquo;baked not fried&amp;rsquo;. Our campaign idea of &amp;lsquo;Bahar se Tedha, Andhar se Seedha&amp;rsquo; captures the thought of being tasty from outside while still being healthy from inside, very succinctly. We believe this will make our product offering more mainstream and appeal to a much wider set of consumers.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/MunchyMasala.jpg" style="width: 400px; height: 503px;" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Too &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Yumm&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;! &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Karare&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;- Munchy Masala&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Available in unique flavor combinations like Chilli Achari, Garlic Peri-Peri, Munchy Masala, Noodle Masala and Southern Spicy, Karare promises to live up to every craving without sacrificing on flavour. Karare is a step forward in Too Yumm!&amp;rsquo;s journey in catering to the increasing number of consumers who are on the constant lookout for tasty yet healthy snacking options. Baked, rather than fried, exalts the brand even higher as its increased competitiveness in offering a healthier and tastier snacking option.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Reflecting her views on the brand&amp;rsquo;s new product Garima Khandelwal, Executive Creative Director, Mullen Lintas said, &amp;ldquo;With the launch of this new snack in the portfolio, we are taking the competition head-on. To land Too Yumm&amp;#39;s differentiated benefit of being baked and healthier but as tasty as its fried competitive product, we drew reference from the category for the advertising and arrived at the campaign idea - &amp;lsquo;Bahar se Tedha, Andhar se Seedha&amp;rsquo;. We wanted to land that Karare is as twisted and tasty as the competition, but there is only goodness inside.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/ChilliAchari(2).jpg" style="width: 400px; height: 494px;" /&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/ChilliAchari.jpg" style="width: 400px; height: 494px;" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Too &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Yumm&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;! &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Karare&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;- Chilli Achari&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Adding to that, Priya Balan &amp;ndash; Sr. Vice President, Mullen Lintas said, &amp;ldquo;Too Yumm Karare campaign is based on a simple insight of how consumers rationalize their unhealthy snacking choice and are cynical about healthier new products because they believe it won&amp;rsquo;t be quite the same palette experience. Our brand ambassador, Virat Kohli charmingly debunks this myth with the line &amp;lsquo;Bahar se Tedha, Andhar se Seedha&amp;rsquo;. That&amp;rsquo;s because Karare is the product format that is a big favorite with consumers but with a key health differentiation by virtue of it being baked, not fried. We are looking forward to exciting times in the category.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Campaign film:&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/TFvNcfgIGsg" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93377-KohliTooYum.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/advertising-news/pulse-candy-lovers-will-go-to-any-lengths-for-just-a-taste-of-their-favourite-sweet-93371.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>10/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Pulse Candy lovers will go to any lengths for just a taste of their favourite sweet</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Pass Pass Pulse, the candy from DS Group, has rolled out another set of three commercials. This takes forward the &amp;lsquo;Pran jaaye par Pulse na jaaye&amp;rsquo; narrative that was introduced with the release of the very first TV commercial.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The TVCs have been conceptualised by J. Walter Thompson Company and the three commercials being released are titled, Astronaut, the Swing &amp;amp; the Bedroom. Each commercial showcases how the protagonists upon seeing a Pulse Candy in their proximity reach out to grab it, even in unfavorable situations.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking on the brand, Shashank Surana, VP, New Product Development, DS Group, said, &amp;ldquo;The Pulse candy has retained number one position, second year in row due to its irresistible taste heightened by a tangy twist. The communication of Pulse is hinged on the temptation to seize a Pulse candy, whatever the circumstances. This three film campaign also highlights the extend people go to get one in &amp;lsquo;Pran jaaye par Pulse na jaaye&amp;rsquo;, situations presented in comical and eccentric plots.&amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Sundeep Sehgal, Executive Creative Director &amp;amp; Vice President, said, &amp;rdquo;The content consumption nature of consumers has changed and Pulse is a brand which is very conscious of this. As a result for this next round of communication we&amp;rsquo;ve created short crisp 10 second commercials that are snackable content for the consumers and also work well from an attention perspective. However the challenge remains to deliver an impactful piece of communication without losing the essence of the brand and I feel this is one such example.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Creative Credits &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;ul&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li&gt;Campaign elements: TVC/Digital&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li&gt;Director (of the films): Shirish Daiya&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li&gt;Production House:&amp;nbsp; Jamic Films&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li&gt;Creative Agency: J. Walter Thompson Company&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Planning: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;ul&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li&gt;Vice President &amp;amp; Execute Planning Director:&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li&gt;Shujoy Dutta&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li&gt;Planning Director: Debasish Das&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Creative Team: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;ul&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li&gt;Executive Creative Directors: Sundeep Sehgal&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li&gt;Creative Director: Nishant Nanda &amp;amp; Kshitij Chandel&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Film Department: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;ul&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li&gt;Girish Kant Singh&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Account management:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;ul&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li&gt;Vice President: Mukund Raina&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li&gt;Account Manager: Naman Joshi&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/azXeNwhAKkg" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/KemcJw8jw8k" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Uce94yKrGDE" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93371-pulse3.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/advertising-news/hersheys-kisses-unveils-first-india-tvc-campaign-93347.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>09/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Hershey’s Kisses unveils first India TVC campaign</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Hershey India Pvt Ltd, a part of The Hershey Company, a leading global snacking giant and the largest producer of quality chocolates in North America, has announced the release of the first ever India TVC for its recently launched iconic and globally-loved &amp;lsquo;Hershey&amp;rsquo;s Kisses&amp;rsquo; chocolate.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The new TVC, featuring Hershey&amp;rsquo;s India brand ambassador Tara Sharma, primarily focuses on how this delightful chocolate enables endearing everyday moments of bonding and affection with loved ones. It celebrates the unique shape and wrapping of Hershey&amp;rsquo;s Kisses that makes every single one perfect for sharing with dear ones.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking about the product launch and the brand&amp;rsquo;s marketing plans, Herjit Bhalla, Managing Director, Hershey India said, &amp;ldquo;We leveraged The Hershey Company&amp;rsquo;s rich chocolate heritage and expertise of 125 years, with the launch of the iconic Hershey&amp;rsquo;s Kisses chocolates. Hershey&amp;rsquo;s Kisses is a global symbol of affection and we have brought this alive in the new TV campaign.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Sarosh Shetty, Marketing Director, Hershey India, shared his view on the new TVC saying, &amp;ldquo;In India, we have created a strong and consistent Hershey&amp;rsquo;s brand that is now a leading player in every category that it is present in. The Kisses launch film is an extension of the Hershey&amp;rsquo;s brand promise in India. It celebrates the unique product proposition of Hershey&amp;rsquo;s Kisses. This delightful chocolate enables one to build a special bond with their loved ones. It is often about those simple, everyday ways to show you care &amp;ndash; which often isn&amp;rsquo;t only words&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The TVC will be played on leading southern channels. This campaign will further be reinforced by an extensive 360-degree campaign across mediums. The Hershey Company brings almost 125 years of quality chocolate-making expertise to the launch of Hershey&amp;rsquo;s Kisses in India.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Today, it is a Fortune 500 company with world-class manufacturing and innovation capabilities to deliver great tasting chocolates. The company makes nearly 70 million Hershey&amp;rsquo;s Kisses every day that are loved by consumers in nearly 60 countries.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Campaign video:&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/hUslMB9KU-U" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93347-HersheyKisses.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/advertising-news/kannur-gives-kerala-new-wings-shows-changes-kannur-airport-will-bring-to-peoples-lives-93352.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>08/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>‘Kannur gives Kerala new wings’ ad shows changes new airport will bring to people’s lives</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Verdana&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Kerala&amp;rsquo;s fourth international airport, Kannur International Airport, will be inaugurated on December 9.&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;Spread over 2,000 acres&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt; in the northern district of Kannur, it is owned and operated by Kannur International Airport Limited. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/kannur%20logo.jpg" style="width: 300px; height: 110px;" /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Verdana&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;With one day remaining for the inauguration, the campaigns centring the airport is garnering rave reviews. The campaign uses everyday scenarios featuring the local people of Kannur to capture their emotions on the momentous change that is to come about in their lives. The films in the campaign focus on the dream and various development aspects such as passenger facilities, boost for trade and tourism, and convenient homecoming for NRIs. Hence it has the theme&amp;mdash;&amp;lsquo;Kannur gives Kerala new wings&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Verdana&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/kannur%20logo.jpg" style="width: 300px; height: 110px;" /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Verdana&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;The campaigns have been done by Maitri Advertising Works. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allowfullscreen="true" allowtransparency="true" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" scrolling="no" src="https://www.facebook.com/plugins/video.php?href=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.facebook.com%2Fmaitriworks%2Fvideos%2F317207435548345%2F&amp;amp;show_text=0&amp;amp;width=560" style="border:none;overflow:hidden" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allowfullscreen="true" allowtransparency="true" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" scrolling="no" src="https://www.facebook.com/plugins/video.php?href=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.facebook.com%2Fmaitriworks%2Fvideos%2F323734138223688%2F&amp;amp;show_text=0&amp;amp;width=560" style="border:none;overflow:hidden" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allowfullscreen="true" allowtransparency="true" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" scrolling="no" src="https://www.facebook.com/plugins/video.php?href=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.facebook.com%2Fmaitriworks%2Fvideos%2F275879189734677%2F&amp;amp;show_text=0&amp;amp;width=560" style="border:none;overflow:hidden" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allowfullscreen="true" allowtransparency="true" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" scrolling="no" src="https://www.facebook.com/plugins/video.php?href=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.facebook.com%2Fmaitriworks%2Fvideos%2F275879189734677%2F&amp;amp;show_text=0&amp;amp;width=560" style="border:none;overflow:hidden" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;iframe allowfullscreen="true" allowtransparency="true" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" scrolling="no" src="https://www.facebook.com/plugins/video.php?href=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.facebook.com%2Fmaitriworks%2Fvideos%2F310439939807269%2F&amp;amp;show_text=0&amp;amp;width=560" style="border:none;overflow:hidden" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Verdana&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;The logo for Kannur International Airport has been designed by Hammer Advertising. G Sreenath, Managing Director, Hammer India, said, &amp;ldquo;In 2011, when Hammer was assigned to design the logo for Kannur international Airport, our creative object was clear. It was to synergize the glory of Kannur&amp;rsquo;s heritage with that of a world class, most modern airport. Seven years hence it is a proud moment for us as Kannur International Airport launches.&amp;rdquo; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/kannurLogo.jpg" style="width: 300px; height: 110px;" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Verdana&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Raju Menon, Director, Operations,&amp;nbsp;Maitri Advertising Works said, &amp;ldquo;We wanted to communicate that this is not just another opening of an airport, but a massive infrastructure project and one of the biggest development initiatives undertaken in the state. It will open up a huge corridor in the North Malabar region and take Kerala to never before heights. We also wanted to spread some positivity among the people after the deluge of 2018.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Verdana&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&amp;ldquo;The pre-launch phase of the campaign kicked off on 28&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; November 2018, with the films being aired on television and simultaneously going live online. The theme song for the airport sung by Kannur&amp;rsquo;s favourite son, Vineeth Sreenivasan, was released on 5&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; December,&amp;rdquo; Menon said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Verdana&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&amp;ldquo;The aim of the campaign was to get an organic reach and create anticipation in the minds of the people for the opening of Kerala&amp;rsquo;s fourth international airport. It has achieved this and more, with the films going viral and being talked about in India and abroad. Potential passengers are now aware of the opening of a state-of-the-art airport in Kannur, and also its proximity to places in Karnataka such as Kodagu and Mysuru. People don&amp;rsquo;t see it as just another modern airport, but as the perfect gateway to North Kerala and South Karnataka,&amp;rdquo; concluded Menon. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Kannur international airport is the second greenfield airport to be built on a public private partnership (PPP) platform in Kerala.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:4.5pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:4.5pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Verdana&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;The Team &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:4.5pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:4.5pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Verdana&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Client:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-hovercard="/ajax/hovercard/page.php?id=764243253761974&amp;amp;extragetparams=%7B%22__tn__%22%3A%22%2CdK-R-R%22%2C%22eid%22%3A%22ARDGu01U-hHWNaV_kumiU_XXOsMs4Ug2gvMtaylr7R8uviyHkrSJTltekTF6P6uOCDZ1hKttRTR3k7Jd%22%2C%22fref%22%3A%22mentions%22%7D" data-hovercard-prefer-more-content-show="1" href="https://www.facebook.com/airportCNN/?__tn__=K-R&amp;amp;eid=ARDGu01U-hHWNaV_kumiU_XXOsMs4Ug2gvMtaylr7R8uviyHkrSJTltekTF6P6uOCDZ1hKttRTR3k7Jd&amp;amp;fref=mentions&amp;amp;__xts__%5B0%5D=68.ARAiVxwuQnASmb89E_mOGV72EcpPjPtiPEDr5ff0YMVnCC5V1w8w2EWz2tzAb6XhibLEGsRZEjTN3aEIEW9-VxtTwyLwZBD-zEjK86eGda2eJRssTa-_5r0mXUtIa8_Qvcj3bnI3nTom5EFhXVniL1_jecQqooBMp4cTgADQVXGkrVJ-JLph0dMRZ4rdZwN0gYMycu9QOch0ZRZ6XfAh5xtdcocjJN7PwE74X7Xz9LUzjhYJnV9r0Ra3OUaje_5HM8Uph61d94kipYqyuAWEE0FsRtvYkjl7hUhecXUJiBxfnyrMjU-zrXTjHlb2SQcq3YekTAu3SPaaS3lV3WNE26QS5IXjh6Ay_iA" rel="nofollow" style="cursor:pointer; color:blue; text-decoration:underline"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Kannur International Airport Limited&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Agency:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-hovercard="/ajax/hovercard/page.php?id=221956641178941&amp;amp;extragetparams=%7B%22__tn__%22%3A%22%2CdK-R-R%22%2C%22eid%22%3A%22ARBIhINdXMLjL2f7amaAC01Lb8QZ_y59epU-shtTdb_S0ZYIFW0HC6Xz3aigPsze3dcATuOa2HYm8LyU%22%2C%22fref%22%3A%22mentions%22%7D" data-hovercard-prefer-more-content-show="1" href="https://www.facebook.com/maitriworks/?__tn__=K-R&amp;amp;eid=ARBIhINdXMLjL2f7amaAC01Lb8QZ_y59epU-shtTdb_S0ZYIFW0HC6Xz3aigPsze3dcATuOa2HYm8LyU&amp;amp;fref=mentions&amp;amp;__xts__%5B0%5D=68.ARAiVxwuQnASmb89E_mOGV72EcpPjPtiPEDr5ff0YMVnCC5V1w8w2EWz2tzAb6XhibLEGsRZEjTN3aEIEW9-VxtTwyLwZBD-zEjK86eGda2eJRssTa-_5r0mXUtIa8_Qvcj3bnI3nTom5EFhXVniL1_jecQqooBMp4cTgADQVXGkrVJ-JLph0dMRZ4rdZwN0gYMycu9QOch0ZRZ6XfAh5xtdcocjJN7PwE74X7Xz9LUzjhYJnV9r0Ra3OUaje_5HM8Uph61d94kipYqyuAWEE0FsRtvYkjl7hUhecXUJiBxfnyrMjU-zrXTjHlb2SQcq3YekTAu3SPaaS3lV3WNE26QS5IXjh6Ay_iA" rel="nofollow" style="cursor:pointer; color:blue; text-decoration:underline"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Maitri Advertising Works&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Digital:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-hovercard="/ajax/hovercard/page.php?id=228374687364428&amp;amp;extragetparams=%7B%22__tn__%22%3A%22%2CdK-R-R%22%2C%22eid%22%3A%22ARAVF5-WH3aZA6-W_S9DIvz4ef21fzgsG94FYuVQzvqNXzp3hnjYAX3LSc3q8ac0YnKDYGNRPeNYHXC_%22%2C%22fref%22%3A%22mentions%22%7D" data-hovercard-prefer-more-content-show="1" href="https://www.facebook.com/winningwayzdigital/?__tn__=K-R&amp;amp;eid=ARAVF5-WH3aZA6-W_S9DIvz4ef21fzgsG94FYuVQzvqNXzp3hnjYAX3LSc3q8ac0YnKDYGNRPeNYHXC_&amp;amp;fref=mentions&amp;amp;__xts__%5B0%5D=68.ARAiVxwuQnASmb89E_mOGV72EcpPjPtiPEDr5ff0YMVnCC5V1w8w2EWz2tzAb6XhibLEGsRZEjTN3aEIEW9-VxtTwyLwZBD-zEjK86eGda2eJRssTa-_5r0mXUtIa8_Qvcj3bnI3nTom5EFhXVniL1_jecQqooBMp4cTgADQVXGkrVJ-JLph0dMRZ4rdZwN0gYMycu9QOch0ZRZ6XfAh5xtdcocjJN7PwE74X7Xz9LUzjhYJnV9r0Ra3OUaje_5HM8Uph61d94kipYqyuAWEE0FsRtvYkjl7hUhecXUJiBxfnyrMjU-zrXTjHlb2SQcq3YekTAu3SPaaS3lV3WNE26QS5IXjh6Ay_iA" rel="nofollow" style="cursor:pointer; color:blue; text-decoration:underline"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Winningwayz&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:4.5pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:4.5pt; margin-left:0cm; text-align:start; -webkit-text-stroke-width:0px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Verdana&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-ligatures:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-caps:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="orphans:2"&gt;&lt;span style="widows:2"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-style:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-color:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="word-spacing:0px"&gt;Project Head:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-hovercard="/ajax/hovercard/user.php?id=1640171640&amp;amp;extragetparams=%7B%22__tn__%22%3A%22%2CdK-R-R%22%2C%22eid%22%3A%22ARBPJzbotVdA3QEV_xzbk75r8kGzaj5zYrCavvYXFUXRZi7-WW3bsGqkNAUgKZCIqm7t2UH-qaU8VAC8%22%2C%22fref%22%3A%22mentions%22%7D" data-hovercard-prefer-more-content-show="1" href="https://www.facebook.com/raju.menon.92?__tn__=K-R&amp;amp;eid=ARBPJzbotVdA3QEV_xzbk75r8kGzaj5zYrCavvYXFUXRZi7-WW3bsGqkNAUgKZCIqm7t2UH-qaU8VAC8&amp;amp;fref=mentions&amp;amp;__xts__%5B0%5D=68.ARAiVxwuQnASmb89E_mOGV72EcpPjPtiPEDr5ff0YMVnCC5V1w8w2EWz2tzAb6XhibLEGsRZEjTN3aEIEW9-VxtTwyLwZBD-zEjK86eGda2eJRssTa-_5r0mXUtIa8_Qvcj3bnI3nTom5EFhXVniL1_jecQqooBMp4cTgADQVXGkrVJ-JLph0dMRZ4rdZwN0gYMycu9QOch0ZRZ6XfAh5xtdcocjJN7PwE74X7Xz9LUzjhYJnV9r0Ra3OUaje_5HM8Uph61d94kipYqyuAWEE0FsRtvYkjl7hUhecXUJiBxfnyrMjU-zrXTjHlb2SQcq3YekTAu3SPaaS3lV3WNE26QS5IXjh6Ay_iA" rel="nofollow" style="cursor:pointer; color:blue; text-decoration:underline"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Raju Menon&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Executive Creative Director:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-hovercard="/ajax/hovercard/user.php?id=528467218&amp;amp;extragetparams=%7B%22__tn__%22%3A%22%2CdK-R-R%22%2C%22eid%22%3A%22ARAtqOm5ls3jUF-C5LaRu89jf81Y9cFKSb8g6JkO_7frvOfsaQcEOel0qFlrjZew053_qH79LJibCUB2%22%2C%22fref%22%3A%22mentions%22%7D" data-hovercard-prefer-more-content-show="1" href="https://www.facebook.com/venugopal.r.nair?__tn__=K-R&amp;amp;eid=ARAtqOm5ls3jUF-C5LaRu89jf81Y9cFKSb8g6JkO_7frvOfsaQcEOel0qFlrjZew053_qH79LJibCUB2&amp;amp;fref=mentions&amp;amp;__xts__%5B0%5D=68.ARAiVxwuQnASmb89E_mOGV72EcpPjPtiPEDr5ff0YMVnCC5V1w8w2EWz2tzAb6XhibLEGsRZEjTN3aEIEW9-VxtTwyLwZBD-zEjK86eGda2eJRssTa-_5r0mXUtIa8_Qvcj3bnI3nTom5EFhXVniL1_jecQqooBMp4cTgADQVXGkrVJ-JLph0dMRZ4rdZwN0gYMycu9QOch0ZRZ6XfAh5xtdcocjJN7PwE74X7Xz9LUzjhYJnV9r0Ra3OUaje_5HM8Uph61d94kipYqyuAWEE0FsRtvYkjl7hUhecXUJiBxfnyrMjU-zrXTjHlb2SQcq3YekTAu3SPaaS3lV3WNE26QS5IXjh6Ay_iA" rel="nofollow" style="cursor:pointer; color:blue; text-decoration:underline"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Venugopal Ramachandran Nair&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Concept &amp;amp; Script:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-hovercard="/ajax/hovercard/user.php?id=100004745618103&amp;amp;extragetparams=%7B%22__tn__%22%3A%22%2CdK-R-R%22%2C%22eid%22%3A%22ARBjsjbOD9iJHPehETkEIzvz_UzszzQom0Q1wvzEnYWEf9TwSwjVc9FI56RxCL_0fAnNfXYZoizX9dMP%22%2C%22fref%22%3A%22mentions%22%7D" data-hovercard-prefer-more-content-show="1" href="https://www.facebook.com/pooja.prasad.56808?__tn__=K-R&amp;amp;eid=ARBjsjbOD9iJHPehETkEIzvz_UzszzQom0Q1wvzEnYWEf9TwSwjVc9FI56RxCL_0fAnNfXYZoizX9dMP&amp;amp;fref=mentions&amp;amp;__xts__%5B0%5D=68.ARAiVxwuQnASmb89E_mOGV72EcpPjPtiPEDr5ff0YMVnCC5V1w8w2EWz2tzAb6XhibLEGsRZEjTN3aEIEW9-VxtTwyLwZBD-zEjK86eGda2eJRssTa-_5r0mXUtIa8_Qvcj3bnI3nTom5EFhXVniL1_jecQqooBMp4cTgADQVXGkrVJ-JLph0dMRZ4rdZwN0gYMycu9QOch0ZRZ6XfAh5xtdcocjJN7PwE74X7Xz9LUzjhYJnV9r0Ra3OUaje_5HM8Uph61d94kipYqyuAWEE0FsRtvYkjl7hUhecXUJiBxfnyrMjU-zrXTjHlb2SQcq3YekTAu3SPaaS3lV3WNE26QS5IXjh6Ay_iA" rel="nofollow" style="cursor:pointer; color:blue; text-decoration:underline"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Pooja Prasad&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Art Director:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-hovercard="/ajax/hovercard/user.php?id=1483606852&amp;amp;extragetparams=%7B%22__tn__%22%3A%22%2CdK-R-R%22%2C%22eid%22%3A%22ARDy-eB7wL9BAsSPAxAQq1Q4gWZqLiiDO4_CU28k9jKc6S0J8LCGnHiMvB3gP7r_nWmsG1qGAvt3LBoj%22%2C%22fref%22%3A%22mentions%22%7D" data-hovercard-prefer-more-content-show="1" href="https://www.facebook.com/iamsiva?__tn__=K-R&amp;amp;eid=ARDy-eB7wL9BAsSPAxAQq1Q4gWZqLiiDO4_CU28k9jKc6S0J8LCGnHiMvB3gP7r_nWmsG1qGAvt3LBoj&amp;amp;fref=mentions&amp;amp;__xts__%5B0%5D=68.ARAiVxwuQnASmb89E_mOGV72EcpPjPtiPEDr5ff0YMVnCC5V1w8w2EWz2tzAb6XhibLEGsRZEjTN3aEIEW9-VxtTwyLwZBD-zEjK86eGda2eJRssTa-_5r0mXUtIa8_Qvcj3bnI3nTom5EFhXVniL1_jecQqooBMp4cTgADQVXGkrVJ-JLph0dMRZ4rdZwN0gYMycu9QOch0ZRZ6XfAh5xtdcocjJN7PwE74X7Xz9LUzjhYJnV9r0Ra3OUaje_5HM8Uph61d94kipYqyuAWEE0FsRtvYkjl7hUhecXUJiBxfnyrMjU-zrXTjHlb2SQcq3YekTAu3SPaaS3lV3WNE26QS5IXjh6Ay_iA" rel="nofollow" style="cursor:pointer; color:blue; text-decoration:underline"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Siva Prasad&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Client Services Director:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-hovercard="/ajax/hovercard/user.php?id=100009181134918&amp;amp;extragetparams=%7B%22__tn__%22%3A%22%2CdK-R-R%22%2C%22eid%22%3A%22ARDPy-lUQarqJRkqfYvxU26ETkjo63zReBaiLZ880JaGiJ1UYh-AcYToufHBo7KsOZROJr6cartSoO2i%22%2C%22fref%22%3A%22mentions%22%7D" data-hovercard-prefer-more-content-show="1" href="https://www.facebook.com/Isumitraj?__tn__=K-R&amp;amp;eid=ARDPy-lUQarqJRkqfYvxU26ETkjo63zReBaiLZ880JaGiJ1UYh-AcYToufHBo7KsOZROJr6cartSoO2i&amp;amp;fref=mentions&amp;amp;__xts__%5B0%5D=68.ARAiVxwuQnASmb89E_mOGV72EcpPjPtiPEDr5ff0YMVnCC5V1w8w2EWz2tzAb6XhibLEGsRZEjTN3aEIEW9-VxtTwyLwZBD-zEjK86eGda2eJRssTa-_5r0mXUtIa8_Qvcj3bnI3nTom5EFhXVniL1_jecQqooBMp4cTgADQVXGkrVJ-JLph0dMRZ4rdZwN0gYMycu9QOch0ZRZ6XfAh5xtdcocjJN7PwE74X7Xz9LUzjhYJnV9r0Ra3OUaje_5HM8Uph61d94kipYqyuAWEE0FsRtvYkjl7hUhecXUJiBxfnyrMjU-zrXTjHlb2SQcq3YekTAu3SPaaS3lV3WNE26QS5IXjh6Ay_iA" style="cursor:pointer; color:blue; text-decoration:underline"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Sumit Raj&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Senior Account Executive:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-hovercard="/ajax/hovercard/user.php?id=1699864760&amp;amp;extragetparams=%7B%22__tn__%22%3A%22%2CdK-R-R%22%2C%22eid%22%3A%22ARCE9jP04L7BI95g0zntPjXOlapeK9TzNn7Ztb44VRGJmhK0jFQQCXcwK99M3laTUBSbFG6SBEufvu3S%22%2C%22fref%22%3A%22mentions%22%7D" data-hovercard-prefer-more-content-show="1" href="https://www.facebook.com/sujin.varghese.7?__tn__=K-R&amp;amp;eid=ARCE9jP04L7BI95g0zntPjXOlapeK9TzNn7Ztb44VRGJmhK0jFQQCXcwK99M3laTUBSbFG6SBEufvu3S&amp;amp;fref=mentions&amp;amp;__xts__%5B0%5D=68.ARAiVxwuQnASmb89E_mOGV72EcpPjPtiPEDr5ff0YMVnCC5V1w8w2EWz2tzAb6XhibLEGsRZEjTN3aEIEW9-VxtTwyLwZBD-zEjK86eGda2eJRssTa-_5r0mXUtIa8_Qvcj3bnI3nTom5EFhXVniL1_jecQqooBMp4cTgADQVXGkrVJ-JLph0dMRZ4rdZwN0gYMycu9QOch0ZRZ6XfAh5xtdcocjJN7PwE74X7Xz9LUzjhYJnV9r0Ra3OUaje_5HM8Uph61d94kipYqyuAWEE0FsRtvYkjl7hUhecXUJiBxfnyrMjU-zrXTjHlb2SQcq3YekTAu3SPaaS3lV3WNE26QS5IXjh6Ay_iA" style="cursor:pointer; color:blue; text-decoration:underline"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Sujin Varghese&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:4.5pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:4.5pt; margin-left:0cm; text-align:start; -webkit-text-stroke-width:0px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Verdana&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-ligatures:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-caps:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="orphans:2"&gt;&lt;span style="widows:2"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-style:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-color:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="word-spacing:0px"&gt;Production House: CREDAYA&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Visualization &amp;amp; Cinematography:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a data-hovercard="/ajax/hovercard/user.php?id=100001933669598&amp;amp;extragetparams=%7B%22__tn__%22%3A%22%2CdK-R-R%22%2C%22eid%22%3A%22ARDp5TpWSzLbmqxsyJPqODf-qBH_woC91W1SZvERwdV8J8Kj9YD-ScfNnurob2IOTMERczyPn5YIFHJZ%22%2C%22fref%22%3A%22mentions%22%7D" data-hovercard-prefer-more-content-show="1" href="https://www.facebook.com/tanu.balak?__tn__=K-R&amp;amp;eid=ARDp5TpWSzLbmqxsyJPqODf-qBH_woC91W1SZvERwdV8J8Kj9YD-ScfNnurob2IOTMERczyPn5YIFHJZ&amp;amp;fref=mentions&amp;amp;__xts__%5B0%5D=68.ARAiVxwuQnASmb89E_mOGV72EcpPjPtiPEDr5ff0YMVnCC5V1w8w2EWz2tzAb6XhibLEGsRZEjTN3aEIEW9-VxtTwyLwZBD-zEjK86eGda2eJRssTa-_5r0mXUtIa8_Qvcj3bnI3nTom5EFhXVniL1_jecQqooBMp4cTgADQVXGkrVJ-JLph0dMRZ4rdZwN0gYMycu9QOch0ZRZ6XfAh5xtdcocjJN7PwE74X7Xz9LUzjhYJnV9r0Ra3OUaje_5HM8Uph61d94kipYqyuAWEE0FsRtvYkjl7hUhecXUJiBxfnyrMjU-zrXTjHlb2SQcq3YekTAu3SPaaS3lV3WNE26QS5IXjh6Ay_iA" style="cursor:pointer; color:blue; text-decoration:underline"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Tanu Balak&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Project Director: Sreenath&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Editor: Aswin G Ashok&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Music: Anand Madhusoodanan&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
CG: Arun&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Post Production: Omlight Creative Studio&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Colour Grading: Black Maria&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Production Controller: Aravindan Kannur&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Art Director: Baiju Krishna&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Associate Editor: Geo Alex&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Camera Team: Sushanth, Mukesh, Aji&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Helicam: Shinu Koshy&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Unit: Dynasty, Calicut&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Production Managers: Binukumar VS, Biju&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93352-kannur_main.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/advertising-news/baggits-new-ad-with-shraddha-kapoor-encourages-women-to-express-their-opinion-93356.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>08/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Baggit’s new ad with Shraddha Kapoor encourages women to express their opinion</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Bag &amp;amp; accessories brand Baggit has launched its autumn winter campaign titled #PutItOnTheTable with Shraddha Kapoor as a part of their association for the year 2018 &amp;amp; 2019. While the first half of the campaign focused on encouraging women to express their own opinions by putting the issues on the table, the second part of the campaign showcases the fun element of how women sometimes reach a decision or make up their minds when there are multiple options available. The campaign again encourages women to be true to their self.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The campaign will be led with a TVC (20 &amp;amp; 30 seconders) that will be launched on GEC channels followed by hoardings in metro cities. This will be supported by a diverse print and an innovative digital campaign in the coming months that will engage the target audience on a deeper brand level, the company said in a statement.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;While the campaign has been conceptualised by Famous Innovations, the TVC has been shot by Curious Films and the print campaign has been shot by ace photographer Prasad Naik.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the campaign Nina Lekhi, MD &amp;amp; Chief Design Curator, Baggit, said, &amp;ldquo;Our first ever TVC received immense love and support from all our customers and the industry at large which was very heartening and encouraging. With the second part of our campaign we continue to extend the concept of #PutItOnTheTable and encourage women to take decisions in their own hands &amp;ndash; however difficult or fun they might be. It is their choice, and no one said they can&amp;rsquo;t have fun while making it. The added fun element makes this one endearing.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Adding on to it, Shraddha Kapoor, Brand Ambassador, said, &amp;ldquo;The Baggit campaign has been immeasurably satisfying to be a part of. The conversation that it has put focus on has helped women take control of the narrative of their individual story. The next part of the campaign deals with a lot of fun that can also be a part of decision making for women. Especially when it is concerned with fashion, I encourage women to have fun with it and don&amp;rsquo;t apologise for it. Be a part of it. Fearlessly. Unapologetically.&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The TVC, print and outdoor campaign will be launched in the month of December.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/At9xf7lQHPI" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93356-shraddhaBag.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/advertising-news/the-glenlivets-new-campaign-celebrates-definitive-moments-in-life-93342.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>07/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>The Glenlivet’s new campaign celebrates definitive moments in life</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;The Glenlivet launched its new &amp;lsquo;THE Campaign&amp;rsquo; in India, celebrating the proposition of definitive moments in life. In line with the brand&amp;rsquo;s modern and contemporary feel, this campaign is an evolution from the brand&amp;rsquo;s heritage as &amp;ldquo;The original one that set the standard&amp;rdquo; and is set to reinforce its role as a visionary within the category.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The campaign has been introduced with two films &amp;ndash; &amp;lsquo;The Bond&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;The Memory&amp;rsquo;, demonstrating the beauty of the unspoilt world and encouraging consumers to seek out &amp;#39;The&amp;#39; moments in their lives with The Glenlivet. The artistic representations help to show consumers that by looking beyond the ordinary they can unlock something special.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Lately, in India, achievers are getting younger and their world is getting busier. In their frantic struggle to the top, they are losing touch with emotions that are truly special in their lives. The Glenlivet, as a brand, aims to identify and celebrate these special emotions or moments that our target audience, senses a connection with. It is the distinct character of such emotions that inspires The Glenlivet to tell a story of an inimitable bond between two people, and a deep-rooted memory that still plays vividly in one&amp;rsquo;s mind, through this endearing and culturally true campaign.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Kartik Mohindra, Chief Marketing Officer, Pernod Ricard India said, &amp;ldquo;The Glenlivet campaign has been designed to celebrate THE moments, which allow us to lead richer and more fulfilling lives. Given how the young achievers are graduating to finer things in life, it was time, we welcomed them to the world of The Glenlivet. Our latest campaign reiterates that in a world with an oversupply of everything- glut, plenitude &amp;amp; noise, what we need is those definitive moments and the Three letter word &amp;ldquo;The&amp;rdquo;, an iconic &amp;amp; distinctive symbol, reinforces the same.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the launch, Miriam Eceolaza, Marketing Director, The Glenlivet said, &amp;ldquo;The Glenlivet campaign is our most ambitious to date. It&amp;rsquo;s a modern and contemporary campaign that stays true to our heritage. India is a key market for The Glenlivet, and we have created this specific campaign to celebrate some of life&amp;rsquo;s definitive moments of the Indian consumer.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Janmenjoy Mohanty, Regional President-North &amp;amp; East, Lowe Lintas India said, &amp;ldquo;Sometimes the most impactful way to put across the brand message is through good old story telling. We chose the most endearing stories that celebrate definitive emotions in an individual&amp;rsquo;s life. Each one has been painstakingly crafted with a fine mix of stunning visuals, underplayed emotions and music that talks to the soul. We hope each of these stories manage to touch a chord with our target audience.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Conceptualised for the Indian market, the campaign has been launched in India, and will be followed by a global release and will be promoted across multimedia platform.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/eZdCYEd-c98" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/GGvBxVOf9bE" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93342-Glenlivet.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/advertising-news/dentsu-impact-we-are-water-foundation-urge-people-to-closeopendefecation-93340.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>07/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Dentsu Impact, We Are Water Foundation urge people to #CloseOpenDefecation</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;On World Toilet Day, Dentsu Impact, the creative agency from Dentsu Aegis Network, joined hands with We Are Water Foundation, CSR wing of Roca Bathroom Products Pvt. Ltd. to launch a movement that&amp;rsquo;s getting everyone talking. This was a social experiment at Sector 29, Gurugram, Haryana for which, a makeshift public toilet was constructed. But when people went in to perform their ablutions, they were in for a surprise. They came face to face with a site, perhaps common to 250 million people in rural India &amp;ndash; a railway track that&amp;rsquo;s used as an open defecating area.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Children and women holding placards delivered the hard facts and adverse effects of open defecation. This not just shocked people but also sensitised them to the plight of rural India. Immediately, people pledged to #CloseOpenDefecation by signing up on the We Are Water Foundation portal. With each sign up/pledge, the foundation is contributing to the construction of more toilets.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The campaign has not been limited only to the social experiment. Prior to it, a film featuring the plight of rural India was launched on social media platforms along with teasers. This was followed up by the Social Experiment film and the option to pledge and tweet was extended to the online urban audience.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Ever since the movement, #CloseOpenDefecation has grabbed enough eyeballs and has trended at the no. 2 spot on Twitter for a day and has garnered 428k views so far.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Soumitra Karnik, Chief Creative Officer, Dentsu Impact says, &amp;ldquo;As advertisers we must create communication which can assist the society we live in, in bringing about a positive change. As communication experts we can and should create content that delivers solutions that can impact a change in our society.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Mayuri Saikia, Management Trustee, We are Water Foundation India &amp;amp; Marketing Head, Roca India says, &amp;ldquo;The problem of open defecation has always been prevalent in the country and still 250 million rural Indians continue to defecate in the open exposing them to various disease and mishaps. Through We Are Water Foundation we have been promoting healthy living, better hygiene and improved sanitation in the country and have done some truly impactful work over the years. When the idea was presented to us, we saw immense potential in it. So far, we have received a heartwarming response for the campaign as more and more are joining the cause with the foundation. As corporates and individuals, we need to realise that beyond government initiatives, we have so much power to drive the desired behavioral change towards usage of toilets and work towards the common goal to #CloseOpenDefecation.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allowfullscreen="true" allowtransparency="true" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" scrolling="no" src="https://www.facebook.com/plugins/video.php?href=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.facebook.com%2FWAWFIndia%2Fvideos%2F360036521397811%2F&amp;amp;show_text=0&amp;amp;width=560" style="border:none;overflow:hidden" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Credits&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Client: Roca Bathroom Products Pvt. Ltd.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Chief creative officer: Soumitra Karnik&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Sr. Creative Director: Ankur Garg&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Creative Director: Debanjan Basak&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Creative Team: Mayank Patel, Nikhita Biswas, Deepali Upadhyay, Suruchi Sirpaul&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Account Management: Navin Singh, Nawal Minj, Mahima Khandelwal&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Digital: Leepakshi Nagrath&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Planning: Krittika Chakarborty, Saurabh Kamalakaran&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Production House: Shades and Motion Pictures&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93340-WorldToiletDay.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/advertising-news/hersheys-kisses-releases-india-tvc-93334.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>07/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Hershey’s Kisses releases India TVC</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;Hershey India Pvt Ltd, a part of The Hershey Company, the global snacking and chocolates giant has released its first ever India TVC for &lt;i&gt;&amp;lsquo;Hershey&amp;rsquo;s Kisses&amp;rsquo; &lt;/i&gt;chocolate&lt;i&gt;.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;The new TVC, featuring Hershey&amp;rsquo;s India brand ambassador Tara Sharma, primarily focuses on how this delightful chocolate enables endearing everyday moments of bonding and affection with loved ones. It celebrates the unique shape and wrapping of Hershey&amp;rsquo;s Kisses that makes every single one perfect for sharing with dear ones. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/hUslMB9KU-U" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;Speaking about the product launch and the brand&amp;rsquo;s marketing plans, Herjit Bhalla, Managing Director, Hershey India, said, &amp;ldquo;We leveraged The Hershey Company&amp;rsquo;s rich chocolate heritage and expertise of 125 years, with the launch of the iconic Hershey&amp;rsquo;s Kisses chocolates. Hershey&amp;rsquo;s Kisses is a global symbol of affection and we have brought this alive in the new TV campaign.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;Sarosh Shetty, Marketing Director, Hershey India, shared his view on the new TVC saying, &amp;ldquo;In India, we have created a strong and consistent Hershey&amp;rsquo;s brand that is now a leading player in every category that it is present in. The Kisses launch film is an extension of the Hershey&amp;rsquo;s brand promise in India. It celebrates the unique product proposition of Hershey&amp;rsquo;s Kisses. This delightful chocolate enables one to build a special bond with their loved ones. It is often about those simple, everyday ways to show you care &amp;ndash; which often isn&amp;rsquo;t only words&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="line-height:115%"&gt;The TVC will be played on leading southern channels. &lt;/span&gt;This campaign will further be reinforced by an extensive 360-degree campaign across mediums.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93334-hershey.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/advertising-news/how-i-knew-23-years-back-that-piyush-pandey-would-become-global-cco-ajay-gahlaut-93329.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>07/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>How I Knew 23 Years Back That Piyush Pandey Would Become Global CCO: Ajay Gahlaut</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;The world needs heroes. And we all need idols. That&amp;rsquo;s what takes the human race forward. People we can look up to and marvel at. People who blaze a trail we can follow. People whose shoulders we stand upon to see farther than we ever imagined. Larger than life men and women who seem to bend the world to their bidding through sheer force of will. Who we watch open mouthed as they weave their mysterious, powerful magic, and say to ourselves &amp;lsquo;I could never do that.&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;It was 1996 and I was working in Sista Saatchi &amp;amp; Saatchi, Bombay when I first saw Piyush Pandey. It was at a media party thrown by Prime Sports and ESPN to celebrate their merger. The venue was a 5 star hotel in South Bombay and the theme for the party was, you guessed it, sports. They had created little booths with all kinds of games around a large banquet hall. You got three chances to throw a basketball through a hoop, or you could race remote controlled cars around a slalom course. There was a bowling machine you could bat against and several other games scattered around the room. You could enter a tournament where points were tallied across all games and the one who scored the highest won a prize. Piyush and Sonal Dabral were working their way around the room playing game after game. Like a star struck Mary&amp;rsquo;s lamb I followed at a discreet distance. Piyush was, as usual, cracking jokes and exploding into his trademark laughter from time to time. But when it would come to the game he would put his whisky glass away and focus totally on the task at hand. A furrow of concentration would appear on his forehead and he would transform into the elite sportsman he once was. At the slightest sound or disturbance from the band of followers around him he would whip around with a fierce scowl, cowing us into, pin drop silence.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;lsquo;My god,&amp;rsquo; I thought to myself, &amp;lsquo;it&amp;rsquo;s just a party game and he actually wants to win this.&amp;rsquo; And. then it dawned on me that the great become great through a winning mind-set. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s a multi crore pitch or a game of marbles it is the attitude that takes you on to victory.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Half a decade later I had the good fortune to join Ogilvy Delhi. One day Vibha Desai, our head of office, came to me and my partner Sudip and said that Piyush would like to brief us personally on the Pulse Polio campaign. I was only an Associate CD then and usually it was the Creative heads who would interact with Piyush. It turned out that I was the only senior enough chap who could write in Hindi at that time. I thanked God for my Kendriya Vidyalaya education and couldn&amp;rsquo;t wait to get cracking on the brief. We met Piyush at the Bristol Hotel in Gurgaon. It was our first interaction with him on work and we were nervous as hell. He put us at our ease and offered us breakfast. We spoke about everything but the Polio campaign and then, just before leaving he turned to us and said, &amp;lsquo;Ek idea hai. Mr Bachchan ko Phir se angry young man banate hain. Filmein likho jin mein woh un logon se naraaz ho rahe hain jo apne bacchon ko Polio ki drops nahin dete. Dil se likho Aur Kal tak mujhe Mail Karo &amp;lsquo;. Saying which he got up and left for some meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;I reached office at 7.30 am the next morning and started work on the scripts. I wrote them and re wrote them and polished them and pruned them and honed them. Finally they were as good as I could make them and, with a shaking finger, I pressed the &amp;lsquo;send&amp;rsquo; button on mail and sent them off to Piyush. The next couple of hours were the longest of my life. I must have checked the mail 50&amp;ndash;60 times in that duration. Finally a mail from Piyush appeared in my mailbox. Nervously I opened it. There was a three word reply. &amp;lsquo;Very nice scripts.&amp;rsquo; Now I have had the good fortune to win many awards and accolades since that day and even been on stage at Cannes to receive a Gold Lion. But no feeling has come close to the euphoria I felt when I read that three word email from Piyush. I printed it out and kept it in my wallet for years, referring to it whenever I felt a twinge of self doubt, until it became a tattered rag and disintegrated with time.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;I have worked with great bosses earlier as well but Piyush goes beyond that. He is a great leader. The difference is, while you&amp;rsquo;re willing to take on any amount of work for a great boss, for a great leader you&amp;rsquo;re willing to take a bullet.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;I remember 2008 as the worst year in my life. I lost both my parents that year. There was some film shoot I was supposed to go for. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t go because my dad had just passed away and there was the 13th day ceremony to perform. The client, who shall remain nameless of course, was informed. Under pressures of his own I suppose, he was upset when he heard that I wasn&amp;rsquo;t attending the shoot. He found it unprofessional. The fact that I had lost my dad did not seem to be enough of a reason for him.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;When Piyush came to know of this he was livid. He picked up the phone and called his boss. &amp;lsquo;I will fill in for Ajay and come for the shoot&amp;rsquo; he told him. &amp;lsquo;But tell your man not to be in my line of sight. Dikhega toh saale ko maar doonga&amp;rsquo;. Of such impulses and spontaneous gestures are great leaders made. I have no shame in saying that if Piyush asks me to jump the only question I will ask is &amp;lsquo;how high.&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Piyush appears to have a double PhD in People and Common Sense. He can meet a person for 5 minutes, exchange two sentences with him and know what kind of person he is. It&amp;rsquo;s uncanny. I&amp;rsquo;ve never known him to be wrong. I have found it in my interest to blindly follow his advice about people. And even more striking is his ability to find solutions by instantly simplifying a complex situation. Now, modesty apart, I have a healthy respect for my own abilities in this regard, but Piyush leaves me open mouthed time and again. It is more than a talent he has. It is a genius.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Perhaps the two phrases that typify him most are &amp;lsquo;woh mera dost hai&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;baaki main sambhaal loonga&amp;rsquo;. I have been all over the world with him and he has a &amp;lsquo;dost&amp;rsquo; everywhere. From Chairmen of rival agency groups to Vietnamese restaurateurs in Cannes, media group owners in Mumbai to Indian Ambassadors in Tokyo. He knows them all. They beam with genuine pleasure when they see him, hug him and invite him home for meals.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;One cannot even imagine the pressure under which Piyush functions. Every client wants a piece of him. Even the smallest local clients say &amp;lsquo;Hume Piyush Ji se milna hai.&amp;rsquo; He has meetings and seminars and media interviews to attend all the time. And yet he is sensitive to his colleague&amp;rsquo;s work load. If he sees me struggling with multiple mandates he will say &amp;lsquo;toh gaana likh baaki main sambhaal loonga&amp;rsquo;. What wouldn&amp;rsquo;t you do for a leader like that?&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;No discussion about Piyush is complete without an allusion to cricket. In 1998 Mark Taylor, the Australian test captain was playing against Pakistan in Peshawar. He was on 334, equalling the highest individual score by an Australian set by none other than the legendary Don Bradman. Taylor declared his innings closed at 334 saying that now &amp;lsquo;my name will always be connected to the Don&amp;rsquo;s.&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Many didn&amp;rsquo;t get it, but I understand perfectly. Even if I walk away from advertising today I will have no regrets whatsoever. I was part of the Pulse Polio campaign with Piyush Pandey. My name will always be connected to The Don&amp;rsquo;s.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(The author is the Chief Creative Officer, Ogilvy North and Deputy CCO, Ogilvy India)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disclaimer: The views expressed here are solely those of the author and do not in any way represent the views of exchange4media.com&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93329-1.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/advertising-news/facebook-announces-new-ad-transparency-policy-ahead-of-india-general-election-93328.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>07/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Facebook announces new ad transparency policy ahead of India general election</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;With an aim to increase ad transparency ahead of the 2019 India General Election, Facebook has announced changes to the way ads are managed on Facebook and Instagram.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;According to a Facebook Newsroom post by Sarah Clark Schiff, Product Manager at Facebook, &amp;ldquo;Now anyone who wants to run an ad in India related to politics will need to first confirm their identity and location, and give more details about who placed the ad. The identity and location confirmation will take a few weeks so advertisers can start that process today by using their mobile phones or computer to submit proof of identity and location. This will help avoid delays when they run political ads next year&amp;ldquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The post also says that from early next year Facebook will add a disclaimer to all political ads providing&amp;nbsp;information about who is placing the ad, and an online searchable Ad Library, which can be accessed by anyone. It will contain all political ads from a particular advertiser and will provide information such as the budget of individual ads, as well as the demographics of who saw the ad, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Facebook also said that they will be rolling out a new policy that requires all politically related ads to be run by advertisers who have completed the authorisations process and be labeled with the disclaimer.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;However the company will&amp;nbsp;not require eligible news publishers to get authorized, and their ads would not be included in the Ad Library.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Adding that &amp;ldquo;By authorizing advertisers and bringing more transparency to ads, we can better defend against foreign interference in India&amp;rsquo;s elections&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93328-Facebooklogo.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/advertising-news/piyush-pandey-the-universal-creative-director-everyone-wants-to-impress-93321.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>07/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Piyush Pandey: The universal creative director everyone wants to impress</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;The appointment of Piyush Pandey to the role of Global Chief Creative Officer came in as an important milestone not just for Pandey and Ogilvy India but for the entire Indian advertising community. It puts India on the world map like never before.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Pandey&amp;rsquo;s mentees, competitors, those who have only known him through his work and those who have been working hard hoping that someday he will take notice are all overjoyed over his elevation, which makes him the first Indian to hold such a position.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s what some of Piyush Pandey&amp;rsquo;s ardent fans and disciples have to say:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Swati Bhattacharya, Chief Creative Officer, FCB Ulka&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;This a matter of huge pride for all of us. Ogilvy is totally wrong if they think Piyush belongs only to them. He belongs to every agency in India. Whichever agency we have all been in, we have thought of him as the unseen creative director whom you want to impress.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;At Cannes this year, when he was winning the Lion of Saint Mark and I was about to win the Gold Lion in the Glass category, he gave me a kiss on my forehead and said &amp;ldquo;Shabaash.&amp;rdquo; That congratulations he gave me and the way he said &amp;ldquo;shabaash&amp;rdquo; recharged my batteries that evening. Last year, I had done an activation for Horlicks Kota. And I was delighted when Piyush included that work in his year-end address on the top five campaigns of the year. I am still flying high.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;His appointment as the global creative chief of Ogilvy also proves that no work is too Indian to be recognised globally. The point is that when you are true to the work you do and the work is authentic, it really doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter. Today, he can guide every other country under the sun because he was so true to his craft. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Navin Talreja, Co- Founder, The Womb&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Piyush would always say &amp;ldquo;Be so good that people can&amp;rsquo;t ignore you!&amp;rdquo; And I think the network could not ignore this man any longer. It is a moment of great pride for India because he is possibly the first Indian to be the Global CCO of a big network agency. The Lion of India to the Lion of St. Mark to the Lion of Ogilvy is a wonderful journey. And one that gives us all something to aim for.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;I started working with Piyush in 1996 as a Senior AE on Pidilite, and circumstances were such that I worked with him directly. I still remember how I would get a call on Tuesday mornings at 6, asking me to come over to his house because he had an exciting idea on Fevicol or Fevikwik and he could not wait to share it. Why this stands out is that he did the same even when I had become the Head of Mumbai. His consistent energy and excitement around a great idea is still there after everything and that&amp;rsquo;s something that stands out for me.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;The biggest thing one learns from him is his ability to keep it simple and real. With the world going crazy around social media, data etc&amp;hellip; his ability to bring all down to a simple idea that will appeal to hearts and minds is inspirational.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;But there is a lot to learn and be inspired about beyond just the work he creates. The ability to define roles of each member of the team, making each person feel valued, having your back, creating an environment that makes you fearless to express, an environment that fosters creativity, his relationships with everyone, and above all, his ability to stay grounded, rooted and humble even after achieving the biggest accolades is something that all of us should learn and be inspired by.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Anil S Nair, CEO &amp;amp; Managing Partner, L&amp;amp;K Saatchi &amp;amp; Saatchi India&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;This is tremendous recognition for Piyush Pandey and India because he has always put India on the world map with is work. He changed the course of the Indian advertising industry by bringing in non-English and non-Western thoughts and ideas into his work. Since then, even the talent entering the industry has seen a shift away from just the convent-educated lot.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;I have never really worked with him because has been a competitor. But even as a competitor, I have great respect for him. In one of the pitches we did for a client, the client had made a decision to give the job to Ogilvy. When the client told Piyush that the idea from our team looked promising, Piyush requested them to share the idea and upon listening to the idea, he asked them to give the work to us. My respect for him went up 10-fold after this incident. He could have easily dismissed it, but he did not. Eventually Ogilvy and L&amp;amp;K Saatchi and Saatchi shared the client.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nima Namchu, Chief Creative Officer, Havas Worldwide&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Like a lot of kids of my generation, I was humming along to &amp;quot;Mile Sur Mera Tumhara&amp;quot; playing on TV, long before I even knew who Piyush Pandey was. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Years later, while working on competing brands, one burnt the midnight oil to write funnier stories than the ones he wrote for Fevicol or more insightful scripts like &amp;quot;Har ghar kuch kehta hai&amp;quot;, which he wrote for Asian Paints.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;I&amp;#39;m perhaps one of the unfortunate few who never had the opportunity to work with the big man. Having said that, whenever I have been in the vicinity, he has always responded to my shy nod or a hello with a nod, a broad grin, and on a lucky day, a pat on the back accompanied by a &amp;quot;How is it going? Keep at it!&amp;quot;...&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;From a respectful distance, I have admired how, at award shows, he would stand in the aisle and congratulate every winner coming down from the stage, irrespective of which agency the person may be from...&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;And some clients we pitched for have called apologetically to tell us that while they liked our work, they just couldn&amp;#39;t let the opportunity of working with Piyush pass them by...&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Perhaps the true measure of the man is in the stories told by people who have never worked with him.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93321-pandey.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/advertising-news/does-whatsapp-indias-first-tv-campaign-make-the-cut-93297.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>06/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Does WhatsApp India's first TV campaign make the cut?</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;WhatsApp India recently launched its first ever TV campaign called &amp;lsquo;Share Joy, Not Rumours&amp;rsquo; as the latest step in a comprehensive effort to address the challenge of misinformation and pernicious rumours.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;WhatsApp worked closely with the Mumbai agency Taproot Dentsu and the filmmaker Shirsha Guha Thakurta to develop three sixty second films that each convey real scenarios about rumours that have spread on WhatsApp via spam as well as in family and school groups. Each film&amp;#39;s protagonist teaches someone important in their lives to not spread rumours and to use WhatsApp controls such as the ability to block senders and leave groups where rumours are spread. We chatted with Neeraj Kanitkar, Creative Director, Taproot Dentsu to understand what went behind conceptualizing the brand&amp;rsquo;s first-ever TVC.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Kanitkar shared that given that WhatsApp has never done an integrated TVC campaign anywhere in the world, this was a thrilling opportunity. He revealed that while conceptualising the campaign, they took a conscious call to not paint indiscriminate forwarders as offenders. &amp;ldquo;Since often, the vast majority of people who forward such messages do it without intending any malice. If they can be convinced to be skeptical about forwarding messages then our hope was that those with malicious intent would be deprived of the oxygen. &amp;ldquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Kanitkar exclaimed that the process of making the films was a real treat. &amp;ldquo;We shot across Delhi and Mumbai, sometimes with real families with almost no acting experience to play key roles, and they did a great job!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expert eye&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Praveen Nair, Creative Director, Jack in the Box Worldwide opines that while it is a great intent shown by the brand to address a very prevalent problem that plagues the society, the execution leaves a lot to be desired. &amp;ldquo;In masking the communication under the goodness of sharing, the brand has missed an opportunity to drive home an important message. Yes, it does explain how positively this messaging platform can be used, but has it brought to fore the impact of its misuse? The only question to ask is... is this campaign powerful enough to initiate a change in behaviour, in this case, a tendency to share things ignorantly and irresponsibly?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Faisal Haq, VP - Operations (North), WATConsult opines that it finally seems that all roads are leading not just only towards 2019 but 2019 general elections&amp;hellip; &amp;ldquo;Just before Rajasthan and Telangana state elections Facebook-owned company WhatsApp have released three one-minute films in nine different languages and with this it is not just conceding but trying to crackdown spread of fake news and rumours on its platform.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Haq terms it as &amp;ldquo;a well-crafted campaign that not just apogee various scenarios we usually deal on daily basis on different WhatsApp personal and profession groups but how to understand the impact and act wisely with the fake news and rumours by talking to the source sending these messages.&amp;rdquo; He likes that the campaign also highlights the app features like remove the user spreading these fake news or leave/delete the group if need be. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Says Rohan Patil, AVP - Client Servicing, Geometry Encompass, &amp;ldquo;With great art direction, the ad has been produced in a lovely manner putting the message across not only seamlessly, but also with such simplicity. Great work WhatsApp! We needed this link (especially my dad), and has been shared on my Family group.&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Rajeesh Rajagopalan, Mumbai Head, Grapes Digital remarks that the campaign works as it&amp;#39;s straight to the point and does that without being preachy. &amp;ldquo;It communicates the thought beautifully, in a manner that&amp;#39;s easy to understand, considering the audience is across age groups, geographies and social strata. And, at the same time it&amp;#39;s entertaining enough to hold the audience for a minute. Fake messages are a serious issue, and any campaign that addresses social issues usually face the challenge of being boring and dry.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Deepak Singh, CCO, YAAP is of the opinion that being the first-ever ad from Whatsapp, which is a cult brand amongst the youth, he expected more from it in terms of story-telling. &amp;ldquo;It is a little too explanatory right now. The execution per se is fine. The characters chosen, the college setting, everything fits the scenario well. But I feel they could have played around with the story and concept to a slightly larger extent,&amp;rdquo; Singh says. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Tm0k-nvk4l4" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/t_gmgnOpA98" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/8ncCkiX0Euw" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93244-WhatsAppCampaign.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/advertising-news/our-secret-sauce-is-our-ability-to-harness-vernacular-languages-umang-bedi-93298.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>06/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Our secret sauce is our ability to harness vernacular languages: Umang Bedi</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Cambria"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#212529"&gt;Umang Bedi, President, Dailyhunt, was awarded the exchange4media Influencer of the Year&amp;nbsp;in November, 2018, for his pioneering efforts to scale a local language content platform. Even before Google and other digital platforms began focussing on vernacular as the key driver of the Internet in India, Dailyhunt had identified a need-gap and began work to create a robust platform for Bharat and Made in India.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Cambria"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#212529"&gt;In an interview to exchange4media, Bedi spoke about how Dailyhunt as a platform was successful in harnessing vernacular languages and yet build a scalable platform that is supported by all technologies. Speaking about Dailyhunt&amp;rsquo;s vision Umang said, &amp;ldquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-family:Arial"&gt;Our mission is to be the Indic platform empowering a billion Indians to discover, consume and socialize with content that informs, enriches and entertains.&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="text-justify:inter-ideograph"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#212529"&gt;Edited excerpts:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="text-justify:inter-ideograph"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial"&gt;What is your vision for Dailyhunt?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin-left:36.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin-left:36.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="text-justify:inter-ideograph"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial"&gt;Dailyhunt aims to become the largest Indic platform empowering a billion Indians to discover, consume and socialize with content that informs, enriches and entertains&amp;nbsp;in multiple formats. We aim to become the largest Indic platform in India by 2020. Hence, the vision is essentially a roadmap that we want to walk on. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin-left:36.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin-left:36.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="text-justify:inter-ideograph"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial"&gt;Traditional definition of news has evolved, and, along with it, the way in which the news &amp;amp; entertainment content is consumed. Over the last year, we have pivoted strongly from text to video. We are adding various additional signals across discovery and socialize dimensions which help the consumer spend more and more time with us and we become more relevant to large parts of Bharat.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin-left:36.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin-left:36.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="text-justify:inter-ideograph"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Overall, this helps us serve immersive experiences across content genres; new age formats with razor sharp focus on video, wider distribution and deeper personalization for the customer so that we serve a meaningful and intuitive experience. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="text-justify:inter-ideograph"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial"&gt;What role does advertising play for Dailyhunt?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin-left:36.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin-left:36.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="text-justify:inter-ideograph"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial"&gt;Advertising is our only source&amp;nbsp;of revenue. Before rebranding as Dailyhunt in 2015, our revenue came from content sales in the form of e-books and other small content pieces. We have been continuously investing in technology so that we can provide higher CTRs and flow-through&amp;nbsp;rates for advertisers. We recently launched our self-serve advertising platform in Beta, which will help small businesses to grow. In the next 18 months, we plan to triple our user base; double the time spent and release five times more inventory, which we are looking to monetize in a big way through video advertising. At present, Dailyhunt has 157 million MAUs,&amp;nbsp;we are poised to hit the 250 million users mark by June 2019. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="text-justify:inter-ideograph"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial"&gt;With fake news remaining a major challenge, how is Dailyhunt differentiating the real from the fake?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin-left:36.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin-left:36.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="text-justify:inter-ideograph"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial"&gt;At Dailyhunt, we tackle this challenge in multiple ways. We ensure that we only work with high-quality, known, large publishers; we then work around professionally generated&amp;nbsp;content providers and license their content. Additionally, we also follow a publisher rating system, from views and feedback on whether the content is disturbing, or the imagery wasn&amp;rsquo;t accurate. We create a score, which is calibrated in real time for each publisher, and we transparently share that feedback with the publisher to differentiate real news from the fake easily.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="text-justify:inter-ideograph"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial"&gt;What are some of the major challenges for a platform like Dailyhunt?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin-left:36.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin-left:36.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="text-justify:inter-ideograph"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial"&gt;Our challenges are two-fold. The first challenge lies in the number of devices that are present in the Indian market. Today, there are nearly 350-400 million smartphones, growing at the rate of 30 per cent every year. Most Indians access the Internet via their mobile devices. However, in a country of 1.35 billion people, there are only 400 million smartphones. The growth of smartphones must happen much faster. The macro ecosystem challenge of adding more and more smartphones must be dealt with on priority. And, the second challenge is that we must continue to have more locally relevant content, as people are attracted to content in their local languages.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="text-justify:inter-ideograph"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial"&gt;What are your thoughts on the growing Internet user base in India? How can Dailyhunt&amp;nbsp;leverage it?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin-left:36.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin-left:36.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="text-justify:inter-ideograph"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial"&gt;The Indian market has 400 million Internet users, making the country the largest online market today, second only to China. It has led to a sudden upsurge of low-cost smartphones and affordable Internet data. As per a report&amp;nbsp;by Internet and Mobile Association of India (IAMAI), the number of Internet users in India is estimated to increase 1.6 times from 481 million in 2017 to reach 762 million in 2022. Driven by the government&amp;rsquo;s digital initiatives,&amp;nbsp;this Internet growth has also percolated into rural areas, sometimes, even exceeding the content consumption in the metros. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin-left:36.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="text-justify:inter-ideograph"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial"&gt;There has been a massive spike in the number of digital-only consumers of content&amp;ndash;an extremely favorable trend for a platform&amp;nbsp;like ours. We will leverage our advantage of being an early adopter of the vernacular approach and learn from our experiences.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="text-justify:inter-ideograph"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial"&gt;How do you battle the duopoly of Facebook and Google, as it attracts almost 80 per cent of the digital ad spend, leaving very little for other platforms?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin-left:36.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin-left:36.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="text-justify:inter-ideograph"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial"&gt;Global giants such as Facebook and Google have built great technology platform-based businesses employing the latest AI and machine learning technologies. The platform approach of these businesses gives them true scalability. Digital platforms that reached only 250 million&amp;nbsp;people till 2017 were able to target the English language audience alone. As per the latest Google KPMG report, the future lies in the growth of India&amp;rsquo;s Internet, which is poised to reach 800 million people of which 600 million are going to be vernacular.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin-left:36.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="text-justify:inter-ideograph"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial"&gt;80 per cent of monetization across the print media happens for non-English publications. The report also states that 65-70 per cent of all advertising on online media will shift to vernacular, and we would find ourselves as the largest platform in that space. Therefore, we believe that&amp;nbsp;our secret sauce truly lies in our ability to harness vernacular languages and yet build a scalable platform, which is supported by all the latest technologies. We would also focus our energies on adopting block chain technology and drive meaningful, personalized, intuitive experiences for local language audiences.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="text-justify:inter-ideograph"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial"&gt;What key role can Dailyhunt play in the upcoming 2019 general elections?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin-left:36.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin-left:36.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="text-justify:inter-ideograph"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial"&gt;I would like to answer this in two parts. First, it is important to explain the rationale behind associating us with the theme of elections and second, I would like to elucidate the potential&amp;nbsp;role Dailyhunt could play in an election-bound country. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin-left:36.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin-left:36.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="text-justify:inter-ideograph"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial"&gt;It is crucial to note that Dailyhunt is one of India&amp;rsquo;s most prominent news and local language content applications with over 227 Million app installs offering 100,000 new news and content artifacts every-day in 14 languages licensed from over 1000+ publication partners. Over the years, our platform has progressed to become country&amp;rsquo;s fastest&amp;nbsp;growing news app in the world adding over 15 million new MAUs for the last 5 months. With the recent #DailyhuntTrustoftheNation survey,&amp;nbsp;best described as India&amp;rsquo;s largest and most definitive independent political digital survey conducted in the country, we accessed 95%+ of pin-codes of India with over 70% from tier 2, 3 and 4 every day. The resounding success&amp;nbsp;of this survey truly reaffirmed our intention and overall objective of becoming a quintessential platform, a unique facilitator for online segment in a nation where large majority of people not just in urban areas but tier 2 and 3 cities and towns are hungry&amp;nbsp;for more and more information in their own native language.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin-left:36.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="text-justify:inter-ideograph"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial"&gt;As far as upcoming elections are concerned, I would like to reiterate that our focus is to leverage our robust content partnerships and upgraded technological infrastructure and&amp;nbsp;become one-stop destination for consuming news content from varied trusted news sources and help Indians make a choice as per their own understanding and political leanings.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin-left:36.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="text-justify:inter-ideograph"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="text-justify:inter-ideograph"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial"&gt;Do you consider other news apps as strong competitors in the market?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin-left:36.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin-left:36.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="text-justify:inter-ideograph"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial"&gt;All kinds of digital&amp;nbsp;platforms are yet to monetize. We are acquiring more MAUs and DAUs than any such player. We are adding around 10-15 million net MAUs on a month-on-month basis.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin-left:36.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin-left:36.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="text-justify:inter-ideograph"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial"&gt;Only Google and Facebook, who today have a duopoly in the digital ad market,&amp;nbsp;are the companies, which are following a strategy of acquiring and monetizing users. Today, the Internet is pivoting to local languages at a much faster rate than anyone can imagine. It is estimated that there will be 800 million people on the Internet, 600 million people will consume content in local languages while the English base, which is at 180 million&amp;nbsp;will only grow to 200 million by 2022.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin-left:36.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin-left:36.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="text-justify:inter-ideograph"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial"&gt;According to a 2017 report by&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/tech/internet/how-online-vernacular-market-is-becoming-the-big-battle-ground-for-tech-cos/articleshow/63248994.cms" rel="nofollow" style="color:#0563c1; text-decoration:underline"&gt;KPMG and Google, &amp;ldquo;Indian Languages &amp;mdash; Defining India&amp;rsquo;s Internet&amp;rdquo;&lt;/a&gt;, there were 234 million Indian-language Internet users and 175 million English users in 2016. By 2021, the gap between the two groups is expected to widen. Users of Indian languages are expected to more than double to 536 million, while English users will increase to only 199 million.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin-left:36.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin-left:36.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="text-justify:inter-ideograph"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial"&gt;In television, 90 per cent of advertising is vernacular. The Top 10 television channels are vernacular. Therefore, when the Internet hits the 800 million people mark &amp;ndash; like the reach of television today, we expect most of the advertising to move to vernacular. We will keep employing AI, machine learning and deep learning technologies on vernacular users and focus on working on years&amp;nbsp;of historic vernacular data.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="text-justify:inter-ideograph"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial"&gt;What are your leadership tips for young entrepreneurs?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin-left:36.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin-left:36.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="text-justify:inter-ideograph"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial"&gt;Push yourself to&amp;nbsp;empower people&amp;rsquo;s lives and help them grow and achieve success. The idea here is to empower&amp;nbsp;them to galvanize their passions and support them to grow. Identify a mission and be mission-driven, have a defined purpose and be crystal clear about the purpose.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin-left:36.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93298-umangbedie4m.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/advertising-news/the-big-mobile-marketing-trends-of-2019-priyanka-shah-93182.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>06/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>The big mobile marketing trends of 2019: Priyanka Shah</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;The number of mobile internet users in India is estimated to touch 478 million by June 2018, buoyed by cheaper smartphones, faster connectivity and affordable services, according to an IAMAI report. The report forecast that given a 59 per cent penetration, urban India is expected to witness a slowdown, while rural India, with only 18 per cent mobile internet penetration, would emerge as the next area of growth.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;The voice-related mobile spends have been coming down since 2013, and the popularity of Voice over IP (VoIP) and video chatting has further amplified this trend. This, in turn, led to a rise in the proportion of data expenditure in comparison to voice expenditures for most users. Between 2013 and 2017, the ratio of data to voice went up from 45:55 to 84:16, as per the IAMAI report. With Jio disrupting the market and semi-urban and rural India being the clear focus, Voice, Video and Vernacular are the clear three trends that will dominate the near future of mobile marketing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Voice has been emerging as the preferred mode of use for new internet users. We&amp;rsquo;re seeing major growth of voice queries in India. Furthermore, online video now accounts for 75 per cent of all mobile traffic. And as for vernacular, the majority of the internet users today are Indian language users, a number expected to reach 500 million plus in the next two years. Further, 95 per cent of video consumption is in vernacular languages. As per Google, 9 out of 10 internet users in the next five years are likely to be Indian language users. And 88 per cent people are more likely to respond to digital ads in their own language. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Low cost of smartphones and data, the rise of Jio, the government&amp;rsquo;s push for digital adoption as well as other factors have accelerated the transitioning from feature phones to smartphones in India.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Key Trends of 2019&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 8pt;"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Vernacular Conversation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;The attenuating share of English on one hand and increased internet penetration in Hindi speaking markets or regional language markets clearly indicate that regional language internet users are poised to drive the next phase of internet adoption in India. This will be as much as 2.5 times more than that of English internet user base by 2021, as per Deloitte India eighth edition report on technology, media and telecommunications released in January this year.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;In fact, by 2021, over 201 million Hindi users, who form 38 per cent of the Indian internet user base, are expected to be online. Nearly 90 per cent of them are more likely to respond to a digital advertisement in their local language as compared to English ads.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;To put it simply, vernacular conversation is essentially about an overarching trend that implies that a large majority of brands in India are focusing on mobile ads in the local language to communicate with their audience.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Voice &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;By 2020, 50 per cent of the searches would be voice searches with semantic search for better understanding the queries. Smart sSpeakers such as Amazon&amp;rsquo;s Alexa, Google Home and Apple HomePod have become increasingly popular with consumers. In fact, 65 per cent of consumers say they wouldn&amp;rsquo;t go back to life without their voice-controlled assistant.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;We will likely see more online publishers embrace voice and publish audio content to these devices in an effort to land a spot on the listener&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Flash Briefing&amp;rsquo;. Also, we will likely see Amazon, Google and Apple monetize their content by allowing companies to buy and sell ad space. Jio will be a game changer in India with its vernacular voice interpretation capabilities customized to Indian markets.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Video viewership and domination of regional language video user base &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Be it Facebook, Twitter or any other social media channel, you can barely scroll through your feed without viewing at least one video. As per KPMG report, 80 per cent of global Internet consumption will be video content by 2019. More importantly, video viewership in India, dominated by the regional language user base, is expected to catapult even further. Consumers today spend about 50 to 60 per cent of the average time on Hindi videos, followed closely by 35 to 43 per cent on regional content videos and only 5 to 7 per cent on English.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;The format of the video will continue to evolve with mobile as a priority, and brands need to embrace the changing landscape. Better connection speeds allow for more quality content and interactive elements, something that is unique to mobile video. Marketers are now trying newer forms of videos like vertical videos, hotspot videos, videos with shoppable links etc to lure the audience.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Dominancy in AR/VR &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Mobile devices can now be converted to devices which provide virtual and augmented reality experience thus making advertising more immersive. Various retail, travel and automobile brands are experimenting with them to wow their audience.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Live Streaming &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;By 2019, about 78 per cent of world&amp;rsquo;s mobile data traffic will be from this domain. Users spend about 3X more on live video content v/s static content as per Facebook&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Podcasts&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Podcasts are episodic series of digital audio files which a user can subscribe to and deals with topics that range from music and books to health. Touted as the new radio of the millennial era, the last one year has witnessed dozens of podcast shows springing up in different cities with localized content in India.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Podcasting as a platform helps brands to create connect with their audiences and also to build brand stories. Brands engage with their audiences using podcasting by:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;ul&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt 36pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Advertising on a podcast with a brand story&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt 36pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Creating integrated native content in a show&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt 36pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Developing advertiser-funded programming&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;The Indian podcast scene has a handful of notable players &amp;ndash; Audiomatic, India&amp;rsquo;s first podcast network launched in 2015, and Indus Vox Media. Even digital music offerings like Saavn, Gaana and Hungama have joined the bandwagon with their original programming line-ups.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Mobile Gaming &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;As per Kantar IMRB report, 50 per cent of smartphone users play mobile games and average time spent on mobile gaming is more than one hour daily. There are 250Mn+ mobile gamers in India and the number is expected to grow to 368Mn in 2022. A total of 48 per cent of gamers are females and 55 per cent are moms. And 1/3rd of gamers are 35+ in age.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Given the dramatic shift towards the way consumers are engaging in mobile media and gaming, in particular, it is very imperative to leverage the opportunities within gaming for brands. E-commerce, FMCG, automobile, telecom, and banking are the top categories whose ads were recalled by gamers &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Location-based advertising&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;With location-based messaging, brands can reach out to consumers while they&amp;rsquo;re near their products in the shopping aisle. This location-based messaging allows brands to offer deals and events based on the consumer&amp;rsquo;s area, creating a targeted experience.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Prominent AI &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Personalisation of information by helping brands cater to consumers in a much more involved manner will revolutionize marketing by 2020. Tractica Project research predicts a virtual digital assistant will be on 3.3Bn devices by 2020&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;PWA &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Progressive Web Apps (PWA) is an emerging technology which is the next big thing for mobile. By 2020, PWA will have replaced 50 per cent of APPs. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;2018 is coming to end and it is time to shed old techniques of planning and strategy in favour of a multi-screen planning approach that would bring incremental results. Those businesses that will tell unique stories and provide jaw-dropping experiences to the target customers are bound to leap ahead in their game. You have to watch for the latest features of the key digital marketing platforms and create personalised and innovative campaigns for your audience. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;(The author is&amp;nbsp;Senior Director, Mobile Isobar)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Disclaimer: The views expressed here are solely those of the author and do not in any way represent the views of&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://exchange4media.com/" rel="nofollow"&gt;exchange4media.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93182-GuestColumn.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/advertising-news/another-first-for-piyush-pandey-only-indian-to-become-a-global-cco-93302.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>06/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Another first for Piyush Pandey, only Indian to become a Global CCO</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;India&amp;rsquo;s beloved ad-man Piyush Pandey was &lt;a href="https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements-news/ogilvy-appoints-piyush-pandey-as-its-global-cco-93292.html"&gt;named Global CCO of Ogilvy &lt;/a&gt;effective January 1, 2019, on Wednesday. He becomes the first Indian to take up the role of a worldwide chief creative officer.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;On the appointment of Pandey, John Seifert, Chief Executive, Ogilvy Worldwide, said, &amp;ldquo;We could not be more thrilled that Piyush will be serving as our Chief Creative Officer, Worldwide and my creative partner. &amp;nbsp;Piyush is a true industry icon who is uniquely suited to lead our global creative efforts. Creativity has and will always be at the heart of the Ogilvy brand and culture. Piyush is the perfect leader to shepherd that legacy as we continue to focus on making brands matter as the leading creative network in the world.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;Pandey entered the advertising industry in 1982 at a time when television ads were gaining popularity and Hindi was becoming a medium of communication on television. Pandey infused advertising with a unique Indian flavour, picking up on the most delicate behavioural, cultural, and emotional nuances of the Indian consumer. He is credited with revolutionising advertising in India by breaking away from Western and English influences.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;Growing up in a family that exposed him to the beauty of Hindi literature, poetry, and music, shaped Pandey&amp;rsquo;s creative instincts. His father loved Hindi literature and poetry and held poetry recitals at the Pandey household regularly. &amp;ldquo;Just being in the house, around my father, I became a lover of poetry,&amp;rdquo; Pandey writes in his book Pandeymonium. He calls his mother the creative director of the factory he grew up in and credits his mother for the inculcating the love for reading and writing in him. Pandey&amp;rsquo;s love for the Hindi language and music stems from his sisters.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;Over the last 35 years, Pandey has influenced creative minds and shaped the Indian creative advertising industry. He is the most illustrious and globally renowned advertising personality from India. Anyone who has lived through the&amp;nbsp;&amp;#39;90s in India remembers the iconic Fevicol, Cadbury Dairy Milk, Asian Paints, and later, Rajasthan and Madhya Pradesh tourism ads that were crafted by him.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;Pandey has won many international awards over the last 35 years. Earlier this year he along with his brother Prasoon Pandey became the first Indians to receive the &lt;a href="https://www.exchange4media.com/advertising-news/piyush-pandeyprasoon-pandey-to-receive-cannes-lions-lifetime-achievement-award-in-2018-87596.html"&gt;Lion of Saint Mark Award for Lifetime Achievement&lt;/a&gt;. It is Cannes Lions&amp;rsquo; highest honour for legends in the communications industry.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;He won his first two Gold Lions for an anti-smoking ad that featured a Marlboro Man lookalike with a dead horse. Unofficially, he worked with brother Prasoon Pandey on Ericsson Cellphone&amp;rsquo;s One Black Coffee ad which is the first Indian campaign to win at Cannes in 1996.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;Pandey was the first Asian to be a jury president at the Cannes Lions International Festival of Creativity, in 2004. He received the Lifetime Achievement Award from The Advertising Agencies Association of India (AAAI) in 2010. In 2012 he was awarded the CLIO Lifetime Achievement Award. In 2016 he became the first person in advertising to receive the Padma Shri.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;Pandey will take charge of leading the creative team at what is called the oldest advertising agency in the world on January 1, 2019. He will lead Ogilvy&amp;rsquo;s 100 offices based while being based in&amp;nbsp;India - a place he calls a storyteller&amp;rsquo;s factory. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93292-piyush.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/advertising-news/godaddys-latest-ad-has-dhoni-educating-entrepreneurs-on-creating-online-presence-93286.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>05/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>GoDaddy’s latest ad has Dhoni educating entrepreneurs on creating online presence</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;GoDaddy has launched its new integrated marketing campaign focused on educating entrepreneurs in India about the value of creating an online presence for their business.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;For the campaign, GoDaddy has signed MS Dhoni, who is portraying a supreme mentor and guide as the &amp;ldquo;Bijness Bhai&amp;rdquo; (business mentor).&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The company, in a statement, said that together, GoDaddy and Dhoni will work towards encouraging people to turn their ideas into reality online. In line with the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to offer products, services and support in local languages, the marketing campaign will be available in seven Indian languages-- Hindi, Gujarati, Kannada, Malayalam, Marathi, Tamil and Telugu.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The campaign, which has two quirky and humorous television commercials, has been conceptualised and created by Lowe Lintas. &amp;nbsp;Dhoni plays &amp;lsquo;Bijness Bhai&amp;rsquo;, a messiah for entrepreneurs, makers and independent doers who helps them with day-to-day problems and advises them to grow their business by going online, using GoDaddy&amp;rsquo;s differentiated online and productivity tools and solutions. The commercials illustrate how the company is strongly focused on supporting the growth of its partner ecosystem, by empowering them with digital solutions to quickly adapt to the changes in the business environment.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Talking about the ad, Dhoni said, &amp;ldquo;Every successful inning requires a strong and stable mentoring. My association with GoDaddy on the next inning of my life is an assurance that I have a mentor and guide to help me reach my goals and bring my ideas to life.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Like me, for all aspiring entrepreneurs out there, with GoDaddy as your partner, your business can realise its true potential, equipped with the right online tools and solutions required to deliver a match winning performance on the challenging pitch of business that lies ahead,&amp;rdquo; he added.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Arun Pandey, cricketer-turned-entrepreneur, Dhoni&amp;rsquo;s friend, manager and business partner, said, &amp;quot;I understand from personal experience how hard it can be to turn one&amp;rsquo;s passion into a business. The key to achieving it successfully is by staying focused and committed to your vision, while building a close connection with your audience. GoDaddy understands the importance of community by making it easy to get an idea online and discovered. I am super excited about my venture with Dhoni and with GoDaddy, helping us advance our dreams and make them bigger and real.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the campaign and collaboration with Dhoni, Nikhil Arora, Managing Director and Vice President, GoDaddy India, said, &amp;quot;We are thrilled to be working with a global phenomenon like Dhoni and share our combined story. He represents a true voice of India with a successful professional journey as a cricketer and now as an entrepreneur. Coming from a small town in the country, Dhoni has worked hard to gain prominence and achieve success by following his passion and doing what he believes in. We hope that his story can inspire and encourage business owners, especially in Tier 2 and Tier 3 cities across the country, to follow their dream and get their ideas online.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;At GoDaddy, we are focused on supporting small businesses by helping them create an online presence to help their ventures grow and thrive. Through this campaign and our association with Dhoni, we want to create awareness about the benefits of going online, while demonstrating the power of our integrated suite of products and services to help emerging India transform digitally.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Currently releasing the two TVCs on GoDaddy&amp;rsquo;s official online and social channels as well as on TV, the company plans to fully launch the campaign by the end of January 2019, rolling it out across radio, print and outdoor channels.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/FqwRRimX1Ks" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/5c7twb4xo5o" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93286-Dhoni.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/advertising-news/layerr-shots-new-ad-with-varun-dhawan-tells-people-to-stop-being-judgemental-93283.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>05/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>LAYER’R SHOT’s new ad with Varun Dhawan tells people to stop being judgemental</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;LAYER&amp;rsquo;R SHOT&amp;nbsp;has come up with a new campaign featuring actor Varun Dhawan. Ads in the deodorant category often talk about making user sexy and appealing to the opposite gender.&amp;nbsp;LAYER&amp;rsquo;R SHOT&amp;nbsp;takes a leap from the existing&amp;nbsp;category&amp;nbsp;clutter with&amp;nbsp;its new refreshing thought of&amp;nbsp;&amp;lsquo;Soch&amp;nbsp;Ho Khushboodaar&amp;rsquo;. The campaign is conceptualised and executed by Triton Communications.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;This campaign revolves around&amp;nbsp;older&amp;nbsp;adults&amp;nbsp;who&amp;nbsp;are judgmental about today&amp;rsquo;s youth.&amp;nbsp;The brand has used this insight to offer their support to the youth by showing them that the new fragrance just spreads good thoughts and eradicates&amp;nbsp;the negative/judgmental thinking happening around them.&amp;nbsp;The brand launched&amp;nbsp;six new&amp;nbsp;fragrances with this campaign&amp;nbsp;called LAYER&amp;rsquo;R SHOT MAXX.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;LAYER&amp;rsquo;R SHOT&amp;#39;s mother company&amp;nbsp;Adjavis&amp;nbsp;Venture Limited was incorporated in 2013.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Talking about the campaign, Devendra&amp;nbsp;Patel, Managing Director,&amp;nbsp;Adjavis&amp;nbsp;Venture, said,&amp;nbsp;&amp;ldquo;It was very important to catch&amp;nbsp;the pulse of today&amp;rsquo;s target audience&amp;nbsp;&amp;ndash; the youth&amp;nbsp;and the problems that they&amp;nbsp;face on a regular basis. Triton understood this and&amp;nbsp;captured the solution to this problem in a very humorous and beautiful way.&amp;nbsp;The agency crafted a&amp;nbsp;nice&amp;nbsp;ending&amp;nbsp;thought to the film -&amp;nbsp;LAYER&amp;rsquo;R SHOT -&amp;nbsp;Soch Ho Khushboodaar&amp;nbsp;and the same was weaved in quite well in the storyline.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Virendra Saini, Executive Director, Triton Communications, said&amp;nbsp;&amp;ndash;&amp;nbsp;LAYER&amp;rsquo;R SHOT&amp;nbsp;has always been a product for the youth. The product has some amazing fragrances and at a very competitive cost. I feel that this campaign will give the product and the brand, the right push and will create a positive stir in the market where competition is really fierce.&amp;nbsp;Also,&amp;nbsp;Varun&amp;nbsp;Dhawan is&amp;nbsp;a perfect fit for this campaign as this product appeals to the youth and who better than&amp;nbsp;Varun&amp;nbsp;to represent today&amp;rsquo;s youth and their thinking. The script demanded someone who has humour and also, someone who can bring freshness and liveliness to the brand.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Jyotsna&amp;nbsp;Parikh, Creative Head, Triton Communications, added, &amp;ldquo;In the perfume category, it&amp;rsquo;s all about &amp;lsquo;boy meets girl&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;boy gets girl&amp;rsquo;. We wanted to break away from this&amp;nbsp;mould&amp;nbsp;and still be relevant to the youth. We&amp;nbsp;realised that today&amp;rsquo;s generation just wants to live and let live but they are constantly judged by society. That&amp;rsquo;s where &amp;lsquo;gandi&amp;nbsp;soch&amp;nbsp;ki badboo&amp;rsquo; originated. By the time we finished the film, it had become a part of everybody&amp;rsquo;s lingo right from the director to the sound engineer to the editor to the VO artist. We&amp;rsquo;re sure it&amp;rsquo;ll pick on with the youth as well.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/k6mrA49tIDk" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93283-varun_dhawan.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/advertising-news/toshiba-unveils-worldwide-corporate-ad-campaign-93281.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>05/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Toshiba unveils worldwide corporate ad campaign</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10.5pt"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:11.0pt"&gt;Toshiba Corporation (TOKYO: 6502) is launching a worldwide corporate advertising campaign to promote its rebranding under a new global identity. Inspired by the &amp;quot;Essence of Toshiba&amp;quot;, the July 2018 restatement of its purpose and values, and driven by the slogan &amp;ldquo;For a new day&amp;rdquo;, the video-based campaign will be rolled out in TV commercials, internet media and Toshiba&amp;rsquo;s own websites. The ads will be released mainly in Japan and Asia, including India, China and the ASEAN countries, and will spotlight how the revitalized Toshiba turns on the promise of a new day. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; text-align:justify"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10.5pt"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:11.0pt"&gt;The &amp;ldquo;Essence of Toshiba&amp;rdquo; harmonizes and integrates Toshiba Group&amp;rsquo;s diverse businesses and operations around the world. It comprises three parts, &amp;ldquo;Basic Commitment of The Toshiba Group&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Our Purpose&amp;rdquo;, and &amp;ldquo;Our Values&amp;rdquo;. &amp;ldquo;Our Purpose&amp;rdquo; expresses Toshiba&amp;rsquo;s unwavering drive to make and do things that lead to a better world&amp;mdash;to combine the power of invention with time-tested expertise, and thereby turn on the promise of a brilliant new day.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; text-align:justify"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10.5pt"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:11.0pt"&gt;&amp;ldquo;For a new day&amp;rdquo;, the advertising campaign slogan, is aligned with &amp;ldquo;Our Purpose&amp;rdquo;. It encapsulates Toshiba&amp;rsquo;s commitment to building a sustainable future by focusing on business domains that support modern life and society, and creating value with reliable technologies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; text-align:justify"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10.5pt"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:11.0pt"&gt;Toshiba has positioned this fiscal year, to March 31, 2019, as the first year of its transformation into an excellent company able to secure profitability comparable to that of the best global companies. The new advertising campaign expresses the &amp;ldquo;Essence of Toshiba&amp;rdquo; that is guiding the transformation and rebuilding the global Toshiba brand, and delivers the message to a global audience on a range of media.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; text-align:justify"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10.5pt"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:11.0pt"&gt;In India, the 360-degree integrated advertising campaign that encompasses digital, television, and print was rolled out from December 3. The first phase of the campaign that will run up till the end of the current financial year, would cover both infotainment and news genres in English and Hindi languages. Digital medium will also be a major component of Toshiba&amp;rsquo;s new advertising campaign in India.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93281-Toshiba.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/advertising-news/mitsubishi-electrics-brand-campaign-salutes-new-india-93280.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>05/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Mitsubishi Electric's brand campaign salutes New India</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p class="gmail-" style="text-align:justify; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:150%"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Mitsubishi Electric&amp;nbsp;brand has created its new campaign &amp;ldquo;PARTNERING INDIA&amp;rsquo;S DREAM TO BE NO.1&amp;rdquo; to clarify the contributions, products and offerings of Mitsubishi Electric in India. The creative thought takes audience through the ambitions of&amp;nbsp;new India. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;The business films are aimed at engaging the viewer with stories representing the new India&amp;rsquo;s vision and how Mitsubishi Electric&amp;rsquo;s businesses are contributing to this vision.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="gmail-" style="text-align:justify; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:150%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Shot in more than 50 Locations across the country with a crew of over 140 staff in 28 days, this integrated brand campaign which has 6 Films telling stories of the aspirations of common Indian and how Mitsubishi Electric is helping to achieve them. The brand film is a summary of all the 6 Films which has been released today. The 6 films will be released phase wise in December and January. The campaign song has been sung by Mohan Kannan and it has an essence of India classical instruments including the Sarangi which is played by Ustad Sabir Khan, son of Legendary Sarangi player and vocalist Padma Bhushan Late Ustad Sultan Khan.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="gmail-" style="text-align:justify; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:150%"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Talking about the new Brand Campaign,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Katsunori Ushiku, Managing Director, Mitsubishi Electric India Pvt. Ltd., said,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&amp;ldquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;The campaign resonates the brand&amp;rsquo;s strength as a premium quality electric &amp;amp; electronic equipment company and explains how as a brand we are ready to support India to grow further. As an integrated brand campaign our purpose is to clarify our brand image and offerings. We will make extensive use of available digital technology to reach out to existing and new customers through this campaign and will support them in the best possible way.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="gmail-" style="text-align:justify; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:150%"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;By this campaign, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;the brand reiterates its commitments and tries to convey the message that how it is supporting the country in meeting its ambitions and fulfilling promises through disruptive technologies, solutions, and infrastructural support.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93280-mitsu.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/advertising-news/bahar-to-jaana-padega-says-goodknight-fabric-roll-on-tvc-93279.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>05/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>"Bahar to Jaana Padega," says Goodknight Fabric Roll-On TVC</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;Having revolutionized the category of mosquito repellents by launching the innovative format of Fabric Roll-On, brand Goodknight has now launched a new TVC. The creative highlights the concern of family members while the children go out to play in the evening and become vulnerable to mosquito-borne diseases like Dengue, Malaria etc.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/oGyJ27wIVgk" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;Sharing his thoughts on the video, &lt;b&gt;Sunil Katatria, CEO &amp;ndash; India &amp;amp; SAARC, Godrej Consumer Products Limited&lt;/b&gt;, said, &amp;ldquo;While there is an alarming rise of vector-borne diseases like Malaria and Dengue in the country, there is also a lack of awareness that the mosquitoes that spread these diseases usually bite during the daytime when children are usually out of the protected zones of their homes. Our core focus is to let children have a happy childhood outdoors which makes them &amp;ldquo;champions&amp;rdquo; in their lives by protecting them from mosquitoes while they play.&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoPlainText" style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoPlainText" style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;Commenting on this new TVC campaign, &lt;b&gt;Priya Pardiwalla and Steve Mathias, Vice-Presidents and Executive Creative Directors, JWT Mumbai&lt;/b&gt;, said, &amp;quot;Every mom knows the importance of playing outside every evening. Of rather not being trapped by the videogame or television. However sometimes she has to say NO and stop her kids from stepping out especially during times of high mosquito infestation such as a dengue epidemic. But now Goodknight Fabric Roll-On, a truly non-intrusive innovation empowers moms to do one of the most difficult things ever - saying YES and allowing their kids to play outside, to learn and explore without worrying about mosquitoes. The commercial is centred around a mother who encourages her kid to go out and knock it out of the park, while the rest of the family is concerned, stressed and worried about mosquitoes outside.&amp;quot; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93279-SC2.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
</urlset>
