<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9" xmlns:image="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-image/1.1" xmlns:news="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-news/0.9">
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements-news/wpp-takes-on-new-identity-to-push-its-radical-evolution-plan-93412.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>12/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>WPP takes on new identity to push its ‘radical evolution’ plan</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;WPP CEO Mark Read on Tuesday announced a three-year plan for &amp;ldquo;radical evolution&amp;rdquo; of the company to deliver improved performance. To reflect the new strategic direction of the company, WPP has launched an evolution of its brand identity.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;Superunion and Landor have collaborated to create the new identity which represents WPP as a creative transformation company that is dynamic, connected and organised around the needs of its clients, according to information available on the agency&amp;rsquo;s site.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;The logo is made up of many parts that combine to form the whole &amp;ndash; a representation of WPP&amp;rsquo;s people, agencies, capabilities and markets that work together as one for clients. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;On-screen, the logo is designed to have a continuously changing form and colour, symbolising creative transformation in itself. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;Talking about the idea behind the new logo, Jim Prior, Global CEO, Superunion, said, &amp;ldquo;Our ambition was to present WPP with the same energy and creativity that we offer to our clients right across the company. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of pride and ambition in WPP that is now united under a strong and dynamic brand identity.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;Jane Geraghty, Global CEO of Landor, said, &amp;ldquo;WPP has always been transformative &amp;ndash; bringing together the best people and ideas to meet the needs of our clients. We now have an evolved brand and expression of purpose that better reflects who we are as a company, our collective capabilities, and what we offer.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;According to WPP, the Superunion/Landor team worked alongside WPP&amp;rsquo;s central team on the new positioning as a dynamic, forward-thinking company with creativity and technology at its heart, and the core purpose of creating better futures for its clients and people.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93412-WPP.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements-news/madisons-hiveminds-wins-google-premier-partner-awards-2018-for-search-innovation-93404.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>11/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Madison’s HiveMinds wins Google Premier Partner Awards 2018 for Search Innovation</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Hiveminds, the newly acquired Search specialist digital agency of Madison World, has won the Search Innovation Award for their work on Curefit, at the 2nd edition of the Google Premier Partner Awards 2018, India.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The Google Premier Partner Awards honours innovation in digital marketing across Search, Mobile, Video, Display, Shopping and Growing Businesses Online. Google Premier Partner Award in search innovation is given for expertise and innovation with Google search ads. Examples include creative uses of auto-bidding or optimizing beyond the last click to help clients achieve their goals online. Out of 300+ Google Premier Partners in India, only six agencies were shortlisted for the award.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Curefit is an FMCG-health &amp;amp; fitness solutions provider, founded by former Flipkart executives Mukesh Bansal and Ankit Nagori. For Curefit, HiveMinds through its continuous effort and stacked approach, has been able to deliver 6X improvement in conversions and helped acquire new users consistently, the company said in a statement.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Hiveminds also used:&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;ul&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li&gt;Hyper localized ads to personalize messaging based on user data signals using Google&amp;rsquo;s smart business feed platform&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li&gt;Compelling ad formats like countdown feature, pin-code based bid adjustments&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li&gt;Smart remarketing strategies&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;All this helped the brand deliver 6X increase in conversions, as well as a 30 per cent drop in overall customer acquisition costs.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Talking about the award, Jyothirmayee JT, Founder &amp;amp; CEO, Hiveminds, said, &amp;ldquo;HiveMinds is arguably one of the strongest performance marketing agencies out of India. Winning this award from Google in the core category of search innovation is very encouraging for us. What&amp;#39;s more special, is the award was for our work with another ambitious startup, growing multifold every month and are destined to be an industry leader like many of our clients whom we have engaged at an early stage&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;HiveMinds specialises in providing end-to-end digital marketing solutions like SEO, Performance &amp;amp; Paid Campaigns, Analytics, Social Media, Digital Branding and Creative &amp;amp; Content services, for leading brands and startups in India, US and the Middle East. HiveMinds handles key clients such as bigbasket, Teabox, Sonata Watches, Portea, Zoomcar and Cloudnine Hospitals.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93404-awardfinal.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements-news/ajay-gahlaut-to-join-publicis-93372.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>11/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Ajay Gahlaut to join Publicis</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Ajay Gahlaut, who recently quit as Chief Creative Officer of Ogilvy North and Deputy Chief Creative Officer of Ogilvy India, is believed to be joining Publicis.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Galaut is expected to succeed Bobby Pawar, who quit Publicis to join Havas Media. Pawar was the Managing Director and Chief Creative Officer, Publicis Worldwide South Asia.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The development has been confirmed to exchange4media by highly-placed sources. We reached out to Gahlaut for a confirmation, but are yet to get a response.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;At Ogilvy, Gahlaut&amp;nbsp;worked on brands such as Pernod Ricard, BMW, KFC, Taco Bell, Dabur, Perfetti Van Melle, Mother Dairy, Pizza Hut, Sprite, Best Foods, HT Mint and Philips.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Gahlaut worked with Ogilvy as a creative consultant between 2001 and 2005, after which he left. He re-joined the agency in 2007 and had been with it ever since. He has previously worked with agencies such as McCann, Saatchi &amp;amp; Saatchi (then Sista Saatchi &amp;amp; Saatchi), among others.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/92572-Ajay-Gahlaut-pic.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements-news/himanshu-shekhar-promoted-to-ceo-groupm-indonesia-93401.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>11/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Himanshu Shekhar promoted to CEO, GroupM Indonesia</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;GroupM has announced that Himanshu Shekhar will be taking over from Ed Thesiger as the CEO of GroupM Indonesia, effective January 1, 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Shekhar has been based in Indonesia since March 2010 when he joined as the Managing Director for Mindshare&amp;rsquo;s business with Unilever. He was later promoted to CEO of Mindshare Indonesia in December 2011.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;While at the helm of Mindshare Indonesia, he consistently delivered strong growth for the agency and positioned Mindshare as the market leader in digital transformation. In January 2015, Shekhar was promoted to his current position, CEO of Mindshare South East Asia, the company said in a statement.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Thesiger, CEO GroupM Indonesia and Vietnam, will be relocating to the UK at the end of March 2019 to set up his own consulting business.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the appointment, Mark Patterson, CEO GroupM APAC, said, &amp;ldquo;Indonesia continues to be a key growth market for us, and I am delighted that we have been able to promote from within for this important leadership position. Himanshu has a proven track record with a depth of experience and industry relationships that is second to none in that market.&amp;nbsp;I would also like to thank Ed for his energy, passion and outstanding leadership over the past seven years.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;We are sorry to see him leave the region and wish him every success on his new venture back in the UK.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Amrita Randhawa, CEO Mindshare APAC, added, &amp;ldquo;Himanshu has built Mindshare into a titan of an organisation in Indonesia and driven its strength, reputation and leadership stature across South East Asia. His knowledge of Indonesia and our clients&amp;rsquo; core needs in the market is unparalleled and therefore there is no one better suited to step into the GroupM leadership position. We are rooting for Himanshu&amp;rsquo;s success in this next chapter of his career and are confident that he will continue to be an incredible partner for Mindshare and our client&amp;rsquo;s growth story in Indonesia.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking of his promotion Shekhar noted, &amp;ldquo;Leading GroupM Indonesia is a massive responsibility. Across our agencies, Mediacom, Mindshare, Wavemaker and Essence, we have some of the brightest minds working with super successful brands on creating media for business growth. I am thankful to our leadership and teams for building trusted partnerships with clients, media and tech ecosystems over the years.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Today, Indonesia&amp;rsquo;s media is among the most vibrant globally. We have global innovation originating here and best practices taking shape in some areas. Our global networks have been deeply committed to this already, and I am excited to add my efforts to this journey. I am thankful for the trust, and look forward to working together with our wonderful teams and partners.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Thesiger added, &amp;ldquo;It has been an absolute privilege leading such a talented group over the past 7 years. Himanshu has been a cornerstone of the team for the duration of my tenure and I look forward to seeing him drive the business on to the next level in the coming years.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Ed will work closely with Himanshu to ensure a smooth transition over the coming weeks.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Details of Ed&amp;rsquo;s successor in Vietnam and Himanshu&amp;rsquo;s successor will be the subject of separate communications in due course, the company said.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Shekhar will continue to be based in Jakarta with his family and will report directly to Mark Patterson.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93401-himanshu.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements-news/the-thick-shake-factory-announces-its-new-board-of-advisors-93399.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>11/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>The Thick Shake Factory announces its new Board of Advisors</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;India&amp;rsquo;s first premium thick shake brand and one of the fastest growing QSR chains in the country &amp;ndash; The Thick Shake Factory - is proud to announce a stellar panel of industry stalwarts joining its board of advisors headed by serial entrepreneur Dr. Anurag Batra, chairman of BW Business World and founder of media group exchange4media. The advisory board consists of mavericks like Dr. Velumani Arokiaswamy, the founder of the Rs 3000 crore valued healthcare Thyrocare, Jayant Kocchar the ex MD, Founder of Lacoste India, Barista, India&amp;rsquo;s 1st Coffee Caf&amp;eacute; chain, Sagar Daryani of Wow! Momo, Srinath Sridharan, the head of Group Chairman&amp;rsquo;s office of Wadhawan Global Capital, which manages $22 billion in assets, Rohit Bayana Co-founder of Lumis Partners, a Private equity fund and Preeti Vyas Chairwoman &amp;amp; founder of VGC - one of India&amp;rsquo;s top design agencies.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking on the announcement, M. Yeshwanth Nag Mocherla, Co-Founder of The ThickShake Factory, said, &amp;quot;All of the newest Board members embody the spirit of entrepreneurship and bring immense experience, expertise and energy to the table. We are very fortunate to have them by our side as we continue on our journey and aim to become a large international consumer brand. With such eminent personalities to guide us, we are confident of executing our vision.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the occasion, Ashwin Mocherla, Co-Founder, The ThickShake Factory said, &amp;ldquo;We currently are operational across 20 cities and two countries with more than 50 outlets in the pipeline to be opened in the coming months. Our vision is to have over 500 outlets in the next three years. We are a profitable bootstrapped company and have continued to grow via internal accruals since our inception five years ago&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking on his inclusion into the Board of Advisors, Jayant Kochar said, &amp;ldquo;With our hectic, stressful, abstemious lifestyles, I think we all deserve a bit of indulgence and joy from time to time. There are very few things that match the sheer bliss of a delicious Thick Shake, and I am pleased to help Yeshwanth and Ashwin spread their flavours of happiness across the country&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Velumani added, &amp;ldquo;As long as the product is really good, packaged well, priced honest &amp;amp; promoted aggressively, there are enough customers to consume in an emerging market like India&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The Thick Shake Factory was founded by Yeshwanth Nag Mocherla and his brother Ashwin Mocherla.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/YeshwantandAshwinMocherla.png" style="width: 300px; height: 300px;" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Yeshwanth Nag Mocherla and his brother Ashwin Mocherla, Founders of The Thick Shake Factory&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Yeshwanth is an engineer from JNTU and completed his Post Graduate Diploma in Management from Xavier Institute of Management, Bhubaneswar &amp;amp; IESEG School of management, France, post which he worked with Tata Consultancy Services for one year before plunging into entrepreneurship. The driving force for him is to create more jobs &amp;amp; add value to the economy.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Ashwin is an engineer from JNTU and had studied his Post Graduate Diploma in Management from Goa Institute of management &amp;amp; Antwerp management school, Belgium, prior to which he had worked with United Health Group for one year &amp;amp; plunged into entrepreneurship right after his post-graduation. The driving force for him is his passion towards the Food &amp;amp; beverages sector.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Yeshwanth and Ashwin are seen as industry leaders in the F&amp;amp;B sector &amp;amp; have been speakers at multiple forums including but not limited to: Women Economic Forum 2018, Food &amp;amp; Beverages Conclave &amp;amp; Expo, 2017, SME Growth Leadership Conclave, 2017, India Food Forum, 2018, T Hub, Hyderabad (India&amp;#39;s biggest Start-up Business Incubator), Jagriti Yatra (World&amp;rsquo;s longest train journey for entrepreneurship), Utkarsh Yatra (Entrepreneurship journey) etc. to name a few.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The New Board Members:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/AnuragBatra.jpg" style="width: 300px; height: 300px;" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Anurag Batra&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Anurag Batra is a serial entrepreneur, media mogul, a journalist and an eternal optimist rolled into one. He is a first generation entrepreneur having acquired the iconic business media &amp;amp; magazine brand BW Business World, and also serves as the Chairman and Editor-In-Chief of exchange4media group. He mentors many budding entrepreneurs and enjoys the process of reverse mentoring of learning from the entrepreneurs.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/DrAVelumani.jpg" style="width: 300px; height: 300px;" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Dr. A. Velumani&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. A. Velumani is maverick entrepreneur. He is the founder, chairman and managing director of Thyrocare Technologies Ltd., an industry leader and a brand worth over Rs. 3000 Crore. A visionary &amp;amp; an able business administrator, Dr. Velumani proves amply clearly to the industry that, &amp;ldquo;Focus gives success&amp;rdquo;. A first generation entrepreneur, he is an infectious motivator &amp;amp; by his unique way, transformed intimidating problems to opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/JayantKochar.jpg" style="width: 300px; height: 300px;" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Jayant Kochar&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Jayant Kochar is one of the pioneers of organized retail in India; an authentic &amp;ldquo;start-up&amp;rdquo; specialist. After a long stint with automobile major Mahindra&amp;rsquo;s, he pioneered the entry of organized retail by launching the French apparel brand LACOSTE in India. He created not just a great brand, but an entirely new category when he conceptualized and built the pioneering chain of espresso bars in India &amp;ndash; Barista. Having also led the Images Group, he now heads India&amp;rsquo;s leading retail consulting practice &amp;ndash; GO FISH. He recently conceptualized &amp;amp; curated an innovative retail strategy conference &amp;ndash; unBox Retail.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/SrinathSridharan.jpg" style="width: 300px; height: 300px;" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Srinath Sridharan&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Srinath Sridharan is the head of the Group Chairman&amp;#39;s Office and convenor of the Group Management Council at the Wadhawan Global Capital which manages $22 Billion in assets. An expert in strategy and a business visionary, he anchors the growth of Wadhawan Global Capital&amp;rsquo;s businesses with one key focus &amp;ndash; robust value creation. Srinath is known to provide unique perspectives that blend consumer-driven strategy, financial acumen &amp;amp; risk management in a seamless manner.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/PreetiVyas.jpg" style="width: 300px; height: 300px;" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Preeti Vyas&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Preeti Vyas, an independent entrepreneur with humble beginnings, has created some of India&amp;rsquo;s most iconic brand stories and redefined the design landscape. She is counted among the 50 most influential women in India according to Business Today, Impact and Verve magazines, and ranked as one of the top creative minds by The Economic Times.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/SagarDaryani.jpg" style="width: 300px; height: 300px;" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sagar Daryani&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Sagar Daryani is the founder of one of the fastest growing QSR chains; the 300 Crore valued brand - Wow! Momo. A graduate of St. Xavier&amp;rsquo;s Kolkata, he along with his partner started Wow! Momo immediately after graduation at the age of 21. A passionate speaker with active Oratory skills, Sagar has given business &amp;amp; motivational talks at various Business Schools &amp;amp; Entrepreneurship Cells across the country.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/RohitBayana.jpg" style="width: 300px; height: 300px;" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Rohit Bayana&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Rohit Bayana is the Managing Partner and coFounder of Lumis Partners, a Private equity Fund. Rohit brings to bear strong experience in building, leading &amp;amp; scaling asset-light businesses while balancing Demand-Supply, working on both strong organic growth as well as acquisition led growth. Before Lumis Partners, Rohit was at GE, and in his last position, he was CEO of GE Software Solutions (later merged with Genpact). Rohit is a postgraduate from the London School of Economics and an Engineer in Computer Science from Delhi University.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93399-TheThickShakeFactory.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements-news/wpp-outlines-strategy-for-growth-93398.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>11/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>WPP to spend £300m over three years for restructuring</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;WPP has announced the results of its strategic review, setting out a new plan to return the business to grow. The strategy reflects a new vision for WPP as a leader in creativity and technology. It incorporates a simpler, improved offer designed to capture the opportunities of a changing marketplace, and a streamlined structure built around the needs of clients. It also includes additional investments in creativity, technology and talent to enhance WPP&amp;rsquo;s proposition to clients and drive top-line growth.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;WPP expects to deliver organic growth (defined as like-for-like revenue less pass-through costs growth) in line with its peers at a headline operating profit margin (excluding associates) of at least 15% by the end of 2021 as a result of the strategy. The company will incur cash costs for restructuring of &amp;pound;300m over the next three years to deliver estimated annual savings of &amp;pound;275m by the end of 2021, approximately half of which will be reinvested in the business.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking about the announcement, Mark Read, Chief Executive Officer of WPP, said&amp;nbsp;&amp;ldquo;What we hear from clients is very consistent: they want our creativity, and they want us to help them transform their business in a world reshaped by technology. This is at the heart of what we do. &amp;ldquo;We are fundamentally repositioning WPP as a creative transformation company with a simpler offer that allows us to meet the present and future needs of clients. This more contemporary proposition has already helped us to win new business, including Volkswagen&amp;rsquo;s creative account in North America.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;He continued, &amp;ldquo;The restructuring of our business will enable increased investment in creativity, technology and talent, enhancing our capabilities in the categories with the greatest potential for future growth. As well as improving our offer and creating opportunities for clients, this investment will drive sustainable, profitable growth for our shareholders.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;We describe our approach as &amp;lsquo;radical evolution&amp;rsquo;: radical because we are taking decisive action and implementing major change; evolution because we will achieve this while respecting the things that make WPP the great company it is today&amp;quot; he added.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;WPP is hosting a presentation for investors and analysts&amp;nbsp;at its new headquarters in London.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Key points of the presentation, which will also be webcast, include:&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Opportunities in a Changing Industry&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Technology is rapidly reshaping our sector, presenting challenges but also opportunities. We believe the industry is facing structural change not structural decline. WPP is adapting at speed to capture these opportunities and to become even more client-centric than it is today.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Vision, Purpose and Identity&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;WPP&amp;rsquo;s vision is to be a creative transformation company, bringing together creativity and expertise in technology and data &amp;ndash; with the purpose of building better futures for its people and clients. This competitive positioning was developed in consultation with our people and clients, and is supported by a refreshed brand identity created by WPP agencies Superunion and Landor.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Simpler, Improved Offer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;WPP&amp;rsquo;s future offer will cover four areas: communications, experience, commerce and technology. Each of these areas is critical to success for modern clients, and by bringing them together the company will better serve clients&amp;rsquo; needs as they react to the changing marketplace, and expand WPP&amp;rsquo;s own business in high-growth sectors.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Communications focuses on advertising, content, media, public relations and public affairs, and healthcare.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Experience reflects the growing need of clients to create a new brand, product and service experiences.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Commerce allows WPP to expand its growing omnichannel commerce business and its work with brands to help them succeed in marketplaces such as Alibaba and Amazon.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Technology underpins WPP&amp;rsquo;s work with both CMOs and CIOs to build and operate marketing technology that supports their consumer- and customer-facing activities.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The areas of experience, commerce and technology already represent approximately one-quarter of WPP&amp;rsquo;s revenue.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Renewed Commitment to Creativity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;WPP&amp;rsquo;s most important competitive advantage is its creativity. It is what makes WPP special and what differentiates it from other professional services firms. WPP has significant creative strengths, having won the &amp;ldquo;Holding Company of the Year&amp;rdquo; award at the Cannes Lions International Festival of Creativity for seven consecutive years between 2011 and 2017 &amp;ndash; but the business must invest more in this area. As part of this strategic review, WPP is making a renewed commitment to creativity, investing an incremental &amp;pound;15m a year for the next three years in creative leadership, with a particular focus on the United States.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technology, Data, Partners &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;and&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt; Platforms&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Alongside creativity, the company will accelerate and promote its technology and data capabilities as clear sources of competitive advantage to WPP. They will follow a consistent approach across WPP by adopting a common technology strategy, leveraging the strengths of our unique technology partnerships, and making our significant existing capabilities in marketing and advertising technology available to all WPP companies for the benefit of our clients.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Simpler Structure&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;WPP has become too unwieldy, with too much duplication. As a result, it is not always as focused or as a fleet of foot as it needs to be to satisfy the needs of clients around the globe. Therefore, central to the new strategy is a simpler structure, built around the needs of clients, to allow easier access to WPP&amp;rsquo;s many resources. The structure is based on three principles:&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Clients: we will become a more client-centric organisation in order to deliver the best of WPP.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Companies: we will have fewer, more integrated companies equipped to adapt to a changing market.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Countries: we will integrate further at a country level to leverage our strengths in individual markets.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kantar&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;As previously announced, the Board of WPP has decided to develop Kantar with a potential strategic or financial partner, with WPP retaining a significant minority interest and strategic links with Kantar. Proposals will be evaluated on their financial and strategic benefits and if a transaction is agreed it is likely to be announced in the second quarter of 2019. Preparations are well underway and we have received numerous unsolicited expressions of interest.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Leadership, Talent and Culture&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;For the first time, WPP has established an Executive Committee drawn from both corporate and company leadership. This Executive Committee will work together to implement the new plan, and we will review the company&amp;rsquo;s incentive arrangements to align with the strategy. To make WPP the natural home for the best and brightest, and to attract the next generation of talent, we will champion a culture across WPP characterized by the values of openness, optimism and a commitment to extraordinary work.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Progress to Date:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Since April this year, the company has made consistent progress towards our goals. This includes the creation of the integrated networks VMLY&amp;amp;R and Wunderman Thompson; the alignment of our US healthcare agencies with integrated agency partners; and the elimination of the sub-holding company WPP Health &amp;amp; Wellness. VML, Y&amp;amp;R, Wunderman, J. Walter Thompson and WPP Health &amp;amp; Wellness collectively account for 23% of WPP revenue. WPP has also disposed of 16 non-core investments and associates, raising &amp;pound;704m to reduce our debt.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2018 and 2019 Outlook:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;WPP anticipates reporting full-year results in line with consensus expectations, with full-year like-for-like revenue less pass-through costs growth now expected to be closer to -0.5%. The company is beginning a multi-year improvement programme and 2019 will be a year of investment in the business with the execution of our cost-savings programme and further actions taken to return the company to long-term sustainable growth.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Previously announced account losses will create the anticipated headwind, particularly in the first half of the year.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Restructuring and Investment:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The company will incur cash costs for&amp;nbsp;of &amp;pound;300m restructuring over the next three years, reflecting actions to position the company for growth, address under-performing units and streamline our operations. The actions include:&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; The integration of VML and Y&amp;amp;R, and Wunderman and J. Walter Thompson.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Right-sizing and disposal of under-performing businesses.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Closure of unsustainable operations.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Further development of Campus co-locations.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Establishing a consistent, shared service infrastructure to support 30 countries over the next five years.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The annual savings from the actions are anticipated to be &amp;pound;275m by the end of 2021. WPP will reinvest approximately half of these savings into 2019 to 2021.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Future Capital Allocation Policy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The company has made good progress on its divestment of non-core assets, raising &amp;pound;704m from 16 disposals to date. We continue to target a reduction in average net debt to EBITDA ratio to within our revised target range of 1.50-1.75x by 2021. Over the next three years, WPP will prioritise the dividend over share buy-backs and will balance targeted M&amp;amp;A with divestments. The Board anticipates declaring a final dividend of 37.3p at the Preliminary Results to deliver a full-year dividend for the current financial year of 60p which it intends to maintain.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Medium-Term Financial Targets&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;As part of the strategic review, WPP has set out new medium-term financial targets that will allow the company to invest in talent and technology, improve its competitive position and deliver sustainable long-term growth rates. These are as follows, to be achieved by the end of 2021:&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Organic growth (defined as like-for-like revenue less pass-through costs growth) in line with peers&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Headline operating profit margin (excluding associates) of at least 15%&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Free cash flow conversion1 of 80%-90%&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93398-wpp.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements-news/harsh-rai-resigns-as-vp-and-general-manager-of-sales-pepsico-93397.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>11/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Harsh Rai resigns as VP and General Manager of Sales, PepsiCo</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Harsh Rai, VP and General Manager of Sales, PepsiCo has resigned from his post according to media reports. It has also been reported that Ajit Dheer, Managing Director of the Tata-PepsiCo joint venture company NourishCo, will succeed Rai. Rai has been with the company for more than a decade.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Rai has been a member of PepsiCo India&amp;#39;s executive committee since 2014 and has worked across functions, including general management, sales and distribution, and business model transformation. He was also responsible for the snacks business, beverages business and also worked as the CEO &amp;amp; MD for NourishCo Beverages.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Prior to his work at PepsiCo, he worked with Wipro Consumer Care and Lighting as General Manager.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93397-HarshRai.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements-news/mufti-to-expand-footwear-retail-to-500-stores-93387.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>10/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Mufti to expand footwear retail to 500 stores</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Mufti has announced&amp;nbsp;its expansion into the footwear category with a multi-fold strategy including the launch of its latest Autumn Winter footwear collection. Over the past two decades, Mufti has redefined the stereotypes of mainstream fashion and now is extending the same ethos in bringing an alternative choice in footwear which is fashionable yet comfortable. The company&amp;#39;s expansion into the footwear segment is a result of the company&amp;rsquo;s in-depth research highlighting the rising demand for trendy footwear in the casual segment for men.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Over the last 12 months, Mufti has launched a select range in its top 100 stores to gauge consumer sentiment. With the overwhelming response that it received, the brand is now looking at beefing up the distribution of its footwear collection in 500+ locations comprising Multi Brand outlets (MBOs), its stand-alone stores and its existing network of retailers in the coming year.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the launch of Mufti&amp;#39;s Footwear Collection, Kamal Khushlani, Founder &amp;amp; Managing Director, Mufti said, &amp;quot;With the current estimated size of Rs. 34,400 crores, the footwear segment is expected to grow over INR 55,400 crores in the coming five years. The expansion into the footwear segment is a part of the company&amp;rsquo;s vision of becoming an Rs. 1000 crore brand on MRP in the coming 3 years. Our footwear collection carries forward our brand ethos and our promise of bringing quality products that comprise of style in the markets. Our primary focus continues to be on delivering more value to the customer with our products as we begin to expand into newer categories.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The brand plans to offer good quality products at accessible prices in the &amp;lsquo;Casual &amp;amp; Sports Lifestyle&amp;#39; segments. The new footwear line is light in weight and is designed with novel fabrics to ensure comfort for long hours of wear. At the same time, the offerings are made available in a range of colours and trendy styles.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;MUFTI&amp;rsquo;S footwear collection ranges from Rs. 3299/- to Rs. 3999/- and is now available at exclusive brand outlets and select leading footwear stores across India.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93387-Mufti.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements-news/myntra-ceo-ananth-narayanan-resigns-reports-93370.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>10/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Myntra CEO Ananth Narayanan resigns: Reports</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Myntra&amp;rsquo;s Chief Executive Officer (CEO) Ananth Narayanan has resigned from his role and his position will be abolished, according to media reports.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The reports mentioned that Flipkart executive Amar Nagaram has been tasked with heading Myntra.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The reports mentioned that along with Narayanan, some other senior Myntra executives such as chief revenue officer Mithun Sundar and human resources head Manpreet Ratia have also resigned.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93370-anantha.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements-news/kirthiga-reddy-joins-softbank-investment-advisers-as-their-first-venture-partner-93344.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>07/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Kirthiga Reddy joins SoftBank Investment Advisers as their first venture partner</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Ex-Facebook India MD, Kirthiga Reddy, announced in a Facebook post that she will join SoftBank Investment Advisers as their first venture partner.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Reddy resigned from her position as Facebook India&amp;rsquo;s Managing Director in 2016. After which she went back to the US to explore new opportunities at Facebook&amp;rsquo;s headquarters in Menlo Park.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;After over seven incredible years at Facebook &amp;mdash; starting as the first employee and managing director for Facebook India and the last two years at HQ as managing global client partner and emerging markets lead &amp;mdash; I am thrilled to join SoftBank Investment Advisers as their first venture partner,&amp;rdquo; Reddy said in her Facebook post.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Reddy is known for her technical and business expertise &amp;ndash; from both enterprise and consumer technology, in developed and emerging markets. At SoftBank, she will be based out of the San Carlos, Silicon Valley office.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I look forward to contributing to their mission to positively shape the future by seeking to back the boldest, most transformative and optimistic ideas of today. Like in other investment firms, the venture partner role enables quick integration of new talent from non-investing backgrounds, which is a perfect fit for me,&amp;rdquo; she added.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;According to media reports, Reddy in her new role will be working closely with SoftBank Investment Advisors on frontier technologies &amp;ndash; AI, robotics, health tech, bioengineering, semis, IoT, quantum computing, and more &amp;ndash; with an aim to enable the next stage of the information revolution.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Post Reddy&amp;rsquo;s resignation, Facebook appointed Umang Bedi as Facebook India head, who resigned in October 2017, just over a year after he joined the social media company. After another year of search, Facebook has now appointed Hotstar CEO Ajit Mohan as MD and VP of Facebook India. Mohan is expected to join the company early next year.&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93344-kirthigaReddy.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements-news/firstpost-elevates-munaf-merchant-to-national-head-sales-firstpost-news-cluster-93319.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>06/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Firstpost elevates Munaf Merchant to National Head - Sales, Firstpost News Cluster</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Firstpost has announced the elevation of Munaf Merchant to National Head - Sales, Firstpost News Cluster, at Network18 Digital. Merchant will be responsible for developing effective marketing strategies and leading the team towards achieving a high-performance sales environment for Firstpost and Tech2.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Having been associated with Firstpost for over five years now, Merchant possesses an experience of close to 10 years in marketing and sales.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Merchant&amp;rsquo;s expertise has garnered client appreciation and has resulted in renewal of business deals repeatedly. In addition to this, he has a proven track record in building and growing properties from scratch, such as Firstpost&amp;rsquo;s 9 Months &amp;ndash; the ground-breaking show on parenting and childcare which is now in its third season, the company said in a statement.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Talking about the appointment, Azim Lalani, Business Head, English General News cluster, Network18 Digital said, &amp;ldquo;Firstpost has consistently led the way in offering innovative and path-breaking content for its readers across segments like politics, sports, business, technology and entertainment. Having grown significantly since its inception, we are creating a stronger digital presence in the sphere of original content with shows like 9 Months, WhatTheApp and Social Media Star. Munaf has brought to the table excellent marketing capabilities in the last few years and we are sure that he will apply the same level of perseverance and determination in his new responsibility of undertaking the national portfolio in sales for Firstpost and Tech2.&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Prior to joining Firstpost, Munaf worked with India Today in Marketing &amp;amp; Sales where he was responsible for generating revenues for India Today megabrand magazines, which included India Today English, India Today Hindi and India Today Tamil among others.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Commenting on his elevation Merchant said, &amp;ldquo;I am delighted to be entrusted with the new position. It is the perfect platform to further channelize the abilities and creativity of the team and ensure delivering excellent offerings to all our readers and clients. With the digital sphere growing rapidly, we plan to strategically strive and lead the online news space with effective partnerships that benefit all our stakeholders, including our consumers, at large.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93319-firstpost.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements-news/prashant-mehta-joins-isobar-as-sr-vp-global-head-of-delivery-from-publicissapient-93312.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>06/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Prashant Mehta joins Isobar as Sr VP, Global Head of Delivery, from Publicis.Sapient</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Global digital agency Isobar part of Dentsu Aegis Network have appointed Prashant Mehta as their Senior Vice President, Global Head of Delivery, effective immediately.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Mehta will be responsible for re-imagining the next generation of Global Delivery Models for the agency, and will leverage the power of Isobar&amp;rsquo;s global network to connect talent and drive complex and strategic business transformation projects for clients. Mehta will report to Mike Mulligan, Isobar Global Chief Operating Officer and will be based in Gurgaon, India.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Mehta will be the agency&amp;rsquo;s lead architect to design cross-border delivery models across technology, creative and commerce, partnering with Vikalp Tandon, Isobar Global Technology Officer; Ronald Ng, Isobar Chief Creative officer and Shawn Mishra SVP &amp;amp; Global Managing Partner, Isobar Commerce. The new delivery model aims to help Isobar&amp;rsquo;s teams across 85 offices in 45 markets deliver global integrated platforms and solutions for clients.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Mehta will also lead Isobar World Sourcing, the agency offshore initiative built to meet the demands of our clients across time zones. In 2018, Isobar evolved its Isobar World Sourcing Offering in India and focused it on leveraging Commerce Cloud and established a sales, service and marketing cloud offshore team in Vietnam.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Mehta has over 22 years of experience in the industry globally across leadership roles, most recently as Group Vice President, Global Service Line Lead for Data / AI, Systems Integration, Cloud &amp;amp; Media Services at Publicis.Sapient. He has extensive experience in building and scaling organisations that deliver large scale, complex, omni-channel digital transformation programs driving strategic business outcomes for Fortune 500 companies in the Retail , CPG, Financial Services, Auto and Travel / Hospitality industry verticals.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Jean Lin, Global CEO, Isobar said, &amp;ldquo;We are delighted to welcome Prashant to the Global Isobar team to lead our Global delivery function. Agile and effective cross-border delivery and locally relevant customer experiences on global platforms, has become one of the biggest strategic challenges when businesses and brands embrace cross-border commerce. Prashant&amp;rsquo;s vast experience from consulting to delivery, and deep expertise of the most advanced worldwide technologies, will be critical in ensuring the success of our clients&amp;rsquo; business transformation journeys.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Mehta said, &amp;ldquo;In today&amp;rsquo;s age, when business are getting transformed and disrupted globally at the speed of light, Isobar has an industry leading proposition to deliver experience led business transformation for our clients in a truly agile way. I am excited to join Isobar&amp;rsquo;s Global team to drive complex &amp;amp; strategic Digital transformation programs leveraging the intersection of Creative, Technology &amp;amp; Data / AI powered by Modern software engineering to ensure our clients thrive and commercially succeed in today&amp;rsquo;s experience economy.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Isobar is a Salesforce Platinum Cloud Alliance Partner, a Global Alliance Solution Partner for Adobe, a Sitecore Platinum Implementation partner, and an Enterprise Magento Partner, winning Regional and Global Commercial Partner of the year in 2018.&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93311-collage3.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements-news/ogilvy-appoints-piyush-pandey-as-its-global-cco-93292.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>05/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Ogilvy appoints Piyush Pandey as its global CCO</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Ogilvy announced it is promoting Piyush Pandey, the Chairman of Ogilvy India, as its new global Chief Creative Officer effective January 1, 2019, replacing Tham Khai Meng, who was asked to leave in July.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;In addition, Ogilvy also announced that it will expand its Worldwide Creative Council from 12 members to 20; the 20 members&amp;mdash;of which half will be comprised of female creative leaders&amp;mdash;will be announced in January of 2019.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Pandey takes over to elevate the quality of creativity across the Ogilvy network. He will retain his current responsibilities leading the Indian business and be based in Mumbai, but from the new year will work in partnership with Ogilvy&amp;rsquo;s Global Chief Executive, John Seifert to oversee creative standards at the company.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;According to media reports, Seifert had considered both internal and external candidates for the global creative role, but found Pandey to be the right candidate &amp;ldquo;who would be true to the creative spirit of founder David Ogilvy&amp;rdquo;. He added that his working partnership with Pandey would become a model for Ogilvy offices around the world, with the creative and business agendas coming fully together.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Pandey&amp;rsquo;s appointment and the corresponding Worldwide Creative Council expansion is the next step in the execution of Ogilvy&amp;rsquo;s Next Chapter transformation. The agency remains focused on accelerating the diversity within its creative ranks, through both external recruitment and more dedicated internal talent development and network mobility. At last year&amp;rsquo;s Cannes Lions, Ogilvy announced its commitment (in partnership with the 3% Movement)&amp;nbsp;to recruit 20 senior women in creative globally by 2020, and it is proud to have taken a big step towards that goal.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;In corresponding creative talent news, Joe Sciarrotta becomes Deputy Chief Creative Officer, Worldwide, reporting to Pandey and Seifert. Sciarrotta&amp;nbsp;will continue to lead creative work assignments for several of our top 50 clients while taking on new duties at the worldwide creative level. Leslie Sims also joins Ogilvy as Chief Creative Officer of Ogilvy USA, reporting to Lou Aversano, Chief Executive, USA.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93292-piyush.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements-news/thomson-reuters-to-cut-3200-jobs-by-2020-93285.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>05/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Thomson Reuters to cut 3,200 jobs by 2020</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Thomson Reuters, the company that runs Reuters News, is expected to cut 3,200 jobs in the next 2 years in an effort to reshift the company&amp;#39;s focus on software services, according to news reports. It is not yet known where the cuts will be made.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;It was reported that Thomson Reuters announced the cuts during an annual investor day in Toronto on December 4, and highlighted that the move is part of an endeavour to cut costs and create a more streamlined organisation with a focus on its legal and tax businesses after selling 55% of its Financial &amp;amp; Risk unit for around $20 billion to Blackstone Group.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Reports state that the company also plans to downsize the number of global offices to 133 by 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;In 2017, Reuters News accounted for 6 per cent of Thomson Reuters&amp;#39; total revenue&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93285-ThomsonReuters.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements-news/times-network-announces-5th-edition-of-india-economic-conclave-93277.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>05/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Times Network announces 5th edition of India Economic Conclave</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;Times Network has announced the 5th edition of its annual signature event, India Economic Conclave 2018. Driving this edition&amp;rsquo;s theme, &amp;lsquo;Shaping India&amp;rsquo;s $5trillion growth agenda&amp;rsquo;, the two-day conclave will engage, enable and encourage global voices with India perspective through discourses among global visionaries, key policymakers and iconic leaders.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
With a focus to enable rapid transformation of India to a global powerhouse, India Economic Conclave 2018 aims to set the tone for constructive dialogues and discussions on the critical points concerning the economy. The event will share the vision and actionable insights to further unleash the true potential of India Inc, the network said in a statement.&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Present at the event will be some of India&amp;rsquo;s most influential leaders such as Arun Jaitley, Minister of Finance and Corporate Affairs; Piyush Goyal, Minister of Railways &amp;amp; Coal; Dharmendra Pradhan, Minister of Petroleum &amp;amp; Natural Gas and Skill Development &amp;amp; Entrepreneurship; Devendra Fadnavis, Chief Minister &amp;ndash; Maharashtra; Trivendra Singh Rawat, Chief Minister &amp;ndash; Uttarakhand; Amitabh Kant, CEO &amp;ndash; NITI Ayog; Sadhguru, Founder &amp;ndash; Isha Foundation; Rajesh Gopinathan, CEO &amp;amp; MD - Tata Consultancy Services; Keki Mistry, Vice Chairman &amp;amp; CEO &amp;ndash; HDFC Ltd.; David Hanson, Founder &amp;amp; CEO &amp;ndash; Hanson Robotics; Arianna Huffington, Founder &amp;ndash; Thrive Global; Dr. Mark Mobius, Founder &amp;ndash; Mobius Capital Partners LLP; &amp;nbsp;Ralph Simon, Founder &amp;amp; Chairman &amp;nbsp;&amp;ndash; Mobilium Global; and actor Ranveer Singh.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;The conclave will provide a platform to initiate dialogues on the future of new India and give shape to its $5trillion agenda, with focus on the benefits to the common man from rising India. The signature event, aimed at anticipating, formulating and executing strategies, will witness a series of power-packed sessions, which will address issues pivotal to the greater economic growth of the nation.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;To register for the event, please log onto&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.indiaeconomicconclave.com" rel="nofollow" style="color:blue; text-decoration:underline"&gt;www.indiaeconomicconclave.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93277-TimesLogo.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements-news/godrej-consumer-products-cmo-kapil-pillai-steps-down-93260.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>04/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Godrej Consumer Products CMO Kapil Pillai Steps Down</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Godrej Consumer Products Limited Marketing Head, Kapil Pillai, has stepped down from his position. He was appointed as the CMO for the GCPL India business in February 2017. GCPL confirmed Pillai&amp;rsquo;s move, noting that his position now lies vacant.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Prior to being appoint the CMO of GCPL India, Pillai was Managing Director &amp;amp; CEO of Godrej South Africa for nearly three years. Pillai joined GCPL for the first time in 2004 as General Manager - Sales &amp;amp; Customer Service, Godrej SaraLee Limited.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;He rose up the ranks over the last 14 years serving in multiple leadership roles, particularly in marketing. He was VP Marketing for the &amp;nbsp;Hair Care and Fabric Care Business between 2012 and 2014. Between 2010 and 2012 he was leading marketing initiatives for the &amp;nbsp;home care (Household Insecticides and Fabric Care) business.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Pillai began his career in 1996 as a Regional Sales Manager for Reckitt &amp;amp; Colman (now Reckitt Benckiser).&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93260-collage_(2).jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements-news/hul-acquires-gsk-consumer-health-india-for-rs-31700-crore-93245.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>03/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>HUL acquires GSK Consumer Health India for Rs 31,700 crore</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Hindustan Unilever has acquired GlaxoSmithKline Consumer Health India for Rs 31,700 crore. The deal is being touted as one of the country&amp;#39;s largest in the consumer goods market.&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
With this deal, HUL will now own iconic brands such as Horlicks and Boost.&amp;nbsp;The transaction is an all equity merger with 4.39 shares of HUL being allotted for every share in GSK CH India.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Announcing the deal, HUL in a statement said, &amp;ldquo;The acquisition is in line with the Hindustan Unilever strategy to build a sustainable and profitable Foods and Refreshment (F&amp;amp;R) business in India by leveraging the mega trend of health and wellness. GSK CH India is the market leader in the HFD category, with iconic brands such as Horlicks and Boost, and a product portfolio supported by strong nutritional claims,&amp;rdquo; said the statement by HUL.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Sanjiv Mehta, Chairman and Managing Director, HUL, said, &amp;ldquo;With this proposed strategic merger with GSK CH India, we will be expanding our portfolio with great brands into a new category catering to the nutritional needs of our consumers. I am confident that this merger will create significant shareholder value through both revenue growth and cost synergies. The turnover of our F&amp;amp;R business will exceed Rs.100 bn and we will become one of the largest F&amp;amp;R businesses in the country. We look forward to welcoming new brands and great talent into the Unilever and HUL family, once the transaction is complete. &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93245-GSK.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements-news/durga-raghunath-resigns-as-ceo-of-the-indian-express-digital-media-services-93241.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>03/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Durga Raghunath resigns as CEO of the Indian Express Digital Media Services</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Durga Raghunath has resigned as the CEO of the Indian Express Digital Media Services, according to media reports.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Raghunath had joined India Express in 2017 and managed the business and editorial operations of all digital brands of the Express Group, taking over from Sandeep Amar who had resigned in July 2017. Raghunath reported to George Varghese, CEO, The Indian Express Group.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;At India Express, Raghunath played an important role in redesigning the newspaper, website and app interface last month. She was also instrumental in launching podcasts, beginning with eight shows across news and in-depth thematic programming in June.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;She was also involvied in the launch of ieBangla, a Bengali language version of it news website, in April this year. The company had launched ieMalayalam and ieTamil in 2017.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Raghunath is the co-founder of Juggernaut Books, along with Chiki Sarkar, but resigned CEO in 2017.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Before that, she served a brief stint at Zomato, as SVP of Growth. Prior to that she had been CEO of Network18 Digital, and had been instrumental in setting up FirstPost. She&amp;rsquo;s also a Facebook #SheLeadsTech mentor.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93241-DurgaRaghunath.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements-news/gaurav-barjatya-joins-wwe-as-marketing-director-93238.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>03/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Gaurav Barjatya joins WWE India as Marketing Director</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;meta charset="utf-8" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Star India&amp;rsquo;s former Vice President- Marketing, Star TV Network, Gaurav Barjatya has joined WWE India, an American integrated media and entertainment company that is primarily known for professional wrestling.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Barjatya had joined WWE India a couple of weeks ago as Marketing Director. Barjatya has confirmed this development with exchange4media.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Barjatya joined Star TV Network in January 2011.Barjatya was with Star India for more than seven years and he quit as VP- Marketing, Star TV.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Prior to that, he was working with Parle Agro as Senior Brand Manager. He was also associated with Idea Cellular for four years.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93238-GauravBarjatya.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements-news/oppo-india-md-yi-wang-steps-down-93228.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>03/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>OPPO India MD Yi Wang steps down</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Amidst its mounting losses and increasing competition from players like Xiaomi, Chinese smartphone brand Oppo Mobiles India&amp;rsquo;s Managing Director Yi Wang stepped down. Media reports mentioned that the net losses in the country expanded to Rs 358 crore in 2017-18 from Rs 42 crore in the previous year. For the half year ending September 2018 losses were recorded at Rs 778 crore. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;In a statement the company mentioned that board of directors of Oppo Mobiles India in consensus took the decision of Yi Wang&amp;#39;S resignation from his position, effective from November 30. It also mentioned that Wang played crucial role in the Oppo&amp;rsquo;s journey since its entry in the market. The new India MD wil be appointed in &amp;#39;appropriate time.&amp;#39; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;The loss can be attributed to its growing marketing costs. Last year it entered into a five-year contract worth Rs 1080 crore with Board of Control for Cricket in India (BCCI) for team&amp;rsquo;s jersey rights. It has been one of the title sponsors of Colors&amp;rsquo; reality show &amp;lsquo;Bigg Boss&amp;rsquo; for couple of years. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Post Wang&amp;#39;s exit, in an interview to Economic Time, Charles Wong, India President, Oppo mentioned that India is a high priority market forming the centrepiece of their global growth strategy. He also pointed out that it has a &amp;lsquo;clear&amp;rsquo; India strategy and will continue launching products to expand its base. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Before Wang&amp;rsquo;s resignation Oppo appointed Tasleem Arif as Vice-President and Head of R&amp;amp;D.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93228-OppoFinal.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements-news/interbrand-appoints-borja-borrero-to-lead-design-operations-in-india-93209.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>30/11/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Interbrand appoints Borja Borrero to lead design operations in India</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin-bottom:10.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="color:#222222"&gt;Interbrand, the brand consultancy, has announced the appointment of Borja Borrero, Chief Creative Director at Interbrand for EMEA (Western Europe) and LatAm, to mentor the India design team. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:10.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="color:#222222"&gt;With the appointment of Borja Borrero to lead Interbrand India&amp;rsquo;s design operations, the consultancy is looking forward to elevate the creative quality and reputation standards for the regions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="color:black"&gt; as well as expanding the team&amp;rsquo;s capabilities into the experiential side of branding.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:10.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="color:#222222"&gt;&amp;ldquo;Interbrand India is the youngest within the global network, and yet has been evolving at a good speed,&amp;rdquo; said Ashish Mishra, Managing Director, Interbrand India. &amp;ldquo;We have the top 5 branding assignments of the decade on our showreel and our engagements with some of the leading brands in India such as Godrej, Mahindra Global Brand, JIO, Infosys and Britannia have made us the prime Brand Consultancy in India. I am confident that Borja will bring in his experience and expertise to guide our India team towards remarkable growth.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:10.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="color:#222222"&gt;Speaking on the transition, Borrero said, &amp;ldquo;The India market has evolved enormously with &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="color:black"&gt;progressive&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span lang="EN-US" style="color:#222222"&gt;consumers and challenges. India is an important market for us and has led us to tremendous growth opportunities. I am looking forward to share my experiences and learnings with the team and support them for servicing our expanding spectrum of clients. We wish to harness these opportunities and create an exciting chapter for all of us.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:10.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="color:#222222"&gt;Borrero has been associated with Interbrand for more than a 15 years&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span lang="EN-US" style="color:#222222"&gt;and has led international projects such as the repositioning and rebranding of &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="color:black"&gt;Iberia, Movistar, Repsol, Bankia or DIA among others. He also led the project of repositioning and rebranding of Grupo AJE in Peru, Renault in France and the merger of LAN and TAM airlines on a global scale&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="color:#222222"&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93209-borja.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements-news/nima-namchu-cco-havas-worldwide-india-quits-93204.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>30/11/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Nima Namchu, CCO, Havas Worldwide India, quits</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Nima Namchu, CCO, Havas Worldwide&amp;nbsp;India has put in his papers.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Talking about Namchu&amp;rsquo;s decision to move on, Rana Barua, Group CEO- Havas Group, said, &amp;quot;We thank him for all that he has done and wish him all the best going ahead.&amp;rdquo; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;The development comes close on the heels of the appointment of Bobby Pawar as the Chairman &amp;amp; CCO of Havas Group India.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Talking about his stint at Havas, Namchu said, &amp;quot;The last three and a half years with Havas have been rewarding and quite a learning experience. I wish the agency and the team the best.&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Namchu has over 25 years of experience in the business and has worked for top agencies such as Cheil, Contract, Publicis, Leo Burnett and McCann Erickson. One of the most memorable campaigns he has worked on is Reebok, which gave Rahul Dravid the nickname &amp;#39;The Wall&amp;#39;. Others are&amp;nbsp;Domino&amp;rsquo;s Pizza &amp;#39;Khushiyon ki Home Delivery&amp;#39; &amp;amp; &amp;#39;Yeh hai rishton ka time&amp;#39;, Reebok&amp;rsquo;s &amp;#39;I am what I am&amp;#39; India campaign and Durex Air&amp;rsquo;s &amp;#39;Hate Condoms Love Durex Air&amp;#39;. He has also worked for brands such as Samsung, LG, MasterCard, Microsoft and Dabur.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93204-NimaNamchu.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements-news/tv-todays-national-revenue-head-hersh-bhandari-quits-93191.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>29/11/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>TV Today’s National Revenue Head Hersh Bhandari quits</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Hersh Bhandari has quit as the National Revenue Head, TV Today. He is expected to take up a new assignment starting 2019. Highly placed sources in the industry have confirmed the development. However, when contacted, Bhandari did not comment.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;exchange4media also reached out to TV Today Group for an official confirmation, but did not get a response till the filing of the story.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Bhandari, who had been associated with TV Today Group for close to two years,&amp;nbsp;is believed to have put in his papers early this week.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Bhandari has over two decades of experience in the media industry and was previously associated with Times Television Network for over seven years as VP Sales &amp;amp; National Revenue Head. He has also worked with other leading networks, including Star TV.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93191-HershFinal.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements-news/unilever-ceo-paul-polman-to-retire-alan-jope-to-succeed-him-93188.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>29/11/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Unilever CEO Paul Polman to retire; Alan Jope to succeed him</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Consumer goods giant Unilever on Thursday announced that its long-time Chief Executive Officer Paul Polman would retire at the end of the year. He will be succeeded by Alan Jope. Jope, 54, is currently the President of the company&amp;rsquo;s beauty and personal care division.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Polman will step down from his role from January 1, but will stay on for another six months to help out with the transition. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="vertical-align:baseline"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#404040"&gt;In a statement issued by the company, Unilever Chairman Marijn Dekkers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;said&amp;nbsp;&amp;ldquo;Paul is an exceptional business leader who has transformed Unilever, making it one of the best-performing companies in its sector, and one of the most admired businesses in the world. His role in helping to define a new era of responsible capitalism, embodied in the Unilever Sustainable Living Plan, marks him out as one of the most far-sighted business leaders of his generation.&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:13.5pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="vertical-align:baseline"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&amp;ldquo;Paul&amp;rsquo;s vision, drive and performance focus, combined with his commitment to serving the best long-term interests of the company, have materially strengthened Unilever. He leaves a more agile and resilient company, well placed to win in this fast-changing, dynamic industry. I&amp;rsquo;d like to thank him personally, and on behalf of the Board, for his contribution to Unilever,&amp;quot; he added.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:13.5pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="vertical-align:baseline"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;On&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Jope&amp;#39;s selection for the role, the company said,&amp;quot;After a rigorous and wide-ranging selection process, the Board is delighted to appoint Alan to the role. Having worked for Unilever in a variety of senior management roles, Alan has a deep understanding and experience of our business, the industry, and the markets in which we operate. He is a strong, dynamic and values-driven leader with an impressive track record of delivering consistent high-quality performance. The Board warmly welcomes Alan to the role and wishes him every success.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:13.5pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="vertical-align:baseline"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&amp;quot;During his tenure, the company has delivered consistent top and bottom line growth ahead of its markets. Its focus on successfully pioneering a new model of sustainable growth has served the needs of its many stakeholders and created excellent returns for its shareholders, delivering a Total Shareholder Return of 290% over that period,&amp;quot; the company said in a statement.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="vertical-align:baseline"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Commenting on his decision to step down, Polman said,&amp;nbsp;&amp;ldquo;It has been an honour to lead Unilever over the last 10 years. Throughout this time, I have been humbled by the commitment and hard work of our people, and their passion for creating a truly purpose-driven company. I am very grateful to them, as I am to Unilever&amp;rsquo;s many other stakeholders, with whom we have worked to build our long-term, sustainable business. I look forward to engaging with many of these partners &amp;ndash; in a different capacity &amp;ndash; to help address the many environmental and social challenges facing the world.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:13.5pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;font face="Times New Roman, serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt;Polman also tweeted about his decision.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-lang="en-gb"&gt;&#13;
&lt;p dir="ltr" lang="en"&gt;It has been a true privilege to be &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/Unilever?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;@Unilever&lt;/a&gt;&amp;rsquo;s CEO, I will always remain a passionate advocate for all the company stands for, immensely proud of what we have achieved over the past 10 year, &amp;amp; will continue to work towards making sustainability commonplace &lt;a href="https://t.co/t56TJ7N0tA"&gt;https://t.co/t56TJ7N0tA&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://t.co/1lIvcK5z97"&gt;pic.twitter.com/1lIvcK5z97&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&amp;mdash; Paul Polman (@PaulPolman) &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/PaulPolman/status/1068048547294138368?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;29 November 2018&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#13;
&lt;script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-lang="en-gb"&gt;&#13;
&lt;p dir="ltr" lang="en"&gt;I have no doubts that I will be leaving the company in excellent hands. Under Alan&amp;#39;s leadership &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/Unilever?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;@Unilever&lt;/a&gt; is well-placed to prosper long into the future, staying true to the values which make it so special, and continue to do well by doing good &lt;a href="https://t.co/uXL1ay8mPk"&gt;https://t.co/uXL1ay8mPk&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://t.co/vIF3237Oxp"&gt;pic.twitter.com/vIF3237Oxp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&amp;mdash; Paul Polman (@PaulPolman) &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/PaulPolman/status/1068046669688827904?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;29 November 2018&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#13;
&lt;script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Talking about his new role, Alan Jope said,&amp;nbsp;&amp;ldquo;It will be a huge privilege to lead Unilever &amp;ndash; a truly global company full of talented people, and brilliant brands. Over the 30 years I have worked at Unilever, I have seen the many ways in which our brands improve people&amp;rsquo;s lives, positively impacting more than 2 billion citizens every day.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;d also like to extend my gratitude to Paul for his remarkable leadership of Unilever and look forward to working closely with him during the transition,&amp;rdquo; Jope added.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:13.5pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;The company has reportedly said that it will soon announce Jope&amp;rsquo;s successor. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:13.5pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93188-Polman.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements-news/cheil-ww-india-announces-emmanuel-upputuru-as-their-chief-creative-officer-93172.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>28/11/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Cheil WW India announces Emmanuel Upputuru as their Chief Creative Officer</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Advertising and marketing communication agency, Cheil WW India, announced the appointment of Emmanuel Upputuru as their Chief Creative Officer. In his role, Upputuru will be responsible for strengthening the creative capability and reputation of the agency.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;With over two decades of experience across reputed communication networks Upputuru is a celebrated creative head and an industry thought leader. He has spoken at various platforms and judged International award festivals. His work has won him global recognition including Lions and Pencils.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Previously he has worked with WPP and Publicis and led some of the most memorable and impactful campaigns for brands like HCL Technologies, Nestle, ITC, American Express, Oxigen Wallet, Dabur, Maruti, Hero, Motorola, Sprite, Cleartrip, etc. His last venture was an exploration with communication entrepreneurship that he named ITSA. Upputuru is inspired by technology and innovation and is known for providing integrated creative solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the appointment, Atika Malik, COO, Cheil WW India said, &amp;ldquo;We are delighted to have Emmanuel join our leadership team. His appointment as the Chief Creative Officer of Cheil indicates our commitment to delivering industry-leading creative solutions across all platforms. We are the Agency built for Now and Emmanuel is an ideal leader to navigate the ever evolving marketing landscape and find innovative solutions to client&amp;rsquo;s business problems. One can look forward to many more pieces of work by Cheil where creativity is inspired by technology.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Talking about his new role, Upputuru said, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m excited to be joining Cheil at this stage of their journey and point in my career. What attracted me to Cheil is their focus encapsulated in a two-word formula: creativity + technology - something that I have always believed in. I think, creativity is more powerful when applied to the whole business, beyond just marketing. Cheil is uniquely placed to deliver this promise. Finally I must congratulate Sagar on a fantastic run.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93172-EmmanuelUpputuru.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
</urlset>
