<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9" xmlns:image="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-image/1.1" xmlns:news="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-news/0.9">
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital-news/2019-will-be-the-year-of-regional-content-tarun-katial-zee5-93411.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>12/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>2019 will be the year of regional content: Tarun Katial, ZEE5</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;2018 has been a rather action-packed year for ZEE5 and the upcoming year or two will only see things getting bigger and better for ZEEL&amp;rsquo;s OTT platform with more investments being pushed in that direction. Punit Goenka, MD &amp;amp; CEO of ZEEL, had mentioned earlier in one of his interviews that the streaming service is their next big bet when it comes to investment and cornering incremental and additional viewers. With increasing investment he is expecting the business to break even in three to five years.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:8.0pt; text-align:start; -webkit-text-stroke-width:0px; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-ligatures:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-caps:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="orphans:2"&gt;&lt;span style="widows:2"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-style:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-color:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="word-spacing:0px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;Tarun Katial, CEO, ZEE5, talks to e4m about the future plans and how the past year has been for the OTT platform, including the reception, region specific subscription pack and original content. Excerpts:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:start; -webkit-text-stroke-width:0px; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-ligatures:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-caps:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="orphans:2"&gt;&lt;span style="widows:2"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-style:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-color:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="word-spacing:0px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;Innovative pricing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;span style="font-size:11.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;Apart from bringing in regional content, ZEE5 played around with the pricing and introduced special subscription packs for Tamil, Telugu and Kannada audience. This enables users to access premium language content at half the price (Rs 49/month).&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Katial shared that the reception to these region specific packs has been &amp;lsquo;great&amp;rsquo; as they are offering live TV, regional original content, digital movie premieres and early access to regional shows even before TV. &amp;ldquo;So it&amp;rsquo;s a healthy bouquet of content with lot of depth for Tamil, Telugu and Kannada consumers. After South, we will take a break for a quarter and go East,&amp;rdquo; revealed Katial. &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
2018 saw original regional content really taking off with OTT players eyeing growth from tier II and III cities. But that, says Katial, was just the tip of the iceberg. &amp;ldquo;2019 will be the actual year of language (regional) content, the big proliferation of original content and digital movies in India. The uptake of original content will move 3-4 times,&amp;rdquo; he said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:12.0pt; text-align:start; -webkit-text-stroke-width:0px; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-ligatures:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-caps:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="orphans:2"&gt;&lt;span style="widows:2"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-style:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-color:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="word-spacing:0px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;Katial also mentioned the launch of a premium brand around ZEE5. &amp;quot;It&amp;rsquo;s in the process of being created. SVOD section will be branded separately. It&amp;rsquo;s a different experience than AVOD subset. Several features will be added to it.&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:start; -webkit-text-stroke-width:0px; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-ligatures:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-caps:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="orphans:2"&gt;&lt;span style="widows:2"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-style:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-color:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="word-spacing:0px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;Content game strong&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;Right from its launch, ZEE5 has kept its content game strong especially for originals and movie acquisition. It came out with 15 originals across six languages including the big-budget &amp;lsquo;Karenjit Kaur&amp;rsquo; and big digital premieres of popular titles such as Mulk, Parmanu, Stree and Veere Di Wedding. The strategy of movie premieres particularly worked as it was one of the major consumption drivers. &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
It&amp;rsquo;s now looking to launch over 90 originals in FY2019 and reach 150+ digital premiers in the next 18 months. Katial mentioned that audience sees value in original content as it&amp;rsquo;s a big differentiator. This explains the deep investment. &amp;ldquo;Original movies did well, case in point being &amp;lsquo;Tiger&amp;rsquo; (Emraan Hashmi) We have &amp;lsquo;Rangbaaz&amp;rsquo; coming up next month with Saqib Saleem which is as big as &amp;lsquo;Karenjit Kaur&amp;rsquo; for us. Then there will be big original shows in Tamil, Telugu, Bengali and Marathi. We will amp up in 2019. A slate of 40-50 big shows will come up over the next two quarters,&amp;rdquo; Katial added.&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
AVOD is not getting overshadowed as Katial sees TV shows and their characters being big drivers. &amp;ldquo;We have content beyond the general shows like character journeys and best scenes. Lot of content is created outside the core content. We will continue to invest behind that as well.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;&amp;quot;Language original content, shows around specific themes and relevant topics will continue to resonate well with Indian consumers. You will see off-take in subscription,&amp;quot; says Katial.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:start; -webkit-text-stroke-width:0px; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-ligatures:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-caps:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="orphans:2"&gt;&lt;span style="widows:2"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-style:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-color:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="word-spacing:0px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;Distribution&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;span style="font-size:11.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;Like any other OTT streaming platform, ZEE5 hasn&amp;rsquo;t left any stone unturned to reach the consumer.&amp;nbsp; This goes beyond the regular tie-ups with telecom service providers, digital wallets and smart TVs. For instance, for travel start-up RailYatri customers, ZEE5 had introduced a sachet subscription which gets bundled with the bookings. Similar partnerships with Oyo, MakeMyTrip and RedBus among others are aimed at travel-loving consumers by offering them discounts. &amp;ldquo;Sachet consumers come for a short period of time and want entertainment on the go.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:start; -webkit-text-stroke-width:0px; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-ligatures:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-caps:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="orphans:2"&gt;&lt;span style="widows:2"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-style:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-color:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="word-spacing:0px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;All this and more is definitely working as the ZEE5 app garnered 41.3 million Monthly Active Users in Sep&amp;rsquo;18, a whopping 190% growth since Apr&amp;rsquo;18, according to data provided by ZEE5. And they have just about begun.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1526893051_UNDgGs_Tarun-Katial.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital-news/learning-a-thing-or-two-from-the-mumbai-police-about-upping-the-social-media-game-93403.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>12/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Learning a thing or two from the Mumbai Police about upping the Social Media game</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Lately, the woman behind the famed Mumbai Police department&amp;rsquo;s Twitter handle (@MumbaiPolice) finds herself catching up on the latest binge-worthy shows, viral memes and Twitter trends whenever she finds the time.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;From Game of Thrones and Stranger Things to Twitter memes like GharSeNikalTeHi, Sunchika Pandey and her team is thinking content round the clock and tries to never miss a social media opportunity for the Mumbai Police. Over the last three years, the Mumbai Police Department&amp;rsquo;s Twitter handle has become every Mumbaikar&amp;rsquo;s go-to channel for latest updates on law and order related happenings in the city, to register complaints, all while being treated to social media memes on the side. The social media strategy is a prime example for consumer facing brands that are trying to establish a strong social media presence.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seeing Content Everywhere&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Content has become a state of mind for the Mumbai Police social media team. &amp;quot;If I see a glass lying around on the table, I wonder how to use it as content!&amp;quot; she says. But she is not cued into all the millenial themes and trends, so she&amp;nbsp;generally gets all her&amp;nbsp;references checked with her&amp;nbsp;team of youngsters.&amp;nbsp;&amp;quot;But now I am also watching all the popular shows,&amp;rdquo; confesses Pandey, who is&amp;nbsp;the Group Director of its Citizen Initiatives &amp;amp; Government division at independent digital agency, Gozoop.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s not just Pandey, even the policemen who run the Twitter operations for the department have begun looking at the world around them through the lens of &amp;ldquo;content.&amp;rdquo; This is the result of the Mumbai Police department&amp;rsquo;s innovative attempt at reaching out to the citizens of Mumbai through the micro-blogging platform three years ago.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Every brand is talking the language of content, and there is no reason&amp;nbsp;the Mumbai Police should be found lagging. &amp;ldquo;What ticks with the readers now-a-days is content. Content that is quirky, trendy, timeless, resonating...&amp;nbsp;the list goes on. Mumbai Police has ticked all the boxes.&amp;nbsp;Messages about safety, social &amp;amp; traffic discipline, celebration, respect for martyrs, cyber security, and all such occasions are so very well weaved into different engaging formats of content. By default you end up consuming these pieces and the point is driven home,&amp;rdquo; says Shekhar Mhaskar, EVP Isobar India, decoding the success of the Mumbai Police&amp;#39;s social media game.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;The first tweet we ever put out was : Why should the police station be the only place where we meet? Let&amp;rsquo;s meet here every day,&amp;rdquo; recollects Pandey. Hers and her&amp;nbsp;team&amp;rsquo;s efforts to make the police department more approachable and less fearful for&amp;nbsp;the citizens has earned the department the moniker Meme-bai Police and Amul of Government departments.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Response Engenders Trust&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Hidden under the satirical content and prompt informative responses from the department is a lesson for all marketers who are trying to create a social media persona for their brands. To Pandey the lesson is very simple: a clear vision plus knowledge of target audience complemented by fulfilment of brand promise = success.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Even Pandey knows this is easier said than done. Social media handles of most consumer facing companies are inundated with complaints from disgruntled consumers every day. These complaints are mostly met with automated responses that only irk consumers further.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;There are instances when a disgruntled consumer feels a loss of trust with the brand because of a negative experience and cannot be assuaged by following documented response matrices. This is where a brand can elevate itself to the next level of sophistication &amp;ndash; with their ability to humanise interactions and setting up of strong internal processes that speak with different departments to effectively act upon their customer commitments,&amp;rdquo; says Sakshi Arora, Strategy Director, Digitas India.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Anticipating the citizen outpouring, at least eight policemen and two senior police officers monitor the Mumbai Police and Police Commissioner&amp;rsquo;s Twitter handles at any given point. The policemen monitor the tweets and direct messages sent to these two handles until 3-4am every day. &amp;ldquo;The clear mandate when we started out was that we must respond to every single tweet,&amp;rdquo; Pandey says.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kidding, but seriously...&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The mission of the Mumbai Police was to utilise Twitter as yet another touchpoint where the department could interact with the citizens. &amp;ldquo;It was not in our plan to make it iconic in the way that it has become,&amp;rdquo; says Pandey with humility.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;We wanted to make people smile and that&amp;rsquo;s how we thought about using humour in our posts.&amp;rdquo; At the same time as the Twitter handle of the police department the content had to always adhere to a certain high moral and ethical code. &amp;ldquo;As Mumbai Police we needed to maintain the dignity of the officers and the uniform. That is why we chose satire.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Mumbai Police has resonated with the citizens of Mumbai by &amp;ldquo;challenging the status quo on the type of online personality an administrative body should have,&amp;rdquo; says Arora. This dark humour coupled with healthy engagement with citizens gives Mumbai Police its clutter breaking social presence and huge organic following.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Brands typically monitor their social media handles but worry that saying something edgy will get them trolled. Typically BFSI, healthcare, and B2B brands are uncomfortable about using humour on social channels. But the Mumbai Police is okay with taking a stance and even responding to citizens. Now the mental impression of Mumbai Police has improved because of the social media presence of the department,&amp;rdquo; says Siddharth Hegde, MD &amp;amp; Founder, Ethinos Digital Marketing.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;All of these factors have made Mumbai Police a social media case study that other police departments across the country have begun to emulate. The Bangalore and Kolkata City Police engage with their citizens on social media very successfully. &amp;quot;Even the UP Police has launched a Twitter account and that has helped the department improve its image,&amp;quot; quips Pandey. As the&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Group Director of its Citizen Initiatives &amp;amp; Government division at Gozoop, Pandey wishes to work with more government bodies, helping them engage in a healthy manner with citizens.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93403-mumbaipolice.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital-news/most-viewed-videos-of-2018-93300.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>11/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Most viewed videos of 2018</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;The power of social media is so huge that it requires no time to make one become famous. It recognises true and unrecognised talents and has given them a platform to display their unique skills. The year 2018 witnessed a bunch of videos going viral making the person depicted in it, famous. From winking girl to daily wager, who is a singing sensation, the list of people who became famous through social media never ends.&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at some of the videos that went viral in the&amp;nbsp;year 2018.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Winking Girl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Priya Prakash Varrier took the internet by storm by a wink. The 19-year model-actress from Kerala was seen winking in a 30 second clip from a song from the movie &amp;lsquo;Oru Adaar Love&amp;rsquo;. It didn&amp;rsquo;t take much time for Varrier to become global sensation. Meltwater, the global media intelligence company, tracked and analysed mentions of the film and of Varrier across online, editorial and social media. According to reports, &amp;lsquo;Oru Adaar Love&amp;rsquo; and Varrier were mentioned 2,723 times on editorial media and 89,785 times on social media globally, in the second week of February.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Varrier has around 6.5 M + followers on Instagram and 6 lakh+ followers on Facebook. The song has garnered 82 +Million views on YouTube. She was signed for Nestle Munch advertisement and a South Indian shopping mall, even before her first movie release.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/W0fKl43QmIE?rel=0&amp;amp;wmode=transparent" width="100%"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dancing Uncle&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Sanjeev Shrivastava fondly known as Dancing Uncle became a sensation overnight with his &amp;lsquo;Govinda&amp;rsquo; dance moves. A video of Shrivastava dancing at a wedding has gone viral in the month of June.&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Bajaj Allianz Life Insurance capitalised on Shrivastava&amp;rsquo;s popularity and quickly roped him for their latest announcement of a one-time special bonus for their policyholders. The video saw him dancing to Bajaj Allianz Life&amp;rsquo;s new jingle &amp;lsquo;Samjho Ho Gaya&amp;rsquo; that captures the essence of the brand&amp;rsquo;s new philosophy &amp;lsquo;Life Goals. DONE&amp;rsquo;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;His Twitter account @Dabbuthe dancer has 8.2K followers.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/dvQb76sRR2E?rel=0&amp;amp;wmode=transparent" width="100%"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Singing Baby from Andhra Pradesh&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;In the month of November, Baby, a native of East Godavari district of Andhra Pradesh &amp;nbsp;was seen in a viral video singing &amp;lsquo;O Cheliya&amp;rsquo; from the movie Premikudu, Telugu version of A R Rahman&amp;rsquo;s popular song &amp;lsquo;Ennavale&amp;rsquo; from the movie Kadhalan. Rahman himself shared the video captioned &amp;lsquo;unknown, anonymous, beautiful voice&amp;rsquo;. The video got millions of shares and likes in no time. She has got her Tollywood break in the&amp;nbsp;movie &amp;#39;Palasa 1978&amp;#39;.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe frameborder="0" height="476" rel="nofollow" scrolling="no" src="https://www.facebook.com/plugins/video.php?href=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.facebook.com%2Farrahman%2Fvideos%2F524106481413224%2F&amp;amp;show_text=0&amp;amp;" style="border:none;overflow:hidden" width="261"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The daily wager who caught Shankar Mahadevan&amp;rsquo;s attention&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;In the month of July a daily wager went viral with his song &amp;lsquo;Unai Kaanadhu Naan Indru Naal Illaye&amp;rsquo; from actor Kamal Haasan starrer film &amp;lsquo;Vishwaroopam&amp;rsquo;. The video was shared by singer Shankar Mahadevan who sang the original song asking people to help him to identify the singer in the video. The person was identified as Rakesh Unni, a daily wager from Kerala who sang during break from his work has met Kamal Hassan and sang for the actor. &amp;nbsp;Unni is soon to get a break in play back singing.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/ZzRqbwiC914?rel=0&amp;amp;wmode=transparent" width="100%"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93300-PriyaVarrier.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital-news/sir-martin-sorrell-has-shopping-plans-in-india-93394.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>11/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Sir Martin Sorrell has plans to buy agencies in India</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Sir Martin Sorrell is in India with plans to shop for agencies in content, data, and media planning space. According to Sorrell, these three sectors are the main focus areas of S4 Capital and he will be interested in pure independent digital agencies and agencies that have broken away from networks and large agencies. Sorrell hopes that his company S4 Capital is seen as a new kid on the block with a different strategy.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Speaking at an event in Mumbai on Monday evening, Sorrell said that version 3.0 of his avatar will be all about technology. &amp;ldquo;The 10 most important companies right now are Google, Facebook, Amazon, Tencent, Alibaba, Apple, Microsoft, Oracle, Salesforce, and Adobe. I would like S4 to be a royalty of the growth of all those companies.&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Calling Google, Facebook, Amazon, Tencent, Alibaba, Apple, and Microsoft &amp;lsquo;seven sisters&amp;rsquo;, he said the last time a group of companies was referred to as &amp;lsquo;seven sisters&amp;rsquo; was with the oil giants. &amp;ldquo;Jeff Bezos is like the John D Rockefeller of today,&amp;rdquo; he said. Sorrell noted that the last bunch of &amp;lsquo;seven sisters&amp;rsquo; were regulated and the same might happen to the current &amp;lsquo;seven sisters&amp;rsquo;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Sorrell broadly spoke about the pressures on the agency business and the disruptions that are shaping the market. He said that agencies are mainly suffering because of pressure from clients and not only because of &amp;lsquo;frenemies&amp;rsquo; like Google &amp;amp; Facebook, competition from consulting companies, and in-housing.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Sorrell felt that mergers of legacy agencies with digital agencies like in the case of JWT with Wunderman and VML with Y&amp;amp;R may affect the brand and image of the older and more established agency. &amp;ldquo;JWT is more well-known in India than Wunderman. Now if people call it Wunderman, there could be a problem. I do believe in the strength of the brands and they have value,&amp;rdquo; he said.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;In the face of the large-scale mergers that WPP has initiated over the last few months, Sorrell said that the senior management of a multinational company like WPP should visit other markets. &amp;ldquo;The senior management of WPP has not visited Latam and Asia in the last six months. If you are going to make structural changes that result in losing 7,500 jobs out of the 135,000 jobs you have, there is a responsibility to visit those places and explain the decision.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Prior to his India trip, Sorrell&amp;rsquo;s S4 Capital bought San Francisco ad tech company MightyHive. It was his second acquisition since leaving WPP and setting up S4 Capital. He made his first acquisition in July with a &amp;euro;300m deal to buy Dutch company MediaMonks.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Before Sorrell arrived in Mumbai, he attended the pre-wedding celebrations of Mukesh Ambani&amp;rsquo;s daughter Isha Ambani in Udaipur.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93394-MartinSorrell.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital-news/facebook-and-twitters-public-policy-experts-root-for-addressing-digital-addiction-93361.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>11/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Facebook and Twitter’s public policy experts root for addressing digital addiction</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:10.0pt; margin-left:0cm; text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;While the rise of social media has given us countless benefits, the flip side of it is gradually becoming the new focus area. Issues such as trolls, data safety and digital addiction are being spoken about more vocally than before and social media platforms such as Facebook and Twitter are taking due cognizance to address these concerns.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:10.0pt; margin-left:0cm; text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;At a recent event in New Delhi, Ankhi Das, Public Policy Director, Facebook -India, South &amp;amp; Central Asia; and Mahima Kaul, Head, Public Policy &amp;amp; Government Partnerships, Twitter India; spoke about the issue of &amp;lsquo;digital revolution and social challenges&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:10.0pt; margin-left:0cm; text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Answering a question on the increasing addiction to social platforms like Facebook and the way to deal with it, Ankhi Das said, &amp;ldquo;We are creating a &amp;lsquo;time spent&amp;rsquo; dashboard and it will&amp;nbsp;help to self-regulate.&amp;nbsp; Also I think it is the responsibility of all of us as a society&amp;nbsp;to address it. We have created a network of safety partners and mental health&amp;nbsp;experts,&amp;nbsp;including institutions like Tata Institute of Social Sciences, to tackle it.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:10.0pt; margin-left:0cm; text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Das also spoke about Facebook&amp;rsquo;s thrust on promoting regional languages and reaching out to people beyond the big cities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:10.0pt; margin-left:0cm; text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&amp;ldquo;Facebook has been upgraded to be available in 16 Indian languages. A lot of consumption is happening in the local languages. If you look at the way media is getting consumed, the patterns of consumption are changing in terms of being more visual and more towards video.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:10.0pt; margin-left:0cm; text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;She also spoke about the collapse of information barriers, something that social media platforms like Facebook have enabled.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:10.0pt; margin-left:0cm; text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&amp;ldquo;The way we access information has changed drastically.&amp;nbsp; People, especially youngster students, don&amp;#39;t have barriers to information today,&amp;rdquo; said Das.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:10.0pt; margin-left:0cm; text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Mahima Kaul of Twitter spoke about the correct use of the micro blogging platform and how the government has made it an effective tool to reach out to public at large.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:10.0pt; margin-left:0cm; text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&amp;quot;If you see, the government is using Twitter in the most efficient way. You can find all the ministries on this platform and they share important information through this platform&amp;rdquo;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:10.0pt; margin-left:0cm; text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Answering a question about the rampant issue of trolling and safety on social media platforms, Kaul said, &amp;quot;There are many product features within the platform that can tackle these issues and most of the users don&amp;#39;t know about them. And when they do, it becomes easier to&amp;nbsp;deal with trolls and address other such concerns.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:10.0pt; margin-left:0cm; text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;The event was organised by&amp;nbsp;Jagran Group.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93361-Jagran-event-pic.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital-news/kirthiga-reddy-a-woman-of-many-firsts-93393.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>11/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Kirthiga Reddy, a woman of many firsts</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Kirthiga Reddy, primarily known for her seven-year stint at Facebook India, created headlines when Japanese investment giant Softbank, roped her in as&amp;nbsp;as a partner in its $100 billion Vision Fund. She is the first female investing partner in a team of over 12&amp;nbsp;people who oversee this venture.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Media reports&amp;nbsp;suggest that Rajeev Misra, who heads the Vision Fund, had been working towards hiring more women into his crew, including at the level of managing partners.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Based out of Silicon Valley, her focus will be frontier technologies such as AI, robotics, health, bio engineering, IoT and more. She will be working closely with Deep Nishar, senior managing partner at SoftBank Investment Advisors, who is located in the Bay Area.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Disclosing this development on Facebook, Reddy wrote:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;quot;I look forward to bringing my technical and business expertise &amp;ndash; from both enterprise and consumer technology, in developed and emerging markets &amp;ndash; to the Vision Fund team.&amp;nbsp;Like in other investment firms, the Venture Partner role enables quick integration of new talent from non-investing backgrounds, which is a perfect fit for me&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;SoftBank&amp;#39;s $100 billion Vision Fund has been touted as one of the biggest disruptors of the venture capital business, and has committed to invest close to $65 billion in companies like Uber, WeWork and Didi, say reports.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Reddy is known for several&amp;nbsp;firsts. One of the first employees at Facebook India, she started India operations from scratch, which included expanding userbase, and helped contribute to its global business through ad sales with major tie-ups such as&amp;nbsp;Coca Cola India and Yepme. She served as the Managing Director for India and South Asia market until 2016, following which she relocated to the company&amp;#39;s US headquarters, serving as Managing Global Client Partner and Emerging Markets Lead. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Most importantly, Reddy led Facebook&amp;#39;s global marketing partnership for the Financial Services vertical and also partnered with the company&amp;#39;s strategic global advertisers on their Emerging Markets strategy, with a focus on India, Mexico, Brazil, Indonesia, Middle East and South Africa. She even led financial services vertical for Facebook Global Accounts and advised on global marketing activations including the&amp;nbsp;Olympics. As a result, she has been one of the leading forces behind the company&amp;#39;s expansive growth in the country. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Prior to this development, she also worked with established companies such as Silicon Graphics and Motorola. During her tenure at Silicon Graphics, she was the youngest director of engineering. In 2008, Reddy started working with the US-based Phoenix Technologies where she led a global team located in US, India, Japan, Korea, and Taiwan.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;An alumnus of Stanford University Graduate School of Business, Reddy comes with over 20 years of experience in building high-growth global businesses in roles spanning sales, marketing, operations, product management and engineering.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;In 2011, she became Fortune India&amp;#39;s Top 50 Most Powerful Women and was also featured in Fast Company&amp;rsquo;s 100 Most Creative People in Business 2013. She t&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;opped the list of IMPACT&amp;rsquo;s 50 Most Influential Women list in media, marketing and advertising in 2015.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93344-kirthigaReddy.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital-news/data-richness-makes-india-an-ideal-market-to-experiment-kaushal-karupati-oracle-93299.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>11/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Data richness makes India an ideal market to experiment: Kaushal Kurapati, Oracle</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Technology is enabling a new marketing dynamic which is making the task for marketers more insightful and efficient while also retaining its own set of complexities.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Sharing the impact and correlation between new marketing technology and brand communication, Kaushal Kurapati, Group Vice President Product Management at Oracle strongly believes that marketing technology has heralded a new era for the domain.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Over the years print has given way to TV and TV now holds a big sway of advertising dollars. &amp;nbsp;Also, the advent of performance marketing, internet and smartphones has unleashed new form factors and new ways of targeting consumers. All of this is primarily because technology is driving consumer behaviour to change. Now marketers have to understand this difference in consumer behaviour and be able to target appropriately. &amp;nbsp;Otherwise they will be missing a big opportunity,&amp;rdquo; said Kurapati.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Underling the difference between big data vs. quality data and the need to give precedence to the latter, Kurapati&amp;nbsp;believes that this issue is not unique to the Indian market but a global phenomenon.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I think that struggle is world over and not just in India. If the data going in is noisy then your prediction and your estimation and all of those factors will be bad as well. Smart businesses or smart organisations have to take care while considering data and I think a lot of people miss that point. So, it is not just about the amount of data but also the quality of data that is important.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;When asked to define the most popular technology solutions that brands are seeking from technology providers, Kurapati&amp;nbsp;explained, &amp;ldquo;Many brands would like to monitor what is going on in the social media space and how people are talking about the brand in terms of the positive or negative sentiment.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Also when it comes to mobile apps, they want to understand what happens to the customer journey as they come and navigate the site and also to understand the overall digital foot print,&amp;rdquo; he further added.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;With growing concerns about data privacy and the implementation of General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) in mature data markets, regulatory concerns may pose challenge to big data usage in the coming time.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;When asked to explain the role of technology providers in such a scenario, Kurapati&amp;nbsp;said, &amp;ldquo;GDPR is having a big impact not just in the European context but also technology solutions are getting compliant that way. Big countries like India want data jurisdiction within their borders, it is happening in the payment space, it will happen in the consumer behaviour space too. It is the question of when not if in my view, and it will require some change on part of the technology providers too.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Sharing his thoughts about the future of marketing technology, Kurapati&amp;nbsp;added, &amp;ldquo;We will see a unified data picture because there is still data in silos even in the advanced data markets. &amp;nbsp;Figuring out what to recommend as a product based on what you already purchased would become more strategic.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Explaining the critical role that India is poised to play as the centre of big data, Kurapati&amp;nbsp;said, &amp;ldquo;India over the years has become one of the lowest data rate markets in the world. &amp;nbsp;This has led to a change in the consumer behaviour and an explosion in terms of spending time on the mobile phone. This consumer behaviour change has made India a data rich market, and because of that data richness I think it is quickly becoming an ideal market to experiment and try out different things.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93299-KaushalOracle.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital-news/amazons-aws-and-salesforce-partner-for-secure-data-sharing-between-platforms-93385.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>10/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Amazon’s AWS and Salesforce partner for secure data sharing between platforms</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;According to media reports, Salesforce and Amazon&amp;rsquo;s cloud arm, AWS, have announced that they are offering a new set of data integration services between the two cloud platforms for common customers.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Customers looking to transform digitally are still primarily concerned about security when moving data between cloud vendors said Matt GarmanMatt Garman, Vice President of Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud. &amp;ldquo;Customers talked to us about sensitive data in Salesforce and using deep analytics and data processing on AWS and moving them back and forth in secure way,&amp;rdquo; said Garman.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;In practice, Salesforce customers can set up a direct connection using AWS Private Link to connect directly to private Salesforce APIs and move data from Salesforce to an Amazon service such as Redshift, the company&amp;rsquo;s data warehouse product, without ever exposing the data to the open internet.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Salesforce customers can set up Lambda functions so that when certain conditions are met in Salesforce, it triggers an action such as moving data (or vice versa). This is commonly known as serverless computing and developers are increasingly using event triggers to drive business processes.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, the two companies are integrating more directly with Amazon Connect, the Amazon contact center software it launched in 2017. Salesforce offers its own contact center services with Salesforce Service Cloud. The two companies found a way to help common customers work together here to build what they are calling AI-driven self-service applications using Amazon Connect on the Salesforce mobile Lightning development platform.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;This could involve among other things, building mobile applications that take advantage of Amazon Lex, AWS&amp;rsquo;s bot building application and Salesforce Einstein, Salesforce&amp;rsquo;s artificial intelligence platform. Common customers can download the Amazon Connect CTI Adapter on the Salesforce AppExchange.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Bret Taylor, President and Chief Product Officer at Salesforce said, &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re enabling something that wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have been possible. It&amp;rsquo;s really exciting because it&amp;rsquo;s something unique in the marketplace.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The two companies have been working together for some time. As Garman points out, Heroku, which Salesforce bought in 2010 and Quip, which it bought last year were both built on AWS from the get-go. Salesforce, which mostly runs its own data centers in the US runs most of its public cloud on AWS, especially outside the US Conversely, Amazon uses Salesforce tools internally.&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93385-amazonSalesforce.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital-news/puneet-gupt-as-been-elevated-as-coo-of-times-internet-93376.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>10/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Puneet Gupt as been elevated as COO of Times Internet</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Times Internet announced the elevation of Puneet Gupt as the COO of Times Internet with immediate effect. Gupt has been associated with the Times Group for over ten years and since 2011, he has been head of Times Internet&amp;rsquo;s vast and diverse News business. Under his leadership, the company has been able to reinforce the #1 position of TOI, reach the #1 position in languages and launched products like eTimes, GadgetsNow and NewsPoint to address emerging opportunities.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Gupt has played a critical role in Times Internet&amp;rsquo;s News business registering a stunning 6.5X growth and enabled the company to become the #1 premium digital publisher.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Announcing Gupt&amp;rsquo;s elevation Gautam Sinha, CEO of Times Internet said, &amp;ldquo;Puneet has been an invaluable asset to Times Internet. He is audacious, customer-obsessed and has rich experience in starting, growing and scaling up digital businesses. Puneet will be working closely with me to drive our ambitious growth agenda. He will lead our efforts in making Times Internet the go-to digital destination for every Indian&amp;rsquo;s information, entertainment and transaction needs.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Gupt added, &amp;ldquo;Times Internet is a company that dares you to think big, and empowers you to make your dreams a reality. I look forward to amplify our growth by identifying and building category defining digital products that become the benchmark in quality and value proposition for our customers.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Times Internet partnered with Tencent to invest in Gaana, acquired and re-launched a video OTT platform MX Play, as well as launched popular gaming platforms like BaaziNow &amp;amp; CricPlay. The company&amp;rsquo;s dining out platform, Dineout acquired restaurant management software firm Torqus last month.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;With 40+ digital products, Times Internet reaches 400+ million people every month. Most of its digital products are market leaders across news, sports, music, video and more in India.&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93376-PuneetGupt.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital-news/kotak-securities-partners-with-cogmat-to-support-their-customer-outreach-93373.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>10/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Kotak Securities partners with CogMat to support their customer outreach</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Kotak Securities, one of the leading stockbrokers in India has tied-up with CogMat Digital to capture their audience&amp;rsquo;s responses on multiple digital channels. The teams will be working in tandem to track and analyse Kotak Securities&amp;rsquo; online presence to synchronize the customer service loop thereby, quickening the customer-query resolution process further.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking on the partnership, Jaimit Doshi, Executive Vice President &amp;ndash; Marketing, Products &amp;amp; Customer Service, Kotak Securities said, &amp;ldquo;We, at Kotak Securities believe that along with providing advanced online trading services, listening to our audience and redressal of their concerns and queries in a timely fashion, goes a long way in building a positive connect with them, thus, leading to long-term relationships and trust. With CogMat&amp;rsquo;s expertise in BFSI domain, we are geared-up for tracking and bridging the knowledge/query gap in order to enable us in strengthening our &amp;lsquo;Brand-Consumer&amp;rsquo; connect.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Adding to this, Rohini Joseph, Head of Operations, CogMat said, &amp;ldquo;Consumers today are extensively using digital platforms to connect with brands both for seeking information and for voicing their queries and concerns about the brand. They want to be heard and expect quick resolutions to their inquiries. We are pleased to be onboard with Kotak Securities, and offer our digital expertise and analytical skills to enable its CRM team to gather its consumer feedback and brand perception.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93373-KotakCogmat.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital-news/ipoy-2018-experts-discuss-why-innovation-and-digital-transformation-are-of-essence-93360.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>10/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>IPOY 2018: Experts discuss why innovation and digital transformation are of essence</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;At the recently held&amp;nbsp;Impact Person Of the Year (IPOY) 2018 Award function, a panel comprising Deepak Iyer, Managing Director, Mondelez India; Prasoon Pandey, Director, Corcoise Films; and Rajan Anandan, VP, Southeast Asia and India, Google; discussed &amp;lsquo;future, innovation and digital transformation.&amp;rsquo; The discussion was moderated by &amp;lsquo;Anurag Batra, Chairman &amp;amp; Editor-in-Chief - BW Businessworld.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;Watch the session here and scroll down to read:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/cDjUwZpb8BU" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;Talking about what Mondelez is doing to be future-ready, Iyer shed light on connected devices and getting automated machines to life. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;&amp;ldquo;So we changed our thinking and instead of having chief creative officer, we thought why don&amp;rsquo;t we have digital ambassadors. We started in all places. In the factory, we had all machines digitally integrated. Instead of having 10 people manning one machine, we have one console that can do the job. There are censors in these machines and we&amp;rsquo;ve been able to get lots of data. We have also moved from annual maintenance to predicable maintenance. Today, there is GPS, Google map, big data out there. There isn&amp;rsquo;t just one function but so many. So we haven&amp;rsquo;t cracked it all. It&amp;rsquo;s just the start,&amp;rdquo; exclaimed Iyer.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;Iyer said a team at Mondelez works on what could be the possible disruptions that might hit the industry. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;Pandey spoke about how making a commercial has nothing to do with the medium-- whether one is&amp;nbsp;doing it on digital or not. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;&amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s like a painting. You could paint on canvas, paper or wall. A lot of people ask me, &amp;lsquo;Are you making a digital commercial?&amp;rsquo; And I tell them that I can&amp;rsquo;t understand the question. It&amp;rsquo;s the same commercial which is played on TV, a movie hall. It&amp;rsquo;s a question of who am I talking to.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;Pandey remarked that the main issue is how does one&amp;nbsp;grab audience attention. And this is a creative issue. &amp;ldquo;Here we are involved only with the painting.&amp;rdquo; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;Speaking about data and research, Pandey said, &amp;ldquo;On research, I have very scant respect. World over, tell me one election prediction that got it right?&amp;rdquo; &amp;nbsp;He pointed out that it&amp;rsquo;s all about gut and observations. &amp;ldquo;What I&amp;rsquo;m watching or observing is being depicted in my commercials,&amp;rdquo; he said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;When Anandan was quizzed on his three predictions for future, he said that AI and machine-learning will impact every industry. He gave the example of the first driverless taxi service which has been launched recently. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;&amp;ldquo;It is a true amplification of AI. It goes back to what can machines do better than humans? Machines can now do a lot of things better than humans. Today you can listen to music which has actually been created by a machine. Machine can predict better than an ophthalmologist.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;Apart from the prediction that AI and machine-learning will dramatically impact industries, Anandan shared that the way we think about life is going to change drastically as we go forward.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;&amp;ldquo;As technology is able to produce more food than the world needs, as technology dramatically brings the cost of energy down, what will we do with all the free time? You will start seeing new kinds of social model developing in the world and the way we think about world today will change.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;Addressing the issue of social media&amp;rsquo;s impact and technology players using data, Anandan shared that you can go to My Account at Google and can figure out what data Google has access to and can also wipe it out. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;&amp;ldquo;Being able to give users the ability to control their data is very important. Platforms should take care they don&amp;rsquo;t use data in the way they shouldn&amp;rsquo;t.&amp;rdquo; He also added that Google is working on a concept for segments who spend a lot of their time online, so that they can tell the machine if they want the network or connectivity to shut down after a point of time. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;Anandan said that Google allows people to flag content that is not desirable. It has over 10,000 human reviewers all over to check if it violates any laws. &amp;ldquo;We are trying to make it easier to flag it and are building the infrastructure and capability at Google to review it. We&amp;rsquo;re also training 8,000 journalists how to use technology and write high-quality content.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;When the experts were quizzed on what they would be doing a couple of years from now, Iyer said, &amp;ldquo;I would be selling moments of joy&amp;rdquo;. Pandey exclaimed that he would be creating.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;Anandan&lt;/span&gt; said, &amp;ldquo;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;Ten years from now, every single person and thing will be connected to the Internet. I want to be there.&amp;rdquo; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93360-Panel.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital-news/i-want-to-see-every-indian-on-the-internet-rajan-anandan-google-93366.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>10/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>I want to see every Indian on the Internet: Rajan Anandan, Google</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Rajan Anandan, VP, South East Asia &amp;amp; India, Google is IMPACT Person of the Year 2018 for being a dynamic leader in India&amp;rsquo;s digital ecosystem, accelerating innovation, growing Internet adoption, enabling vernacular language access of the Internet and making &amp;lsquo;Internet for every Indian&amp;rsquo; his mission.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;At Google&amp;rsquo;s headquarters in Gurgaon, Anandan, the company&amp;rsquo;s leader in India and South-east Asia, is affable and charming as he settles in for this interview. Google India is profitable, its many initiatives to help people use the Internet to better their lives are taking off and Anandan&amp;rsquo;s mission &amp;ndash; to get every Indian on the Internet &amp;ndash; has begun in right earnest. Therefore, it is a happy Anandan who talks to us, quick to slip from poking fun at himself to seriously dwelling on life, leadership and lessons learnt.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The first time I used the Internet, I actually didn&amp;rsquo;t know it&amp;hellip;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Working on programming at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology&amp;rsquo;s Athena labs in Cambridge in the early 1990s, the first time I used the Internet, I actually didn&amp;rsquo;t know I was on the Internet! It was before the launch of the commercial Internet as we know it, and it wasn&amp;rsquo;t called &amp;lsquo;the Internet&amp;rsquo; at the time&amp;hellip; that&amp;rsquo;s my earliest recollection. And then when the commercial Internet arrived, Netscape, Yahoo Mail&amp;hellip; I remember buying some books in 1997-98 after Amazon had launched and having them delivered&amp;hellip; it was a magical experience&amp;hellip; how you could order something and get it delivered at your doorstep. It&amp;rsquo;s incredible to see how the Internet has evolved.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As a child, I actually wanted to be a pilot&amp;hellip;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
When I was a child, I actually wanted to be a pilot, and fly planes. In fact, when I was 16, I actually took all the pilot training classes, but I was told afterwards that I was too young to actually take the test for a pilot&amp;rsquo;s licence. So, I lost interest in it and moved on to other things, otherwise I would probably have been flying Jet Airways or something!&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There is no one model of great leadership&amp;hellip;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
There are many different models of great leadership&amp;hellip; no one model... What&amp;rsquo;s important is for everyone to find their authentic style of leadership, instead of trying to copy a style or a model because it&amp;rsquo;s successful&amp;hellip; For me, a few things have been important. One, the ability to have a long term vision, being able to say, &amp;lsquo;This is where we want to go&amp;rsquo;, and &amp;lsquo;This is why we want to go there&amp;rsquo;. Two, being able to build very strong teams&amp;hellip; I think leaders build teams because at the end of the day, that&amp;rsquo;s how you can actually build scale and velocity&amp;hellip; Three, it&amp;rsquo;s very important to communicate clearly and communicate often, and without ambiguity. Four, it&amp;rsquo;s important for leaders to listen, and to be open to feedback, even if it is critical, and then be able to act on that feedback. The best leaders probably speak less and listen more. Five, the ability to quickly absorb data, listen to different points of view and make decisions quickly is very important in this technology era, because if you don&amp;rsquo;t make that decision, something would have happened, and before you know it, you are out of business. Lastly, being humble is very important.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t think I have become a leader yet&amp;hellip;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
I don&amp;rsquo;t think I have become a leader yet, I am still working on it! You become better every day and at some point, may be you become reasonably good. I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t say leadership but I started managing people when I was in my early 20s at McKinsey, where I became an engagement manager. That was the first time where I actually had to convince other people, depend on them to do things collectively and get things done. It was an incredible experience. I learnt how to motivate people, how to inspire them&amp;hellip; I have had this incredible privilege of having worked with truly inspiring leaders that I have learnt a lot from. My view is, you can learn from everybody. And you should also seek out opportunities where you can learn from teams, from leaders&amp;hellip; I am just very fortunate that I started my career at McKinsey with a set of really awesome leaders. Since then too, it&amp;rsquo;s been a journey of learning from other leaders.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Forcing ads on people - that idea&amp;rsquo;s time is gone&amp;hellip;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
It&amp;rsquo;s a very exciting time to be in the advertising and media ecosystem because there is so much change around us. On one hand, consumer behaviour is changing very dramatically and we have on an average 400 million Indians who are spending 3-4 hours a day connected to the Internet. What they are doing online is changing. You have to deeply understand those changes to change your strategies. The new set of digital technologies is much more measurable - the effective ROI that you can get from them is very interesting. Programmatic is fascinating. There are going to be things that machines can do better than people. Machines can buy much more efficiently at scale than many people can. Creating and serving 10,000 creatives instantly across an audience is possible today. Hyper-targeting, hyper-personalization, hyper-efficiency, hyper-creatives at scale, targeted creatives at scale&amp;hellip; it&amp;rsquo;s slowly moving towards this idea of &amp;lsquo;segment of one&amp;rsquo; - please show me an ad that I want to see when I want to see it and let me control whether I want to see it or not. True view is a fantastic format because you decide whether you want to watch the ad or not. I don&amp;rsquo;t watch mainline media anymore because I don&amp;rsquo;t want to watch things I don&amp;rsquo;t want to watch. This idea of forcing ads on people &amp;ndash; it&amp;rsquo;s time has gone.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I resonate with Google&amp;rsquo;s moonshot thinking&amp;hellip;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
I resonate a lot with Google&amp;rsquo;s moonshot thinking&amp;hellip; the idea of 10x thinking. Most companies are trying to improve things 10%, trying to grow 10%, trying to reduce cost by 10% as opposed to 10x. The core belief around moonshot thinking is something that I deeply value, and I have tried to imbibe it in what we do, both personally as a leader, but more importantly in our teams. So, when we launched the &amp;lsquo;Internet Saathi&amp;rsquo; initiative, we said, &amp;lsquo;India has 6,00,000 plus villages. We want to get to 300,000 villages with a physical network of &amp;lsquo;Internet Saathi&amp;rsquo; in three years&amp;rsquo;. We have to remember we are Google, a digital company, and we don&amp;rsquo;t build physical networks of anything. And that we were going to do exactly that, was really a moonshot idea. Over the next year, we will certainly reach that target. We have embarked on many moonshots; some have worked, some have not. Another leadership philosophy is that it&amp;rsquo;s really important to take a risk. I never &amp;lsquo;play it safe&amp;rsquo;. People always remember the things you did well and your big successes. The only person who obsesses about all the other things, all the times you failed, is actually you. So, I don&amp;rsquo;t agonize about failure. I just focus on trying to go for the big wins.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are Google&amp;rsquo;s ambitions in India, and what is on your priority list right now?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Our mission for the last several years has been Internet for every Indian. So, we said this when India only had about 100 million users. Today, we are at 400 million Internet users and we have over almost a billion Indians to go. There are more than 900 million Indians who are not connected to the Internet. So, everything that we are doing in India is focused on how do we get Internet for every Indian. We have developed a very deep understanding of all the challenges and barriers there are to getting Indians online, and we are addressing them.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Recently you identified voice, video and vernacular as the three driving forces of the Indian Internet ecosystem. How has the Internet landscape evolved of late?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
The Indian Internet ecosystem has changed pretty dramatically over the last few years. As we speak, we have 400 million monthly active users on the Internet. One thing that we have observed over the last year or so is that a large number of Internet users who come to the Internet for the very first time are now accessing it primarily through voice. It&amp;rsquo;s a combination of voice technology or voice access getting much easier, both on regular smartphones like Android, and also Jio connected phones. Most people would much rather speak than type. And as computer technology has got very big on voice, that&amp;rsquo;s become the primary access point. Video is really exploding. We have over 250 million active users on YouTube in India. As mobile broadband has become more affordable - a gigabyte of 4G data has gone down from Rs 250 to Rs 25 a month. Video consumption has gone from being very expensive to quite affordable, and that&amp;rsquo;s driven this explosive growth in video. Lastly, local languages - these new Internet users are accessing the Internet and consuming content in local languages, both in video as well as text. So, 100% of new users that are coming on to the Internet today are only proficient in their own Indian languages, be it Hindi, Tamil, Kannada, Bangla or others. So, these are three very interesting trends among the new set of users who are coming online today.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How is the video explosion in India different to what is happening around the world?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
It&amp;rsquo;s different in a couple of interesting ways. First, there is just a lot more consumption of video. About 75% of data consumption on the Internet in India is video, and that&amp;rsquo;s very different to where India was a few years ago. It&amp;rsquo;s been entirely enabled by the affordable broadband revolution in India. The first thing that new Internet users do in India is consume video. India is the world&amp;rsquo;s first &amp;lsquo;video first&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;voice first&amp;rsquo; Internet. I don&amp;rsquo;t think there is a single country in the world where you can get a gigabyte of data for Rs 25. And that&amp;rsquo;s really driven this massive explosion in video.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s predicted that by 2020, India will have more than 600 million people online. What does a connected society of that size and scale mean to you? And what are the opportunities&amp;hellip; what can you expect to make of it?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
We will certainly be at well north of 600 million users by the time we get to the end of 2020. But, even at 600 million, we are still less than half of India. The most important part of this is the consumers who are connected to the Internet. Internet in India is going to enable all users to get access to very high quality basic services to which many Indians today can&amp;rsquo;t get access. For example, if you take education, we don&amp;rsquo;t have enough schools, we certainly will never have enough teachers, enough physical schools to be able to deliver very high quality education. But, with digital, especially with data becoming much more affordable, you can actually develop and deliver very high quality education through online tutorials to hundreds of millions of Indians at scale. For something basic like learning English, India will never be able to build enough centres, or have enough English teachers. If you really want to have 500-600 million Indians proficient in English compared to 200 million today, the only way to do that is through digital. Even in healthcare, India will never have enough hospitals &amp;ndash; but somebody sitting in a small village in Karnataka can get access to the best doctors sitting in Bangalore or for that matter anywhere in the world if they are connected to the Internet. Access to affordable healthcare is going to increase. Internet is going to be an enabler in many ways, beginning to solve some of India&amp;rsquo;s more severe challenges that also become opportunities, especially for Indian start-ups. For brands and marketers, it&amp;rsquo;s already a scale medium with YouTube at 250 million users. Today it&amp;rsquo;s got more reach in urban India than any TV channel. But, it can be very targeted, so you don&amp;rsquo;t have to target all 250 million. You can target basically the 10 million Indians who are going to buy a smartphone next month, and just target them with the messaging that you want. How brands will drive engagement, how they will acquire users as well as how they will support and service and engage after purchase with consumers will change dramatically. There will be an extraordinary opportunity for brands to do things very differently.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;With Google on every smartphone, sometimes users get a feeling that their privacy is invaded. Google knows everything. Is our data safe?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
We take privacy very seriously; consumer privacy and consumer safety are most important for us. Many still don&amp;rsquo;t know that you can actually go to Google and see all the data that Google has on you as a consumer, and we give you the option to delete all that data at the tap of one button. Or you can take the data and import it to wherever you like. One, we want to be very transparent on what data we have on you. Two, we want to be transparent on how we use the data that we have on you. And three, and most important, we want to give you control. You should control the data that any platform has about you, and you should control whether or not you want that platform to have the data and what they use it for.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Can you tell us about some of the non-traditional or regional advertisers that are coming on board? And what are the things that they are doing differently?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
There are 51 million small businesses in India. Only a few of them advertise on any medium today. About 10,000 of them advertise on Television, 1,50,000 advertise on Print. And today 2,00,000 advertise on Digital. So, the real advertising story in India is going to be about how do we get this medium Digital to become the first, probably the only way in which 20-30 million small businesses will advertise, because those advertisers want a medium that is easy, and extraordinarily focused on return on investment. They also want a medium that is very interactive. They want to run an ad now and get a lead in the next 30 minutes as opposed to run an ad now and see brand metrics improve. So, that is one very big story that is evolving in India today. But then, lots of traditional advertisers are doing some very interesting things, especially leveraging YouTube as a platform as well as programmatic.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advertising contributed a huge 69% to Google&amp;#39;s turnover with Google Search ads continuing to be the go-to place for digital advertisers in India. But the digital advertising market in India is still very small. What are the factors preventing it from taking off?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
We&amp;#39;re focused on helping advertisers get the most out of their online spends. There might be any number of reasons why a marketer hasn&amp;#39;t tried digital yet. What we do know is that once marketers give it a go, digital&amp;rsquo;s mix of transparent, measurable results speaks for itself. There is a growing realization that Internet today is not just a marketing channel - it is influencing purchase decisions and marketers are now looking at digital to drive revenue growth. In fact, many auto companies are shifting their marketing spends from Print to online. In 2017- 2018, in categories like Auto and Banking, Financial Services, and Insurance (BFSI), there was even a direct correlation between online research and offline purchase: 20% of sales in a leading auto original equipment manufacturer (OEM) were driven by digital. In fast-moving consumer goods (FMCG) and banking, consumers relied on digital throughout their purchase journeys, leveraging search to discover products and educate themselves before converting online.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93366-RAJAN.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital-news/facebook-ties-up-with-business-standard-for-subscription-programme-93358.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>08/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Facebook ties up with Business Standard for subscription programme</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Social media giant Facebook has tied up with the Business Standard as part of its subscription programme. The announcement was made by Facebook on Friday. Facebook said it had added a total of 28 such partners globally. Business Standard is the only one from India, according to media reports.&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
The development follows Facebook&amp;#39;s&amp;nbsp;announcement last year that it was developing a paywall for subscription publishers to use in &amp;lsquo;Instant Articles&amp;rsquo; with the goal of improving subscriber acquisition from the social media site.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Some of the other publications that Facebook has partnered with include, The Washington Post, The Los Angeles Times and The Boston Globe.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93358-FBBusinessStandard.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital-news/we-have-seen-20-times-growth-in-internet-consumption-rajan-anandan-93353.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>08/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>We have seen 20 times growth in Internet consumption in India: Rajan Anandan</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Rajan Anandan, Vice President, Southeast Asia and India, Google, took home the IMPACT Person of the Year 2018 Award, instituted by the exchange4media group to recognise excellence in the advertising, media and marketing domain. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;He won the award for driving Internet adoption across India, especially in Tier II and Tier III towns, through several initiatives including &amp;lsquo;Navlekha&amp;rsquo;, Google&amp;rsquo;s platform for users in India who are not conversant with English, &amp;lsquo;Internet Saathi&amp;rsquo;, an initiative to bring more rural women online, and the Indian Railways high-speed Wi-Fi project, providing free Wi-Fi to consumers at railway stations across the country. He has also been responsible for accelerating innovation in India and Southeast Asia for Google. Under Anandan&amp;rsquo;s leadership, the company saw its profits increase from Rs 306.6 crore in 2016-17 to Rs 407.2 crore in 2017-18, with a total turnover of Rs 9,337.7 crore.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Watch&amp;nbsp;Anandan&amp;#39;s speech here and scroll down to read:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/0MqQ1LH1fu4" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Commenting on his win, Anandan said the recognition isn&amp;rsquo;t about him but about the incredible Internet users in India.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s very humbling to win this award. I congratulate all the other nominees. But this recognition isn&amp;rsquo;t about me. It&amp;rsquo;s a recognition for the incredible Internet users in India and the recognition of the amazing products that Google has and of the amazing team at Google as well as the ecosystem partners we have been fortunate to work with. From the bottom of my heart, I&amp;rsquo;m truly appreciative of being at Google,&amp;rdquo; he said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Anandan remarked that India is at an interesting time when it comes technology. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&amp;ldquo;When it comes to consumer Internet, what we are seeing in India is unparalleled; something that we haven&amp;rsquo;t seen in the history of Internet. We have witnessed a scale of growth and consumer behaviours that we haven&amp;rsquo;t seen before. And this makes it very exciting. There are 400 million Internet users in India and we&amp;rsquo;re adding 8-10 million Internet users every month. As data is becoming more affordable, all of these users are spending more time online,&amp;quot; he explained.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Anandan shared that the average consumption per user per month has crossed 10 gigabytes. &amp;ldquo;Two and a half years ago, that number was less than one. So we&amp;rsquo;ve seen 20x growth in Internet consumption.&amp;quot; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Shedding light on the emerging Internet user behaviour, he said it is largely being driven by voice. &amp;ldquo;The new Internet user wants to speak to the Internet and doesn&amp;rsquo;t want to type.&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;He revealed that India has the highest online video market in the world and also pointed out how going vernacular is another trend the brand has taken note of. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&amp;ldquo;There are over 300 million online video users with watch time growing rapidly. And users today prefer accessing the Internet in their local language,&amp;rdquo; Anandan added. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Making a case for what Internet is doing for the masses, Anandan spoke about how it is enabling world-class facilities at their fingertips. &amp;ldquo;What excites me the most is what Internet is enabling for the real India. Today, there is an app that uses AI to deliver world-class diagnostics even in the most tiny, remote villages. People can also easily get access to education with many online courses and programmes at their disposal.&amp;rdquo; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Speaking about Internet Saathi, Google&amp;rsquo;s initiative to bridge the online gender divide in India, he said, &amp;ldquo;As we started working on it, we learnt that only 10 per cent Internet users in rural area were women. The digital gender divide in rural India was worst.&amp;rdquo; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Anandan acknowledged that this stemmed from constraints such as no access to smartphones, societal pressure and lack of understanding of what Internet could do for them. Google decide to give them a smartphone and show them how to use the Internet apart from giving them a stipend, he said.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;In the process, they trained over 20 million women. Through this initiative, he shared, Google gathered insights on what these women actually wanted. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&amp;ldquo;They want to get access to education for their families, they want to know how they can make more money and want healthcare of their families. Internet is bringing the best of the world to India and is extra-ordinarily relevant to India,&amp;rdquo; he asserted.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Anandan shared how the power of the Internet converted some of these &amp;#39;internet saathis&amp;#39; into rural entrepreneurs. He highlighted how they didn&amp;rsquo;t know what Internet was able to do for them. But as they learnt how to start a business, they started making 10 times more than what they did earlier. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;He left the audience with an interesting question.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&amp;ldquo;I want you&amp;rsquo;ll to think where would India be when every single Indian will be online?&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93353-rajanfinal.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital-news/facebook-2018-year-in-review-festivals-cricket-and-support-for-kerala-connected-india-93333.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>08/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Facebook 2018 Year In Review: Festivals, Cricket and support for Kerala connected India</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12px;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;Facebook has announced its 2018 Year in Review, highlighting the top ways people came together on the platform to talk about some of the year&amp;#39;s key events with their family and friends. This information combines the top single-day moments throughout the year with the top ways the Facebook community used the platform to come together around these moments.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;span style="font-size:12px;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;The moments that people discussed most in India in 2018 were:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;ul&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12px;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Festivals ruled the roost: &lt;/b&gt;India set Facebook buzzing on festivals in 2018 with Krishna Janmashtami, Eid al-Adha, Thai Pongal, Navratri driving the most conversations on the platform, as Indians took to Facebook to celebrate the biggest of occasions with their friends and family.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12px;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Community Connect: &lt;/b&gt;The community came together on Facebook to lend support and offer help as Kerala was affected by torrential floods. Facebook features such as Safety Check tool, Live, creating Page, and raising funds enabled people to reach to their near and dear ones, seeking help and informing of their safety.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12px;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bereavement: &lt;/b&gt;The demise of Atal Bihari Vajpayee, former Prime Minister of India was a reminder of impact that his leadership had in serving the nation with many Indians expressing their sadness, but also sharing tributes by sharing his poetry and inspiring stories of his life.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12px;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sports bring India together: &lt;/b&gt;Nothing unites India like sport does and 2018 was a year that saw a flurry of high octane, exciting, global sporting events. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&#13;
	&lt;ul style="list-style-type:circle"&gt;&#13;
		&lt;li style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12px;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;Cricket continued to rule to hearts of Indian sports fans on Facebook as it was one of the most popular topics driving conversations on the platform.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
		&lt;li style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12px;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;Millions of Indian football fans also came together to support their favourite teams and players as FIFA Football World Cup 2018 showcased the best in class footballing action and talent to fans worldwide.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
	&lt;/ul&gt;&#13;
	&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-left:36.0pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-left:36.0pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12px;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;Globally the events that were most talked about on FB were: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-left:36.0pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;ul&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12px;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="vertical-align:baseline"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="border: 1pt none windowtext; padding: 0cm;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#333333"&gt;International Women&amp;rsquo;s Day:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color:#141924"&gt;For the second year in a row, International Women&amp;rsquo;s Day on March 8 was the #1 most talked about moment of the year. But in 2018, IWD conversation was about more than the day itself. Women and men around the world discussed a wide range of topics, issues and causes related to women.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12px;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="vertical-align:baseline"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="border: 1pt none windowtext; padding: 0cm;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#333333"&gt;March for Our Lives:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color:#141924"&gt;&amp;nbsp;Survivors of the violence in Parkland, Florida announced the March for Our Lives movement on February 18, which drove conversation and action around the world. Over the next month, more than 1 million people showed interest in attending a Facebook Event for March for Our Lives, and more than $2.5 million was raised through Facebook Fundraisers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12px;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="vertical-align:baseline"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="border: 1pt none windowtext; padding: 0cm;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#333333"&gt;Civic Engagement:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color:#141924"&gt;The Brazilian Presidential Election on October 7 and the US Midterm Elections on November 6 were top moments for conversation about voting and elections.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12px;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="vertical-align:baseline"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="border: 1pt none windowtext; padding: 0cm;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#333333"&gt;World Cup:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color:#141924"&gt;More than 383 million soccer fans from around the world took to Facebook to cheer on their favorite teams through 2.3 billion posts, comments, reactions and shares. France&amp;rsquo;s World Cup victory on July 15 and England&amp;rsquo;s Semi-Final match against Croatia on July 11 were two of the top most-discussed moments of the year.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12px;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="vertical-align:baseline"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="border: 1pt none windowtext; padding: 0cm;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#333333"&gt;Super Bowl 52:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color:#141924"&gt;&amp;nbsp;The Philadelphia Eagles secured their first Super Bowl win against the New England Patriots on February 4. More than 62 million people turned to Facebook following Tom Brady&amp;rsquo;s incomplete Hail Mary pass at the end of the game, and Justin Timberlake&amp;rsquo;s halftime performance paying tribute to Prince.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12px;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="vertical-align:baseline"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="border: 1pt none windowtext; padding: 0cm;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#333333"&gt;The Royal Wedding:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color:#141924"&gt;&amp;nbsp;The much-anticipated nuptials between Prince Harry and Meghan Markle on May 19 connected 42 million people on Facebook who about posted about the ceremony, the newlyweds, and the pomp and circumstance.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12px;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="vertical-align:baseline"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="border: 1pt none windowtext; padding: 0cm;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#333333"&gt;Nelson Mandela 100:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color:#141924"&gt;&amp;nbsp;July 18 marked 100 years since Nelson Mandela was born, and millions of people came to Facebook to celebrate Mandela&amp;rsquo;s life of dedication to human rights and social justice.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12px;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="vertical-align:baseline"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="border: 1pt none windowtext; padding: 0cm;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#333333"&gt;Keeping Legacies Alive:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="color:#141924"&gt;&amp;nbsp;The world lost many influential and inspirational people in 2018. From musical icons Aretha Franklin, Avicii, and Dolores O&amp;rsquo;Riordan of The Cranberries, to scientific visionaries like Stephen Hawking, influential storytellers like Anthony Bourdain and Hollywood stars like Burt Reynolds. People around the world shared millions of posts on Facebook to memorialize the global impact and work of these individuals.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12px;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;The top moments of this year&amp;#39;s Year In Review were determined by gathering a list of the top keywords by volume mentioned in a single day on Facebook between January 1 and November 11, 2018. To identify which topics were unique to 2018, Facebook compared these keywords to the previous year&amp;#39;s maximum single-day volume. This means that keywords like Mother&amp;#39;s Day and Halloween, which typically represent the top moments every year, do not repeatedly appear at the top of the list.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0px; text-align:start; -webkit-text-stroke-width:0px"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93333-yearender.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital-news/rajan-anandan-wins-impact-person-of-the-year-2018-award-93332.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>07/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Rajan Anandan wins IMPACT Person of the Year, 2018 Award</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Rajan Anandan, Vice President, Southeast Asia and India, Google has won the &amp;nbsp;IMPACT Person of the Year, 2018 Award, instituted by the exchange4media Group to recognize excellence in the Advertising, Media and Marketing domain. He wins the award for driving Internet adoption across India, especially in Tier II and Tier III towns, through several initiatives including &amp;lsquo;Navlekha&amp;rsquo;, Google&amp;rsquo;s platform for users in India who are not conversant with English, Google &amp;lsquo;Internet Saathi&amp;rsquo;, an initiative to bring more rural women online, and the Indian Railways high-speed Wi-Fi project, providing free Wi-Fi to consumers at railway stations across the country. He has also been responsible for accelerating innovation in India and Southeast Asia for Google. Under Anandan&amp;rsquo;s leadership, the company saw its profits increase from Rs 306.6 crore in 2016-17 to Rs 407.2 crore in 2017-18, with total turnover of Rs 9337.7 crore.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;On winning the IPOY Award, Rajan Anandan, Vice President, Southeast Asia and India, Google said, &amp;ldquo;I am truly honoured that I have been given this award. In fact, I am thrilled and speechless. So, thank you to the jury, to IMPACT and also to everybody in the ecosystem; most importantly my team, as well as all our clients and our partners.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the IMPACT Person of the Year 2018, Annurag Batra, Chairman and Editor-in-Chief of the exchange4media Group, said, &amp;ldquo;Rajan Anandan is the scale man, always thinking big and executing big. Global MNCs have strong tailwinds. Yet for building a Rs 10,000 crore revenue company in India, leading it well with continuity, supporting the right causes, navigating the regulatory environment well, creating and nurturing an ecosystem of entrepreneurs, being the go-to man for digital and entrepreneurship in India, Rajan Anandan is richly deserving of the IMPACT Person of the Year award.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The other nominees&amp;nbsp;for the award this year were Naveen Tewari, Founder and CEO, InMobi who led the Bangalore-based ad tech major to become India&amp;rsquo;s second most profitable unicorn in 2017, making an impressive entry into the digital advertising club; Nadia Chauhan, Joint MD &amp;amp; CMO, Parle Agro who revamped popular brands, Frooti and Appy Fizz and led the company to report a turnover of Rs 2,800 crore in the Rs 4,500 fruit drink category last fiscal; Sanjay Gupta, Managing Director, Star India who was responsible for Star India winning the telecast rights for IPL last year and scripting Hotstar&amp;rsquo;s success story, and under whose leadership the company has grown over three times in revenue; Deepak Iyer, Managing Director, Mondelez India who has led the company to consistently report double-digit revenue growth for four straight quarters, while growing Mondelez India&amp;rsquo;s rural business significantly; Ritesh Agarwal, Founder, Oyo, a 24-year-old college dropout who, by virtue of turning Oyo into a $5 billion company with plans to become the largest hotel chain in China, has turned his dream into reality; Sanjiv Mehta, Chairman &amp;amp; MD, Hindustan Unilever Limited (HUL), a visionary leader under whose leadership HUL&amp;rsquo;s market capitalization has overtaken ITC&amp;rsquo;s for the first time in 13 years, while also surpassing FMCG disruptor Patanjali Ayurved with steady double-digit growth in the last three quarters; Piyush Pandey, Executive Chairman and Creative Director, Ogilvy South Asia (now Global CCO, Ogilvy) and Prasoon Pandey, Director, Corcoise Films, the brothers who made the Indian advertising industry shine on the global map by becoming the first Asians to win the prestigious Lion of Saint Mark this year, the highest honour bestowed by the Cannes Lions International Festival of Creativity; and Sriharsha Majeti, Rahul Jaimini, Nandan Reddy, Co-founders, Swiggy, who together led the food delivery platform to become one of the fastest entrants into the billion dollar club of start-ups, making good on their promise of &amp;lsquo;changing the way India eats&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Past winners of the IPOY award &amp;ndash; now in its 14th year - include Baba Ramdev of Patanjali Ayurved, Vijay Shekhar Sharma, Founder and CEO of Paytm, Arnab Goswami, then President &amp;amp; Editor-in-Chief, Times Now and ET Now, Punit Goenka, MD &amp;amp; CEO, Zee Entertainment Enterprises Ltd; Vineet Jain, MD, Times Group; Ambika Soni, then Minister for Information &amp;amp; Broadcasting; Agnello Dias, Founder, Taproot India, Haresh Chawla, then Group CEO, Network18 and Viacom18; Uday Shankar, CEO, Star India; Raghav Bahl, Founder, Network18 and Rajdeep Sardesai, then Editor-in-Chief, CNN-IBN.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The IMPACT Person of the Year 2018 award was presented by Colors and exclusively powered by Zee News, with Nickelodeon, 9X Jalwa, Shemaroo Entertainment and Republic TV as co-gold partners, empowered by Colors Infinity, with Sakal Media Group and Discovery as associate partners and Radio City and BTVI as co-partners.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93332-awards.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital-news/google-india-hosts-partners-summit-in-mumbai-93346.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>07/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Google India hosts Partners Summit in Mumbai</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;At the second edition of the Google India Partners Summit, experts shared insights on how technology and digital creativity are changing the media and advertising landscape and creating new opportunities for agencies to grow their business.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Themed on &amp;lsquo;Agency of the Future&amp;rsquo;, the Google India Partners Summit centered around four sessions, that covered media and advertising industry trends, and how advertising agencies will need to adapt to be future ready. &amp;lsquo;Building Tech Capabilities&amp;rsquo; discussed how embracing automation and improvements in technology can drive better client and customer results.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;lsquo;Breakthrough the clutter with storytelling&amp;rsquo;, talked about reaching the right audience through the right formats and rethinking creative approach moving from traditional to emerging story arcs.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;lsquo;Building the right team&amp;rsquo; brought in former Indian cricket captain, Sourav Ganguly, to share insights into developing a great team that can compete internationally and understands the key principle around attracting and retaining top talent.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking on the sidelines, Shalini Girish, Director - Google Marketing Solution, Google India said, &amp;ldquo;The consumer landscape is evolving rapidly, and the advertising industry must adapt quickly to continue delivering value to brands. Through the Partners Summit, we want to enable our partners to be future ready and rethink their approach for a digital-first world. Together with our agency partners, we want to create better opportunities for brands to understand customer journey, predict marketing outcomes and personalise the customer experience.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93346-Google.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital-news/youtube-2018-hyundais-celebrating-20-years-of-brilliant-moments-most-watched-ad-93315.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>07/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>YouTube 2018: Hyundai’s ‘Celebrating 20 years of brilliant moments’ most watched ad</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Wrapping up the year 2018, YouTube on Thursday released its annual ads leaderboard for India. The YouTube Ads Leaderboard captures ads that receive the maximum views, shares, and love from audiences across India.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;This year, India truly became a &amp;lsquo;video-first&amp;rsquo; country with YouTube reaching over 245 million monthly active users, the company said in a statement. Brands capitalised on YouTube&amp;rsquo;s popularity by creating engaging ads that people truly loved. Cumulatively, the following 10 ads have clocked an incredible 18 million hours of watch time, 88 per cent of which came from mobile devices.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Building on the trend of emotional storytelling, the top two ads are themed on bonds between family and friends. Topping the charts this year is Hyundai&amp;rsquo;s 20 years of Brilliant Moments ad, focusing on family bonds and moments that are treasured for a lifetime; followed by Samsung&amp;rsquo;s #voiceforever campaign themed on their first personalized AI voice assistant can help Motor Neuron Disease patients. Together, these ads have clocked 423 million views.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s the list of most watched ads on YouTube this year:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;1.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Hyundai: Celebrating 20 Years of Brilliant Moments&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/qSZ4h7YSGnQ" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;2.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Samsung India: Samsung Bixby Voice Assistant-MND mother helps daughter with &amp;nbsp;#VoiceForever&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/5OhJ00an0mI" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;3.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Indiabulls Dhani: Get Phone se loan in 3 simple steps directly in your bank account&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/M5PiclN3GX4" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;4.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Honda 2 Wheelers India: Honda New Corporate TVC&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/_veGecgvKEM" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;5. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Garnier India: Makeup off in 1 swipe with Garnier Micellar Water&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/wm9qCYJjfzI" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;6. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Tata Motors: Reach For A Dream; #ChaseTheSupermoon&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/kavGRDS8N1M" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;7. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Kwality Wall&amp;#39;s: New Kwality Wall&amp;rsquo;s Family Packs&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/s7dbKEMNxLQ" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;8. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Apple India: #8 iPhone &amp;mdash; Unlock &amp;mdash; Apple&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/qp4n8OFrjto" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;9. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Uber India: #MoveForward with Uber - Badhte Chalein Feat. Virat Kohli&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/z5rtC1YgdQg" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;10. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; OPPO India: OPPO F7 - Real Support Makes Real Hero&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/M04wOhEXYhs" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93315-yearender.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital-news/zee5-strengthens-presence-in-apac-mena-and-africa-partners-with-zeasn-93335.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>07/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>ZEE5 strengthens presence in APAC, MENA and Africa; partners with Zeasn</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;Close on the heels of its global launch, ZEE5, Zee Entertainment Enterprises Ltd&amp;rsquo;s digital entertainment platform today announced a key strategic alliance with Zeasn, the leading home digital entertainment service provider. The partnership will make ZEE5 available on millions of Zeasn devices across Asia, the Middle East and Africa.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&amp;ldquo;Asia, Middle East and Africa are among the fastest growing markets in the world for online entertainment content and are key markets for us, given the huge South Asian diaspora, and the universal love for Bollywood content even among the locals there. By enabling over 2.5 million Zeasn users to access our unparalleled content library, this partnership further underscores our commitment to bring the best of language entertainment to viewers across devices of their choice,&amp;rdquo; said &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/ArchanaAnand_?lang=en" rel="nofollow" style="color:#0563c1; text-decoration:underline"&gt;Archana Anand, Chief Business Officer &amp;ndash; ZEE5 Global&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="MsoHyperlink" style="color:#0563c1"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration:underline"&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;div style="border-bottom:solid windowtext 1.0pt; padding:0cm 0cm 1.0pt 0cm"&gt;&#13;
&lt;p style="border:none; text-align:justify; padding:0cm; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&amp;ldquo;Bollywood content has a large number of fans around the world and it is a very important part of the world&amp;#39;s cultural treasure. The strategy partnership will enable the consumers to enjoy wonderful Bollywood content efficiently on their smart TV devices, that will greatly help enrich the content of family digital entertainment system,&amp;rdquo; said Jason He, Chief Executive Officer &amp;ndash; Zeasn.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="border:none; text-align:justify; padding:0cm; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;Available across 190+ countries globally, ZEE5 offers multi-genre and multi-lingual content across English, Tamil, Hindi, Malayalam, Telugu, Kannada, Marathi, Bengali, Oriya, Bhojpuri, Gujarati and Punjabi. ZEE5 comes packed with 1,00,000 hours of On Demand content, including Movies and TV Shows, Music, and Health and Lifestyle videos along with a slew of Originals, across 12 languages. It also has an extensive Live TV offering with 60+ popular Live TV channels.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="border:none; text-align:justify; padding:0cm; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;With over 2.5 million Zeasn connected device users now being able to watch ZEE5 across any screen of their choice, this partnership further strengthens ZEE5&amp;rsquo;s international reach, while giving Zeasn users access to the largest library of over 1,00,000 hours of language content across genres. Over the next year, the ZEE5 app will be made available on all Zeasn enabled devices, offering Whale Eco consumers access to ZEE5&amp;rsquo;s premium content.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;/div&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93335-zeasn-zee5.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital-news/lack-of-revenue-models-deterrent-to-growth-of-streaming-platforms-experts-93323.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>07/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Lack of revenue models deterrent to growth of streaming platforms: Experts</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;At the ongoing 7th CII Big Picture Summit in New Delhi, a panel discussion on &amp;lsquo;Game Changers in Media and Entertainment (M&amp;amp;E) Landscape&amp;rsquo; saw experts debating about challenges and opportunities that are shaping the M&amp;amp;E sector.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking about the rise of streaming platforms and their growing relevance, Karan Anshuman, Director of Web Series, Mirzapur said, &amp;quot;There are several reasons and several factors&amp;nbsp;that are at play over here.&amp;nbsp;One of the reasons could be the medium itself, such as the rise of the short format&amp;nbsp;online. Also, you see some of the best talent in writing, directing and acting&amp;nbsp;gravitating towards&amp;nbsp;television and streaming shows.&amp;quot; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Sharing that streaming platforms offer more ground for experimentation and that has become its biggest force multiplier, Anshuman added, &amp;quot;Everyone is trying to crack the formula when it comes to films,&amp;nbsp;over here (online)&amp;nbsp;there isn&amp;#39;t any&amp;nbsp;fixed notion of what works or what does not work,&amp;nbsp;so one can be a lot more experimental&amp;nbsp;with what one is doing.&amp;nbsp;This is also giving voice to the bunch of new&amp;nbsp;generation of writers and filmmakers who&amp;nbsp;want to express themselves.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the rise of streaming content platforms and whether it was forcing big filmmakers to rethink about their business model, Shobu Yarlagadda, Producer of the iconic Baahubali franchise said, &amp;quot;The big-budget films&amp;nbsp;will dominate the theatre market.&amp;nbsp; For people to go to&amp;nbsp;theatres,&amp;nbsp;they need big films like Baahubali&amp;nbsp;which can be enjoyed in theatres. But romcoms,&amp;nbsp;dramas, and slice-of-life films are meant for more intimate viewing and can be enjoyed&amp;nbsp;as a personal experience.&amp;nbsp;So they are more conducive to the streaming services&amp;nbsp;and online platforms.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;There is going to be segmentation of what kind of content is going to be placed where. The big ticket events will go to the big screens.&amp;nbsp; Also, we don&amp;#39;t have enough screens in India and for the rural population the easiest option will be mobile phones,&amp;rdquo; he added.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;According to Neeraj Roy, MD Hungama Digital, streaming consumption will continue to grow since traditional entertainment platforms have an inherent content overlap. &amp;quot;If you look at television,&amp;nbsp;it is not that we have a shortage of channels,&amp;nbsp;we have almost 950 channels,&amp;nbsp;but when you look at the programming that is being done,&amp;nbsp;there is almost 80 per cent overlap.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;In the last two years, we have seen 1500 per cent increase&amp;nbsp;in streaming consumption and it is set to grow further.&amp;quot; When asked if there are there enough revenue models to justify the growing number of streaming platforms, Hiren Gada, CEO, Shemaroo Entertainment said, &amp;quot;At this point, the real challenge that digital is facing is the monetization model,&amp;nbsp;because the base is not yet big enough for big bucks from advertising to kick in. The paid ecosystem on top of that is below one per cent&amp;nbsp;from what we hear see and understand.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Television is a very high-value service&amp;nbsp;because for 300 rupees you get 400 channels&amp;nbsp;and India is a very value-conscious market,&amp;nbsp;so that is why TV is a&amp;nbsp;deterrent for the digital ecosystem&amp;nbsp;to grow,&amp;rdquo; he added.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93323-OTTpanel.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital-news/digital-revenue-moving-much-slower-than-eyeballs-in-india-bcg-cii-report-2018-93325.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>07/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Digital revenue moving much slower than eyeballs in India: BCG CII Report 2018</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt; text-align:start; -webkit-text-stroke-width:0px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;&lt;span style="font-style:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-ligatures:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-caps:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight:400"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="orphans:2"&gt;&lt;span style="text-transform:none"&gt;&lt;span style="white-space:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="widows:2"&gt;&lt;span style="word-spacing:0px"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:#ffffff"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-style:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-color:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:15.5467px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri, sans-serif"&gt;Digital revenue is moving at a much slower pace than eyeballs in India, as observed by the BCG-CII report titled &amp;lsquo;One Consumer, Many Interactions.&amp;rsquo; As shown in the diagram below, digital video comprises merely 8&amp;nbsp;per cent of total ad revenue as against 92 per cent of TV video in India. Digital video consumption takes around 18 per cent compared to TV&amp;rsquo;s 82 per cent.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt; text-align:start; -webkit-text-stroke-width:0px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;&lt;span style="font-style:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-ligatures:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-caps:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight:400"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="orphans:2"&gt;&lt;span style="text-transform:none"&gt;&lt;span style="white-space:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="widows:2"&gt;&lt;span style="word-spacing:0px"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:#ffffff"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-style:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-color:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:15.5467px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri, sans-serif"&gt;UK has the highest per cent of dollars moving into digital as it takes 27 per cent of the ad revenue. It levels up with digital video consumption, which is at 28 per cent. China follows UK where digital video consumes up to 20 per cent of ad revenue as against 80 per cent of TV&amp;rsquo;s.&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;img height="248" src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/bcg-digital-dollar.jpg" width="600" /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt; text-align:start; -webkit-text-stroke-width:0px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;&lt;span style="font-style:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-ligatures:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-caps:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight:400"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="orphans:2"&gt;&lt;span style="text-transform:none"&gt;&lt;span style="white-space:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="widows:2"&gt;&lt;span style="word-spacing:0px"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:#ffffff"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-style:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-color:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:15.5467px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri, sans-serif"&gt;Even though digital media is currently the big thing, there are real questions about making the media portfolio work as pointed out by the report. It said, &amp;ldquo;While on one side digital offers a solution-based approach, new ideation, sharper targeting and return metrics, on the other side there are unanswered questions around measurement of ROI and impact, and rethinking multi-platform advertising strategies. This is one of the reasons why monetization of digital media has been a challenge and dollars have moved slower than eyeballs.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt; text-align:start; -webkit-text-stroke-width:0px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;&lt;span style="font-style:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-ligatures:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-caps:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight:400"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="orphans:2"&gt;&lt;span style="text-transform:none"&gt;&lt;span style="white-space:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="widows:2"&gt;&lt;span style="word-spacing:0px"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:#ffffff"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-style:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-color:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:15.5467px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri, sans-serif"&gt;On metrics the common complaint is they are self-reported and there&amp;rsquo;s no independent trustworthy third party. Then there&amp;rsquo;s also the problem of brand safety. Measurement is another issue (difference between view for three and five second).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt; text-align:start; -webkit-text-stroke-width:0px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;&lt;span style="font-style:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-ligatures:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-caps:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight:400"&gt;&lt;span style="letter-spacing:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="orphans:2"&gt;&lt;span style="text-transform:none"&gt;&lt;span style="white-space:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="widows:2"&gt;&lt;span style="word-spacing:0px"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color:#ffffff"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-style:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-color:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:15.5467px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri, sans-serif"&gt;What marketers really want is a converged offer that is anchored cross platform and brings in sharper targeting as well ideation and storytelling. The media houses of the future will need to create this converged offer bringing in personas, higher attribution and weaving in narratives and content native to the platform across advertising.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93325-main-bcg.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital-news/facebook-accused-of-using-peoples-data-to-favour-certain-partners-93305.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>06/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Facebook accused of using people’s data to favour certain partners</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Facebook has been accused of using user data to favour certain partners by giving them access to its platform while cutting off others. This was claimed by a British parliamentary committee that is investigating online misinformation, according to media reports.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The reports claim that the committee released internal Facebook emails and other documents to establish the charge. The documents pertains to the period from 2012 to 2015.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The documents reportedly show that Facebook treated data as the company&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;most valuable resource&amp;rdquo; and used it for its advantage. It has been claimed that Chief Executive Officer Mark Zuckerberg and Chief Operating Officer Sheryl Sandberg were involved in such decisions.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The release of the internal documents will add to Facebook&amp;rsquo;s woes. The social media giant is already grappling with issues of privacy and spread of misinformation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Facebook, meanwhile, issued a statement, saying that the documents had been selectively chosen to be embarrassing and misleading as part of a &amp;ldquo;baseless&amp;rdquo; lawsuit.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Like any business, we had many internal conversations about the various ways we could build a sustainable business model for our platform,&amp;rdquo; media reports quoted the company as saying. &amp;ldquo;But the facts are clear: We&amp;rsquo;ve never sold people&amp;rsquo;s data.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Zuckerberg posted his response on Facebook, saying the company had limited its access to certain apps and made other changes to prevent abuse of its platform.&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/92451-Facebook-Logobig.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital-news/our-motive-is-to-provide-localised-user-experience-raj-mishra-tiktok-93296.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>06/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Our motive is to provide localised user experience: Raj Mishra, TikTok</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;TikTok is a short video sharing app where users can watch and create quick videos. Earlier this year, popular sister app Musical.ly was merged to it. Founded in 2012, TikTok is one of the country&amp;rsquo;s fastest-growing tech start-ups and is known for its use of algorithms and artificial intelligence to select videos and other features.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;In an interview with exchange4media, Raj Mishra, Business Head, TikTok India, spoke about the app, how the brand keeps its creators engaged, product innovations and more.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Edited Excerpts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How is TikTok planning to strengthen its leadership position in India?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Our mission is to capture and present creativity, knowledge and moments that matter. TikTok enables everyone to be a creator and encourages users to share their passion and creative expression through their videos.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;What enhances the experience is TikTok&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;For You&amp;rsquo; feed. It offers personalised recommendations to users according to their viewing preferences. The content is curated in a way that instead of serving up videos from only the popular users on the platform, users also get recommendations of video content shared by regular users of the app. With this feature, TikTok is enabling more users to find success in being a creator on the platform and reaching new, global audience.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why was Musical.ly merged to TikTok when it was already popular among audience?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Through TikTok, we want to capture the world&amp;rsquo;s creativity and knowledge and remind everyone to treasure every precious life moment. Combining musical.ly and TikTok was a natural fit, given the shared mission of both the experiences. TikTok not only ensures that the content shared is localised, based on the users viewing patterns and interest, but at the same time allows all users to showcase their talent in front of a larger, global audience.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is the core business model of TikTok? Are you majorly dependent on monetization? If yes, then how are you looking to strengthen it?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Currently our focus is on making our app better than before and creating engaging content for our users. We want to continuously provide fresh, novel features on TikTok and ensure that our users have an excellent in-app experience.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How are artificial intelligence and machine learning helping you in sorting content according to consumer demand? Any plans to come up with new product innovations?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
TikTok incorporates artificial intelligence (AI) technology that has global applications and provides unique in-app features, thus allowing users to enjoy unique and personalised experiences.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;AI technology enables video and image recognitions. Users can make short format videos within minutes, and share them with their friends and fans on the app. At TikTok, our advanced machine learning algorithms are constantly optimising and personalising content feeds for our users. This allows us to customize content feeds based on individual preferences and deliver new content based on topics and trends users find most interesting. We are working on enhancing the user experience further and to innovate ourselves to ensure we stay relevant.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TikTok is one of the most downloaded apps of 2018, but internet security experts warn that it is not appropriate for young users. What are you doing to change this notion, as it can seriously affect the business of the brand?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Apart from ensuring best user experience, privacy and protection are of utmost importance to us. We are committed to maintaining a safe in-app atmosphere for our vibrant and creative user community. We have recently launched a new safety centre and have robust community guidelines in place which provide tips and resources to help users navigate through a range of topics and build a safe online experience.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Overall, our priority is to promote a positive environment that allows our users to showcase their talent on a global platform. We have also implemented a moderation technology based on an algorithm and a robust human team. The moderation team, based on the expansive community guidelines, ensures the digital wellbeing of our users.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How do you consider India as a market in terms of business and how much of your content is localised for Indian audience?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;India is an important market for us, given the presence of a vibrant user base. In addition to TikTok being a global platform, we are dedicated to bringing in the localised user experience regardless of which market we operate in.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Our localisation strategy helps us in encouraging users to create relevant and local content along with incorporating global trends in localized flavour. Our operations team is in sync with the market needs to ensure that TikTok provides the best community support for creativity and discovery for our local users.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;As part of our journey to discover and provide a platform to showcase creativity, we are continuously working towards improving the user experience and delivering a more diverse and compelling content.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93296-TikTok.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital-news/2018-twitter-moments-sunil-chhetris-plea-for-football-support-most-retweeted-tweet-93290.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>05/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>2018 Twitter moments: Sunil Chhetri’s plea for football support most retweeted tweet</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;In 2018, people on Twitter connected, campaigned, learned, debated, and had conversations. They came to share opinions and see other points of view. From &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23MeToo&amp;amp;src=typd"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#MeToo&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt; to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23Sarkar&amp;amp;src=tyah"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#Sarkar&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23IPL&amp;amp;src=typd"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#IPL&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;, state elections, and everyday interests, Indians flocked to Twitter to find out what&amp;rsquo;s happening in the world and to talk about it. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;As the year comes to a close, Twitter has issued &lt;span style="background:white"&gt;lists of the topics and accounts tweeted about the most in the worlds of TV, politics, sports, entertainment, music and social movements in India&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;The Golden Tweets: Most Retweeted and Most Liked &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Indian football team skipper Sunil Chhetri (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/chetrisunil11"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;@chetrisunil11&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;) &lt;span style="background:white"&gt;had an eventful 2018. &lt;/span&gt;His appeal to football fans across the country asking them to fill the stadiums in for the Intercontinental Cup 2018 tugged at heartstrings as citizens united to support the home team and earned him the &lt;span style="background:white"&gt;most Retweeted Tweet of the year for 2018. The video Tweet from &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/chetrisunil11"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;@chetrisunil11&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt; has been Retweeted almost 60K times: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-lang="en-gb"&gt;&#13;
&lt;p dir="ltr" lang="en"&gt;This is nothing but a small plea from me to you. Take out a little time and give me a listen. &lt;a href="https://t.co/fcOA3qPH8i"&gt;pic.twitter.com/fcOA3qPH8i&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&amp;mdash; Sunil Chhetri (@chetrisunil11) &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/chetrisunil11/status/1002892448513679361?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;2 June 2018&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#13;
&lt;script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:#fefefe"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Virat Kohli&amp;#39;s (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/imVkohli"&gt;&lt;span style="background:#fefefe"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;@imVkohli&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:#fefefe"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;) Tweet featuring a picture with Anushka Sharma (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/AnushkaSharma"&gt;&lt;span style="background:#fefefe"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;@AnushkaSharma&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:#fefefe"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;) on the occasion of &lt;i&gt;Karvachauth, &lt;/i&gt;quite literally won hearts on Twitter. With over 215K Likes, the Tweet showcasing the celebrity couple in ethnic wear emerged as the Most Liked Tweet of 2018*.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-cards="hidden" data-lang="en-gb"&gt;&#13;
&lt;p dir="ltr" lang="en"&gt;My life. My universe. ❤❤ Karvachauth ❤? &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/AnushkaSharma?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;@AnushkaSharma&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://t.co/a2v18dh8rH"&gt;pic.twitter.com/a2v18dh8rH&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&amp;mdash; Virat Kohli (@imVkohli) &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/imVkohli/status/1056235319685722112?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;27 October 2018&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#13;
&lt;script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Top 10 hashtags in India in 2018*&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Tweets and hashtags connect people across the world during key moments in news, politics, entertainment, music and sport. They share joy, humour, news, ideas and opinions about the biggest conversations in real time. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;In 2018, regional entertainment conversations expanded and generated massive engagement on Twitter in India. South Indian films &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23Sarkar&amp;amp;src=typd"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#Sarkar&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23viswasam&amp;amp;src=typd"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#Viswasam&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23BharatAneNenu&amp;amp;src=typd"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#BharatAneNenu&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23Aravindhasametha&amp;amp;src=typd"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#AravindhaSametha&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23Rangasthalam%20&amp;amp;src=typd"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#Rangasthalam&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23Kaala&amp;amp;src=tyah"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#Kaala&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt; and TV show &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23BiggBossTelugu2&amp;amp;src=typd"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#BiggBossTelugu2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt; clinched 7 of the top 10 hashtags this year. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Beyond entertainment, the return of Chennai Super Kings with &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?src=typd&amp;amp;q=%23WhistlePodu"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#WhistlePodu&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt; and the emergence of &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23MeToo&amp;amp;src=typd"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#MeToo&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt; in India added to the top hashtag trends. &lt;span style="background:white"&gt;Here are the 10 biggest hashtags in India on Twitter in 2018:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/Twitter1.jpg" style="width: 450px; height: 253px;" /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;1. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23Sarkar&amp;amp;src=typd"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#Sarkar&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Released in 2018, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23Sarkar&amp;amp;src=typd"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#Sarkar&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt; the Tamil film starring Thalapathy Vijay &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/actorvijay"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;@actorvijay&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;) has been making massive gains worldwide, winning the appreciation of fans on Twitter. Underlined by a political theme, the buzz around the movie was further amplified with audiences taking to Twitter to express their opinions, and making &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23Sarkar&amp;amp;src=typd"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#Sarkar&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt; the top hashtag trend of 2018.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;2. &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23Viswasam&amp;amp;src=tyah"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#Viswasam&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Viswasam, the upcoming 2019 Tamil action film featuring Ajith Kumar in a dual role, has started making waves on Twitter. The unveiling of the first look of the film led to the industry and fans Tweeting their excitement, enabling &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23Viswasam&amp;amp;src=tyah"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#Viswasam&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt; to emerge as a top hashtag on Twitter in anticipation of its launch.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;3. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23BharatAneNenu&amp;amp;src=typd"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#BharatAneNenu&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;The Telugu blockbuster Bharat Ane Nenu was released in 2018 and became one of the biggest hits in the lead actor Mahesh Babu&amp;#39;s (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/urstrulyMahesh"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;@urstrulyMahesh&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;) career so far. The film received positive reviews from the audience and critics, with fans taking to Twitter to celebrate its success. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;4. &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23Aravindhasametha&amp;amp;src=typd"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#AravindhaSametha&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Aravindha Sametha &amp;ndash; the 2018 Telugu release broke all records at the box office as the movie minted more than Rs 100 crore in just three days worldwide. Starring Pooja Hegde (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/hegdepooja"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;@hegdepooja&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;) and Jr NTR (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/tarak9999?lang=en"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;@tarak9999&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;), the movie&amp;rsquo;s huge success reflected on Twitter as fans voiced their appreciation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;5. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23Rangasthalam%20&amp;amp;src=typd"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#Rangasthalam&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Rangasthalam is a 2018 Telugu-language period action drama film that became the third highest grossing Telugu movie of all time after the Baahubali series. The success of the film was evident from the volume of conversations on Twitter, with the industry and audiences pouring in their praise and applause earning the film one of the top hashtags of the year.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;6. &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23Kaala&amp;amp;src=tyah"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#Kaala&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;The Tamil-language socio-political drama film starring superstar Rajinikanth, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23Kaala&amp;amp;src=tyah"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#Kaala&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;, evoked a massive response from fans worldwide. The first-ever Rajinikanth emoji on Twitter further led the movie to be a topic of high interest on Twitter amongst fans, audiences and industry.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;7. &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23BiggBossTelugu2&amp;amp;src=typd"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#BiggBossTelugu2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Now in its second season, the Telugu edition of the reality TV series Bigg Boss continued to be one of the most talked about shows in the world of television in India and on Twitter. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;8. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23MeToo&amp;amp;src=typd"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#MeToo&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;The &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23MeToo&amp;amp;src=typd"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#MeToo&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt; movement emerged in India this year. As the hashtags &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23MeToo&amp;amp;src=typd"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#MeToo&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt; and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/metooindia?lang=en"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#MeTooIndia&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt; continued to trend in the country, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;people started to pay more attention to women&amp;rsquo;s safety issues across sections of the Indian society, including government, media and the Bollywood film industry. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;9. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23WhistlePodu&amp;amp;src=typd"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#WhistlePodu&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;With 2018 being their comeback year, Chennai Super Kings (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/ChennaiIPL"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;@ChennaiIPL&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;) had the crowd chanting &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?src=typd&amp;amp;q=%23WhistlePodu"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#WhistlePodu&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt; as they made the dash for the coveted IPL 2018 trophy. Encouraging fans to cheer for the team, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/ChennaiIPL"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;@ChennaiIPL&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt; made a special video for &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?src=typd&amp;amp;q=%23WhistlePodu"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#WhistlePodu&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;, the colloquial expression in Tamil which means &amp;lsquo;to whistle&amp;rsquo;, and drove the fans into a Tweeting frenzy with their performance.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;10. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23IPL2018&amp;amp;src=typd"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23IPL2018&amp;amp;src=typd"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;IPL2018&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;India&amp;rsquo;s biggest cricket extravaganza &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23IPL2018&amp;amp;src=typd"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23IPL2018&amp;amp;src=typd"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;IPL2018&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt; continued to be a major topic of conversation on Twitter even in its 11th edition. Special Twitter emojis for all the eight franchises this year added to fans&amp;rsquo; enthusiasm on Twitter in support of their favourite teams and amplified the cricket excitement on the platform.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Most Influential moments in 2018 *&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;2018 was also the year when Twitter reacted en masse as people demanded &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23JusticeForAsifa&amp;amp;src=typd"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#JusticeForAsifa&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;, engaged in ongoing political debates on &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/karnatakaelection?lang=en"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#KarnatakaElection&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt; and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23Aadhaar&amp;amp;src=typd"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#Aadhaar&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;. But it wasn&amp;rsquo;t just politics and movements that had people Tweeting in 2018. India celebrated &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/deepveer?lang=en"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#DeepVeer&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&amp;rsquo;s romance as well as major wins at global sporting occasions like &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/asiangames?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Ehashtag"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#AsianGames&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt; as Indian athletes, including Bajrang Punia (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/BajrangPunia?lang=en"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;@BajrangPunia&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;), Hima Das (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/himadas8?lang=en"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;@HimaDas8&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;) and PV Sindhu (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/Pvsindhu1"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;@Pvsindhu&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;), won laurels. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;These are among the most influential moments on Twitter - &lt;span style="background:white"&gt;where Indians went first to get answers or share their opinions around the biggest conversations happening in India and the world throughout 2018: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/Twitter4.jpg" style="width: 450px; height: 253px;" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;ENTERTAINMENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;#Sarkar and the rise of regional entertainment &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;South Indian film &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23Sarkar&amp;amp;src=tyah"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#Sarkar&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt; led the rise of regional entertainment conversations on Twitter this year. The film starring Thalapathy Vijay (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/actorvijay"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;@actorvijay&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;) earned massive engagement from the film aficionados on Twitter for its star power and generated conversations on its political theme. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;The &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/deepveer?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Ehashtag"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/deepveer?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Ehashtag"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;DeepVeer&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt; Wedding &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;From the launch of Padmaavat (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/filmpadmaavat?lang=en"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;@filmPadmaavat&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;) earlier this year to wedding bells in November, celebrity couple Deepika Padukone (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/deepikapadukone?lang=en"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;@deepikapadukone&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;) and Ranveer Singh (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/RanveerOfficial"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;@RanveerOfficial&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;) continued to give people major relationship goals and became the talk of the town on Twitter in 2018.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;NEWS &amp;amp; POLITICS:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Women speak up against sexual harassment in the #MeToo movement&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;The emergence of the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23MeToo&amp;amp;src=typd"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#MeToo&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt; movement in India saw women across industries speaking out against sexual harassment. The movement has drawn global attention and increased awareness of women&amp;rsquo;s safety in India, an exemplary representation of hashtag activism. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Karnataka election&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Twitter saw more than 3 million mentions in relation to the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23KarnatakaElections2018&amp;amp;src=tyah"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#KarnatakaElections2018&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;from Apr 25 - May 15, 2018. Despite the fact that the election occurred in one state of India, i.e. Karnataka, discussions on Twitter were vibrant all over the country and even overseas. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Kerala floods unite the nation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;The &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23keralafloods&amp;amp;src=typd"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#KeralaFloods&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt; brought together government agencies, relief organisations, famous personalities and regular people on the platform to help rebuild Kerala. The people utilized Twitter to share information and crowdsource relief and assistance. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;India demands Justice for Asifa&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;The heinous crimes committed against 8-year-old Asifa Bano led to widespread protests and international attention. Outraged citizens flooded Twitter, expressing their angst and demanding &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23JusticeForAsifa&amp;amp;src=typd"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#JusticeForAsifa&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;The Aadhaar debate&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Conversations around the Aadhaar&amp;rsquo;s privacy issues resurfaced in 2018. As the &lt;span style="background:white"&gt;Supreme Court upheld the constitutional validity of Aadhaar, &lt;/span&gt;Indians across the world exchanged their opinions on the platform regarding the verdict and the &lt;span style="background:white"&gt;provisions on linking the unique ID with various non-essential services.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;SPORTS:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;IPL 2018 Mania&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Fan engagement touched new heights on Twitter as the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23IPL&amp;amp;src=typd"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23IPL&amp;amp;src=typd"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;IPL&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt; completed its 11th season. To mark this landmark season, fans on Twitter cheered on their teams and celebrated with specific emojis for all the eight franchises part of the competition this year, based on their taglines. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;CSK&amp;rsquo;s #WhistlePodu comeback&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;With 2018 being their year of comeback, Chennai Super Kings (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/ChennaiIPL"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;@ChennaiIPL&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;) had the crowd chanting &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?src=typd&amp;amp;q=%23WhistlePodu"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#WhistlePodu&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt; as they made the dash for the coveted IPL 2018 trophy.&amp;nbsp; Encouraging fans to cheer for the team, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/ChennaiIPL"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;@ChennaiIPL&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt; made a special video for &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?src=typd&amp;amp;q=%23WhistlePodu"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#WhistlePodu&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;, the colloquial expression in Tamil which means &amp;lsquo;to whistle&amp;rsquo;, and drove the fans into a Tweeting frenzy with their performance.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;India shines at the Asian Games&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;As Indian athletes, including Bajrang Punia (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/BajrangPunia?lang=en"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;@BajrangPunia&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;), Hima Das (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/himadas8?lang=en"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;@HimaDas8&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;) and PV Sindhu (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/Pvsindhu1"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;@Pvsindhu&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;), won laurels at the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23AsianGames2018&amp;amp;src=typd"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#AsianGames&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23AsianGames2018&amp;amp;src=typd"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;2018&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&amp;nbsp; and clinched a total of 69 medals, congratulatory Tweets poured in from all parts of the country to rejoice in their victory and welcome the heroes home. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Most Talked about Indian accounts in 2018 *&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;With the backdrop of the state elections in India, it is no surprise that political conversations were at an all-time high in 2018, with 6 politicians making it to the Top 10 Most Talked About Indian Accounts list. Prime Minister Narendra Modi (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/narendramodi"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;@NarendraModi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;) tops the charts. Entertainment completes the rest of the Top 10 represented by actors Pawan Kalyan (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/PawanKalyan"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;@PawanKalyan&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;), Shah Rukh Khan (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/iamsrk?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Eauthor"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;@iamsrk&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;), Thalapathy Vijay (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/actorvijay"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;@actorvijay&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;), and Mahesh Babu (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/urstrulyMahesh"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;@urstrulyMahesh&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/Twitter2.jpg" style="width: 450px; height: 253px;" /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;You can share your biggest stories, memories and conversations of 2018 today. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23ThisHappened&amp;amp;src=typd"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#1155cc"&gt;#ThisHappened&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-left:-36.0pt; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Arial,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;(*Data as of Jan 1-Nov 10, 2018)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93290-sunilchetri.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital-news/kantar-connected-intelligence-ai-voice-will-transform-media-in-the-new-year-93287.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>05/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Kantar: Connected Intelligence, AI &amp; Voice will transform media in the New Year</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Kantar today released its perspective on the major trends that will shape the media landscape for brand owners, agencies and media platforms in 2019. The predictions report outlines 12 key trends that will transform the next year in media. Exploring advances from augmented reality, through gender portrayal to vertical video, the 12 predictions are:&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;1. Advanced Analytics and Artificial Intelligence (AI) will resolve the integrated online/offline return on marketing investment dilemma.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;2. Voice technology will break through in creative planning and the marketing mix.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;3. Chinese leadership in social media and social media analytics will be &amp;lsquo;fast-followed&amp;rsquo; by the west.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;4. The emergence of the &amp;lsquo;branded experience network&amp;rsquo; will transform media management in to &amp;lsquo;internet of everything&amp;rsquo; management.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;5. Brands will start to take the portrayal of women in advertising seriously.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;6. Amazon will emerge from the advertising world &amp;lsquo;shadows&amp;rsquo; to make the duopoly a triopoly.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;7. Vertical video will lead the way in creativity.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;8. The big screen will make a comeback, bigger and better than before.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;9. Attitudinal insights combined with predictive modelling will make programmatic buying more agile and accurate.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;10. Influencer marketing strategies will pivot to prioritise credibility ahead of reach.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;11. GDPR compliance will drive more sophistication in brand data strategies.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;12. Augmented Reality (AR) will start to shape both the consumer journey and customer experience.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Constant innovation and change in the media landscape continues, but I think the speed of adoption of technologies like artificial intelligence will be surprising. Connected intelligence in all its forms will start to dominate the narrative, as well as new opportunities like voice,&amp;rdquo; said Eric Salama, CEO, Kantar.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;He further added, &amp;ldquo;How we measure media and its effectiveness is evolving quickly, and the industry needs to work together so our clients can understand the impact of their investments. There has never been a more exciting time in marketing.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93287-kantar1.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
</urlset>
