<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>www.exchange4media.com (Fullstory)</title>
    <link>https://www.exchange4media.com</link>
    <description>News Marketing India advertising Indian brands tv media newspapers</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <item>
      <title>We are constantly obsessing about the reader: Rajiv Lochan, MD &amp; CEO, The Hindu Group </title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/media-print/we-are-constantly-obsessing-about-the-reader-rajiv-lochan-md-ceo-the-hindu-group_92340.html</link>
      <description>The launch of The Hindu newspaper on September 20, 1878 was indeed a turning point in the history of Indian journalism. It was started with an aim to support the campaign of Sir T Muthuswamy Iyer for a judgeship at the Madras High Court and to oppose and counter the propaganda against him by the British Press. The then&amp;nbsp;eight-page weekly was published by six individuals&amp;nbsp;-&amp;nbsp;four&amp;nbsp;law students and two&amp;nbsp;teachers&amp;nbsp;- T. Rangacharya, P. V. Rangacharya, D. Kesava Rao Pantulu and N. Subba Rao Pantulu, led by G. Subramania Iyer and M. Veeraraghavacharyar. The newspaper’s ideology was rooted in fervent patriotism and commitment towards the&amp;nbsp;common public. The Hindu was one among the&amp;nbsp;many newspapers launched during the freedom movement period, but today it is one&amp;nbsp;which withstood the course of time and evolution in print media, unlike its&amp;nbsp;contemporaries. The edits, articles and op-ed columns published in the newspaper over these 140 years became referral materials.  The campaigns launched by The Hindu focused on raising awareness among&amp;nbsp;people. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As&amp;nbsp;The Hindu celebrates 140 glorious years of being in the business,&amp;nbsp;exchange4media spoke with&amp;nbsp;Rajiv Lochan, Managing Director &amp;amp; CEO, The Hindu Group, on&amp;nbsp;the group’s journey over the&amp;nbsp;years, campaigns run by the group and the&amp;nbsp;road map ahead. Excerpts:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;  &lt;strong&gt;The Hindu @140, how has&amp;nbsp;the journey been so far?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is a rare privilege that readers have reposed their trust in us over the past 140 years. From an initial print run of 80 copies in 1878 to nearly 16 lakhs certified copies in circulation every day and a readership of almost 60 lakhs across the country, the journey has been filled with highs and lows. Perhaps what is most gratifying is that our sense of purpose and duty to our readers has allowed us to withstand the challenges that have come our way. As we turn 140, we recommit to our readers and resolve to work hard to retain their trust.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;    &lt;strong&gt;Unlike its&amp;nbsp;contemporaries when the newspaper first went to print,&amp;nbsp;The Hindu lasted the course. What are the factors you attribute this&amp;nbsp;growth to?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Hindu has always focused on its sense of purpose and&amp;nbsp;duty as the primary reason-to-be and focused on honing our strengths – credible and high quality journalism, unmatched technical excellence, a focus to deliver value to advertisers and a commitment to working with all our stakeholders fairly.&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/1538549498_PTeqDx_kasturi.jpg" style="width:350px;height:235px;float:right"&gt;We are constantly obsessing about the reader. Our founders started the newspaper with the objective of “giving voice to the natives” and we have stayed true to that mission over the past 140 years. We have also been clear over the years that the viability of the newspaper depends both on our readers’ loyalty and our ability to deliver value to advertisers. Our code of editorial and business values ensure that we consistently serve our readers and advertisers with their interest at&amp;nbsp;the core of&amp;nbsp;our mission. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;      &lt;strong&gt;What are strategies followed by The Hindu in these 140 years to understand and analyse the need of the readers?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;The Hindu has always sought to serve its readers based on their needs – whether it was using an aircraft to deliver newspapers to the neighbouring Southern states in the 1960s to introducing pioneering technological innovation to substantially enhance the experience of our readers to reinventing the content and design every 10-15 years. This is the only media house in the country with a Readers’ Editor, who has the mandate to be informed about and relay the readers’ perspective, regardless of the editorial stand. A unique 1-800 number is published daily inviting feedback from readers&amp;nbsp;- from content to delivery. The Editor meets with readers in interactive forums across the country to get insights into what their changing needs are. The website and apps have been designed keeping in mind reader experience, winning laurels at WAN IFRA’s Digital Media Awards. In the last two&amp;nbsp;years, a Reader Intelligence Unit has helped gather consumer insights on their needs beyond news/information to shopping patterns, digital usage, and brand preferences, which is providing advertisers with valuable insights on tailoring their value propositions to various reader categories (across demographics, geographies, etc.).&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The campaigns by The Hindu namely&amp;nbsp;Behave. The Youth Are Watching, #SundayIsForReading were major hits, tell us about some&amp;nbsp;other major campaigns by The Hindu and the influence it has made on the readers?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;These were indeed memorable campaigns! Behave was the voice of the youth with a hard-hitting message to the country’s political class, while #SundayIsForReading encouraged people of all ages to spend quality time reading. Another campaign that still gets an instant connect with a range of audiences (readers and non-readers) is Stay Ahead of the Times – every situation and copy in that series was a hit because it was extremely relatable.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;The Hindu has always been focused on raising awareness and instigating action on civic and social issues. A Bengaluru-focused campaign in 2017 called Spirit of Bengaluru had an emotion-stirring song by the Kannada artist Raghu Dixit showing the two sides of the city, the evergreen paradise interrupted by the bustling woes of traffic and garbage, using a mobile auto-rotate innovation.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;At a time when many are questioning the purpose and value of the printed word, The Hindu ran a campaign #FortheLoveofPrint as its salute to the passion and diligence of the different people who come together every single day to curate, print and deliver the newspaper. The Hindu, as a newspaper of record for 140 years, has never been known to shy away from putting to print both great and small moments of history. #FortheLoveofPrint explores the underlying commitment and emotion that got them started and continues to exist today, endearing this newspaper with its readers.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;The most recent Get South Smart with The Hindu campaign showcases the newspaper’s understanding of its readers. As the most read English newspaper in South India, The Hindu has been studying the purchase preferences as well as behaviours of its readers through its Reader Intelligence Unit, and is now helping advertisers fine-tune their campaigns for more effective reach and returns across South India.&lt;br&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;    What are the key focus areas and goals for the next decade?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;The news consumers’ requirements, preferences and behaviours are evolving rapidly in today’s age of information overload. Increasingly readers are seeking trusted news sources for perspectives and analyses (less so for breaking news) on the go, in quickly digestible formats – willingness to pay for content that is relevant to their needs is also developing. We believe that the future in the digital space is through a smart balance of advertising, subscription and commerce revenues and we are experimenting extensively with products, pricing models and consumer acquisition.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;The Southern states are growing 30% faster than other states in GDP terms, consumers in the South are better educated, better informed and more importantly consume more news than their fellow citizens around the country. Not surprisingly, we are seeing increasing advertiser appetite to connect emotionally with the South Indian consumer in order to position their brands for growth. Insights from our Reader Intelligence Unit on consumer preferences for e-commerce, FMCG product consumption, durables purchase considerations are helping advertisers understand the drivers of purchase to skew their media planning and communications for better outcomes. The Hindu Group’s combined assets, beyond the English newspaper, including vernacular publications, 500+ curated events, access to 3000+ schools and 1000+ colleges across the country, a vast vendor delivery network, unparalleled digital and social media reach and engagement have helped in reaching and connecting with the relevant target segments through holistic solutions to the brands’ challenges in the South Indian markets.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Our goal is to serve both readers and advertisers with the same devotion and purpose as we have for the past 140 years through our continued commitment to the profession of journalism, while smartly connecting audience&amp;nbsp;with brands.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Urvasi, Urvasi… Take it easy PharmEasy!</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/advertising/urvasi-urvasi-take-it-easy-pharmeasy_92355.html</link>
      <description>We all know the feeling of humming a song from an ad without having a bull’s notion about it. It is true-&amp;nbsp;few things can drive an advertising message home like a catchy jingle or a song. Whether your listeners love it or hate it, it will relate your brand name with a concept, idea, or promotion seamlessly.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hitting the right notes, Pharmacy aggregator - PharmEasy recently released ads showing customers dancing to 'Urvasi Urvasi', a track composed by A R Rahman for the 1994 Tamil movie, Kadhalan. Conceptualised by Mullen Lintas' Mumbai office, the campaign thought focuses on the core of the service promise - ease of ordering with a healthy dose of saving on every order. The film opens with a shot of a PharmEasy app user who looks visibly surprised with the ‘FLAT 20% Off’ offer on his medical bill. In the following shot, the user is shown fulfilling his long-awaited desire, something that he could spend on only by saving money on typically exorbitant medical bills. Lyrics in the song have been tweaked to include the line ‘Take it easy PharmEasy’.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The creative cut&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dhaval Shah, Co-Founder, PharmEasy, says that the team wanted to launch the brand nationally with a 360-degree&amp;nbsp;campaign which includes TV, print, outdoor, radio and digital. He opines that the current e-pharmacy space in India is cluttered with a common messaging of X percentage off on medicines. “The biggest challenge was to create a differentiated brand that stands out from the ‘sea of sameness’ that exists in this category today. Our brief to the agency was to come up with a campaign which can seamlessly integrate with all&amp;nbsp;media components. All this in a manner that builds the foundations of core brand positioning in an evocative, emotionally compelling way that over time builds a differentiated brand identity and persona with emotive connect, and as a corollary enables and amplifies consumer word of mouth/referral,” says Shah.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amer Jaleel, Group Chairman and CCO, MullenLowe Lintas Group, shares that he found it a pretty cool coincidence that PharmEasy sounds like pharmacy. “Once we asked ourselves the question ‘What can you do with the savings that PharmEasy promises?’, the combination of that answer with the fact that whimsically you could imagine someone dancing to the tune of ‘take it easy’, made for a pretty interesting and amusing creative cut. Also we wanted to make the brand quite sticky since more than a couple of such e-comm players have already been around for a while. Invoking Prabhu Deva, you will admit, does it&amp;nbsp;some amount of justice,” says Jaleel. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Over to experts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to Titus Upputuru, National Creative Director, Dentsu One, the ads are quick and smart. “They add some life into the otherwise ‘dard se peedith’ pharma advertising. Despite being engaging and entertaining, the key message of discount is not lost,” asserts Upputuru. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For Shrenik Gandhi, Co-Founder and CEO, White Rivers Media, the category has seen some interesting marketing campaigns in the last few months, but this one takes the cake. Gandhi believes that the campaign will give the brand a far better share of voice and recall. “This series has perfect characters, tight script, catchy music, and apt cinematography. PharmEasy has come a long way from its once, 'emotional appeal' driven 'kadvi dava meethe daamo me' to this campaign. 'karlo apne shauk pure' as a campaign covers both, inherent virality and instant thought gratification,” he shares.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ad filmmaker&amp;nbsp;Gaurav Gupta says that the ad has won the battle to attention due to its catchy composition. "It’s good to see such a fun ad in a category like this. From the time I've watched it, I couldn't stop humming 'Take it easy, PharmEasy’. So I'm sure it will fetch the brand the desired brand recall and attention. Moreover, the ad communicates the brand offering beautifully," Gupta concludes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deepak Singh, Chief Creative Officer, The Social Street feels that the execution is fine. “Lot of brands have taken funny routes, but they too work only when there is a strong insight,” says Singh. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Campaign Links&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/IuVPsLuOvvc" rel="nofollow" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;  &lt;br&gt;&lt;iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/WPZyjqoMlTI" rel="nofollow" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our business in India has doubled in the last four years: Baxter Jolly, Weber Shandwick</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing/our-business-in-india-has-doubled-in-the-last-four-years-baxter-jolly-weber-shandwick_92360.html</link>
      <description>The role of traditional Public Relations (PR) agencies has changed with the coming of digital. Also, with many brands going for in-house agency solutions, traditional public relations firms have upped their game and moved to providing not just communication strategy but also business solutions to stay relevant.&lt;br&gt;On his recent visit to India, Baxter Jolly, CEO APAC, Weber Shandwick, spoke about the factors that have kept traditional PR agencies strong despite numerous challenges and explains why in-house agencies are no longer a threat to the domain.&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/1538709795_Y4DOtD_IPRCCA-logo_%281%29.jpg" style="width:350px;height:164px;float:right"&gt;&lt;br&gt;Edited excerpts:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In your view, how has the communications domain evolved over the last 10 years?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;From our experience, what we have seen in the last 10 years is the constant evolution of the communications industry. I think what has driven that, to a large extent, is the advent of digital and social which has changed the landscape very rapidly in terms of the way we engage with our stakeholders. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When I joined the agency many years ago, it was very much media relations driven and very traditional, but over the years the change has been very rapid. I think the next phase of this change will be equally important and what our clients would want us to do will be far different from the campaign type of work and we will be more focused on providing business solutions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do you think public relations has more opportunities to diversify and get more work as boundary lines across sectors are getting blurred? How is Weber leveraging it?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;I think integration is definitely driving a lot of change. Some of firms have not evolved enough to face the opportunities on that front. Weber as a firm had started investments with that view many years ago. I think our journey happened 6 to 7 years ago when people were still thinking of digital and social and we were already driving that. We were also changing the type of talent we had in our organization by bringing different kinds of skill sets into the firm. So rather than having traditional media relations, we were bringing designers, production people, planners etc. into our organisation to meet those client opportunities. If you look at where we are today, we have started bringing a lot of focus on data and analytics in the organisation. I think we have constantly evolved to stay ahead of the game and stay relevant to the client’s needs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There is a growing trend of corporates opting for in-house agency solutions, how is that working out for the PR industry at large?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Firstly, I think it is an equally competitive environment for the client too. Many of the clients have transformed their own businesses to meet the advent of the digital world, artificial Intelligence and all of that. So they are changing and they are under tremendous pressure to differentiate themselves in the toughest business environment. So having an in-house agency is something they tend to look at, but many of them want our help in terms of providing business solutions. Many of them do still believe in having an agency on hand to bring in a different perspective of how we look at things. So having that external dimension and that external point of view is still very critical for the clients. They are coming less to us for the tactical reasons and more for the strategic insights which we bring as an organization. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How would you describe the factors that have kept Weber strong despite growing competition in the domain?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;As we know, the biggest challenge in our industry is talent. Having the right talent is critical and we have seen that in India where our business has doubled in the last 4 years. Moreover at Weber Shandwick, we are proud of the strong stability of our leadership and most of them have been with the organisation for more than a decade. So having that stability at the top leads to stability in the lower ranks.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I see no reason why we should slow down: Punit Misra</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/mediatv/i-see-no-reason-why-we-should-slow-down-punit-misra_92368.html</link>
      <description>Punit Misra, Chief Executive Officer of the Domestic Broadcast Business of Zee Entertainment Enterprises Limited, is upbeat about two things – one, high growth in viewership (non-sport and non-news) that the network has achieved, with consistent numbers since April 2017, and two, that he has been able to infuse a process-driven culture in the working of the organisation since taking over the role in October 2016. Today, what enthuses him most is the numbers achieved by the network comprising 37 channels in nine languages.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;“Our topline has always grown ahead of the market. Also, our bottomline has grown ahead of our topline. The good thing is, some of that growth has accelerated and at 19.1% viewership share, we have hit the No. 1 network position, and that is hugely satisfying. This is viewership share, 2+, all India, Urban+Rural, since April last year. So, we are not talking one week, one market, one socio-economic class, Urban or Rural. We are talking the pristine, full number. That’s incredible,” says Misra. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The network has garnered a weekly cumulative viewership  of 669 million (average of last 13 weeks) across all channels in its four broad clusters - Hindi GECs, Regional Entertainment channels, Hindi Movie channels and English Premium/Niche channels. On how it relates to revenue, Misra says, “Get the eyeballs, revenue will follow. I am clear about the revenue model.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here are edited excerpts from a conversation with Punit Misra:&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;   &lt;img src="https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/1538643512_p3dBzR_Regional.jpg" style="width:300px;height:1481px;float:right"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From seasoned marketer at an FMCG major to CEO of the domestic broadcast business of ZEEL - what are the learnings that have worked for you over the last two years?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;I did not know anything about the industry, and entered it with humility and a really huge appetite to learn. I still rate myself as a learner. My belief in brands, belief in consumers and the need to build that ability to get closer and closer to understanding consumers and customers, is something which has been of immense value. I have thoroughly enjoyed the ability to transfer some of those learnings into what we are trying to do here. Be it innovation process or capability building process, the aim was to institutionalise pockets of brilliance which already existed at ZEEL, into what I would call building repeatable models that are key to consistency of performance across markets.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is your own assessment of the overall domestic broadcast business of ZEEL? How do you rate its performance in terms of reach and revenue over the term that you have been at the helm?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Let’s look at the organisation and its totality of existence, an organisation which is now in its 26th year of existence and a pioneer in the business of creating content which people love. Right from 2011, as a business we have been gaining viewership share. So, 11% viewership share is what we had in 2011. And as of last month, it is nearly 20% in the entertainment genre, which is non-sport and non-news. The second is the width of that leadership, because we have been gaining and leading market after market, be it the Tamil market where three years ago we were low single digit and are now near 20% share and growing, or Kannada where for eight weeks we are the No. 1 channel. As for Zee Bangla, where we were leaders several years ago, and lost that position maybe 8-9 years ago, we are now the No. 1 channel and growing share every month. We have further strengthened our position in Marathi and crossed 400 odd GRPs recently. Big Magic or Bhojpuri, is a business that we acquired, and we are growing there too, as well as in the FTA genre. The regional genre contributes 25% to 35% of the network’s total advertising pie. We are all set to launch a Malayalam channel, and evaluating opportunity for others. So, it’s a very broad-based, robust growth. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What have been some of the big challenges that you faced?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first big challenge in any successful place is tackling the question ‘What’s the case for change?’ Why change, as the 11% viewership share of 2011 was already 16% in 2016. We needed to sit together as a leadership team and be clear about the case for change. That took its time, and we went through it in a pretty organised ‘Zee’ way. The second challenge for me was keeping the core entrepreneurial strength of the leadership team at heart, while talking of process and institutionalising things - somewhere they clashed. But we went ahead on that without a single leadership change, with the belief that here is a bunch of very successful leaders who know the trade, the business, the brand and the viewer. We have to make this change happen with those strengths intact. We brought in a few people as we created new jobs. And over a period of time, obviously some individuals do move, but 85% of the team if not 90%, is intact and getting better by the day.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is the uptake on the new brand philosophy ‘Extraordinary Together’? Has it had an impact in the short term?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Extraordinary Together’ has set us on a journey of a bit more of consumer connect, a bit more of marketing savviness, being built into our own DNA. We had set up the whole marketing function when our CMO Prathyusha Agarwal came in, and this was the first big exercise under her leadership. And from there, we moved to doing the same for our Zee TV master brand. We made it travel to some of our other brands like the Zee Tamil re-launch. Also brand re-launches that we did on &amp;amp;flix and &amp;amp;Prive, and then Zee Bollywood. It helped us in institutionalising some of these things so that they are starting to travel deeper and wider across the organisation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is the CAGR that you would like to see in the next three to five years?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;We have gained 200 basis points on viewership share in the last two years. That averages 100 a year. We should continue with that and get better. On revenue, the numbers are in the public domain. Why should we not continue to grow at that rate continuously for the next 3 to 5 years? I see no reason why we should slow down.&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/1538643551_4ReMAb_changes.jpg"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Looking ahead, what would be the three game-changers for the domestic broadcast business of ZEEL? &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;I am a firm believer that ‘more is more’ - as more great content gets created, and gets served, we will see more consumption. I have seen that play out in all our regional markets. More quantum, better quality of content justified through more number of hours of consumption. The marketer or the content creator’s challenge is how to get more market-share. Then from a creative standpoint - how do you continuously create content brands that people will love? The third challenge is the challenge of talent. Getting new talent - be it writing talent, or acting talent, or young executive producers and group heads and so on… We have to be the place for the best business talent, the best marketing talent, the best creative minds. &lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/1538643933_kkl2P4_gfx2.jpg" style="width:300px;height:291px"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/1538643679_1iUJEz_marketshare.jpg"&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sagar Mahabaleshwarkar, CCO, Cheil WW India, quits: Sources</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/advertising/sagar-mahabaleshwarkar-cco-cheil-ww-india-quits-sources_92372.html</link>
      <description>Sagar Mahabaleshwarkar, Chief Creative Officer at Cheil WW India, has quit the agency, highly placed sources within the industry have confirmed. Mahabaleshwarkar had been with the agency since December, 2015. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prior to this Mahabaleshwarkar has held prominent roles in agencies such as Bates CHI&amp;amp;Partners, Rediffusion Y&amp;amp;R and Ogilvy &amp;amp; Mather. We reached out to Sagar Mahabaleshwarkar for a comment but he did not confirm or deny the news.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hey! Mr agency guy, go beyond the brief, be my partner, say marketers</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing/hey-mr-agency-guy-go-beyond-the-brief-be-my-partner-say-marketers_92378.html</link>
      <description>Clients want more from their media agencies than ever before. A competitive and dynamic market where customers are not falling for push advertising has put pressure on brands to master and deliver effective advertising communication that informs and educates the consumer. This demands incisive insights on consumer behaviour to create relevant campaigns to catch the consumer at the right moments. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Businesses are opting to transform their marketing processes for a digital ecosystem where an omni-channel approach that leads with personalisation is taking precedence over traditional targeting. This new world order requires agencies to reinvent themselves for brands. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/1538717644_6p7gNH_amit_quote.jpg" style="width:204px;height:240px;float:right"&gt;Some marketers exchange4media spoke to said they want agency partners to solve business problems and go beyond conventional media buying services. Kashyap Vadapalli, Chief Marketing Officer, Pefferfry.com, says, “Agencies we have been working with do a good job of delivering to the brief. What we are looking for now is the media agency’s input in terms of solving business problems like what is the next market we need to go for.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vadapalli said that this need to source business solutions from agencies is especially needed in shaping marketing communication for new markets. “Obviously, we have a sense of this because we are in the business, but it can be in terms of helping us understand what should we do differently in media to target the new markets. We get performance to a brief of a fairly good quality, but what we are looking for is consulting in terms of ideas for approaching new markets and new sources of gain,” he said. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a media landscape that is being overtaken by programmatic buying, agencies need to don a consultancy role, a study has found. The study by Forrester found that CMOs see media as a significant opportunity to drive personalization, commerce, and growth. “CMOs constantly scrutinize the global media market for higher levels of accountability, additional performance capabilities, and total transparency — not just buying power,” says&amp;nbsp;Jay Pattisall, principal analyst at Forrester and author of the report.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/1538717680_1WrrUG_ace_logo.jpg" style="width:400px;height:500px;float:right"&gt;Commoditization of media offerings has lead to a devaluation of digital media and planning capabilities in particular. “The solutions that agencies are dishing out these days are standard solutions layered with a minor customisation for a brand. Other than the minor customisation, the solution is given without understanding the business aspect of the brands,” points out Mayank Shah, Category Head, Parle Products. He added that it is very important that the agency understands the client’s business. Instead, agencies are approaching brands with the intention of selling something rather than offering a thought-through and worked-upon solution for the brand. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A handful of brands have the agency team sitting alongside the brand team to work on campaigns. But marketers feel that lack of such a set-up should not stop agency teams from becoming an integral part of the brand team. “My dream as a marketer is to get my agency’s creatives, media, sponsorships, etc to talk to each other. I also want my agency to be a part of my extended team rather than the two working as separate entities,” said Mansi Narasimhan, VP &lt;br&gt;Marketing and Communications Area Marketing, Mastercard. She too said that what she looks for in an agency is a partner who understands the brand’s business problems. “I would like for my agency to be integrated and aligned with the goals and objectives of my business.” &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What the marketer now also wants is for the agency to analyse data and extract simple useable insights. Amit Tiwari, VP Marketing, Havells, said that in an ecosystem where every agency has proprietary tools, it would be good to see the agencies use them to give insights from the data they have. He strongly felt that the role of the agency now has to be more participative than consultative. “Clients want a recommendation backed by logic and conviction - this is the dire need today,” he added. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In some cases, marketers also want to be challenged by their agency partners and even aid with media strategies across platforms. Tiwari said, “A brief is just a piece of paper that tells an agency what the operating framework of the brand is. We want the agency to start approaching the brand problem from a macro perspective on every medium.” &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tiwari said he wants a media agnostic recommendation from agencies. “Please challenge us,” he said, adding “we want recommendations on what the agency believes the client must do irrespective of whether the client agrees or not.” He said that if an idea is backed by solid logic and data, the client will support a recommendation from the agency.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hathway launches Android-based OTT Set Top Box </title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/mediatv/hathway-launches-android-based-ott-set-top-box_92379.html</link>
      <description>Cable and FTTH broadband operator, Hathway Cable and Datacom have&amp;nbsp;launched an OTT Set Top Box (STB), based on Google’s Android TV. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hathway has also announced the&amp;nbsp;launch of a&amp;nbsp;Cable Hybrid box, Hathway Ultra Smart HUB on Android. This Smart Hub combines linear TV with Play services in HDR quality.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We have seen more and more consumers want the&amp;nbsp;best of OTT services available on large screens. The idea of launching this box was to give them OTT services along with&amp;nbsp;linear TV on large screens and of course to look for consumer benefits&amp;nbsp;as well. Over a period of time this will segment our consumers. The top 25 per&amp;nbsp;cent consumers will go for these OTT services. Any OTT service provider will be happy to do a tie up because it helps them to increase&amp;nbsp;reach,” said&amp;nbsp;Rajan Gupta, Managing Director, Hathway.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The box is&amp;nbsp;priced at Rs 2,999 and the product will launch in 15 days through tie ups with local cable operators (LCOs). Consumers can book the boxes starting&amp;nbsp;November 1 and the boxes will get installed by the end of November. Gupta said, “ Starting December 1, we should have a&amp;nbsp;TVC for this product and the team is&amp;nbsp;also&amp;nbsp;working on a&amp;nbsp;360-degree marketing campaign.&amp;nbsp;Obviously creating awareness right from metros to mini metros will be key. We will also be closing working with LCO&amp;nbsp;partners to reach all&amp;nbsp;homes.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aiming to make viewing&amp;nbsp;experience on OTT TV in India easy, the&amp;nbsp;Hathway Play Box, which carries a dedicated You Tube, Netflix and Google Play button on the remote control, gives&amp;nbsp;the ability to consumers to access their favourite shows&amp;nbsp;on the big screen with just a simple click.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Consumers can use Google Assistant through a simple voice remote for applications such as finding their favourite web series, setting timers, answering questions, weather forecast and even placing e-commerce orders. It also has an&amp;nbsp;inbuilt Chromecast, which allows consumers&amp;nbsp;to mirror content from phone to TV. Hathway Play Box also allows consumers to experience Android gaming on the&amp;nbsp;big screen, including multiple users.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;"Right now we have a&amp;nbsp;capacity for 100,000 boxes per month but it&amp;nbsp;can be increased&amp;nbsp;based on&amp;nbsp;consumer demand," added Gupta.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;With easy to use smart interface, users can navigate between their linear TV channels and their play services and also customise Smart Hub with&amp;nbsp;apps downloaded from the Google Play store.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;"We are pleased to be working with Hathway and look forward to leveraging their extensive broadband and cable network to enable a&amp;nbsp;more exciting and useful Android TV experience&amp;nbsp;for consumers," said Pranab Mookken, Head Android, Chrome &amp;amp; Play Business Development, India.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why some PR teams successfully extract their pound of flesh: Siddhartha Mukherjee, Eikona</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/guestcolumn/why-some-pr-teams-successfully-extract-their-pound-of-flesh-siddhartha-mukherjee-eikona_92381.html</link>
      <description>Year on year, PR machineries, comprising the corporate communications desk and their PR agencies, have been losing out on their desired appraisals and&amp;nbsp;hikes. However, I do know of quite a few client-agency teams who have transformed themselves into amazing mavericks. These maverick PR teams are scientific, focused and very well measured. They know how to extract their pound of flesh —&amp;nbsp;corporate communication desk extracting from top management and consultancies from their clients. They are achieving this because they are breaking the decades old convention and rigidity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Well, on a separate note, number of such positively focused maverick PR teams need to go up rapidly if we want the growth of our industry in realistic terms. Broadly, from what I understand of the current market condition, while on one side, there has been no fee hikes for many agencies, on the other, corporate communication budget allocation by client management too has been kind of flat.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coming back, the question of WHY some PR teams successfully extract their pound of flesh should get answered if we understand HOW are the maverick brains thinking and executing their ideas. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Below is a seven-pointer sneak peek of what maverick corporate communication desks &amp;amp; PR consultancies are doing to get their pound of flesh from their respective customers: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1.  PR Mavericks believe in ‘India principles’:&lt;/strong&gt; They have a mind of their own. They do not need inspiration from the copy-paste of western markets or principles. Well before these western principles came to the rescue of many marketing and analytics agencies in India, these maverick teams understood the universal principles of brand communications, strategic use of PR/earned media, ROO &amp;amp; ROI and their marriage with data &amp;amp; analytics. Which is why they know what it means to achieve results in the India environment. No wonder, it calls for the world to learn from ‘India principles’.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2.  PR Mavericks depend radically on data:&lt;/strong&gt; In today’s age, which is only about ROOs and ROIs, data has to be the start and end of everything that we do. PR mavericks, despite their past exposure to data being limited, are today breaking the barriers. They are making brand and&amp;nbsp;business data, research, measurement and analytics their armoury and part of their daily lives.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3.  PR Mavericks do not mix monitoring with measurement:&lt;/strong&gt; PR mavericks are brave-hearted. Why? Well, while EAVs or AVEs have been an industry cancer for decades, mixing of PR monitoring with measurement has been an industry epidemic. They are clearly two separate worlds. As much as one tries, monitoring will end up make us chase our own tail…which is what has been happening in the last two decades. Monitoring allows basic tactical moves, but will never attract genuine respect from our respective customers. Daily news updates, AVEs, count of clips, tonality, journalist details, spokesperson scores, geography-wise analysis etc are all part of PR monitoring. On the other hand, PR measurement is an actual data science that can show the outcome of every inch of effort the PR team has put in. Measurement is governed by ROOs, ROIs and lots of interrogations across What, Who, Where, Why, How, When &amp;amp; Whom. Needless to say, this approach needs a lot of brave-heartedness.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4.  PR Mavericks identify disguise: &lt;/strong&gt;Ever since the concept of PR monitoring was started in India by PR agencies and self-claimed dedicated monitoring agencies almost two decades ago, they have been operating and shelling out monitoring services under the “garb of measurement”. No wonder, because of the continued disguise, even today, 8 out of 10 industry members think monitoring and measurement are mere synonyms. More so, the only way these disguised service providers got to project intelligence, value and aristocracy was when they got access to some international principles on measurement. ‘Copy &amp;amp; paste’ was the only simple and available mantra that they could think of. Interestingly, that continues to happen even today. The good news, however, is that the mavericks are quick to identify the deception. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5.  PR Mavericks give huge emphasis to ‘Whys’:&lt;/strong&gt; PR measurement starts with asking all kinds of questions? Importantly, maverick PR teams do not care even if the client or the corporate communication desk’s internal customers express discomfort with the interrogations mentioned above. They keep going. Who is the TG? What is the current vs desired mood? What do we communicate? When do we communicate? How do we communicate and so on…Well, there can be many such question combinations. However, the paramount question mavericks go deep into is ‘why are we doing this PR initiative? Why a press release? Why a press conference? The series of Whys do not stop till the time the PR team is convinced that their efforts will bring value to the brand quotient and/or the business.&lt;br&gt;  &lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6.  PR Mavericks establish PR machinery as a revenue centre:&lt;/strong&gt; Unlike the common perception of PR being a cost centre, maverick PR teams are being able to strategically showcase themselves as a revenue centre. Through PR measurement (and not monitoring), it is easy to show the savings and/or revenues accrued by the organisation with the help of PR. When the end users of PR, the CXOs, see the measured brand &amp;amp; business values PR has brought on the table, they have no other option but to consider the machinery as a strategic desk. If not ROI, even if ROOs are met, savings or revenues have got a nudge, they are more than happy to acknowledge the maverick team in the board room discussions. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7.  PR Mavericks use data to fortify client-consultancy relationship:&lt;/strong&gt; Ours is an industry that is led by knowledge and processes. To build a brand and establish the pay-offs from PR, one needs long standing relationship between client and agency. On ground, changing agency every 2-3 years don’t work. Smart PR machineries make PR data and analytics central to their day-to-day operation and interaction. Planning, implementation and execution are all guided through data. This creates wonderful camaraderie between client and agency and joint onus of what PR is meant to achieve. As a result of clever maverick thinking, in many cases, clients have been supporting the service extension of the agency.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mavericks are known to revolutionise and change norms. PR industry needs mavericks because there are plenty of norms to be broken and revolutions to be set in. My feeling is that the real growth of our industry is being contributed by these PR maverick teams who are quietly but effectively functioning across various industry verticals. I wish someone would take the onus of collating and documenting their efforts and achievements.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;PR machinery extracting its pound of flesh is not only an indication of getting acknowledgement and accruing financial benefits but more importantly, it is an indication of the start of a movement – ‘PR needs PR, thru data &amp;amp; measurement’, something that I had called for in the E4M IPRCCA panel discussion way back in 2008. Happy to see the needle starting to move.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The author is the Business Head of Eikona &amp;amp; Senior&amp;nbsp;VP - Corporate Communications&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;Disclaimer: The views expressed here are solely those of the author and do not in any way represent the views of exchange4media.com.&lt;/em&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#FeedOurFuture: UNWFP, UFO Moviez, FB launch global ad campaign to fight hunger</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/advertising/feedourfuture-unwfp-ufo-moviez-fb-launch-global-ad-campaign-to-fight-hunger_92382.html</link>
      <description>A powerful advertising campaign called ‘Feed Our Future’ - aimed at getting global cinema audiences involved in the fight against hunger - was launched by the United Nations World Food Programme (UNWFP), with the support of UFO Moviez, Facebook and SAWA, the Global Cinema Advertising Association, in Mumbai on October 4.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Via a Facebook Live from Facebook’s Mumbai office, a discussion on the issue of hunger hosted by television personality Mini Mathur had adman and film-maker R Balki, the Founder of Feeding India - Ankit Kawatra, celebrity chef Vicky Ratnani, CMO of UFO Moviez Siddharth Bhardwaj, UNWFP Director of Communications, Marketing and Advocacy - Corinne Woods, actor Gladys Kyotungire, and UNWFP India Director Hameed Nuru as participants.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 60-second cinema advertisement has been conceived by advertising legend Sir John Hegarty and The Garage Soho, directed by Lynne Ramsay and produced by Somesuch &amp;amp; Co. SAWA, in association with WFP, will air ‘Feed Our Future’ on cinema screens in more than 30 countries with a call to action to download WFP’s mobile app, ShareTheMeal.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;strong&gt;What the Ad says&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ad shows a bustling news conference with journalists vying to interview the recipient of a breakthrough medical research award. But the journalists learn that there was ultimately no medical breakthrough – the chilling conclusion reveals that Miriam Adeke, the young woman in question, had in fact died of hunger when she was only eight years old. “The creative challenge was to find a way of engaging the audience without resorting to endless images of starving children. Creating empathy by reminding the viewer that when a child dies, we all lose,” Sir John Hegarty said over a video message.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Watch the ad here&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/eqrZdUK5C_k" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The FB marketing drive&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saket Jha Saurabh, Head - Entertainment Partnerships, Facebook India spoke of Facebook’s association with the campaign, which is supported by a Facebook and Instagram marketing drive.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook is bringing the campaign to life through an integrated digital campaign. A team of award-winning creatives and Facebook’s Creative Shop have come together to create a Facebook Messenger experience that will give viewers the opportunity to engage with a bot version of the main character from the ad and learn more about hunger by searching ‘ShareTheMeal’ on Messenger. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hunger must be tackled&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“This is the first time in India that a campaign of this magnitude has run towards a global cause,” said Sanjay Gaikwad, Managing Director of UFO Moviez. “We’re happy to address the issue of global hunger in India with the UN World Food Programme. Cinema is the most impactful medium to deliver such a message to the audience in a highly captive environment.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Three million children die every year of hunger or malnutrition," Woods said. “When partners like SAWA and their members step up, it helps us create a movement and generate support for our work to ensure that every child has the vital food and nutrition they need – not only to survive - but also to thrive," she added.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I wanted to join the fight against hunger so that children across India and the world will never have to go hungry. As a film-maker, I know first-hand the power of cinema to inspire and engage people. The fact that the WFP’s #FeedOurFuture campaign will be screening across the country makes me sure that we really can make a difference. The premise is simple and striking - by denying access to nutritious and sufficient food to a generation of children, we can't deny the future world of the many doctors, scientists, film-makers and change-makers we could be in the making, simply because they do not have access to food, something that should be their unconditional right," Balki observed at the event.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millennials, who are educated, socially aware and a hard to reach demographic, make up a large part of the cinema audience and these are the people that are expected to facilitate change.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hindu Group names Pradeep Gairola as Digital Media Business Head </title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital/the-hindu-group-names-pradeep-gairola-as-digital-media-business-head_92383.html</link>
      <description>The Hindu Group has appointed Pradeep Gairola as Business Head for its Digital Media business.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Gairola is an industry veteran and has extensive exposure to all aspects of building a digital company — subscription, commerce and advertising. In his association of over two decades in media, he has been associated with ABP Group, Mid-Day and Times of India Group. More recently he also has experience growing education technology businesses as Chief Operating Officer of Meritnation. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;He will lead the growth plans of The Hindu Group for its digital business. He will grow the current advertising revenue stream while also gradually building the subscription business for its flagship brand The Hindu, which recently completed 140 years, as well as Business Line, The Hindu Tamil, Sports Star and Frontline. He will also lead the development of new products that the Group plans to launch to serve new target segments as well as to strengthen engagement with its current digital audiences. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In last 18 months, The Hindu Group has experimented with digital subscription and commerce through its epaper offering as well as its first paid app The Briefcase that delivers five most relevant stories for the day. It also has an AI-based digital education app and website, STEP (Standardized Testing for English Proficiency), which tests for English proficiency in reading, writing, listening and speaking and offers a range of training programs based on consumer needs. Additional digital products requiring subscription or registration include a children-oriented Young World Club, a BusinessLine on Campus offering continuous business education and BusinessLine Portfolio that gives research-backed investment advice to its subscribers.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quintillion Media network clocks over 30 million unique visitors in Sept</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/industry-briefing/quintillion-media-network-clocks-over-30-million-unique-visitors-in-sept_92384.html</link>
      <description>Online publication and content creator Quintillion Media has claimed to have reached 1 million subscribers on YouTube and nearly 8 million followers on Facebook. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to a statement issued by the company, the platform has garnered more than 100 million pageviews and over 30 million unique visitors on its websites, along with 10 million unique visitors on YouTube in September. Quintillion Media has a monthly reach of 170 million+ and nearly 1 billion impressions on Facebook.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In September,&amp;nbsp;the group’s flagship products thequint.com and hindi.thequint.com took home prizes across 15 categories at some of the prestigious awards. Bloomberg|Quint (BQ), a joint venture between Quintillion Media (74%) and Bloomberg Media (26%) was conferred with ‘Website of the Year (Business)’ award in the English language category.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ritu Kapur, Co-founder &amp;amp; CEO of Quintillion Media, said, “We have consistently used technological innovations to transform the digital news space in India through our two platforms, Bloomberg|Quint and The Quint. The unique mix of strong, credible journalism and novel digital reporting formats has helped us achieve this amazing milestone and establish The Quint as the go-to-platform for young, digitally-savvy users to access high-quality and relevant news content.”</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple, Google, Amazon top 2018 Best Global Brands: Interbrand Report</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing/apple-google-amazon-top-2018-best-global-brands-interbrand-report_92385.html</link>
      <description>Interbrand has announced Apple, Google, and Amazon as the three most valuable brands in its 2018 Best Global Brands report, with luxury and retail as the two dominant sectors. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For six consecutive years, Apple and Google hold the top positions. Apple’s brand value grew by 16 percent to USD $214,480m, and Google’s brand value by 10 percent to USD $155,506m. Amazon achieved 56% growth and is the third brand to achieve a 100 billion dollar brand valuation (USD $100,764m), as well as the top performer among 28 brands with double-digit percent growth. Following Microsoft at #4 (USD $92,715m), are Coca-Cola (USD $66,341m), Samsung (USD $59,890m), Toyota (USD $53,404m), Mercedes-Benz (USD $48,601m), Facebook (USD $45,168m) with McDonald’s (USD $43,417m) at #10.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The five Top Growing Brands include Amazon (56 percent growth) 2017 new entrant Netflix (45 percent), Gucci (30 percent), 2017 new entrant Salesforce.com (23 percent), and Louis Vuitton (23 percent). After five years as the Top Growing Brand, Facebook declines six percent. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This year, the list features two new entrants and three re-entrants. Spotify joins at #92 (USD $5,176m), and Subaru at #100 (USD $4,214m) for the first time. Chanel re-enters at #23 (USD $20,005m). Hennessy also returns at #98 (USD $4,722), and Nintendo at #99 (USD $4,696m).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“A decade after the global financial crisis, the brands that are growing fastest are those that intuitively understand their customers and make brave iconic moves that delight and deliver in new ways,” said Charles Trevail, Global Chief Executive Officer of Interbrand. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The days of talking about why transformation is a business imperative are over. It’s now time to mobilize. How? By cutting through complexity and unlocking the inner strength of your brand to channel the confidence to make change happen. After all, being brave in the face of turbulence today is no longer optional; it’s the price of entry to even be in the game,” said Ashish Mishra, Managing Director, Interbrand India.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;More than half of the Best Global Brands came from five sectors: Automotive (16), Technology (13), Financial Services (12), Luxury (9), and Fast-Moving Consumer Goods (9). Luxury is the new Top Growing Sector in percentage terms (42%), replacing Retail, which continues impressive growth at second (36%). Electronics is third (20%), Sporting Goods is fourth (13%), followed by Financial Services (10%). &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The combined total value of the Top 100 crosses the two trillion dollar threshold with USD $2,015,312m, an increase of 7.7% from 2017. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now in its 19th year, the report’s 2018 theme is Activating Brave, and examines the role that brand strength plays in the bold transformation of the world’s leading businesses.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABP gears up for 2019 election with ‘Desh ka Mood’ show</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/industry-briefing/abp-gears-up-for-2019-election-with-desh-ka-mood-show_92386.html</link>
      <description>ABP News Network will begin its new show ‘Desh Ka Mood’ that will present a holistic and insightful chronicle of the general elections 2019. The show will have an in-depth analysis of the projections and the changing trends, helping the discerning viewer with the election build-up. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Talking about the show, Avinash Pandey, COO, ABP News Network, said, “Staying ahead of the industry, we started our very first show of 2019 elections on January 1st, 2018 and we are the first one to set a benchmark in setting decisive trends in terms of covering and engagement during the elections.  ‘Desh Ka Mood’ is a unique format that would add a touch of freshness to the entire election proceedings.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The show will be a complete one-stop shop on all aspects on the general elections and will cover a wide range of questions pertaining to ratings for national leadership, top of the mind issues and satisfaction parameters with the Central government. The format of the show will be to engage the well-versed audience to provide them with ‘food for thought’ with reference to the elections. The show aims at educating, updating and inspiring the viewers,” he added.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Desh Ka Mood’ will be on all India projections, 6 monthly waves of vote and seat share for all 29 states along with Delhi and UTs, making a cumulative projection for all 543 Lok Sabha seats.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Living Foodz presents the Station Master's Tiffin with Ranveer Brar</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/industry-briefing/living-foodz-presents-the-station-masters-tiffin-with-ranveer-brar_92387.html</link>
      <description>Station Master’s Tiffin is a series that journeys across India to celebrate this unique Indian mode of transport that everybody in India has a fond memory of. Resonating this emotion, LF, the travel, food and lifestyle channel embarks on an exciting adventure airing this 14 part special series that will be a romantic exploration of the Indian Railways and its intersection with food, culture and people.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The show will encapsulate the unique journey of Ranveer Brar –anchor and traveler who is shown as a restless explorer wanting to know his country at a deeper level while following the footsteps of India’s heroes and luminaries, he undertakes this journey on the Indian Railways, across its many bridges, platforms, compartments and meets the real India.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;From a salt train in Rajasthan to introducing Mahatma Gandhi’s journeys in the ‘3rd class, as was popularly known during British Raj to the trams in Kolkata to the Konkan Railway to Pamban Bridge at lands’ end in Rameshwaram to the no-inch-given local trains in Mumbai, the journey this is unlike an experience ever shown before on Indian television.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ranveer will be embracing the different forms of art, cuisine, religious places, local heroes, history, folklore, unique fans and lesser known places. The Station Master’s Tiffin will take you on this exciting journey across India; celebrating India in a presentation created like no other.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commenting on his experience with the show, Chef Ranveer Brar says, “Shooting for Station Master’s Tiffin has been an exhilarating experience! Being a part of the culinary field, I have had the opportunity to visit various countries and learn new culinary techniques. But travelling through my own country in trains, visiting some wonderful places, discovering inspiring stories of people who treat you as their own household member, was hands down one of the best experiences of my life. The entire journey encompasses all the four corners of the country and viewers will get to enjoy an insider’s perspective.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adding to this, Amit Nair, Business Head LF states, “From our original format content we’ve always been ambitious in capturing the unique stories of India and its culinary landscape. Station master’s tiffin takes that to another level. With more than a year in research, permissions and production that is international in look and feel, this is Event Television unfolding for the viewers. From breathtaking shots, colorful people, unseen locations and delectable food, this is a never before seen show capturing the glory of train travel, the people and the joys associated with it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you are a travel enthusiast and want to seek inspiration for your next Indian destination, or looking to do a family trip in one of the Railway’s most special trains, or are a foodie who delights on the visuals of television, or simply looking to taste some special delicacies of some of India’s special destinations, this show is for you. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;DS Group’s Catch Salts and Spices and Nerolac Paints are the sponsors on the show.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protinex is proud of its brand ambassador &amp; cricketing prodigy Prithvi Shaw</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing/protinex-is-proud-of-its-brand-ambassador-cricketing-prodigy-prithvi-shaw_92388.html</link>
      <description>Nutrition brand, Protinex, had signed on cricketing prodigy, India’s under-19 cricket team captain, Prithvi Shaw, as its brand ambassador earlier this year. The brand is proud of Shaw’s achievement, as he became the youngest Indian to score a hundred in his test debut match against West Indies. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, he is the 15th Indian batsman to score a hundred in his first test and the second youngest Indian to score a test century. The record is still held by cricketing legend Sachin Tendulkar. The young Mumbai cricketer will feature in key brand campaigns and initiatives for Protinex over the next five years.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commenting on this occasion, Himanshu Bakshi, Managing Director, Danone India said, “It’s a proud moment for brand Protinex. We salute Prithvi for his huge achievement. Being a sportsman, it’s very important to stay fit and maintain good muscle health. We signed up Prithvi as our brand ambassador as he resonates well with our brand’s promise of providing a healthy solution for an active lifestyle &amp;amp; good muscle health. We would like to congratulate him for his achievement and wish him luck for his future endeavours.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In India, Danone started its nutrition business in 2012 through the acquisition of the nutrition portfolio from Wockhardt Group. Danone's life nutrition business embodies a holistic nutrition approach offering a full range of products for pregnant mothers, infants, young children as well as adults, under recognized brands like Aptamil, Neocate, Farex, Protinex, Dexolac and Nusobee.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rooter renews association with Delhi Dynamos FC for the upcoming ISL season </title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/industry-briefing/rooter-renews-association-with-delhi-dynamos-fc-for-the-upcoming-isl-season_92390.html</link>
      <description>The Hero Indian Super League is back in action with its 5th edition, and Rooter, the sports social engagement platform, has again taken over its role as the official fan engagement partner of Delhi Dynamos FC, one of the most popular teams in the league. Continuing from where it left off last season, Rooter will provide unique virtual engagement for the club’s fans, who will be able to predict the outcome of every Delhi Dynamos game on the platform’s Prediction Game. Just like last year, Rooter will reward users with exclusive merchandise from the club.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Being a multi-sport platform, Rooter will help popularise the club, and the game of football, to fans of other sports to connect with newer audiences. During the matches, Rooter will provide live scores and statistics to the fans from the matches while also generating key data and insights on fan engagement metrics such as fan behaviour data and sentiment analysis for the club’s management.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The app will provide an opportunity for the team to engage with fans on the live match chat forum, thereby offering a great interactive platform for the club to build a relationship with its fans and promote their offerings.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dipesh Agarwal, Co-Founder, Rooter said, “We had a very successful association with Delhi Dynamos last year and are looking forward to having a great season this year as well. The team lineup looks great, with players such as Barcelona’s youth team player Adria Carmona adding pace while Slovenian midfielder Rene Mihelic bringing his experience of having been part of the winning Chennaiyin squad last year. We are hoping for a brilliant show from the team in a tournament that has turned to be the greatest advertisement of Indian football in the world!”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ashish Shah, CEO, Delhi Dynamos further added, “Rooter has established its identity as one of the world’s most unique and engaging dedicated sports social engagement platforms that makes the virtual experience of watching sports as exciting as being on-field. Throughout the last season, we had a great time interacting with our fans on the Rooter app and engaging with them substantially. The platform provides the best data, analysis and expert insights on the beautiful game which further enhances the user’s experience, while offering many fun, exciting and interactive avenues such as the Prediction game. We are looking forward to enjoying the season, and the beautiful game, with our fans and Rooter all over again.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rooter users will also have a chance to meet their favourite players from the club exclusively.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch: Brands need to create content, not communication: Amitabh Pande, IKEA</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing/watch-brands-need-to-create-content-not-communication-amitabh-pande-ikea_92324.html</link>
      <description>&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;A Bloomberg Quint Initiative&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amitabh Pande, Strategic Planner, IKEA India, speaks to exchange4media about the relevance of content marketing to&amp;nbsp;the success of an organisation and key performance indicators for a content marketing campaign. Pande believes that every brand needs a well thought-out content strategy and needs to bring that to life. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A detailed content marketing strategy is essential for the success of most organisations. Your thoughts?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;The simple answer is yes. I think the real question is: what does&amp;nbsp;that strategy means? As brands, we need to move from creating communication to creating content. Communication means speaking to consumers. Content creation, on the other hand, is done for the love of entertainment and engagement, and the brand is a part of it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The second part in content strategy is the authenticity of what a brand stands for. It needs to reflect in the content. So, it is not about creating content only to sell, but creating content that brings the values to&amp;nbsp;support what the brand stands for. If you call that a strategy, then yes, every brand needs a content strategy. If you look at most of the content that you consume today, you will realise that it is well thought-out and strategised. For example, if you look at the Marvel Avengers series, they have been working on their content strategy for the last 7-8 years. It is very well planned and deliberated. So this kind of a thinking is what you need. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are the key performance indicators for a&amp;nbsp;content marketing campaign?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;From a brand’s point of view, there are two ways to look at it. First is whether the content is watched, loved and shared. Second is whether your brand affinity is growing over a period if you are constantly engaging with consumers through content. But again, the big word is: Not to look at it in a short term, but look at it in a long term over a period of time.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;  Video:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/_LOu9254t1g" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aspire to help brand partners achieve their objectives: Sandeep Bhushan, Facebook</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/advertising/aspire-to-help-brand-partners-achieve-their-objectives-sandeep-bhushan-facebook_92338.html</link>
      <description>Advertisers and marketers continue to invest and increase ad spends on Facebook. The reason being that the platform provides them with a number of different ad formats starting from lead ads, dynamic product ads, carousal ads, stamp ad, canvas ad, slideshow ads to video ads, through which they can focus on their target ad sets efficiently.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;exchange4media spoke with Sandeep Bhushan, Director, Facebook India and South Asia, who also leads the Global Marketing Solutions (GMS) teams in India and South Asia, about Facebook’s offerings to several brands and advertisers that help them achieve their desired objective,&amp;nbsp;be it brand imagery or brand sales.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Edited excerpts: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What kind of advertising works best for brands on Facebook?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook at the core is a community of people where users get to connect with family, friends, communities, and follow trends. It allows advertisers to reach our users very quickly. Given this construct, Facebook has spent time making ad products to help advertisers achieve their objectives. Facebook works better than any other platform because of its real identity trait where one can reach out to a person perfectly as per the frequency desired by the advertiser. Hence, real identity, perfect sequencing, frequency and the scale of a large number of Indians sets up a marketing engine and a support system like none existed before.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In this context when we work with businesses, we engage with brands focusing on one variable which is ‘Value created’. Value happens on two-dimensions, one being brand imagery and the other is brand sales. Facebook&amp;nbsp;products are able to achieve both because of the power of outreach, perfect targeting and perfect scale.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We also measure the value of both these dimensions. Therefore, we report back brand imagery lift or sales lift with various tools and our third party partnership like that with Nielsen. Hence, the core of how we go to market includes three factors: improve imagery, improve sales and have a feedback report built on it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Have all the recent controversies about fake news, fake traffic etc&amp;nbsp;impacted brand spending on Facebook?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s an ongoing debate as to what quality of information one should act on and what should be ignored. However, consumer engagement on our platform continues to grow. At Facebook we shall continue to push two agendas - one being privacy and the other regarding usage of right contents on the platform. On the advertiser side, the conversation continues to be as to how can we create and prove value for businesses. Brand owners are interested in knowing if their investment resulted in good returns or not, to which the answer is a resounding&amp;nbsp;Yes. We have a long-standing partnership of trust with our advertisers. The advertising community in general has been very appreciative of the changes that we've been introducing and all the communication that we've been doing since past few months about the same. We completely believe that targeted advertising and privacy can co-exist. We just have to raise the bar of educating our consumers and giving them control on their advertising experience with respect to their own personal data.  Our consumers are aware of that and businesses are confident. Advertisers continue to see tremendous value and know there is no material consumer difference on the platform.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How has money spending on Facebook shifted in the last one year? As for money being spent on Facebook posts, is it more on videos now or any other medium?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook algorithm will constantly change to get best value for a consumer’s time, to be able to participate in meaningful social interactions. For consumers to spend more time on the platform we focus on curating one’s feed with right content as per the interest area.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We understand that video is the most pervasive way consumers are interacting today. Video is not just about a 30 min, 3 min or a 3 sec worth content but in fact much wider than that. For instance, when you go Facebook live, you are broadcasting potentially to 2 billion people, that’s the kind of impact a video has. It is about recognising how consumers behave differently in the context of videos. We believe our video products will continue to be most engaging, as they are in line with where the consumer is shifting to. Within each of these videos, advertising is a possibility.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How is Facebook helping brands organise themselves for digital success?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;I believe all consumers that matter today are on mobile. For instance, Facebook has more than 217 million monthly active users in India. NCCS ABC in this country is smaller than that, which means the consuming class in urban India is entirely on mobile. This presents a huge opportunity for us to help brands and advertisers in reaching out to their audience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additionally, we need to measure and find out if communication on platforms like Facebook and Instagram work. According to Millward Brown’s Meta study last year, which included several cross media platforms, where they measured the impact of TV, Facebook etc., Facebook was proven to be the most cost efficient medium for Brand Motivation (Consideration + Purchase Intent) against TV, other digital platforms and certainly against print and outdoor.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Finally, brands also need to understand the tools that marketers and advertisers need now to win. One way is by being creative and the other is investing in media planning. Studies such as that of Millward Brown can help us decide the percentage allocation between TV, print and outdoor mediums. Therefore the readiness for brands will be on two dimensions - a brand’s planning technique in various channels and the right creative for each of those channels.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is the current split between growing mobile and desktop ad revenue in India? With the evolving figures how will Facebook engage with brands to set them up for success?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Consumer time in India is virtually entirely mobile across every platform. Therefore, advertising dollar will chase consumer time. When we talk about brands, their focus is to connect with more consumers be it through Facebook or any other platform.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Facebook, bulk of user time is spent on mobile, and we are focused on building advertising for mobile. However, we also have the ability to deliver a certain kind of video ad type for desktops exclusively. For example, in a situation where a desktop is connected to a wi-fi connection and mobile is on 2G, we can customise and separately deliver two different kinds of advertising to the same consumer, but then it’s inconsequential as users are more mobile-friendly, because today, digital means mobile.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is Facebook's revenue aspiration from ad sales in India? What are the key drivers that will help you achieve it? &lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our revenue numbers are disclosed in our quarterly reports continent wise and not as per region. Our aspiration is that we want to partner brands as our reach allows us to help them deliver any objective they aim at. This starting from brand knowledge, brand awareness to brand love and then finally sales. Small businesses too avail our platform for their growth.   &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Today likes &amp;amp; shares can be bought and fiddled with, how do you ensure you have a pure measurement metric to record the correct data while you engage with brands?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When we speak of business outcomes we do not think of likes &amp;amp; shares. 95 per cent of consumers might not have ‘liked’ a share but must have received the brand’s message. While evaluating story readership on a website, reaction is only a few percentage point of people who have actually read the story. We partner with third party bodies like Nielsen to measure the impact on brand imagery to those who saw the ad v/s to those who did not. Nielsen measures the difference and is therefore able to say that because of Facebook advertising the brand moved up.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We also engage in complicated and sophisticated studies for e.g. Global First wherein Nielsen goes to retail and picks up sales data every week for brands that are advertising, and then reports back on whether advertising on Facebook impacted sales or not. Whatever be the business objective, our aim primarily is to ensure that we deliver the content correctly to the right audience and then we work on various measurements with partners to figure out what’s the best result.    &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;With the growing user base for Instagram, how does Facebook per se&amp;nbsp;position itself to brands?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Instagram consumer has a higher socio-economic classification. However, as an advertiser one doesn’t have to choose between the two platforms. Facebook can efficiently find where the consumer is and accordingly showcase the brand to that particular group. User’s identity is the same on both platforms and to use that advertisers don’t really have to make a choice.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How is Facebook planning to increase its user base in India, especially when we speak about tier&amp;nbsp;II&amp;nbsp;cities?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook globally works with the vision of helping build communities for everyone. We can’t build communities if we aren’t available to people living worldwide. We have various programs to be at the edge of connectivity and will remain to be part of such efforts globally. In a scenario where Jio builds a phone in India which is very well priced and opens up a new segment of internet users, at Facebook, we make sure our products are built for each and every platform that has a wide reach across the country in order to bring all of India online.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How has the privacy issue been addressed by Facebook for consumers in India post the Cambridge Analytica scandal?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The platform changes are global as privacy is a global concern and we are continually working towards educating our consumers and giving them control on their Facebook experience with respect to their own personal data. We are committed to letting our users take charge of privacy and have full control of their data and this is being done globally. For instance, apps that may have taken your permission once to use your data, will no longer be able to access it if they remain inactive for a specific amount of time. This is one such change. We have taken additional steps to put people more in control of their privacy and redesigned our entire settings menu on mobile devices from top to bottom to make things easier to find. We also announced a few more changes to our platform and APIs to maintain trust with people who use our products and the data ecosystem built around Facebook. In addition, we have also updated our ‘Terms of Service’ and ‘Data Policy’ to make them easier to read and more transparent about how we collect and use people's data.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>News18's Rajiv Singh joins SonyLIV as Head- Ad Sales and Monetisation</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital/news18s-rajiv-singh-joins-sonyliv-as-head-ad-sales-and-monetisation_92351.html</link>
      <description>Sony Pictures Network India’s video streaming platform SonyLIV has appointed Rajiv Singh as Head - Ad Sales and Monetization in September. This update was mentioned in his LinkedIn profile, however, when contacted Singh declined to comment. He will be reporting to Uday Sodhi, EVP and Head Digital Business, SPN India.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Previously, Singh served as the Business Head for News18.com for nearly two years. In the past he had taken care of digital ad sales at Flipkart for more than a year. Singh’s experience spans over two&amp;nbsp;decades across different media sectors such as, Star India where he served as the Vice-President of Sales. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;He was also responsible for setting up Amagi Media, and prior to that, he was part of Radio Mirchi in various capacities across India.&amp;nbsp;Singh is an alumnus of IIM Kozhikode.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media Ace Jury Meet: Objective parameters trump "preconceived notions"</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing/media-ace-jury-meet-objective-parameters-trump-preconceived-notions_92352.html</link>
      <description>The jury meet for the fourth edition of exchange4media’s Media Ace awards was held in Mumbai on Wednesday. A grand jury of 13 marketers led by Harit Nagpal, MD and CEO, Tata Sky, held&amp;nbsp;a&amp;nbsp;day-long deliberation to choose the most deserving agencies and agency heads who have been heralding change in the industry while delivering exceptional results for their clients. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The jury decided to choose the winners based on a simple voting process, awarding the top honour to the entry that won the most votes. While in most categories there was a clear winner who trumped all others by a significant margin, in some categories the jury was spoilt for choice and had&amp;nbsp;to declare a&amp;nbsp;tie&amp;nbsp;and honour two best entries. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In choosing the winners for the Agency of the Year, Digital Agency of the Year, Network of the Year, Network Head of the Year, Agency Head of the Year, and Digital Agency Head of the Year awards, the jury strictly went by data and objective parameters. The jury based their votes on the data on businesses won and lost during the judging period and the quality of those wins and loses. “In the judging process we relied a lot on data, events, and activities which were more objective in nature than use our preconceived notions on the entries,” said Nagpal on the jury process. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The jury used data gathered from the agency and from the Research Company Evaluating the Media Agency Industry (RECMA) to judge the entries. The jury made sure that past wins or the overall perception about an agency or an agency head did not influence the votes in favour of or against a particular entry. Nagpal and other jury members looked for innovation in processes and chose to award change-makers and thought leaders.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The grand jury which deliberated along with Nagpal included: Amit Tiwari, Vice President, Marketing, Havell’s, Jishnu Sen, Chief Marketing Officer, Big Bazaar, Kashyap Vadapalli, Chief Marketing Officer, Pepperfry, Manasi Narasimhan, Vice-President, Marketing and Communications, South Asia, MasterCard, Mayank Shah, Category Head, Parle Products, Nishant Kashikar, Country Manager, Tourism Australia, Rajan Bhalla, Chief Business Officer &amp;amp; Group Chief Marketing Officer, HT Media, Sachin Dingankar, Head Marketing, Zydus Wellness, Sagar Boke, Head of Marketing - Consumer Products Business and Business Head - Spices, Tata Chemicals, Shabnam Panjwani, Executive Vice President &amp;amp; Head Marketing &amp;amp; Communications, Edelweiss Group, Sujith Sudhakaran, Sr. Director, Brand Marketing, and Vikas Khanchandani, Chief Executive Officer, Republic TV. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Media Ace awards will be announced on October 16.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We need to look at Havas per se as an entire concept: Vishnu Mohan and Rana Barua</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/advertising/we-need-to-look-at-havas-per-se-as-an-entire-concept-vishnu-mohan-and-rana-barua_92354.html</link>
      <description>"What you will soon find is the kind of expertise and the rollout of the integration journey; how we would rollout this working together as a concept, getting the entire strength of this group, which is doing magnificently well outside. We have not even tapped most of it in this country,"&amp;nbsp;announces Vishnu Mohan CEO, Havas Group India &amp;amp; South East Asia/ CEO Havas Media APAC as he introduces his one day old India Group CEO, Rana Barua. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As clearly defined by Mohan, Barua’s biggest challenge as the Group CEO is to focus on integration of all Havas business and make maximum out of each. “If you look at Havas Group as a concept, it has advertising, it has media, health and if you look at the group per se, to which Havas belongs, it has Universal Music, which I would like to work closely with. There is also Gameloft, which is another big asset the group has and there is Dailymotion. These are the assets which we can work closely with,” Barua explains. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mohan explains that the plans to merge and integrate all the group assets started sometime early last year. However, it has formally&amp;nbsp;come to India only now. “Yes, it began last year. But it has been rolled out bit by bit. We are not rushing into a blanket timeline, but we are on the path to making it happen in every single market. Actually in my region, after India, the only market left is Malaysia, all of the rest are under an integrated structure,” he adds.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;He further added that while everyone talks about content and data as the two most important things which drive business very few are able to use it in an integrated manner. “If you see, content sits largely with the creative side of things and data sits with media. So how do you make these two important things talk for each other if you do not create a structure that allows them to talk? And this is a big challenge which everyone recognises. All of the networks understand that the integration is key, because you cannot make content and data work together unless you create a structure. Fortunately, our scale, size and less silos, make it a lot easier.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The media experts, also talked about the burning industry issue of pitches being driven by price discounts and not strategy. “I wouldn't say that this is 100 per cent true, but I wouldn't say that this is not true either, because at the end of the day, for any client who spends millions of dollars in advertising, prices will be key because any client would want to see the most optimised media planning in the best price,” said Mohan. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;However, Mohan adds that it must not come at the cost of diminishing the value of strategy. “But I think some clients are doing it, and it is happening everywhere. When we talk about media prices, under-cutting on fees is completely different. If agencies are devaluing themselves by undermining their own value by going low on commission, then that's a completely different problem. But the prices bid is something else. That's a challenge, and if I put it through the lens of a client, then why wouldn't I want the lowest and best price from any agency,” he added. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barua, who in his previous two stints has spent almost a decade in creative agencies, says the problem exists there too. “Whether you see it from the creative side, or the client's side, it's a common problem. Clients will always try to get the maximum buck out of work. Most of our integrated propositions have always worked on that. But I think the big change that you will probably see coming forward, is that it is getting very tough. I think it's natural that clients will ask for it, so it's up to the group, the network, or the agencies to take a hard stand on it,” said Barua.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mohan, however, believes, that a part of the solution lies with digital. “Digital is the biggest leveler now where skill has become more important than scale. Therefore with skills, you can outwit the scale. Also, when you look at the level of platform related buying, etc., these are all audience planning where we are trying to marry the inputs to the outcomes. And as the world moves more towards accountable media spending, this whole notion of pricing will actually go away, because what will really matter would not be so much the price of the media, but what it would take to actually get a unit sold. And that is what really matters. What is involved in a unit being sold is a combination of so many things, such as strategy, thinking, planning and targeting. Pricing is just one element,” Mohan said.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPN, Tata Sky continue to lock horns over channel drop</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/mediatv/spn-tata-sky-continue-to-lock-horns-over-channel-drop_92357.html</link>
      <description>A day after Sony Pictures Network (SPN) issued a statement condemning Tata Sky for choosing to drop 22 SPN channels from its subscription, sources in Tata Sky claimed that the channels dropped barely comprise 3 per cent viewership. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Ten SPN channels that have 97 per cent viewership are still available on Tata Sky. It’s true that we have not renewed the contract with the network, but channels are available to our subscribers as we have bought them as per the Reference Interconnect Offer (RIO) available with TRAI,” claimed a reliable source who did not wish to be quoted. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPN, however, claims that the channels discontinued include the likes of Sony Earth and Sony Mix which, as per TRPs, are mostly among the top three channels in their respective categories.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sources in Tata Sky confirmed that TV Today channels, which&amp;nbsp;were affected by the move, were back on the platform by Wednesday noon. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Industry sources claim that the dispute between the two started sometime in July when ahead of the&amp;nbsp;renewal of its three-year contract with Tata Sky, SPN sought a&#13;
hike in its monthly rates considering an&amp;nbsp;increase in the&amp;nbsp;subscriber base of the former&#13;
in last three years.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Tata Sky’s subscriber base has increased from 10 million to 16 million in the last three years, which means increased consumption. On the basis of this, we sought a hike in our monthly payment. Also, we must clarify that we never increased our channel rates as that is not permissible under TRAI regulations,” said the SPN spokesperson. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;However, the increased rates were not acceptable to Tata Sky, which in turn discontinued the contract. Following this, Sony sent a notice to Tata Sky, asking for discontinuation of its channels from its operating system. However, to resolve the crisis, Tata Sky switched to al carte consumption of SPN channels instead of buying the network’s bouquet comprising 35 odd channels.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sources claim that the move will cause significant advertising loss to SPN, considering the&amp;nbsp;drop of its 22 channels from the bouquet.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Earlier&amp;nbsp;this week, SPN termed Tata Sky’s move as an “unfortunate event”. In a statement, SPN said, “Tata Sky unilaterally chose to drop 22 SPN channels from its subscription, even though SPN has not increased the rates of its channels.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The statement further reads, “SPN channels are leaders in their genres and the network one of the most popular in the country. By unilaterally dropping the channels, Tata Sky is depriving it's viewers of the opportunity to watch world class entertainment and live sporting action. Further, by compelling existing subscriber to give separate ‘missed’ calls even to continue watching the SPN channels they have already paid for, Tata Sky is not acting in the consumers’ interest.” &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meanwhile, sources in SPN claim they are open to negotiations if Tata Sky is willing to renegotiate.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Mobile Marketing Conference – Screenage at The Maddies</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing/announcing-mobile-marketing-conference-screenage-at-the-maddies_92358.html</link>
      <description>The days are inching closer for the forthcoming conference on Mobile Marketing – Screenage that is set to take place on October 31 in Mumbai. The event will see discussions on the effective measures for a fruitful mobile marketing strategy, such that brand marketers in India can allocate more funds to mobile marketing and therefore bridge the gap between consumer behaviour and mobile marketing budget.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the Mobile Marketing - Screenage conference leading Indian experts of content, digital and mobile marketing will discuss on the theme ‘Mobile marketing: Claiming a bigger share of the marketer’s purse’. The full-day conference will have keynote sessions by industry experts, panel discussions with digital marketing heads &amp;amp; CEOs, a fireside chat and speaker sessions by top brands followed by the awards night that makes up for high brand visibility and great networking opportunities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fireside chat session will be chaired by Ashish Bhasin, Chairman &amp;amp; CEO, Dentsu Aegis Network South Asia. A total of three Panel Discussions, two keynote speaker sessions and four standalone sessions are to be held at the event. Keynote speaker Unnat Verma- Managing Director, Pizza Hut (India Subcon) - Yum Restaurants International will cover the topic ‘Consumer Engagement in a Mobile Centric World’. He will address every advertisers’ challenge of engaging with multi-screen users in order to build trustworthy brands in a mobile first world. The session will also include details on how to engage consumers through emerging mobile technologies and the check and balances to ascertain effective growth in the mobile marketing pie. The second keynote speaker session will discuss the topic ‘Leveraging Mobile to deliver on Business Objectives’ setting the agenda for utilising mobile both as a platform and channel to drive growth.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first panel discussion at the event will be moderated by Sanjay Trehan, Digital &amp;amp; New Media Consultant, and will cover the topic ‘Brand building on Mobile Only: A Reality or Myth? Industry experts at the e4m conference will discuss if mobile is strong enough to become a medium of brand building and if not where is the gap. And if mobile marketing has become all about social media. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The second panel discussion revolves around the topic ‘Journey to the Next Mobile Frontier’, wherein the discussion will be based on utility apps, mobile audio, explosion of entertainment options in OTT video and innovation shaping up the app-mania indigenously. Speakers involved in the panel sessions will be Channan Sawheny, Head of Digital Marketing Consumer India - Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson; Mahip Dwivedi, Heads Mobile Marketing App – Flipkart; Sai Narayan, Associate Director &amp;amp; Head Marketing - Paisabazaar.com; Abhishek Joshi - SVP &amp;amp; Head-Marketing, Subscriptions &amp;amp; Content Licensing - Digital Business, Sony Pictures Networks India; Shouneel Charles, SVP &amp;amp; Business Head – Digital-Times Network; Jason Wu- Chief Strategy Officer – Momagic; Nachiket Pantvaidya- Group COO &amp;amp; CEO- Balaji Telefilms; Jahid Ahmed- Head- Digital Marketing &amp;amp; Web analytics- HDFC Bank; and Vinay Singhal- Co Founder &amp;amp; CEO- WittyFeed. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first standalone speaker session will cover the topic ‘The mCommerce Opportunity’ discussing if brands and the mobile ecosystem was working together to fully realise the mCommerce Opportunity. The second standalone session will include a thorough brainstorming conversation on the topic ‘The Mobile Wallet Wars’ picking up on which providers were best in the market: Mobile payments, staging Digital Wallets &amp;amp; the New Changes; Building a Mobile Service through Partnership and Innovation. The third standalone session talks about ‘The Mobile Marketing Performance Dilemma’ discussing how can marketing professionals decode the measurement puzzle to indicate the ROI in mobile. The panel will also suggest ways on what can be done to grow the mobile marketing spends in India. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, the fourth session will involve speakers conversing on the topic ‘Tech first to be mobile ready’. It will include an in-depth dialogue on how CTOs, product heads and other disciplines are working together to ensure being in line with progress in technology to make most of the mobile ecosystem and what have been the tech lessons from mobile experiences so far. Speakers for the fourth standalone sessions will include  Sanjay Gupta- Marketing Head-Uber; Sankalp Potbhare- MD South Asia- Kraft Heinz; Sandeep Verma- President- Bajaj Corp; and Siddharth Bannerjee – EVP Marketing, Vodafone.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For more details on speakers and the agenda, visit: &lt;a href="https://e4mevents.com/the-maddies-awards-2018/"&gt;https://e4mevents.com/the-maddies-awards-2018/&lt;/a&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star India likely to earn Rs 200-250 crore from PKL 6&#13;
</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/mediatv/star-india-likely-to-earn-rs-200-250-crore-from-pkl-6_92359.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/1538623331_wum8Ti_PKL_graphic.jpg" style="width:348px;height:450px;float:right"&gt;It may not be as popular as an IPL or a Cricket World Cup, but Pro Kabaddi League (PKL) is definitely one of the most popular non-cricketing events in India today. The sixth season of the league&amp;nbsp;will kick off on October 7 and official broadcaster Star India is all set for the extravaganza with some big brands on board.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to an estimate by media planners, Star is likely to generate Rs 200-250 crore in advertising revenue from TV and digital. The broadcaster last year signed a five-year title sponsorship deal with Vivo for Rs 300 crore (Rs 60 crore a year). Apart from Vivo, the channel has roped in Thumps Up as ‘powered by’ sponsors and&amp;nbsp;Bajaj Electricals, Honda &amp;amp;&amp;nbsp;Tata Motors&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;deshketruck&lt;/em&gt; as ‘associate’ sponsors and RR Kables as ‘broadcast’ sponsors.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Talking about Tata Motors'&amp;nbsp;association with the league,&amp;nbsp;UT Ramprasad, Head-Marketing &amp;amp;&amp;nbsp;Brand Communication- Tata Motors Commercial Vehicle Business Unit, said,&amp;nbsp;"The successful experience&amp;nbsp; of the earlier&amp;nbsp;seasons&amp;nbsp;has encouraged Tata Trucks to come on board with&amp;nbsp; PKL as a central sponsor (in addition to&amp;nbsp;our association with UP Yodha team), thus allowing a deeper and more integrated association with the sport. This association is&amp;nbsp;allowing us to&amp;nbsp;showcase&amp;nbsp;our&amp;nbsp;entire range, thus&amp;nbsp;garnering greater ROI on the investment made. Among our portfolio, we are liaising for Tata Yodha as a brand that&amp;nbsp;stands for kabaddi."&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tata Motors has been associated with PKL for&amp;nbsp;three years now. The partnership began&amp;nbsp;with an&amp;nbsp;association with&amp;nbsp;U-Mumba in Season 4 and then&amp;nbsp;UP Yodha began in Season 5.&amp;nbsp;&lt;p&gt;According to RR Kabel, kabaddi is one of India’s best loved&#13;
sports and its fan following includes many of their priority markets and user&#13;
segments.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;“RR Kabel is delighted to be associated with Pro Kabaddi&#13;
League for the second year in a row. The excitement of the sport and the&#13;
passion and dedication of the players is a great parallel to the spirit of RR&#13;
Kabel,” said Shishir Sharma, Head of Marketing, RR Kabel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;“We built our sponsorship into an integrated online/offline&#13;
marketing plan that enhances the relationship between our brand, our customers,&#13;
and kabaddi. This includes social media contests,&amp;nbsp;digital activations, and&#13;
user-generated content. Last year, we saw a direct connection between our&#13;
sponsorship association and our digital engagement and we look forward to the&#13;
next phase of marketing innovation,” Sharma added &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though Star has not given out any official figures yet, sources in the industry claim that the channel quoted Rs 8-12 crore for ‘associate’ and Rs 5-6 crore for ‘other’ sponsorships. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to media planners, around 70-80 per&amp;nbsp;cent inventory has been sold already&amp;nbsp;and the&amp;nbsp;rest&amp;nbsp;has been kept on hold for sale later at higher rates. For the sixth season, the ad rate&amp;nbsp;for a 10-second slot during matches is estimated to be around Rs 1.5- 2 lakh. “They have sold all sponsorships, from ‘associate’ to ‘co-partners’. They could be clocking anything between Rs 200 and Rs 250 crore,” said a media planner.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another senior media planner says that PKL is a good property and Star does a good job selling it. “There are a lot of sports inventory in the market right now. But PKL is a good property and Star does a good job at selling it. I will be surprised if they don’t increase their sales by 20-25 per cent this year,” said the planner. “Rs 200-250 is a fair figure to go. If the market responds well to Star’s proposal, it can be&amp;nbsp;close to Rs 300 crore,” he added.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to GroupM’s ‘Sporting Nation in the Making’ report 2018, going by television ratings, PKL is the second-most popular league in India after IPL. The gap between the TV ratings of PKL and&amp;nbsp;IPL is narrowing (in 2017, PKL delivered 1.5 TVR with 312 million reaches and IPL delivered 2.7 TVR with 411 million) and PKL has emerged as a popular sport property. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Validating the report, another media planner said that&amp;nbsp;in terms of reach, ratings and cost efficiency, “PKL is nothing less than IPL.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Brands are leveraging on this property. In today’s scenario, PKL&amp;nbsp;is the only non-cricketing property in India encashed by advertisers. In terms of reach, ratings and cost efficiency, it's nothing less than IPL. For brands that want to target male audience but do not have the kind of budget to be associated with IPL, PKL is the best entry point,” the planner explained.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;During the fifth season, the tournament expanded, both in terms of number of teams and duration. Four new franchises-- Gujarat Fortunegiants, Tamil Thalaivas, UP Yoddha and Haryana Steelers--were added, taking the total to 12.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to&amp;nbsp;Vidhu Sagar, National Director - PointNine Lintas at MullenLowe Lintas Group, PKL is "doing great" and is "shaping up quite well".&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“PKL is a great property. It's a property which is doing extremely well. Star India is of course banking on it for the avenues. Since it's the sixth season, the league has caught the momentum now&amp;nbsp;and they will be consolidating from here. They have everything to look forward to. If PKL continues to go this way, I won’t be surprised if they soon cover the gap between them and IPL. It's shaping up quite well. Of course, IPL is the way ahead in terms of revenues, rates, appeal and traction, but kabaddi is an Indian sport and so has given rise to this interesting phenomenon. This is a league which is now ready to give reward to the broadcaster.”&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;Indranil Das Blah, Founding Partner at Kwan Entertainment and Marketing Solutions, believes that the sixth season of PKL should be successful. “PKL&amp;nbsp;has done well for itself  every season since its inception. I think it should be a successful season,” he said.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Beginning October 7, the league will travel across 13 host cities and culminate in Mumbai. The 12 teams have been divided into 2 zones of 6 teams each. Each of them will be playing 15 intra-zone and 7 inter-zone matches prior to the playoffs. The playoff stage will comprise three action-packed qualifiers and two eliminators scheduled to take place in Kochi and Mumbai.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;exchange4media reached out to Star for an official response on the story, but is yet to get a reply.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aparna Kulkarni resigns as GM &amp; Marketing Head of Movies Now and MN+ </title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements/aparna-kulkarni-resigns-as-gm-marketing-head-of-movies-now-and-mn_92361.html</link>
      <description>Aparna Kulkarni, General Manager and Marketing Head of Movies Now and MN+ has resigned from the Times Network, according to media reports. She is expected to join Diamond Producers Association as Director of Marketing Communications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kulkarni has worked with the Times Network for two years, during which,  she was also Deputy General Manager and Marketing Head, Movies Now and MN+.  She previously worked with Star India for four years and also with Viacom18. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Alumni of Mudra Institute of Communications, Ahmedabad (MICA), Kulkarni holds a bachelor's degree in Psychology from Sophia College, Mumbai and has also worked with other reputable companies such as, CNN IBN and Big Broadcasting.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hershey India awards communications mandate to Adfactors PR&#13;
&#13;
</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing/hershey-india-awards-communications-mandate-to-adfactors-pr_92362.html</link>
      <description>Hershey India Pvt Ltd, a part of The Hershey Company, a leading global snacking giant and the largest producer of quality chocolates in North America, has awarded its communications assignment to Adfactors PR, India’s largest public relations firm. The assignment follows a multi-agency pitch process.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adfactors PR has been tasked with leading strategic communications and provide integrated solutions for the company’s corporate reputation and brands in India.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/1538635731_ZWfdV0_image001_%281%29.jpg" style="width:300px;height:275px;vertical-align:middle"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;Herjit Bhalla, Managing Director, Hershey India  &lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;Herjit Bhalla, Managing Director, Hershey India, said, “We are delighted to get Adfactors PR onboard as our communications partner. We are confident that Adfactors’ strong capabilities will help us shape opinion amongst our consumers and key stake holders. We look forward to Adfactors being a strategic partner in driving our business goals.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/1538635745_HLcfl8_image002.jpg" style="width:299px;height:259px;vertical-align:middle"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;Madan Bahal,&amp;nbsp;Adfactors PR Co- founder and Managing Director &lt;/em&gt;   &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaking about the mandate, Adfactors PR Co- founder and Managing Director, Madan Bahal, said, “We are thrilled and honoured to be selected as the communications partner for Hershey India. Our team is determined to drive a positive impact through compelling PR campaigns for the company and its brands.”</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Langoor launches an exclusive B2B focused unit- Langoor Business</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing/langoor-launches-an-exclusive-b2b-focused-unit-langoor-business_92363.html</link>
      <description>Langoor, a full-service digital-first agency made of creative technologists, has launched a specialised unit focusing on the B2B space called – Langoor Business. Through the course of 2016 the Langoor team realised that the B2B digital space is being under-served across APAC region. They started working closely with a host of clients in the space. To help B2B brands reach their full potential, the team felt the need to launch a dedicated unit specialising only in B2B.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Langoor Business excels in the integration needed to understand a B2B mandate with the passion to create work that stands apart – to help brands reach their abilities. They help B2B companies through digital strategy, digital transformation, creative services and digital marketing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Langoor Business is being led by Saurabh Das, SVP at Langoor Digital. Das has more than 18 years of experience across marketing communication services, client management and business management.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commenting on this new initiative, Saurabh Das, SVP, Langoor Digital, said, “Over the last 3 years we noticed a strong need for a focussed delivery model to address the ever-growing demands from B2B brands. A need that can be addressed only by making focussed investments in appropriate technologies and talent that understands the nuances of B2B marketing. At Langoor Business, we have talent that runs deep in delivering for B2B clientele - be it creating immersive experiences leveraging new tech or delivering purposeful brand campaigns that hinge on deep customer/market insights derived from data and trends.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the recent years, we have successfully delivered large ABM campaigns for G2K (Global 2000) clients, where success depends on the critical amalgamation of data and analytics blended with media and technology – reaching audiences with a kind of precision that keeps getting better at the micro level.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venugopal Ganganna, CEO, Langoor, said, “This unit comes as a breakthrough for us and further reinforces our USP as Creative Technologists – who are redefining the world of conventional advertising and marketing. It is this creativity that has helped us gain confidence from existing B2B clients and launch this exclusive unit for them.” &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Langoor Business has been working with clients such as Mitsubishi, Adobe, Infosys, Intuit, Wipro, Edgeverve Systems, NIIT, Tech Mahindra, Aris Global, Accenture and the like in the B2B space.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magicbricks launches brand building digital solution for real estate developers</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing/magicbricks-launches-brand-building-digital-solution-for-real-estate-developers_92364.html</link>
      <description>Property website, Magicbricks, has come out with an industry-first brand building digital solution called Brand Store that is aimed at mid and small-size developers to drive brand affinity and create a strong connect with consumers.  &lt;br&gt;Bangalore-based 5 Elements Reality has become the first developer to use this innovative brand building solution to enhance its consumer reach.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a post Real Estate Regulatory Authority (RERA) world, older USPs like timely delivery, quality of construction and etc. have now become statutory norms for all developers leaving them with just one differentiator, the brand. This has opened up a world of opportunities for aspiring brands like 5 Elements Reality to be at par with the already established brands. And with digital becoming the way of life, Magicbricks’ Brand Store is an innovative digital solution that helps developers influence the consumers’ home buying decision through engaging video content. Brand Store also brings in a paradigm shift in developers’ increasing focus on digital from traditional channels of marketing, primarily print. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Capitalising on the increase in consumption of video content, Magicbricks Brand Store comprises a series of video based customised content that would help developers’ narrate their brand story to the consumers in an engaging, compelling and a persuasive manner to build reliability and trust on a neutral platform of Magicbricks. For consumers, it offers a peek into the other side of the developer and also understand their future plans and get an honest feedback from their existing customers and business partners. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commenting on the launch of Brand Store, Prasun Kumar, Marketing Head, Magicbricks said, “Every business needs to invest in its reputation and image to make a name, churn revenue and most important, be loved by consumers. So far in real estate, the consumer’s relationship with the developer has been very transactional, operating at a functional level and add to that the issues of trust deficit. There is little brand affinity for any developer.  The solution lies in a developer’s ability to tell his story in an environment that is seen as neutral, trustworthy and credible. Brand Store helps developers connect all these dots that are emerging in a new world order through engaging video content that is engaging, compelling and trustworthy.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaking at the launch Kashinath B, MD, 5 Elements Reality said, “In today’s internet age, where traditional media is getting replaced by digital media it is certainly the way forward in real estate. Magicbricks has always innovated with new products and we are happy to associate with them for first-of-its-kind Brand Store, which can do the job of building a Real estate brand in a much more efficient manner. Home buying is always an emotional journey and developer brands must drive brand affinity by connecting deeper with consumers. We are confident that Magicbricks Brand Store will help us in creating the consumer connect and establish trust and reliability.” &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Magicbricks Brand Store’s microsite will have five dedicated sections like Captain’s Innings, CEO’s Desk, Factoids, Future Ready and Testimonials. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Captain’s Innings enables developers showcase the person behind the brand. It covers topics like, life journey, milestones, family, hobbies and more; they will see the human side of the builder’s brand. Through CEO’s Desk, the consumers are presented with the professional aspects of the brand. The CEO talking about his brand and what it stands for will give your brand the launch pad it needs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Factoids feature all the interesting facts and trivia of the builder brand and buyers get to know the finer details about the brand. In Future Ready, potential buyers get to know how the builder is adapting to the changing policies, technology and consumer mind-set and this helps them take an informed decision. Testimonials will help create a positive disposition of the brand among the buyers. Developer will display all the testimonials of the stakeholders and consumers to strengthen their outlook towards their brand.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHAREit appoints Karam Malhotra as CEO for the Indian market&#13;
</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements/shareit-appoints-karam-malhotra-as-ceo-for-the-indian-market_92365.html</link>
      <description>SHAREit, India’s largest content-integrated distribution platform has appointed Karam Malhotra as the CEO for India. With an aim to deepen its reach into the Indian market, sharpen the focus on local consumers, attain more user base in India and build into an infrastructure company, Karam Malhotra will lead the business in the Indian market.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SHAREit recently acquired South India’s number one OTT platform FastFilmz which was co-founded by Karam Malhotra in 2015. With the acquisition of FastFilmz, Karam Malhotra, the founder of FastFilmz became the CEO of SHAREit India. In 2008, Malhotra started his career as a senior analyst in McKinsey &amp;amp; Company. In 2011, Karam went to Chicago, USA and attended Kellogg School of Management in Northwestern University. Karam then returned to McKinsey London where he ended up as a Junior Partner in the firm serving media, entertainment and tech clients in Asia and Europe. Besides being the co-founder of Fastfilmz, Karam also co-founded Greatest Common Factor (GCF), an ed-tech company which looks to revolutionize how students prepare for exams and consume digital first education content in the competitive learning space.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaking on the development, Karam Malhotra, CEO, SHAREit India says, “Increase in the digital content in India has always been at a high rate and will continue to grow over the years to come. Content developers in India are focusing on developing high quality content, country’s hugely diverse local markets still remains a challenge. SHAREit is looking forward to ramp up its presence in the country and capitalise on the massive shifts in consumer behavior. My vision for SHAREit is to nurture a community that looks to share all aspects of their digital entertainment, using technology at the core of new user experiences. I am excited to bring all our learnings from FastFilmz of serving the masses and apply that to SHAREit to further drive its popularity in the country.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;With an aim to become India’s leading social digital entertainment platform, SHAREit has collaborated with leading Indian content aggregators to strengthen its content catalogue. Recently, SHAREit has partnered with companies like Times Music, Speed Records, Comedy One and Juggarnaut book publishing etc. These partnerships with all the local content generators and aggregators have been made with an aim to become the largest source of entertainment for its users in India.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SHAREit has over 1.5 billion users globally and the app has reached out to more than 200 countries and regions and it is currently available in 39 languages. It is the most preferred platform for data sharing and content acquisition among internet users worldwide. SHAREit has over 400 million user base in India and wants to make digital content accessible for everyone.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Times Group launches Win Easy contest</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/industry-briefing/times-group-launches-win-easy-contest_92367.html</link>
      <description>Win Easy is a first of its kind consumer promotion by a publishing house. The Times Group has launched this initiative for the festive period starting in the week of Ganesh Chaturthi and ending in the Diwali week. The promotion will be live for nine weeks.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The aim of the Win Easy programme is to build up the festive fervour by encouraging consumers to shop to their heart’s content and get rewarded for it. The contest will be open to all consumers who shop for more than Rs. 2500 by purchasing products of any of the brands advertised in the Times Group publications viz., The Times of India, The Economic Times, Mirrors, Navbharat Times, Maharashtra Times, Ei Samay and Vijay Karnataka. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Consumers need to log on to www.wineasy.shop to upload their invoice, write a slogan and be eligible for the weekly draw. The draw will happen every week (defined as Monday to midnight of Sunday) and invoices dated within a respective week will be eligible for that week’s draw. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks to Win Easy, brands now have one more reason for advertising in the Times Group publications, as consumers are incentivised to purchase their products. The more they advertise, the more they stand to gain. Consumers stand to win a car every week. Other prizes include 40 inch TVs, Smartphones and 2gm gold coins. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now, Consumers and Advertisers have a lot to look forward to this festive season. For terms &amp;amp; conditions, please visit &lt;a href="https://www.wineasy.shop" rel="nofollow"&gt;www.wineasy.shop&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radio Nasha celebrates 35 years of 'Jaane Bhi Do Yaaro'</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/industry-briefing/radio-nasha-celebrates-35-years-of-jaane-bhi-do-yaaro_92370.html</link>
      <description>Nasha Premiere Nights is a flagship property of Radio Nasha where the magic of classics of 70s, 80s, and 90s is brought back to the silver screen. In both Delhi and Mumbai, in the last two years, films like ‘Qayamat Se Qayamat Tak’, ‘Silsila’, ‘Dilwale Dulhania Le Jayenge’, ‘Disco Dancer’, ‘Don’, ‘Maine Pyar Kiya’ and many others have been screened.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On 29th September 2018 Radio Nasha, in association with National Film Development Corporation, screened the cult classic ‘Jaane Bhi Do Yaaro’ to celebrate 35 years of the movie and pay tribute to Kundan Shah and Om Puri. The screening was a grand affair and was attended by cast of the movie - Satish Kaushik, Satish Shah, Rajesh Puri, Sudhir Mishra, wives of late Om Puri and Kundan Shah, and the crew. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/1538645308_XUew3e_NPN-JBJY-P2.jpg" style="width:400px;height:250px;vertical-align:middle"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The screening was preceded by a red carpet interaction with RJ Anmol who hosts the show ‘Ek Main Aur Ek Tu’. After the screening, the complete cast interacted with Radio Nasha and spoke to RJ Rohini who hosts Jhakkas Mornings about their special moments from the film and fondly shared behind the screen stories. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On this occasion, Harshad Jain, CEO – Radio and Entertainment, HT Media Ltd., said, “With Radio Nasha our endeavor to always to take our listeners for a nostalgic trip down the memory lane. Nasha Premier Nights is our initiative where we screen a classic of 70s, 80s and 90s in a large auditorium and reminisce the nostalgia with the listeners, cast and crew. Jaane Bhi Do Yaaro is a cult classic and with the screening we are sure that we gave our listeners a ‘money can’t buy’ experience. We are thrilled at the response we received from the listeners, sponsors and the star cast of the movie, and stand  committed to present many more “Cool Retro” experiences. ”</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICICI Bank CEO, Chanda Kochhar has quit</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing/icici-bank-ceo-chanda-kochhar-has-quit_92371.html</link>
      <description>Chanda Kochhar has quit as CEO of ICICI Bank with immediate effect. The board decided to appoint Sandeep Bakhshi as the Managing Director and Chief Executive Officer. His appointment will be for a period of five years until October 3, 2023, subject to various approvals. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to media reports, the private lender ICICI Bank on Thursday said that it has accepted Chanda Kochhar's request for early retirement. In a communication to BSE, the bank said: “The Board of Directors of ICICI Bank Limited accepted the request of Ms Chanda Kochhar to seek early retirement from the Bank at the earliest. The Board accepted this request with immediate effect. The enquiry instituted by the Board will remain unaffected by this and certain benefits will be subject to the outcome of the enquiry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Ms Kochhar will also relinquish office from the Board of Directors of the Bank’s subsidiaries The Board decided to appoint Mr. Sandeep Bakhshi as Managing Director &amp;amp; Chief Executive Officer. His appointment will be for a period of five years until October 3, 2023, subject to regulatory and other approvals.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The other terms and conditions of his appointment, such as remuneration, would remain unchanged. Separately, due to health reasons Mr MD Mallya, Independent Director, resigned from the Board and the same was accepted.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kochhar was earlier sent on forced leave pending an investigation into allegations of her having favoured family members in lieu of providing loans to a corporate house. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kochhar joined ICICI Bank in 1984 as a management trainee and had a dream run at the bank until controversies erupted. Kochhar, 56, who had headed ICICI Bank since May 2009, is also stepping down from the board of directors of its units, the bank said in the statement.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big FM ups core market ad rates by 12-15% this festive season</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/mediaradio/big-fm-ups-core-market-ad-rates-by-12-15-this-festive-season_92373.html</link>
      <description>With markets stabilizing post demonetisation and the implications of GST, BIG FM has spiked its national as well as region specific rates for the upcoming festive season. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Parallelly, BIG FM is also looking at partnering with advertisers for deep integration, long tenure and sponsorship sales. The radio network is invariably looking at providing a clutter free experience by reducing ad inventory in key markets. The radio network intends to increase rates by approximately 12 – 15 % in core markets and a rate correction Rs. 25 – 35 / 10 secs in smaller stations. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commenting on the same, Asheesh Chatterjee, CFO, BIG FM, says, "The idea is to offer our advertisers with unique value proposition by providing plethora of festival spikes, unique integration restricting cloud burst and providing extremely good ROIs for advertisers. With 90% of our stations ranked amongst the top stations as per IRS 2017, we look forward to seamlessly serving our advertisers and listeners with interesting and exciting content.”&amp;nbsp;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/1538653774_O7xhQP_gfx3.jpg"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Radio penetration has showed a growth of nearly 100% across India between 2014 and 2017 as per a report by IRS. Only 35% of Indians have access to the internet as compared to broadcast radio which has access to 99% of the Indian population. Radio medium also holds far stronger position over internet in priority states including Bihar, MP, Tamil Nadu, UP, West Bengal, Orissa etc.  &lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZEE5 expands presence globally </title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital/zee5-expands-presence-globally_92374.html</link>
      <description>Bringing its library of multilingual content to the South Asian diaspora and beyond across the world, ZEEL’s digital entertainment platform ZEE5 has been launched across platforms and will offer viewers around the globe a completely integrated entertainment offering both on-demand and Live TV across devices.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Outlining the global strategy, Amit Goenka, CEO – ZEE International and Z5 Global, said, “As a global content company, ZEE has always been at the forefront of bringing the best of Indian entertainment content to audiences around the world. With the launch of ZEE5 across 190+ markets, we have moved into the next phase of our growth story. Launching ZEE5 globally rather than in a staggered manner has been a conscious move in order to capitalise on the tremendous love and following the brand has amassed over the years overseas. This new chapter further strengthens us as a media &amp;amp; entertainment behemoth and reiterates our claim to the India story, bringing to our audiences around the globe an unrivalled content offering, using robust technology.” &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaking on the soft launch, Archana Anand, Chief Business Officer- ZEE5 Global said, “With over 1,00,000 hours of content across genres and languages, ZEE5 is the singular platform that Indians and South Asians have been waiting for. With the launch of ZEE5 globally, we intend to own the India peg completely and be the unequivocal go to destination for Indian content for South Asians and beyond, wherever they may be.”</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kishore Tadepalli to head JWT Mumbai</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/advertising/kishore-tadepalli-to-head-jwt-mumbai_92375.html</link>
      <description>With Rajesh Gangwani, head of JWT Mumbai moving on&amp;nbsp;to explore other avenues, J. Walter Thompson India has announced senior leadership changes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/1538714444_14DjdA_Kishore_Tadepalli.jpg"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kishore Tadepalli has taken&amp;nbsp;over as the head of JWT Mumbai.  Tadepalli&amp;nbsp;has around three decades of experience in advertising and marketing communications and is currently the Senior Vice President &amp;amp; Managing Partner of JWT Bengaluru.  Under his leadership JWT Bengaluru has shown remarkable growth and has produced some of the best work. A Thompsonite at heart, he has spent over 17 years with the agency and over the years, he has worked on a multitude of brands across categories in addition to leading large teams successfully. This is his second stint at&amp;nbsp;JWT Mumbai.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/1538714478_0SoJ3D_Rajesh_Gangwani.jpg"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/1538714493_uhfYbJ_Tarun_Rai.jpg"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commenting on Rajesh Gangwani, Tarun Rai, CEO,&amp;nbsp;J. Walter Thompson,&amp;nbsp;said, “Rajesh has been a ‘lifer’ at JWT, having started his career with us in 1991 at our Mumbai office. He grew through the ranks and got the opportunity to head our Bengaluru office in 2008 and was given the additional responsibility of Chennai in 2011. He came to head Mumbai in 2014. Under his leadership, JWT Mumbai has diversified its capabilities and built a very strong team. The office has shown strong growth since he took over. Rajesh has had an excellent career with us and I thank him for his contribution to the agency over the years and wish him the very best for the future.”  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commenting on Kishore Tadepalli, Tarun Rai, CEO, J. Walter Thompson, said, “Kishore has been leading our office in Bengaluru for the past couple of years.  Under his watch the office has shown aggressive growth in addition to building new capabilities. Kishore is no stranger to Mumbai having lived and worked here most of his life. He is looking forward to his new role and I am confident that he will contribute significantly both to our clients as well to JWT Mumbai.”&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/1538714511_Qgp8Ca_Kundan_Joshee.jpg"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kundan Joshee takes over from Tadepalli   as the head of JWT Bengaluru. He brings around 20+ years of experience as a Marketing and Communications professional having worked both at agencies as well as a client.  In his long career he has worked on brands like Samsung, Pepsi, Slice, Tropicana, Aquafina, Zee TV, Vodafone, Maruti Suzuki, Whirlpool, Sony, National Geographic, Fox Life, Apollo Munich to name a few.  He joins from Cheil Worldwide.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commenting on Kundan Joshee, Tarun Rai, CEO J. Walter Thompson said, “I found Kundan’s energy infectious.  He is a consummate advertising professional with extensive experience in creating high impact, integrated communication solutions across traditional, digital, activation and retail platforms. I am sure both our clients as well as the office will benefit from his experience. He is excited to come back to JWT and lead our fantastic team of professionals at Bengaluru."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The changes come into effect from October 15, 2018.   &lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZEE5 adds Republic TV to its news offering</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital/zee5-adds-republic-tv-to-its-news-offering_92376.html</link>
      <description>ZEE5, the OTT platform of Zee Entertainment Enterprises (ZEEL) strengthened its news offering by launching the live-stream of Republic TV on the platform. Having launched its operations in February 2018 with a steady slate of original content, the platform has now strongly established its news section too.&lt;br&gt;Manish Aggarwal, Business Head, ZEE5 India said, “ZEE5, through its premium quality content – both syndicated and original – strives to create an immersive experience for viewers. With the addition of Republic TV, the platform is looking to connect with viewers who are digitally savvy but do not want to lose on the live news experience. Our association with Republic TV aligns well with our commitment to making ZEE5 as the one-stop destination for digital content consumption.”&lt;br&gt;With the already existing news library of leading regional news channels on the platform such as Doordarshan News, 24 Ghanta and Raj News, ZEE5 now brings in one of the latest news channels Republic TV. Additionally, the platform also gives viewers access to international news channels such as BBC World News, CNNi SA and Chardikla Time TV. Republic TV will be listed under the news category of the live streaming section on the ZEE5 app. With this association, ZEE5 will open its platform to viewers who want to be constantly updated about the latest happenings in and around the globe through live streaming of the news channel.&lt;br&gt;With over 3500 films, 500 TV shows, 4000 music videos, 35 theatre plays and 90 LIVE TV Channels across 12 languages, ZEE5 presents a blend of content offering for its viewers across the nation. With ZEE5, the global content of Zindagi as a brand, which was widely appreciated across the country, has also been brought back for its loyal viewers.&lt;br&gt;The OTT platform runs on freemium model with both free and paid premium content. Viewers who subscribe to the ZEE5 subscription pack get access to the entire library of content using the limited period special subscription offer of Rs 99 for two months and Rs500 for a year. This offer is valid till October 31.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vyoma Media wins Digital Outdoor Advertising mandate for TVS Victor</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/out-of-home/vyoma-media-wins-digital-outdoor-advertising-mandate-for-tvs-victor_92377.html</link>
      <description>Vyoma Media, the out of home digital solutions company, has won the Digital Outdoor Advertising mandate for TVS Victor.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;TVS Victor’s new model will be the first bike in its segment to feature a unique Daytime Running Lamp (DRL), along with a host of other class leading features. Vyoma Media will aim to build on the massive affinity towards the TVS brand by engaging consumers through their smart dispays at ticket counters across the Kolkata Metro and Bihar railway stations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first phase of TVS Victor’s ‘Badi Bhi Badhiya Bhi’ campaign will be for a duration of two months and then will be seen across other markets.&lt;br&gt;The multi-lingual creatives, in English, Hindi and Bengali, will play simultaneously across locations and will allow consumers a chance to win the brand new TVS Victor bike.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This campaign will take content localisation to the next level by not only displaying content in the three languages but also delivering the resulting SMS on the viewers’ mobile phones in the same language as shown in the creative they have responded to. Further consumer engagement will be ensured when the consumer is redirected to the brand’s Facebook page to participate in a contest to win more goodies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kendraj Joshi, Head – Commuter Motorcycles Marketing, said, “We wanted to come up with a unique campaign with a focus on interactive and localised creatives. This initial phase, with Vyoma’s intelligent displays at eye-level at the ticket counters, allows us to integrate and amplify the brands campaign across two key markets. It will also ensure our brand loyalists are aware of our new innovative bike features and help us maintain our unrivalled market presence. The second phase of the campaign will be across cities in Karnataka, Maharashtra and Telangana.”</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital large and growing part of our total marketing investment: Ravi Desai, Amazon India</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/advertising/digital-large-and-growing-part-of-our-total-marketing-investment-ravi-desai-amazon-india_92327.html</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;With customers today enjoying both, a one-stop-shop platform available online along with the convenience of home delivery and a tangible touch and feel experience of products before making purchases in physical stores, it is vital to weigh both sides of the spectrum. Seems like it’s no longer brick and mortar vs online retail as retailers are looking to unify their channel strategies and build a hybrid-model that has the best-of-both-worlds approach.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an interview with exchange4media, Ravi Desai, Director, Mass and Brand Marketing, Amazon India, spoke to us about Amazon’s first ever ‘Festive Home’ a physical store like arrangement in Delhi, where in the brand positioned itself as a one-point shopping destination for all of consumers’ festive and household needs this Diwali. The offline arrangement of Amazon’s Festive Home showcased different themes and décor items, electronic appliances, fashion collection, washroom accessories etc. Stating digital as the core part of Amazon’s business model, Desai also spoke about their need to go offline. According to him, their offline approach would make it easier for users to tangibly experience the breadth of Amazon in terms of the sheer selection of products that has been put together for customers. Excerpts:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amazon is primarily an online retail brand, with concepts like the Festive Home, why is the brand now looking at an offline presence as well?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The thing with online is that at times you don’t get the feel of the breadth of the entire product range available, because you are literally going in product by product, on the site. Hence, when we shared pictures of Amazon’s Festive home with few people, we found out how our layout of every item in this 'home' is helping our consumers understand the entire catalogue of products, which is coming out of one store, i.e. Amazon.in. This concept brings alive the fact that customers have access to 170 plus million products on sale available on the site. Our festive home this year clearly symbolises how consumers can literally decorate every single person’s room in the family using Amazon products.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/1538534720_0oAPed_amazonroom.jpg" style="width:443px;height:232px;float:right"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In order to create both brand love and business in the market, is it necessary for brands to have an online as well as an offline presence?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is a new habit as far as India is concerned. An offline presence like that of a Festive home, which we built in 21 days, makes it easier for us to connect with consumers, as they can actually interact with someone who they think represents Amazon.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Also for e.g. Amazon Udaan stores, these are points where customers can actually walk up as a new user and take help in opening up an Amazon account or in terms of ordering items. Today, there are quite a few Udaan points, which have deliveries happening at their end. So as far as the new customer is concerned, there is a physical entity nearby where they can actually reach out for any kind of help or query. It’s also a matter of time where in the initial stages, people might hesitate, but over a period of time and with experience consumers begin to trust the brand in their journey. They realise the kind of value we offer both in terms of selection, pricing and convenience. All of this results in building a level of comfort with the brand following which consumers invest more time in the brand.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;iframe frameborder="0" height="315" src="https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/4vOqKeEq9Zs?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" rel="nofollow" width="100%"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Is customer acquisition easier in offline vs an online medium? Has the consumer experienced change in this journey? &lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;The offline concept helps us to add another touch point in the consumer journey. However, the offline touch points again have a limited scale as we can have 4-5 such Amazon Festive Homes at max, whereas the site is accessed by millions of Indians today. It also depends on who the customer is and what kind of journey they have already had. With Internet per se and online commerce like Amazon, we are observing how more than 85% of the customers today come from tier- II &amp;amp; III cities, who haven’t spent much time on the Internet. So for them their online journey is probably in its second or third year both in terms of what they do with it and what the Internet can do for them. This is the biggest determinant of how comfortable they feel with shopping online. According to our study, while people in small cities had access to products of few brands that they had heard of, those brands on the other hand did not experience a demand high enough in order to set up stores in those cities. With clearly no physical stores available, having access to those brands through Amazon and the Internet is actually an eye opener for the tier-II and III city consumers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/1538534737_Wc7cpo_amazonroom1.jpg" style="width:400px;height:231px;float:right"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How is Amazon targeting Tier-II and Tier-III cities? &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;From Tier-II and Tier-III cities we are expecting to receive huge&amp;nbsp;demand especially from new customers. The selection available in Amazon’s Hindi app caters to&amp;nbsp;customers living in metros like Delhi and also&amp;nbsp;those in areas like Lucknow. As far as media is concerned, Television, print, Out of Home, radio and digital, innovations around on-ground event etc. are being invested in to spread the word around the campaign across cities. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is the revenue split like in offline and online form of retail and how is Amazon finding a balance between both?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;For us from a marketing standpoint, the north-star metric is about making more and more customers aware of Amazon. Our aim is to get them to know all about Amazon in such a way that they are compelled to try us. The fact that they have placed their first order online is where the awareness translates into business. Thereafter comes the comfort that they get with that experience. Their ability to access the selection then takes over and gets them into a sense of repeat habit of buying more categories online and test out products more frequently. We are also thinking of some ideas on how Diwali can be made more special for our prime members.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How is Amazon spending on digital ads. With the concept of brick &amp;amp; mortar stores what other ad spends are being involved?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Digital is a large and growing part of our total marketing investment. It is a core part of our business model itself. We have experienced a lot of success in the last one year through digital. Our investment in digital is primarily about getting our consumers to be comfortable on the Internet and thereafter make the first attempt at buying online.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coming to other ad-spends, for this particular campaign around Diwali, we have already started with our inputs on television. The whole campaign thought is about how this ‘Diwali India ke khushiyon ke beech budget nahin ayega’. Lot of Indian families put off purchases and prioritise the items that they would like to buy during festive season. Keeping in mind these families, which are at the heart of this entire campaign, we put in effort behind getting Amazon’s selection ready, along with affordability levers for consumers this Diwali. The ad displays the concept of a band which depicts an over the top celebration this festive season symbolising a carrier of happiness message to our consumers. Users need not worry about their budget constraints as Amazon is here to provide them with various affordability levers this season.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How is the e-commerce industry shaping up in India and what role is Amazon playing in this?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As far as e-commerce is concerned, in India it’s probably the dawn. With five years of brand journey in India, Amazon as a retail platform has experienced a huge amount of adoption in the market. Many users from tier-II &amp;amp; III cities are getting onto Amazon almost as the first thing that they buy on the Internet. This Diwali millions of new users will also make their first purchase online. Our app is now also available in Hindi, which will aid the journey of many new and existing Hindi-speaking users on our platform.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indian e-commerce is waiting to be tapped. In the end it’s just about serving the customer through the right offerings.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are the biggest challenges that the e-commerce sector is facing in India today?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We at Amazon believe, the customer has every right to be discontent with any service that is out there, as services need to keep getting better with time. India’s heterogeneity is one of the major challenges in e-commerce. There are almost around 40 languages in India spoken by 1 million people today. While this is very unique with regard to our culture and tradition, it remains a challenge to penetrate into all vernacular markets equally and be relevant to every Indian. Retail is something most Indians experience widely. Therefore, this remains to be an exciting challenge to be resolved for our consumers. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Infrastructure in India is again something that can evolve to benefit all. Scheduled delivery time should not be delayed once a user places an order. But then again, the condition of roads in India can always be improved to overcome such hurdles. Patchy network and electricity are some of the key concern areas too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/1538534767_xODezx_amazonroom4.jpg" style="width:443px;height:292px;float:right"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Any future plans of Amazon opening a brick &amp;amp; mortar store in India?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are plenty of innovations that are being tried out like Amazon Go, like that of a cashier less store, Amazon books stores where based on ratings given by people one can actually check out books, scan smile code in the book store and probably buy the book or get it delivered. While there are few new innovations being tried out, it’s only a matter of time when something right for India will fit in and hence be brought into the market.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIB sets timeline for rights holders to inform Prasar Bharati about any sports event &#13;
</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/mediatv/mib-sets-timeline-for-rights-holders-to-inform-prasar-bharati-about-any-sports-event_92332.html</link>
      <description>The Ministry of Information and Broadcasting has directed in accordance with the Sports Broadcasting Signals (Mandatory Sharing with Prasar Bharati) Act 2007, that&amp;nbsp;all sporting events, which are notified as sporting events of national importance by this ministry,&amp;nbsp;are to be shared with Prasar Bharati by the right holders.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to the notice, every content rights owner and television or radio broadcasting service provider intending to carry a live television broadcasting on any cable television network or DTH or intending to make a radio commentary broadcast in India, of a sporting event of national importance shall at least 45 days&amp;nbsp;prior to the proposed date of telecast or broadcast, inform the Prasar Bharati, about the same and offer to share the live signals in the manner. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The notice further stated that all the broadcasters/permitted private satellite TV channels, who gets the broadcasting rights of any sporting events, which have been notified as sporting event of national importance by this ministry, are hereby called upon to comply with the above provisions of the rules and inform Prasar Bharati about the same immediately so as to enable it&amp;nbsp;to approach the right holders well in time before the start of the event for better planning, scheduling, marketing&amp;nbsp;and coordination.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BARC Week 38: Google Pay enters list of Top 10 brands at seventh spot</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing/barc-week-38-google-pay-enters-list-of-top-10-brands-at-seventh-spot_92335.html</link>
      <description>In the list of&amp;nbsp;BARC Top 10 Brands for Week 38 (September 15-21), Harpic led the category with 14,600 insertions. Trivago, Santoor Sandal and Turmeric, Roop Mantra Ayur Face Cream and Colgate Dental Cream were at&amp;nbsp;the second, third, fourth and fifth spots with 10,682, 8974, 8440 and 8433 insertions, respectively. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wipe retained its sixth spot with 8326 insertions. The category saw a new entrant Google Pay at the seventh spot with 7949 insertions. E-commerce giants like Amazon.in and Flipkart slipped to eight and tenth spots with 7444 and 7363 insertions, respectively. Ministry of Health and Family Welfare entered the category at the&amp;nbsp;ninth spot with 7414 insertions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the same week, in BARC Top 10 Advertisers list, FMCG brands Hindustan Lever and Reckitt Benckiser continued to&amp;nbsp;lead&amp;nbsp;at&amp;nbsp;the top two spots with 1,45,676 and 84,429 insertions, respectively. ITC Ltd also retained its third spot with 32,998 insertions. Godrej Consumer Products climbed to fourth spot with 28,180 insertions.&amp;nbsp;Berger Paints entered the category at fifth spot with 26,220 insertions.&lt;br&gt;Cadburys India climbed to sixth spot with 25,345 insertions while Procter &amp;amp; Gamble dropped to seventh spot with 24,192 insertions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marico climbed to the&amp;nbsp;eighth spot with 23,919 insertions. Amazon Online India and Colgate Palmolive India entered the category after a brief hiatus at ninth and tenth spots with 22,930 and 22,558 insertions, respectively.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eros International appoints Rafiq Gangjee as CMO </title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing/eros-international-appoints-rafiq-gangjee-as-cmo_92336.html</link>
      <description>Eros International has&amp;nbsp;appointed Rafiq Gangjee as its new CMO. Previously this role was carried out&amp;nbsp;by Prerna Singh, who has now&amp;nbsp;moved to the&amp;nbsp;content team as VP - Talent &amp;amp; Short Films. She served as CMO of Eros since June 2014.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Eros International confirmed the development to exchange4media. "Rafiq Gangjee has joined us as Chief Marketing Officer and Prerna Singh &#13;
will commence her new role of being part of Eros Now’s Content Team as&#13;
 VP - Talent &amp;amp; Short Films," informed a&amp;nbsp;spokesperson.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;Gangjee was earlier with Yash Raj Films where he served as Vice President, Marketing and Communications.&amp;nbsp;He had&amp;nbsp;joined the production house in 2007 as GM Marketing during which he worked in&amp;nbsp;over 30 movies including&amp;nbsp;‘Ek Tha Tiger', ‘Dhoom 3’ and ‘Jab Tak Hai Jaan’ amongst others. He quit YRF&amp;nbsp;in 2015.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Prior to YRF,&amp;nbsp;he was with Balaji Telefilms as&amp;nbsp;Vice President. He also runs his own consultancy firm, Zabardast Communications, which he started in 1989. He devoted a considerable amount of time developing ad films- from conceptualisation to shooting and execution- and his clients include HUL, Videocon, Kenstar, Dilmah Tea (Sri Lanka, and its subsidiaries in several countries), Colgate, San Miguel, J&amp;amp;J, Škoda, Reckitt &amp;amp; Colman, amongst others. &lt;br&gt;His previous stints also include being a teacher at St. Xavier’s College, Mumbai; a Marketing Manager at&amp;nbsp;a shipping company and later at advertising agencies as account director for&amp;nbsp;several brands. Gangjee has also&amp;nbsp;worked at Everest and&amp;nbsp;Rediffusion-DY&amp;amp;R.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPNI hits back as Tata Sky drops Sony and TV Today channels</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/mediatv/spni-hits-back-as-tata-sky-drops-sony-and-tv-today-channels_92337.html</link>
      <description>Sony Pictures Networks India hits back at Direct to Home (DTH) operator Tata Sky for removing 22 channels by the operator along with TV Today Network’s channels which is officially distributed by SPNI. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPNI expressed it as an unfortunate event in a statement, stating, “Tata Sky unilaterally chose to drop 22 SPN channels from its subscription, even though SPN has not increased the rates of its channels.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The statement further reads, “SPN channels are leaders in their genres and the network one of the most popular in the country. By unilaterally dropping the channels, Tata Sky is depriving it's viewers of the opportunity to watch world class entertainment and live sporting action. Further, by compelling existing subscriber to give separate ‘missed’ calls even to continue watching the SPN channels they have already paid for, Tata Sky is not acting in the consumers’ interest.” &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The broadcaster reassured to Tata Sky subscribers that the SPN channels are available under the TRAI mandate Reference Interconnect Offer (RIO). And requested subscribers to call Tata Sky and demand that the channels be provided to them. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The operator has faced a lot of backlash by its subscribers on social media. Tata Sky has requested its subscribers to bear with them and assured that they are committed and working in the interest of its subscribers. “Commercial negotiations with the broadcasters broke down as what they were seeking would have forced us to hike our prices. Hence we have had to drop a few channels while keeping the popular ones on. We request our subscribers to bear with us, as we are doing this in their best interest,” said Harit Nagpal, CEO &amp;amp; MD of Tata Sky.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The DTH operator further mentioned, that if people have already subscribed to the following 11 channels which include SET, Sony SAB, Sony Six, Sony Ten, Sony Pix and Aaj Tak among others, they just need to add the channel at no extra cost by giving a missed call.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though this is not the first time Tata Sky has dropped channels. Last month, the DTH operator published a public notice in an English daily on September 9 saying that the DTH platform will cease close to 100 channels of Network 18 in 15 days’ time due to the failure of mutual understanding to renew the agreement between the parties.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We have no plans to enter tier II &amp; III cities: Rajat Mathur, Script</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing/we-have-no-plans-to-enter-tier-ii-iii-cities-rajat-mathur-script_92339.html</link>
      <description>Godrej &amp;amp; Boyce recently launched a new outlet in Delhi’s Kirti Nagar for its furniture brand Script. The store has been launched as part of the brand’s expansion plan. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Script’s first store was inaugurated in December last year in Bengalauru. The company aims to open 18 more stores in seven major cities– Bengaluru, Delhi-NCR, Mumbai, Pune, Hyderabad, Chandigarh, and Kolkata-- by the end of 2020. The brand plans to open five new outlets in Delhi- NCR alone as they see Delhi as a major market. In the coming month, Godrej will also launch its first store in Mumbai. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Talking about the one-year journey of the brand, Rajat Mathur, Business Head, Script, said, “The business has been phenomenal in the last one year, and we’re confident that the brand will become a niche in the coming time”. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The brand is eyeing sales of Rs 320 crore from its mid premium home furniture in the next three years, said Mathur, adding that they expect the Delhi- NCR region to contribute nearly Rs 60 crore as it’s among their key markets. Script is tapping into a market size that is estimated to be around Rs 10,000 crore.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company plans to invest around Rs 50 crore per annum-- Rs 20 crore on expansion and Rs 30 crore-- for branding and marketing expenses respectively. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Expounding on the furniture industry, Mathur said, “The industry has been growing at a CAGR of 6%, the overall furniture industry in India is estimated to be around 50,000 crore, in which around 60% stimulates to the home furniture category.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;He also said, 80% of the furniture market is unorganized, but it’s gradually improving with the entrants of several players in the market.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sharing the brand’s core vision, “The entire idea behind the brand depicts the 'new living.' That's what Scripts stands for. We are slightly unique because we believe we have disruptive designs. In this industry, we are the first brand which provides a very premium economy experience”. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mathur said the brand doesn’t aim to enter the Tier II &amp;amp; III&amp;nbsp;cities. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I don't think the brand is ready for that,” said Rajat. He also pointed out that besides the traditional brick and mortar format, Script is opting for omni-channel approach to business, “Online gives reach, creates awareness and deliver high level of engagement, whereas offline stores work as an experience centres. Nearly 20% of our customers are digitally influenced”. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stating an example, Mathur said, “Online players are investing a lot in the offline brick and mortar space because they were not able to sell furniture purely through the particular space”.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the offline segment, Godrej is looking to open these stores in three formats. The large format stores will be of 14,000-12,000 sq ft, smaller format stores of 6,000-8,000 sq ft. While, the brand will open smaller boutique stores in the 1,500-2,000 sq ft range and afterward, customers would be assisted through technology devices.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of the marketing strategy of the brand, Mathur said, “70% of our marketing goes to&amp;nbsp;the&amp;nbsp;digital. We don’t have plans to invest in television as of now. We have executed hoardings in Delhi from Kirti Nagar to South Extension, we've taken up 20 digital screens as well. Our objective for the next year is to create awareness and engagement. For TV, I think let's have a bigger presence first”. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaking about the growing competition in the sector, he said, “Competition will always exist. It's healthy for businesses. Competition pushes each other to raise the bar and giving better services and products are the only way to stay ahead of the curve.”</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sridhar Ramaswamy steps down as Google’s advertising chief</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital/sridhar-ramaswamy-steps-down-as-googles-advertising-chief_92341.html</link>
      <description>Sridhar Ramaswamy, SVP of Advertising and Commerce at&amp;nbsp;Google, has stepped down from his role.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ramaswamy, who joined Google in 2003, is said to have&amp;nbsp;played a critical role in growing Googles’ ad revenue from $10 billion in 2013 to the current&amp;nbsp;over $100 billion. Ramaswamy will be replaced by Prabhakar Raghavan, who was VP of engineering for Google’s Cloud apps.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to reports, Ramaswamy is all set to start his new innings as a venture capitalist with Greylock Partners, the well-known Silicon Valley VC firm.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commenting on his move, Ramaswamy was quoted as saying, “It’s been a dream journey to be a&amp;nbsp;part of this amazing growth engine that is part of Google.&amp;nbsp;It’s been an amazing business success. I thought&amp;nbsp;I need to reinvent myself,&amp;nbsp;and a lot of what I was inspired by is working with people and working on innovative projects.”</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch: Traditional content marketing is not going out of style: Prachi Mohapatra, fbb</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing/watch-traditional-content-marketing-is-not-going-out-of-style-prachi-mohapatra-fbb_92342.html</link>
      <description>&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;A Bloomberg Quint Initiative&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prachi Mohapatra, CMO, fbb - Future Group India, has full faith in traditional medium&amp;nbsp;despite brands increasingly going digital. The CMO spoke about the transition of branded content over five years and how it has become sharper.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Excerpts &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your comments on content marketing from what it was five years ago as against now.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;If anything, it has become sharper. If anything has to be said about the context or medium, it is much more thought-through. For instance, we are making our content much more relevant to someone who wants to consume it in a vernacular language. Five years ago, as marketers, we would not be able to give content in vernacular language so that consumption would go up. Primarily because it entails several processes. But now it has become way more sharper and customised for the person who is consuming it. This has given us a much more synchronised approach on how we are developing content &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Is traditional content marketing being left out in the digital push?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is in no way going out of style or context. Traditional medium is here to stay. However much we push content on digital medium, the consumption still happens on traditional medium and the skew towards this is still exceptionally high. While smaller towns and cities are consuming digital content far more than earlier we cannot overlook the impact that traditional media had or has currently. So it’s here to stay for a very long time.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When content creators approach you what do you look for?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s never a formula on how content is created. It depends on the objective of the campaign. So it can vary from brand building to a business proposition. Taking the example of our recently created ‘World’s Shorts Day’ campaign where we had a business objective. Shorts as a product has never been spoken about. So the objective out of the entire content creation was to create a lot of noise using influencers and the content had to be very relevant. It has to speak to a young customer who is not only young in age but also young at heart.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The content was created in such a way and the medium chosen was so sharp that it reached out to the perfect TG. And the numbers spoke for themselves. We had 120 per cent sale jump week-on-week after the same campaign.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Video:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/yJ95WhZItBg" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rana Barua joins Havas Group as CEO</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements/rana-barua-joins-havas-group-as-ceo_92343.html</link>
      <description>Havas Group has bolstered its leadership strength with the appointment of Rana Barua as CEO of Havas Group India. This is in sync with Havas Group’s overall global strategy of accelerating integration by breaking silos across creative and media functions, the agency said in a statement. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In his new role, Barua’s mandate will be to chart Havas India’s journey of transformation and exponential growth with a focus on collaboration and partnerships, new business momentum, and building &amp;amp; leading future-ready teams. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barua will report to Vishnu Mohan, Chairman &amp;amp; CEO of Havas Group, India &amp;amp; Southeast Asia, and work closely with the existing leadership teams. The appointment is effective immediately.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;An innovative brand and marketing communications leader with over  22 years of experience, Barua has held CEO roles with Contract India, Creativeland Asia, as well as worked with agencies such as Ogilvy, Rediffusion Y&amp;amp;R, McCann, JWT and held leadership profiles in leading radio stations such as Red FM and Radio City.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The appointment also marks evolution of Havas Group’s “Together” strategy that brings together Havas Group agencies of different disciplines -- creative, media, health -- within a single location known as Havas Village under a unified, client-centric leadership structure with the creation of a Group CEO position.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commenting on the appointment, Mohan said: “Rana’s appointment is a key milestone in the Group’s ongoing efforts to build agile teams and integrated structures to deliver the most impact for clients. Rana is an ideal candidate as his expertise will build on what we have already achieved in India and take Havas Group India forward in its next phase of growth and expansion. Not only will his leadership strengthen our integrated product but also facilitate the collaboration between Havas Group and other Vivendi companies -- Universal Music, GameLoft, Daily Motion -- to create a powerful marketing force, unique only to Havas Group in the market. As a group, we are committed in our efforts to make Havas Group an indomitable force in the industry and Rana’s appointment is the first of a number of significant appointments and developments to move us ahead in that direction. I am delighted to welcome Rana to the Havas family and I am confident that he will propel Havas Group India in its next phase of evolution.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barua said, “The growing complexity of platforms and channels calls for a multi-dimensional approach to marketing and advertising and the Havas Village model of collaboration and integration is exactly what clients are looking for. I am extremely excited to be a part of Havas Group’s futuristic agency model and looking forward to working with the team to start a new chapter for Havas Group in India.”</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Maddies speaker session with Sanjay Gupta, Head of Marketing, Uber</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing/the-maddies-speaker-session-with-sanjay-gupta-head-of-marketing-uber_92344.html</link>
      <description>Digital marketers are excited to run mobile campaigns because they know that mobile users are motivated buyers. The earlier you start reaching out to them, and solving their problems, the more results you will get in your business. The exchange4media Mobile Awards – The Maddies, acknowledges and recognises marketing stories that employ an effective mobile marketing strategy done in India. &lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/1538535537_t8VthD_Maddies-Logo_%281%29.jpg" style="width:300px;height:422px;float:right"&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fourth edition of The Maddies Awards 2018 will be held on October 31, in Mumbai. Along with the awards, The Maddies will also host speaker sessions with industry experts, and an exclusive event for marketing professionals to expand their network and stay on top of the latest developments in the world of mobile marketing. The theme for the conference this year is 'Mobile Marketing: Claiming a Bigger Share of the Marketer’s Purse'.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sanjay Gupta, Head of Marketing, Uber, will address a session on mobile marketing at the conference. With over 15 years of experience in brand and consulting, Gupta’s expertise lies in delivering growth, evangelising strategic brand shifts and building power brands. He is passionate about leading the growth, innovation and people agenda. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prior to joining Uber, Gupta was the Chief Marketing Officer at Urban Ladder. Befrore that, he worked with Marico and Accenture. During his 10-year stint with Marico, he led the charter for Saffola’s journey from a single category niche brand to a food brand strengthening its association with preventive heart care. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the sharpest marketing minds in the country, Gupta was recognised as India’s ‘Top 40 Under 40 Hottest Business Leaders’ in 2015. Several marketing campaigns created by him have also won recognition at EMVIE and Effie, leading advertising and media awards in the industry. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gupta holds a PGDBM in Marketing from MDI Gurgaon and a degree in Economic Honors from SRCC, and he has done a course on Strategic Marketing from Harvard Business School. He is based in Delhi with his wife, daughter and two dogs. He loves spending time with his family, and is an avid follower of Chelsea F.C. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Share your story with us by entering The Maddies 2018: &lt;a href="https://e4mevents.com/the-maddies-awards-2018/"&gt;https://e4mevents.com/the-maddies-awards-2018/&lt;/a&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isobar India wins digital duties for Marks &amp; Spencer </title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital/isobar-india-wins-digital-duties-for-marks-spencer_92345.html</link>
      <description>Isobar India, the digital agency from Dentsu Aegis Network, has bagged the digital mandate for Marks &amp;amp; Spencer, the&amp;nbsp;iconic British retailer that is present&amp;nbsp;across India.  The agency won the account following a multi-agency pitch and will now manage it from its Delhi office.&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/1538541465_v6kONG_jamesmunson.jpg" style="border:0px  #000000;width:200px;height:200px;float:right"&gt;Commenting on the association, James Munson, Managing Director - Marks &amp;amp; Spencer, said, “We look forward to working with Isobar India as our digital partners. Isobar demonstrated a well-rounded understanding of M&amp;amp;S and our audience, which has led to this partnership. We look forward to integrating our marketing strategies with their creative intellect on digital marketing.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marks &amp;amp; Spencer, with 67 stores across 30 cities in India,&amp;nbsp;had&amp;nbsp;signed a JV with Reliance Retail in 2008 making it Marks &amp;amp; Spencer Reliance India Pvt Ltd.&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/1538541396_TDdmf1_gopa.jpg"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commenting on the win, Gopa Kumar, Executive Vice President, Isobar India, said, “We're excited and proud that Marks &amp;amp; Spencer has appointed us to manage their digital duties. We are looking forward to make their digital presence stronger and create a great brand narrative as we move forward.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publishers on Twitter can now monetize video views from global audiences</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital/publishers-on-twitter-can-now-monetize-video-views-from-global-audiences_92346.html</link>
      <description>In-Stream Video Ads were designed to unlock incremental revenue for top publishers who want to monetize their videos on Twitter, while making it easier for advertisers to reach influential audiences and align with great content. Over the past year, Twitter has expanded this capability to nearly 20 global markets, including India. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter on Wednesday announced that publishers can now monetize their entire global video audience on the platform through In-Stream Video Ads. Previously, In-Stream Video Ads were limited to the markets in which publishers are based, but in many cases, publishers have a global following and global appeal. Twitter is introducing this update following feedback that there is demand to monetize a publisher’s organic following, outside of their home country. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter expects this opportunity to build on the momentum publishers across the world are seeing on Twitter: Over the first half of 2018, publisher earnings for In-stream Video Ads have more than doubled relative to the same period in 2017, the company said in a statement.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Publishers will be able to select markets where In-Stream Video Ads are available to monetize their organic audiences. They can change this setting just as they would all other account and monetization settings, and it will be defaulted to their home market only. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reacting to the new feature, Aakash Chopra, cricket commentator, said, "Twitter has been a great partner and the In-Stream Video Ads solution has been a revelation to build revenue opportunity for my videos and grow my audience. The initial collaboration has been a success and I'm excited to see how the new update will help deliver more impact and reach new global audiences."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ankit Dhadda, Head, Marketing &amp;amp; Product, Bloomberg|Quint, said, “Bloomberg|Quint is seeing an exponential growth in video consumption on Twitter and In-stream Video Ads allow us to monetise it meaningfully. It provides brands an opportunity of running video ads with high viewability score and on content which is brand safe. Brands should look at In-stream Ads as they are more impactful than gaming the algorithm for manufacturing trends.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ken Blom, SVP of Branded Content Distribution &amp;amp; Ad Operation at BuzzFeed, said, “This is a big win for monetization against the way BuzzFeed creates global content. We typically see our content travel beyond the local handle it was created in and extend to many other markets. Often times, the most viral content reaches global audiences and this update helps advertisers align with that content."</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV news anchor Karma Paljor launches East-region specific digital portal</title>
      <link>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital/tv-news-anchor-karma-paljor-launches-east-region-specific-digital-portal_92347.html</link>
      <description>Popular television news anchor Karma Paljor has launched a digital news portal for the east, eastmojo.com. Based in Guwahati it has started operations with reporters in eight northeastern states and north Bengal. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commenting on the need for an east-specific portal, Paljor said, “The eastern most part of India – specifically the northeastern states that are separated from the rest of the country by a narrow corridor of land, aptly called the 'chicken's neck' -- has long been the proverbial cog in the wheel of this mighty nation. We, however, feel it is time to change that perception. We, at East Mojo, know and believe that this remote but functionally significant region of the country has a lot to offer, and we're not just talking about its green valleys and undulating hills. As a mouthpiece of this region, we intend to give the 'nation' what it hasn't been represented with till today -- 'the eastern opinion'.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;East Mojo intends to add Assamese and Hindi languages by next year and spread presence to Orissa and West Bengal. It also has plans to report from Myanmar, Bhutan, Nepal and Bangladesh with tie ups in by 2020&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apart from the traditional modes of reporting, East Mojo has decided to adopt new media technologies that will present content (reports, essays, analytical pieces, commentaries, etc.) accessible in various formats including info-graphics, interactive applications and audio-visual media. &lt;br&gt;Commenting on the USP of East Mojo, Paljor said, “Our 'mojo' will be the network of citizen-reporters from across the region who will be trained in mobile journalism or 'MoJo', an emerging form of new media storytelling. This set of reporters will be the medium of change. Our mobile-first platform aims to revolutionize the way news and content are viewed and consumed. A core team of senior journalists, aided by innovative fact-checking tools, will form the backbone of this network. We envisage to be a balanced, unbiased and factually-correct news platform. We intend to be the 'mojo' that will excite not only millennials but users across the spectrum.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paljor is an award winning journalist with over 18 years of experience. He has had stints at The Times of India, CNBC TV18, CNN NEWS 18. He was also the recipient of the Ramnath Goenka Award for excellence in Journalism- 2011 and 2014. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Co-founder Tanushree Hazarika is an entrepreneur with 11 years of experience of launching and running two start-ups. She is also the founder of Brahmaputra Valley Film Festival. Hazarika is a Business Management Graduate from Boston University's School of Management.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 18 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
