<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9" xmlns:image="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-image/1.1" xmlns:news="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-news/0.9">
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing-news/wpp-to-cut-3500-jobs-93414.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>12/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>WPP to cut 3,500 jobs as part of restructuring</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;WPP&amp;rsquo;s radical evolution plan laid down at the Investor Day on Tuesday indicates that following the hiring freeze, the network will be cutting jobs globally. It was revealed that WPP&amp;rsquo;s restructuring will include shutting 80 offices globally and combining operations of a further 100 in locations where business is slow.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&amp;ldquo;Fewer businesses make it easier to manage, but unfortunately there will be job losses from bringing businesses together,&amp;rdquo; said Mark Read, CEO, WPP, during his presentation. The company is said to cut 3,500 of its 1,34,000 global workforce. WPP has 400 ad businesses in more than 3,000 offices in 112 countries.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Responding to a question from an analyst about further consolidation in the WPP group of companies, Read clarified that WPP will not be looking at more mergers for now. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Over the last three months, WPP has reviewed and restructured agencies that make up for 23 per cent of its revenue. Read called the mergers of VML with Y&amp;amp;R and Wunderman with JWT &amp;ldquo;tough choices&amp;rdquo; and added that the merged companies should be able to provide more integrated solutions to clients. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&amp;ldquo;There is nothing worse than running a company in a so-called traditional area that is doomed forever to the client,&amp;rdquo; he said.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;In this new radical phase of WPP, Read said, he is banning the use of the word &amp;ldquo;digital&amp;rdquo; and veering more towards technology. WPP is positioning itself as a &amp;ldquo;creative transformation company&amp;rdquo; that uses &amp;ldquo;creativity as differentiator and technology as growth engine,&amp;rdquo; Read said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&amp;ldquo;Any company that is not deeply investing in technology will not be successful in the next 5 or 10 or 25 years. I think it is incumbent on us to do that in the right way,&amp;rdquo; he added.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Talking about the mergers that WPP has undertaken recently, Read said the artificial difference between analog and digital is not helpful in understanding the world. &amp;ldquo;Removing those distinctions helps you get to the answer better,&amp;rdquo; he said. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Making a reference to ex-CEO Sir Martin Sorrell&amp;rsquo;s reference to Google and Facebook as frenemies, Read said those companies should be treated as &amp;ldquo;technology partners not as frenemies; as partners and also increasingly and interestingly as clients.&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;He further said that WPP&amp;rsquo;s technology strategy is to become a developer of technology and not just an integrator. &amp;ldquo;We cannot compete with Google or Adobe in terms of technology, but we can leverage the spend of many large partners and stitch their systems together to give us what we need.&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93414-read.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing-news/we-aim-to-be-in-top-3-brands-in-the-water-heater-category-by-2020-rakesh-kaul-hsil-ltd-93413.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>12/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>We aim to be in top 3 brands in the water heater category by 2020: Rakesh Kaul, HSIL Ltd</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Water heater brand Hindware Atlantic, part of the sanitaryware company HSIL, recently released its first TVC campaign for the Ondeo Series &amp;lsquo;Fresh Hot Water Saalon Saal&amp;rsquo;. The TVC highlights the industry-first and Patented O&amp;#39;Pro Protection Technology and Titanium Core Shield of the Ondeo range which prevents internal corrosion, thereby enhancing the life of water heaters. In 2015, HSIL had entered the home appliances segment with a collaboration with Groupe Atlantic of France.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the insight&amp;nbsp;behind the TVC for its water heater brand Hindware Atlantic, Rakesh Kaul, President and Chief Executive, Consumer Products Division &amp;amp; CEO EVOK Retail, HSIL Limited says, &amp;ldquo;We wanted to bring a campaign to help consumers understand what is happening inside their water heaters as they are not aware of the corrosion and dirt deposits that are formed inside the tank over the years. Thus the first ad campaign focuses on our water heaters equipped with the Patented O&amp;#39;Pro Protection Technology and its Titanium Core Shield helps protect the tank longer from corrosion. The &amp;lsquo;Fresh Hot Water&amp;nbsp;Saalon&amp;nbsp;Sal&amp;rsquo; campaign emphasizes the prolonged life of Hindware Atlantic water heaters as compared to any other ordinary water heaters.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Conceptualized and created by DDB Mudra, the film captures how corrosion and dirty deposits impact the longevity of a water-heater in a light-hearted neo-mythological format. Speaking on the brief given to the creative agency, Kaul says, &amp;ldquo;Our brief to the agency was to voice the aforementioned insight in a humorous and light-hearted manner. Hindware Atlantic Ondeo series comes with patented technology which prolongs the life of the product,&amp;nbsp;our&amp;nbsp;ask from the agency was to keep this messaging at the heart of the commercial while creating an ad that is not just engaging but also entertaining.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Hindware has taken a multi-pronged marketing approach for the commercial through various platforms such as Electronic and Digital. For a wider reach, the TVC is being aired on key regional channels in languages like Bengali, Kannada, Tamil, and Telugu including prominent Movies and News channels. Kaul says, &amp;ldquo;We&amp;#39;ve kept a sizable budget for the TV&amp;nbsp;campaign&amp;nbsp;so that it&amp;#39;s well tailored to reach out to our target audience.&amp;rdquo; Talking about ad-spends he says, &amp;ldquo;We will spend up to Rs 50 crores this financial year on marketing to build our brands across categories. The majority of the spends will be on digital marketing and advertising during festival season.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking about the company&amp;rsquo;s growth Kaul says, &amp;ldquo;We have grown phenomenally in all the categories we are present in over the years. In the chimney segment, we are already among the Top 3 players with a 15-16% market share. Our water heaters category is doing extremely well and in a span of 24 months, we have grown 165% more than last year and currently have 6-6.5% market share in this category.&amp;rdquo; Looking ahead he adds, &amp;ldquo;We aim to be amongst the top 3 brands in the category of water heaters by end 2020 and similarly be amongst the top 3 in the water purifiers category in next 5 years and are working to extend our distribution and retailer network, after sales network and introduce tech led variants in the categories to ensure we achieve our target.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Campaign video:&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/0K5lDBjI5l4" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93413-RakeshKaul.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing-news/our-purpose-is-to-bring-value-not-kill-competition-bhaskar-bhat-md-taneira-93389.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>12/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Our purpose is to bring value, not kill competition: Bhaskar Bhat, MD, Titan</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Titan Company Ltd, which has successfully launched many lifestyle brands over the years-- Titan, Tanishq, Fastrack, Xylys, Raga, Skinn (fragrances), has now entered the textile category with its new offering Taneira.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The company might be a late entrant in the category, but it plans to draw on its strong brand appeal to build its presence across the country.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;At the launch of Taneira&amp;rsquo;s first flagship store, Bhaskar Bhat, Managing Director, Titan Company Limited, spoke about Titan&amp;rsquo;s new offering and the changing retail landscape in the country.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Excerpts:&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What was the thought behind launching this new category?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;See where I sit,&amp;nbsp;which is as the head of the company,&amp;nbsp;it has to be a combination of&amp;nbsp;inspiration and business sense.&amp;nbsp;We have what is known as a sandbox,&amp;nbsp;it&amp;#39;s called the Titan hexagon,&amp;nbsp;which we apply to look at the future.&amp;nbsp;One of the important sides of this hexagon is the under-served and underpenetrated&amp;nbsp;and under-organized.&amp;nbsp;Any category which has two out of three of these,&amp;nbsp;we would like to explore.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;So in that process, we found this (Taneira) as one, and we have several others.&amp;nbsp;And as we explored more and more, we realized&amp;nbsp;that it has&amp;nbsp;a significant proportion of unorganized. We also realized that this is a category where we can bring more value,&amp;nbsp;and it is a very big category.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Looking at the size of this category and given our ability to transform the category combined with our strong retail play is a big strength that we have. Also, branding in this category has not happened so often in the past, and branding is something we bring to the table&amp;nbsp;apart from retail expertise.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In a world which is betting big on digital and considers mobile as the future, how would you contextualize this big investment in offline retail?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t think offline will ever go away for categories where&amp;nbsp;standardization is not the driver of the demand.&amp;nbsp;Anything which has touched and feel has a very strong offline component.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;But&amp;nbsp;the marriage of the two is what we do,&amp;nbsp;which is called Omni, and we are doing that very well, for example in the eyewear category.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Would you call yourself a late entrant in this category? How do you plan to take on players who have been in this business for a long time?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Our impulse is never to compete, our impulse is to serve. I&amp;#39;m not saying this in any philosophical manner. We have found great value and inspiration in being&amp;nbsp;totally driven by the consumers.&amp;nbsp;So consumer insight is a very important function&amp;nbsp;in the company.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;In every store, we listen to our customers and&amp;nbsp;we are driven by the customers. That is what has brought us size and scale,&amp;nbsp;and what happens to the competitors&amp;nbsp;in a way is not our problem. Our purpose is not to kill the competition; our purpose is to bring value. I believe we will create so much value&amp;nbsp;that people would want to come to us.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You have &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;helmed&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt; the success of Titan across categories, what would you call the enablers of this success story?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Fundamentally, customer-centricity; we are driven by the customers;&amp;nbsp;fantastic people orientation in the company. We have a theory about people-- which is unconditional positive regard.&amp;nbsp;It means people first before any other stakeholder. So we are totally people focused. The other factor is design.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How do you see the future of retail panning out in India over the next few years?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;I think it will be Omni&amp;nbsp;and the relevance of&amp;nbsp;brick and mortar stores will continue.&amp;nbsp;As I said,&amp;nbsp;for standard products and technology led products,&amp;nbsp;it will&amp;nbsp;become less and less relevant&amp;nbsp;but there will be flagship stores,&amp;nbsp;which will be less for sales and more for showcasing.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93389-BhaskarBhat.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing-news/delivery-boy-eating-customers-food-will-the-viral-video-brew-trouble-for-zomato-93408.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>12/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Delivery boy eating customers' food: Will the viral video brew trouble for Zomato?</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Online food ordering and restaurant reservation platform Zomato found itself at the receiving end of public ire after a video showing one of its delivery boys consuming food out of its boxed orders appeared on social media. In the two-minute video, the boy was then seen re-sealing the packages, which were likely to be delivered, and putting them back into the delivery bag. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;The video has gone viral and has &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;prompted widespread outrage on social media, with people questioning the brand and its credibility. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-lang="en"&gt;&#13;
&lt;p dir="ltr" lang="en"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/deepigoyal?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;@deepigoyal&lt;/a&gt; Hope you are doing something to repose the trust on your brand &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Zomato?src=hash&amp;amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;#Zomato&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://t.co/Z6LuSL3cGW"&gt;pic.twitter.com/Z6LuSL3cGW&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&amp;mdash; Samrat Ghosh (@SamratYokel) &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/SamratYokel/status/1072381186125774849?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;December 11, 2018&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#13;
&lt;script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-lang="en"&gt;&#13;
&lt;p dir="ltr" lang="en"&gt;What is this &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/Zomato?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;@Zomato&lt;/a&gt; I just placed an order, should I cancel it? &lt;a href="https://t.co/L6izWHajpO"&gt;pic.twitter.com/L6izWHajpO&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&amp;mdash; Ankita (@Miss_Takken) &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/Miss_Takken/status/1072150302592253952?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;December 10, 2018&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#13;
&lt;script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-lang="en"&gt;&#13;
&lt;p dir="ltr" lang="en"&gt;It&amp;#39;s not fault of employee but it is d biggest mistake of Brand name &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/Zomato?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;@Zomato&lt;/a&gt; who made it&amp;#39;s packing so that employee can unpack it thn repack it &lt;a href="https://t.co/yLlIi16uWz"&gt;https://t.co/yLlIi16uWz&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&amp;mdash; ONK (@omkak55) &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/omkak55/status/1072212529575645184?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;December 10, 2018&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#13;
&lt;script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-lang="en"&gt;&#13;
&lt;p dir="ltr" lang="en"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/Zomato?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;@Zomato&lt;/a&gt; Here is what I received on Whatsapp!! Please attend to it or it can damage the Brand really badly. &lt;a href="https://t.co/fpoLk49iLW"&gt;pic.twitter.com/fpoLk49iLW&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&amp;mdash; Ajay Sharma (@itz_aj) &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/itz_aj/status/1072207501901381632?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;December 10, 2018&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#13;
&lt;script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-lang="en"&gt;&#13;
&lt;p dir="ltr" lang="en"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/Zomato?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;@Zomato&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/ZomatoIN?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;@ZomatoIN&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/zomatocare?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;@zomatocare&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
What the heck is this .. Customers trust the brand blindly and this is what we get in return . Cant dare to believe that we are being served such kind of food . ?? &lt;a href="https://t.co/4O85PEz6nb"&gt;pic.twitter.com/4O85PEz6nb&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&amp;mdash; James Chacko (@JamesChacko1984) &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/JamesChacko1984/status/1072196597658894336?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;December 10, 2018&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#13;
&lt;script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;The question that now arises is will the brand be impacted due to this? What&amp;rsquo;s interesting is that Zomato&amp;rsquo;s competitor Swiggy recently rolled an ad communication asking consumers to empathise with delivery partners, as they, like each one of us, have a name and unique identity that they would like everybody to acknowledge. Will this incident then jeopardize Zomato&amp;rsquo;s image and give its competitors an edge over it? Or will Zomato be able to reclaim itself just right post the fiasco?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Kiran Khalap, Co-founder &amp;amp; Managing Director, Chlorophyll&amp;nbsp;Brand &amp;amp; Communications, calls this a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;classic crisis and contends that besides sacking the delivery boy, the brand will have to engage directly with the end-consumer to explain putting into place processes that will prevent recurrence of such incidents. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&amp;ldquo;Hopefully Zomato has a crisis management manual. It is the same with the Cadbury&amp;rsquo;s or the Nestle Maggi crisis: telling the truth always helps! It is difficult, but it can be done. And if done well, Zomato will regain its lost goodwill,&amp;rdquo; reasons Khalap. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Brand expert Gaurav Gulati opines that the video has surely damaged the brand reputation and is a lesson that even others in the category should pay heed to. &amp;ldquo;This surely is going to create a lot of trouble for the brand. Moreover, people might start poking the brand and Zomato delivery boys with sarcasm and prefer to use the services of their competitors instead. But it is high time for all these brands to take food tampering and hygiene very seriously.&amp;rdquo; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Gulati adds that Zomato recently raised fresh funding of $210 million from Alibaba&amp;rsquo;s Ant Financials for payment solution, but as things have changed, they should probably utilise most of the funds on image building and fixing brand reputation. After all, it&amp;rsquo;s the matter of existence now.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Harish Bijoor, brand guru &amp;amp; founder of Harish Bijoor Consults Inc, remarks that pulling one delivery boy off roster does nothing and is a big hit not only to Zomato in terms of &amp;nbsp;consumer-imagery and impression, but to the entire food and beverage delivery category altogether. &amp;ldquo;When a brand outsources literally everything it does, issues such as these are bound to be a constant bother. It is important to make food handling and delivery totally tamper-proof. Packaging can play a crucial role here,&amp;rdquo; says Bijoor.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Meanwhile, responding to the criticism, Z&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;omato released an official statement, saying that it will soon introduce tamper-proof packaging.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;&amp;quot;In our commitment towards mitigating any possibility of tampering with food,&amp;nbsp;Zomato will soon introduce tamper-proof tapes and other precautionary measures to ensure we safeguard against any chances of tampering of food. Zomato has a zero tolerance policy for tampering of food.&amp;rdquo; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;&amp;ldquo;We have found that the video was shot in Madurai. The person in the video is a delivery partner on our fleet. We have spoken to him at length - and while we understand that this was a human error in judgement, we have taken him off the platform. This incident only makes our commitment to fleet training, scheduling and process even stronger. We stand behind our extensive fleet who do the right thing across many hours of the day,&amp;rdquo; the statement said further.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93408-zomato.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing-news/tech-mahindra-announces-key-leadership-appointments-93407.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>11/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Tech Mahindra announces key leadership appointments</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Tech Mahindra announced key leadership appointments to drive the organization&amp;rsquo;s growth and lead the digital transformation journey. The leadership changes will be effective from &amp;nbsp;January 1, 2019.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Jagdish Mitra, currently the Chief Strategy &amp;amp; Marketing Officer, will be in charge of the Enterprise Business. With his experience in the digital space, he will drive growth across Enterprise Business Verticals and Strategic Business Units. He will also drive Strategic Partnerships and Alliances for Tech Mahindra. Sanjeev Nikore, currently leading Strategic Initiatives, will now take over as the Head of Marketing at Tech Mahindra.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Manoj Chugh, who is currently the Enterprise Business Head at Tech Mahindra, will take over as President, Corporate Affairs at Mahindra &amp;amp; Mahindra Group.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;CP Gurnani, Managing Director and Chief Executive Officer, Tech Mahindra said, &amp;ldquo;I wish everyone a great success in their respective roles. This will help the organization accelerate the digital transformation journey, as part of the TechMNxt charter. I am confident that this team will propel Tech Mahindra&amp;rsquo;s growth globally.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/92770-techmahindra.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing-news/quaker-launches-the-last-meal-film-as-part-of-its-feed-a-child-initiative-93402.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>11/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Quaker launches 'The Last Meal' film as part of its Feed a Child initiative</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;As part of the Quaker Feed a Child initiative that aims to create awareness for the issue of hunger amongst children, Quaker India&amp;nbsp;has released a new, thought-provoking digital film &amp;lsquo;The Last Meal&amp;#39;. Produced in association with Culture Machine, the video takes an authentic social experiment route to bring forth the dichotomy of the world we live in, where the privileged masses take access to food for granted, versus the underprivileged who struggle for each meal.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Capturing a real-life social experiment conducted on the streets of Mumbai, the new digital film for Quaker Feed a Child shows people talking about their love for food and yet struggling to remember their most recent meal. In contrast, the film moves to show children from underprivileged backgrounds immediately recalling their last meal, with some even stating sadly that they hadn&amp;rsquo;t eaten anything. The film ends poignantly with some of the children requesting for a meal, as they are hungry. The film also features celebrated&amp;nbsp;Michelin starred Chef Vikas Khanna making a call to action to all viewers to make their new year special by feeding a hungry child.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking about the initiative, Nobel Dhingra, Brand head - Quaker, PepsiCo India, said, &amp;ldquo;It is disturbing that less than one-third of children in India receive adequate nutrition. Quaker Feed a Child is a social initiative based on a powerful thought that urges us all to make every festival or occasion more meaningful by simply pledging a fistful of nutrition to feed a child. With the new year approaching, we hope that people will choose to share their festive cheer by taking a pledge to feed a child.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Commenting about his association with the initiative, Chef Vikas Khanna, Michelin-starred Chef said, &amp;ldquo;The problem of hunger and malnutrition in India cannot be solved overnight. If each of us take a step forward to help the underprivileged children, I believe we can take a big leap towards ensuring no child goes to bed hungry. I am happy to be a part of Quaker Feed A Child to raise awareness for this important and heart-wrenching issue.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Sharique Khan, Vice President- Brand Solutions, Culture Machine added,&amp;nbsp;&amp;ldquo;One of the most unfortunate facts today is that most children in our country do not have access to timely meals to satiate their hunger; which is the most basic necessity to any life form. It is our duty and responsibility, as humans and own beings , to create an awareness and also to do whatever we can in our small way to end this, one child at a time. Culture Machine in association with Quaker, urges its viewers to take a pledge and do their bit for this humane cause.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Quaker&amp;rsquo;s new digital film will feature on Culture Machine&amp;rsquo;s digital platform, Being Indian, and aptly captures how the value of a single meal could differ for those who are food secure and those deprived of food. The film reiterates the vision of the Quaker Feed a Child initiative, that aims to raise awareness for the problem of hunger amongst children, given India has one of the highest rates of hunger among children where one in five children go hungry each day. Till date, Quaker Feed a Child has supported over half a million meals for underprivileged children through Smile Foundation.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Video:&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/x0KshTHkgWY" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93402-TheLastMeal.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing-news/clinique-and-supari-studios-collaborate-to-launch-we-hear-you-campaign-93386.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>10/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Clinique and Supari Studios collaborate to launch ‘We Hear You’ campaign</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Digital content studio, Supari Studios, produced the latest campaign for Clinique&amp;rsquo;s Even Better range of products. Bringing on board four diverse influencers, Supriya Joshi, Lisa Mishra, Leeza Mangaldas and Teena Singh, they put together a series of fun and spunky films that offer viewers a glimpse into each influencer&amp;rsquo;s personality. In a candid chat about what beauty means to them, these influencers describe the role that Clinique&amp;rsquo;s Even Better products play in their lives, helping them in achieving their goals. The films use a very realistic tone and are accompanied by polished visuals and catchy music, aiming to fill its viewers with a sense of joy and independence, much like the products themselves.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking about the campaign, Sameer Ghauri, Director of the film said, &amp;quot;Our goal was to keep the tone of the films honest and real, complemented by clean and elegant visuals that are crisply edited to music handpicked to pair with each lady&amp;rsquo;s distinct personality. The colour tone of each film was also meticulously chosen to complement the different skin tones of our influencers. The aim of the films was to celebrate the diversity of smart, independent Indian women and at the same time highlighting that the brand caters to over 50 types of different skin tones, and I feel our films managed to achieve that quite successfully.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Adding to this, Mitali Sharma, Executive Producer, Supari Studios said, &amp;ldquo;With this campaign, we wanted to focus on the tagline &amp;lsquo;Even Better&amp;rsquo; by bringing out the strong personalities of each of the influencers and how they don&amp;#39;t like to settle in life, just like the Even Better foundation. We tried to encapsulate a piece of their life into the films by throwing in some minimal props that gave a suggestion of their profession. We also highlighted how Clinique Even Better Foundation helps each influencer, by mentioning a specific benefit of the foundation that works for them.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Link to campaign:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://https://www.instagram.com/p/Bp4BQmhFHlb/?utm_source=ig_web_copy_link" rel="nofollow"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/p/Bp4BQmhFHlb/?utm_source=ig_web_copy_link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93386-Clinique.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing-news/sattviko-launches-initiative-to-help-fight-against-plastic-93384.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>10/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Sattviko launches initiative to help ‘fight against plastic’</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;In an endeavour to contribute to the advancement of the environment, Sattviko, a packaged food company providing light snacks of Indian origin, launched a &amp;lsquo;Sattviko wrapper exchange initiative&amp;rsquo; across India. The initiative will commence from the first week of January and will continue for a year.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The wrapper exchange campaign that Sattviko has initiated encourages consumers to avoid disposing of the wrappers of its products but instead, consumers can exchange 10 empty Sattviko wrappers for one free packet of Sattviko snacks. The quantity, size and the flavour of the packets have to be the same as the ones sent by the consumer, via post to Sattviko or to any of its registered retailers.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking of the initiative, Prasoon Gupta, Co- Founder and Director, Sattviko said, &amp;ldquo;India produces around 26,000 tonnes of plastic waste every day. Most of this is single-use plastic that can take up to 100 years to decompose. Plastic causes major environmental damage and a small initiative such as this can make a huge difference. Sattviko intends to reach out to a maximum number of consumers through this campaign. We hope to inspire others to make a difference with such an initiative. This is in support of our fight against plastic pollution and we hope that we are able to bring a behavioural change in the society at large.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Sattviko is also looking at proactively&amp;nbsp;spearheading the debate on &amp;lsquo;How can cutting down on plastic in FMCG be functional&amp;rsquo; with an aim to engage consumers and producers, and educating them to avoid the usage of plastic for a better environment.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93384-Sattviko.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing-news/walmart-india-announces-sameer-aggarwal-as-chief-business-officer-93381.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>10/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Walmart India announces Sameer Aggarwal as Chief Business Officer</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Sameer Aggarwal has been made Chief Business Officer of Walmart India with immediate effect.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Aggarwal, currently Chief Strategy &amp;amp; Administrative Officer, will now lead Strategy, Merchandising, Cost Analytics, E-Commerce, Technology, Marketing and Replenishment. He will continue to report directly to Krish Iyer, President &amp;amp; CEO, Walmart India.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Prior to joining Walmart India in April 2018, Aggarwal was Chief Finance, Development &amp;amp; Supply Chain Officer for KFC, Thailand. Before KFC, he worked with Sainsbury&amp;rsquo;s in UK &amp;amp; China as Head of Strategy and Executive Assistant to the CEO. He also worked with McKinsey &amp;amp; Co, UK &amp;amp; Australia as an Associate Partner. He holds a Masters Degree in Business Administration from the London Business School and is a fellow member of the Institute of Chartered Accountants of India.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Anuj Singh has joined as Head - Category Merchandising of Walmart India and will lead Category Merchandising, Merchandise Planning &amp;amp; Execution and Private Brands development. Singh will report to Sameer Aggarwal. Singh comes with 23 years of experience in leading consumer goods organizations across India, Europe &amp;amp; Middle East. Before joining Walmart, Singh was Business Executive Officer responsible for Nestl&amp;eacute;&amp;rsquo;s Food Services business in the South Asia Region. Earlier, he worked with organisations such as Philip Morris International, Hindustan Lever Limited, ITC Limited and Asian Paints. Singh holds Masters Degree in Business Administration from London Business School.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, Devendra Chawla, EVP &amp;amp; Chief Operating Officer - Merchandising, Marketing, and eCommerce, has decided to move on to pursue other opportunities outside Walmart India.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Announcing the changes, Krish Iyer, President &amp;amp; CEO, Walmart India said, &amp;ldquo;I am extremely pleased to announce Sameer Aggarwal as our Chief Business Officer. Sam joined Walmart India in April this year and within a short period of time he has developed a great understanding of our company and our culture. He has already made very good contributions to the business and also developed strong relationships internally and externally. He brings an international and strategic perspective to our business in India. His experience of supporting the governance functions at Walmart India will help us grow further in the right way. He is passionate about growing people and making them successful. I have no doubt he will lead and support his teams to strive for excellence in everything we do.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;I am very happy to welcome Anuj Singh into the Walmart India family. Backed with rich experience of 23 years in India and international markets, I am confident he would lead the business to achieve more success.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;I am very excited with the progress we are making in the country. We recently opened our 23rd Best Price Store and the second Fulfillment Centre in the country and are excited at the opportunity of continuing to create shared value for kiranas, resellers, small businesses, small farmers, associates, and the community at large. With our expansion, we are opening up our mission to more members and helping them save money to live better while enabling kirana/reseller members to prosper by efficiently managing their inventory and lowering their operational costs. While growing the business, we will set new benchmarks in the B2B Cash&amp;amp;Carry format, create thousands of local jobs and continue to invest in making our operations sustainable through renewal energy, waste management, water recycling and replacing single-use plastic with sustainable solutions in a phased manner.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;I wish Sam &amp;amp; Anuj the very best in their new roles. I would also like to thank Devendra Chawla for his contributions to the company, especially for making a difference to our Private Brand business. I wish him good luck in his future endeavours,&amp;rdquo; concluded Iyer. &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93381-Sam.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing-news/khelo-india-youth-games-maharashtra-2019-will-be-held-in-pune-93375.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>10/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Khelo India Youth Games, Maharashtra 2019 will be held in Pune</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;After a successful inaugural edition of Khelo India School Games, Ministry of Youth Affairs and Sports along with Star Sports kick started the countdown to Khelo India Youth Games, Maharashtra 2019 with an appeal to encourage India to play more - with the evocative &amp;lsquo;#5MinuteAur&amp;rsquo; campaign.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The campaign has a strong call to action, taking the Khelo India movement forward, featuring - Manu Bhaker, Jeremy Lalrinnunga, Saurabh Chaudhary, Lakshya Sen, Esha Singh, Tababi Devi, Srihari Natraj and champions Mary Kom, Sushil Kumar amongst others bringing childhood playground memories to life. The #5MinuteAur campaign created this year has a simple insight, we are all born with an inherit instinct to play, kids and adults alike.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;In its inaugural edition, Khelo India had a strong message &amp;ldquo;Kheloge Kudoge Banoge lajawaab&amp;rdquo; encouraging more kids to play every day, it was an effort towards changing an age-old belief. Building on the core of this message through the #5MinuteAur campaign, Star Sports and the ministry want India to encourage kids to play for those extra 5 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The 5 minutes is symbolic, with an assumption that if each child plays a little bit longer, we will add a billion minutes of play every day that has the potential to translate into 50 medals for the country.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Portraying this five-minute agreement between a mother and a child, the aim with #5MinuteAur is to spark a fire in every enthusiast in India to strive for better through sports. Establishing the message that sports builds and defines our personalities, the more we play the better we get. The manifesto, &amp;ldquo;Hum Aaj Aur Khelenge Toh Kal Aur Jeetenge&amp;rdquo; is true not just for the sport we play, but for life itself.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Scheduled to take place at Shree Shiv Chhatrapati Sports Complex in Pune from January 9 to 20, 2019, Khelo India Youth Games, Maharashtra 2019 will see over 10,000 participants from 29 states and 7 Union Territories. The games will bring to life by over 6200 athletes, 1800 Technical Officials, 1000 volunteers and 1000 personnel working behind the scenes.Conceptualised to revive the sports culture in India at grass-root level by building a strong framework for all sports played in our country, the upcoming season of Khelo India Youth Games will be held across 18 sporting disciplines in the Under 17 and Under 21 age categories.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;The success of Khelo India School Games is a testimony to the hunger and multitude of sporting talent in India. Buoyed by the terrific response for Khelo India School Games and with an aim to increase participation in sports across all age groups, we have not just added two sports this year but have also increased the age limit to allow even more enthusiasts to participate and flourish. The &amp;lsquo;5 minute aur&amp;rsquo; campaign is a reflection of the immense strides we&amp;rsquo;ve made and the journey that lies in front of us to make India a truly sporting nation. We hope it will inspire India to work towards incorporating sports as a way of life,&amp;rdquo; said Col. Rajyavardhan Singh Rathore, Minister for Sports and Youth Affairs (IC).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;To support the Khelo India initiative by the Ministry of Youth Affairs &amp;amp; Sports, Star India has doubled the level of promotion and broadcast coverage for Khelo India Youth Games, Maharashtra 2019. The coverage of the upcoming season will include live telecast in five languages (Hindi, Tamil, Telugu, Kannada and English) and telecast of all 18 disciplines for both age groups.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Sanjay Gupta, Managing Director, Star India said, &amp;ldquo;The first edition of Khelo India exceeded expectations and instilled an aspiration for sports amongst the youth in India and now, with &amp;lsquo;5 minute aur&amp;rsquo;, we are aiming to trigger more pro sport conversations to make India adopt sports as a way of life. The campaign calls for the Indian sports enthusiast to not only support their heroes, but also work towards emulating their feats.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Staying true to our commitment of bringing the best in class sports experience to the passionate Indian sports fan, we will broadcast Khelo India Youth Games in 5 languages this season along with LIVE telecast of 9 disciplines,&amp;rdquo; he further added.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Khelo India Youth Games will telecast live across Star Sports Network and Hotstar.&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93375-KheloIndia.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing-news/nobbys-warmth-humility-kindness-personified-him-paulomi-dhawan-93368.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>10/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Nobby’s warmth, humility, kindness personified him: Paulomi Dhawan</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Nabankur Gupta (NOBBY), a marketing industry veteran, was a master in adding a high level of professionalism wherever he went. Warmth, humility, kindness personified him.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;I first met Nabankur Gupta when he was at Videocon. (I was with the ad agency). He developed strategies for sub-branding and multi-branding in the consumer durables business for the first time in India which won him international accolades. Advertising Age International, New York recognised him for this successful initiative by awarding him with the title of &amp;ldquo;Marketing Superstar&amp;rdquo; (amongst 20 recipients of this title in 1996 in the world).&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Mr Gupta...a client first then my boss and above all a mentor...who I owe a lot to. He was always there to guide, support me. He initiated my move to Raymond.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Mr Gupta joined the Raymond Group (from Videocon) as the Group President and board member in 2000. During his tenure he acquired some highly synergistic companies to support the strategic growth plans - Color Plus, launched designer label Be among others. The retail presence of Raymond grew aggressively, adding new formats across smaller towns in India.&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
He re-launched the brands in the textile and apparel space and further reinforced Raymond&amp;rsquo;s leadership position. Brand building was his forte. New advertising campaigns like &amp;quot;Feels like heaven, feels like Raymond&amp;quot; were during his time. The &amp;ldquo;Baby&amp;rdquo; commercial was launched on the cricket platform &amp;ldquo;Champions Trophy&amp;rdquo;. He had an eye for guiding the work with a great sense of the brand core. He brought back the &amp;ldquo;Teacher&amp;rdquo;. He did the Father and Son, Father and Daughter, Man and Puppies ads and many more. The campaign contemporised &amp;ldquo;The Complete Man&amp;rdquo; making him more sensitive, younger.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Media consolidation at Raymond and introducing the Corporate Communication cell was his vision. We did some amazing work together-he was always supportive on any path-breaking idea. Dressing TV anchors, owning news segments, print innovations, style guides, the much prized Haji Ali hoardings were in his time. It was 360 degree marketing solutions, including ET Awards for Corporate Excellence initiated by him to synergize with the Raymond core values of Excellence, Leadership, Innovation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Mr Gupta interacted with media &amp;ndash; both the editorial with interesting insights and their marketing teams, ever ready to hear a new idea at a cost effective solution. As an advertising friend said, &amp;ldquo;The two of you were a formidable and good team.&amp;rdquo; Extremely soft spoken and well-mannered in his handling of difficult situations and he was truly a marketing genius. He represented Raymond on many industry bodies like MRUC, ABC delivering wisdom and experience. He was truly an industry leader.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;In 2005, he relinquished the post to start his own management consultancy &amp;ldquo;Nobby Brand Architects &amp;amp; Strategic Marketing Consultants&amp;rdquo;. He was on the Board of many companies, including Raymond.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;A warm, good human being who was highly respected by all, irrespective of rank or creed. A gentle leader, a man of principles, a guide and mentor to many, humble, a great professional and a thorough gentleman. His warmth, his quiet demeanour was like none other!&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Thank you Mr Gupta for being there!!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;At 70, he leaves behind his wife Nita, son Kaustabh and daughter Timira, and a very large family of indebted souls whose lives he touched. RIP.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;God, please give his family the strength to bear this immense loss.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(The author is the Strategic Advisor Paulomi Dhawan Advisory)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disclaimer: The views expressed here are solely those of the author and do not in any way represent the views of exchange4media.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93368-Nobby.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing-news/walmart-india-coo-devendra-chawla-quits-reports-93367.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>10/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Walmart India COO Devendra Chawla quits: Reports</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;Walmart India COO Devendra Chawla has quit after a 15-month stint, say reports. He is currently believed to be serving the notice period following an internal announcement on Friday.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Sameer Aggarwal, executive vice president, chief strategy and administrative officer Walmart India, is likely to take over Chawla&amp;rsquo;s role, say reports. Aggarwal, who joined Walmart India in April, currently leads finance, technology, legal, audit and strategy functions. An MBA from London Business School, he was earlier chief finance, development and supply chain officer at KFC Thailand and had worked with Sainsbury&amp;rsquo;s in UK and China.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Chawla, an alumnus of Harvard Business School, was executive vice president and COO responsible for merchandising, marketing, procurement and omni-channel at Walmart India. He was also a director on the board. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:9.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Before joining Walmart India, Chawla was CEO of Future Consumer, and Future Group president for food, FMCG and brands. He also had a stint at Coca Cola India as Director.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93367-dc.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing-news/barc-week-48-trivago-leads-top-10-brands-93324.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>10/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>BARC Week 48: Trivago leads Top 10 Brands</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Trivago climbed up to the top spot to lead the top spot in Top 10 Brands for Week 48 (November 24-30, 2018) with 12,014 insertions. Santoor Sandal and Turmeric and Axis Bank Credit/Debit Card moved to a second and third spot with 10,324 and 8712 insertions respectively.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Ortho Oil and Capsule entered the category in the fourth spot with 8604 insertions. Flipkart slipped to the fifth spot with 8505 insertions. Goodknight Power Active Plus retained its sixth spot with 8187 insertions. Roop Mantra Ayur Face Cream, Vaseline Intensive Care Lotion, Godrej Expert Rich Cr&amp;egrave;me Hair Color and Freecharge forayed into seventh, the eighth, ninth and tenth spot with 8069, 7769, 7744 and 7515 insertions respectively.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;In the same week, in the BARC Top 10 Advertisers list, FMCG brand Hindustan Lever, Reckitt Benckiser, and ITC Ltd continued to lead this category with 1,22,400, 46,007 and 39,453 insertions respectively.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Ponds India and Cadburys India moved up to fourth and fifth spot with 30,886 and 30,640 insertions respectively. &amp;nbsp; Godrej Consumer Products slipped to the sixth spot with 30,082 insertions. Wipro moved up to the seventh spot with 28,879 insertions. Procter &amp;amp; Gamble slipped to the eighth spot with 27,001 insertions. SBS Biotech forayed into the category at ninth spot with 23,348 insertions. Brooke Bond Lipton India retained its tenth spot with 21,581 insertions.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93324-BARClogo.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing-news/iprccc-2018-panel-discussion-on-corporate-social-responsibility-and-nation-building-93365.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>10/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>IPRCCC 2018: Panel discussion on Corporate Social Responsibility and Nation Building</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;The ninth edition of exchange4media&amp;#39;s India PR &amp;amp; Corporate Communications Awards 2018 is the most extensive and exhaustive awards to recognise the contribution and success of the PR Industry. With five categories and 22 subcategories, IPRCCA 2018 is the path-breaking initiative to salute and recognise the contribution of PR Consultancies and Corporate Communications.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The event is scheduled to be held on December 13 at The Leela Ambience in Gurugram.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The event will also witness an all-day India PR &amp;amp; Corporate Communications Conference 2018. The theme for the conference this year is &amp;lsquo;The importance of integrated communications and its challenges&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The topic for the seventh session at the conference is on &amp;lsquo;Corporate Social Responsibility and Nation building; how communication supports in building blocks, bridging the gap between social responsibility and political governance&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Our esteemed speakers Sameer Bajaj, Director - Corporate Communications and External Affairs, Discovery India and Dr. Ranjana Kumari, Director, Centre for Social Research, will discuss how brands are sensitive towards society and its development. Government initiative enforced brands commitment towards nation building through human capital. Role of communication person is to ensure CSR falls in line with brands business interest and the impact it has on people. The key is to define and device a key strategy which enhances brands reputation. Media, on the other hand, is a crusader in sensitizing the public about the issues and how corporate and nodal agencies are addressing those issues through their initiative.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Sameer Bajaj has over 20 years of work experience in strategic communications, advocacy, public relations, internal communications and CSR with global organisations across different industries. He is currently working with Discovery Communications India as Director &amp;ndash; Corporate Communications &amp;amp; External Affairs. Prior to Discovery, Sameer has also led Corporate Communications verticals for Amway India and STAR Sports.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;A renowned social activist and a prolific academician, Dr. Kumari is also the Chairperson of Women Power Connect. She has dedicated her life to empowering women across the South Asia region and is also a prolific writer of many well-known publications.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Dr. Kumari went to school in Varanasi, Uttar Pradesh. Her paternal grandfather, a freedom fighter, Pandit Vishwanath Sharma, was the founder member of the famous Kashi Vidyapith of Varanasi, which was the first modern University organised by Indians in British India. After finishing her schooling, she moved to Delhi and did her MA, MPhil, and Ph.D. in Political Science from Jawahar Lal Nehru University.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Her foray into social work was initiated by her concern for a dowry death that took place near her home in 1976. This led to her activism on world famous publication &amp;ldquo;Brides are not for Burning&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;She has served as the Coordinator of the South Asia Network Against Trafficking (SANAT) in Persons and is a member of the Central Advisory Board on &amp;ldquo;Pre Conception and Pre Natal Diagnostic Tests Act, 2001&amp;rdquo;, as well as the Central Advisory Committee for Prevention of Trafficking in Women and Children. Some of her most passionate causes have been the participation of women in democracy and governance, the termination of dowry practices and dowry-related violence, and the abolition of female foeticide.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;In the past, she was a member of the Task Force on Industrial Relations for The International Labour Organisation (ILO) in Geneva and worked as a senior professional at United Nations. Currently, she is a member of the Global Safety Advisory Board of Facebook. She is also a member of the Twitter&amp;rsquo;s Trust &amp;amp; Safety Council.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;For the event, Ad Factors is the presenting partner of the IPRCCA and is co-Powered by Media Mantra &amp;amp; MSL. The gold partner is Kaizzen, PR Pundit &amp;amp; AvianWe. The urban mobility partner is Uber. The digital media partner is Media Value works. Policy Bazaar is the knowledge partner and is co-partnered by Text 100, The Publicist &amp;amp; Kommune. The lifestyle PR partner is ActiMedia, TV partner is NewsX, creativity partner is Webershandwick. The partner For IPRCCC is Pearl Academy.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;For more detail, click here:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://e4mevents.com/iprcca-2018/"&gt;https://e4mevents.com/iprcca-2018/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93365-IPRCCCLogo.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing-news/sony-music-india-broadens-segmentation-study-itc-nykaa-among-others-on-board-93326.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>10/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Sony Music India broadens segmentation study; ITC, Nykaa among others on board</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Every brand, irrespective of its category, understands the important recall factor that music&amp;nbsp;brings in. This is evident from well-established instances such as&amp;nbsp;MTV Coke Studio and Mahindra Blues Festival among others. In keeping with the&amp;nbsp;changing music consumption pattern, Sony Music updated its Sony Music India Segmentation Study, which now covers 31 unique segments. This&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;is one of India&amp;rsquo;s first and largest research&amp;nbsp;undertaken to analyze psychographic and demographic profiling of Indian audience&amp;nbsp;based on their music consumption patterns. It offers an interesting insight into the life of a consumer over-laid with their music preferences. Over the last three years the study has helped around 80 brands leverage its power&amp;nbsp;by tying up with the right music artistes. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;The updated study now uncovers 31 unique segments of music consumers classified under a model called as FECI - Fanatic, Enthusiast, Casual and Indifferent, based on how central music is to their lives. The trend study also researched the usage and consumption habits,&amp;nbsp;spends by teenagers in urban cities, music discovery patterns across age groups, music consumed on daily basis, brands consumers admire and spend on with respect to music and the role it plays in marketing and advertising.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Kiran Dcruz, Director, Brand Partnerships, Sony Music, says, &amp;ldquo;It helps you plan a strategy to use music effectively to a larger subset.&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Around 20&amp;nbsp;brands across categories including&amp;nbsp;Yamaha, Nexa, Hitachi , Amazon and Nykaa have leveraged the updated segmentation study to bring out campaigns that marry the DNA of brands and music artistes. These include Nexa Music Lounge 2018 and 7UP Madras Gig.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Dcruz is also working with FMCG brand&amp;nbsp;ITC that&amp;nbsp;has still not ventured into the content space. Without divulging much, he says, &amp;ldquo;Through Segmentation Study we have been able to give them insights on how to effectively use music and also helped them choose an artiste.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Mahesh Kanchan, Marketing Director, Carlsberg India, says, &amp;ldquo;We have had a four-year relationship with Sony Music and through these years they have successfully been able to use their understanding of the segmentation study to help&amp;nbsp;achieve our marketing objectives. We are working on something exciting next year too, and will soon share information on the same.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:106%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Online beauty retailer Nykaa has also lined up a project which is scheduled to be out soon. Hitesh Malhotra, Chief Marketing Officer, Nykaa.com, says, &amp;ldquo;We have been working with Sony Music over the last few months and they have been most clear in understanding our marketing and brand objectives. &amp;nbsp;This year we are planning something new and innovative with them through their segmentation study and we are confident that it will be a massive success.&amp;rdquo; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;The proprietary Sony Music Segmentation Study is conceptualised and managed by the International Insight Team at Sony Music UK and India along with market research giant GMI (Global Market Insite) with the objective of providing audience insight and music trends across different consumer segments in key markets. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93326-sonymusic.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing-news/brand-factory-launches-3rd-edition-of-free-shopping-weekend-with-dontshopatfsw-campaign-93348.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>09/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Brand Factory launches 3rd edition of Free Shopping Weekend with #DontShopAtFSW campaign</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;While the rest of the world is going gaga about the Black Friday and Single&amp;rsquo;s Day Sale, Indians will not feel left out, courtesy Brand Factory by Future Lifestyle Fashions. Announcing, Free Shopping Weekend (FSW) with a tongue in cheek humour, Brand Factory tells its customers #DontShopAtFSW if they like being rewarded only with discounts.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;FSW is every shopaholic&amp;rsquo;s dream as they get to shop for more than 200 National and International brands for FREE! The 3rd season of Brand Factory Free Shopping Weekend will be held from 12th to 16th December 2018.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The last two years of Free Shopping Weekend saw great success, with lakhs of customers queuing up outside the stores. The wait this year was palpable, resulting in more than 1 lakh RSVPs online, on Day 1 itself. Brand Factory rolled out a 360-degree integrated campaign where #DontShopAtFSW campaign received an overwhelming response of over 1.2 million views on Facebook. The campaign is supported by print, TV, digital, OOH, radio along with corporate and student community tie-ups. This year, the event will be held on a scale larger than ever before with the increased store presence in Tier II and Tier III markets.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking about the scale of the Free Shopping Weekend, Roch Dsouza, CMO, Brand Factory says, &amp;ldquo;This is one of our biggest property and we wanted our communication to not only be direct but also fresh and exciting. #DontShopAtFSW is not just an attempt to break the clutter but it&amp;rsquo;s backed by solid consumer insights. We took this route for our digital campaign and both the films bring out the true customer experience when they hunt for deals online or during EOSS of full price retailers. They are as direct and convey the message spot on. We backed this idea with content and we are already witnessing some crazy response.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;FSW is India&amp;rsquo;s only national ticketed shopping event conducted in 88 stores and 37 cities. Given the scale of the event, shoppers need to pre-book their entry passes at a minimal cost of Rs.250 (Premium passes for two: for early entry to the store from 8 am) and Rs.100 (Classic passes for two: for entry post 11am). Tickets can be booked via on brandfactoryonline.com, insider.in or by visiting the nearest Brand Factory store. You can also redeem the value of your pass on your next purchase during 18th to 31st December.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;During the Free Shopping Weekend, you shop for MRP worth Rs.5000, pay just Rs.2000 and get that back too, in the form of free apparel worth Rs.500, gift vouchers worth Rs.1200, and another Rs.300 in your Future Pay wallet. Nobody would want to miss a shopping experience as big as this. Shoppers across the country unite, here&amp;rsquo;s an experience you cannot afford to miss!&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Campaign video:&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/djuYOhsBCVc" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93348-ClubFactoryFSW.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing-news/marketing-veteran-nabankur-gupta-no-more-93359.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>08/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Marketing veteran Nabankur Gupta no more</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;Marketing veteran Nabankur Gupta, popularly known as &amp;lsquo;Nobby&amp;rsquo; Gupta, has passed away following a brief illness. According to media reports, Gupta (70) breathed his last on Friday. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;Gupta was a marketing master with over three decades of experience in the industry. He had been associated with companies such as Raymond, Videocon Industries and Philips.&amp;nbsp; He was serving as an independent director on the boards of several companies. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;Gupta was the first Indian to have been conferred the tittle of &amp;lsquo;Marketing Superstar&amp;rsquo; by Advertising Age International, New York, in 1995. He retired as Group President of Raymond in 2005, after which he started his management consultancy, Nobby Brand Architects &amp;amp; Strategic Marketing Consultants. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93359-NabankurGupta.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing-news/m-s-dhoni-partners-with-indi-platform-for-social-media-fan-engagement-93337.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>07/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>M S Dhoni partners with Indi platform for social media fan engagement</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;World-class cricket player, Mahendra Singh Dhoni, has partnered with Indi, a digital word of mouth engagement and monetisation platform, to extend and enhance relationships with his global fan base.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The Indi platform will enable Dhoni&amp;rsquo;s fans to become brand ambassadors for his Seven by MS Dhoni line of footwear, apparel and accessories while earning revenue on sales they generate.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Dhoni&amp;rsquo;s reputation and ability to inspire 1.3 billion Indians has always amazed me. We are truly impressed with his motivation to give back to the fans who have given him so much. The chance to become a brand ambassador for Seven is a privilege indeed, and we are honored to be powering this groundbreaking opportunity for millions,&amp;rdquo; said Indi CEO Neel Grover.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Seven by MS Dhoni offers a range of quality lifestyle and athletic apparel at affordable prices. Fans, athletes and gym goers find a unique range of daily wear to cricket-specific products ranging from cricket shoes to sweat-resistant tees. The latest technology, classic designs and highest quality materials are crafted into the Seven catalog.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s a special opportunity to be able to empower my fans and Seven by MS Dhoni customers with opportunities to not only engage with my label but to also increase their income by earning referral fees on sales they make across social media,&amp;rdquo; Dhoni noted.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The Indi Brand Ambassador program for athletes offers a range of options for enhancing fan engagement including sponsorships, advertising, product recommendations, branded merchandise and two-way video on demand. The platform also provides detailed information on the athlete&amp;rsquo;s Indi fan base, social traffic and income generation.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Another way athletes can engage their fans on Indi is through challenges where fans create and post videos and photos. Challenge winners are then selected based on criteria such as the &amp;ldquo;best&amp;rdquo; post and the most Indi Buzz generated by those posts.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Arun Pandey, Chairman and MD of Rhiti Group, stated, &amp;ldquo;While we continue our aggressive push in growing the number of stores to 100 by end of this year, I am thrilled that we are in association with a leading brand like Indi in the digital space. I look forward to working with Indi.com and the founder&amp;rsquo;s wealth of experience at such a promising time in India&amp;rsquo;s e-commerce landscape to promote a healthy and fit lifestyle which Seven by MS Dhoni embodies.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93337-msdhoni.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing-news/estee-lauder-signs-actress-diana-penty-as-first-brand-ambassador-for-india-93336.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>07/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Estée Lauder signs actress Diana Penty as first brand ambassador for India</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Skincare, makeup and fragrance brand, Est&amp;eacute;e Lauder has announced actress and model, Diana Penty, as their Brand Ambassador for India. Penty will feature in skincare and makeup campaigns across digital and in-store platforms. Her first campaign will be for Est&amp;eacute;e Lauder&amp;rsquo;s Advanced Night Repair.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;We are thrilled to welcome Diana to Est&amp;eacute;e Lauder India as our first Brand Ambassador. Her independence, confidence, sophistication and radiance reflect the modern Indian woman today and will bring a fresh attitude to our brand legacy and style. We&amp;rsquo;re excited to reveal our first campaign with Diana and truly believe she will help connect our brand with female consumers around the country,&amp;rdquo; said Rohan Vaziralli, General Manager, Est&amp;eacute;e Lauder Companies India.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the announcement, Penty said, &amp;ldquo;It is an honour to be the first face for Est&amp;eacute;e Lauder in India. Being the first Indian woman to represent this iconic global brand is a dream come true. I think confidence and inner happiness makes one beautiful and I hope that I can inspire other young women to bring out the beauty in them.&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Penty will front the Advanced Night Repair and Pure Color Love Lipstick campaigns in India. She will also lead the DoubleWear Stay-in-Place Foundation campaign, joined by local influencers representing diverse backgrounds and skin tones.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93336-DianaPenty.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing-news/impact-person-of-the-year-d-day-has-arrived-93331.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>07/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Impact Person of the Year: D-Day has arrived!</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:14.0pt"&gt;D-Day is here and the spotlight will shine on the winner of the 14th IMPACT Person of the Year award at the Grand Ballroom of Taj Santacruz, Mumbai tonight. Just before the moment of truth, however, industry leaders share their top picks on who they think is the most deserving winner among the nine nominees this year.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:14.0pt"&gt;This year, the nominees for the award are Naveen Tewari, Founder and CEO, InMobi; Nadia Chauhan, Joint MD &amp;amp; CMO, Parle Agro; Sanjay Gupta, Managing Director, Star India; Deepak Iyer, Managing Director, Mondelez India; Rajan Anandan, Vice President, South East Asia and India, Google; Ritesh Agarwal, Founder, Oyo; Sanjiv Mehta, Chairman &amp;amp; MD, Hindustan Unilever Limited (HUL); Piyush Pandey, Executive Chairman and Creative Director, Ogilvy South Asia and Prasoon Pandey, Director, Corcoise Films; and Sriharsha Majeti, Rahul Jaimini, Nandan Reddy, Co-founders, Swiggy. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:14.0pt"&gt;Here is what some senior industry leaders have to say about the nominee of their choice and why they think he or she should win the coveted IPOY 2018 title. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:14.0pt"&gt;Raj Nayak, COO, Viacom18&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:14.0pt"&gt;Most of the people who have been nominated are my friends. Also, all the nominees are super-achievers in their own right. This makes it very difficult to pick one name. However, there are two or three people who have done fabulous work for their organization. Sanjiv Mehta of HUL had a great turnover and great story this year. Sanjay Gupta of Star TV&amp;nbsp;has played a key role in the Star TV&amp;rsquo;s fabulous performance, with the acquisition of IPL, and the company that it has evolved into. I also think Nadia Chauhan is deserving because she&amp;rsquo;s taken Parle Agro to a completely new level. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/sYCIP6v1f_k" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:14.0pt"&gt;Amer Jaleel, Group Chairman and Chief Creative Officer, MullenLowe Lintas Group&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:14.0pt"&gt;For me it&amp;rsquo;s 100% Swiggy because they&amp;rsquo;ve changed the game in my house the most. It used to be a task thinking of a place you want to order your food from, but now whatever you want, you call Swiggy and you get it. In my family, Swiggy has had the biggest impact and if there are many families like that, then it has to be the biggest impact anyone has ever made. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/HgMRl27zM0c" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:14.0pt"&gt;Jyoti Bansal, CEO, PHD India&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:14.0pt"&gt;My vote goes to Sriharsha Majeti, Rahul Jaimini and Nandan Reddy of Swiggy for what they&amp;rsquo;ve done for office lunches and the way India orders its food today. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/PmV48UpGv0A" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:14.0pt"&gt;Santosh Padhi, Chief Creative Officer &amp;amp; Co-founder, Taproot Dentsu&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:14.0pt"&gt;Nadia Chauhan should win because of the aggressive work that she and Parle Agro have done so wonderfully for some of the Parle products, despite a few ups and downs in the category. They have still emerged in a strong way and she&amp;rsquo;s the one who has been fronting the brand and deserves to win the IPOY title, among the nominees that have been listed. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/9KFdRYTaRb0" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:14.0pt"&gt;To know more about the event, please click here: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://e4mevents.com/ipoy-2018/" style="color:#0563c1; text-decoration:underline"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:14.0pt"&gt;https://e4mevents.com/ipoy-2018/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93331-ipoy18.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing-news/unilever-cmo-keith-weed-quits-93320.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>06/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Unilever CMO Keith Weed Quits</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Chief marketing officer of Unilever, Keith Weed has announced his&amp;nbsp;retirement from the business.&amp;nbsp;He spent nearly&amp;nbsp;four decades with Unilever. As CMO,&amp;nbsp;he was responsible for the marketing, communications and sustainable business functions at&amp;nbsp;Unilever.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-lang="en-gb"&gt;&#13;
&lt;p dir="ltr" lang="en"&gt;Wow! Where did the last 35 years go? Time has flown. I&amp;#39;ve had the pleasure of working with super people in Unilever &amp;amp; beyond. It&amp;#39;s with a happy and heavy heart that I&amp;#39;ve decided to retire from Unilever in April It&amp;#39;s been over a year in planning with exciting challenges 2 follow &lt;a href="https://t.co/IMcuyBNMkN"&gt;pic.twitter.com/IMcuyBNMkN&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&amp;mdash; Keith Weed (@keithweed) &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/keithweed/status/1070718944066056192?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;6 December 2018&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#13;
&lt;script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Weed will leave the FMCG giant in May next year. Unilever has not confirmed who will be stepping up to take on the top marketing role.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;His departure follows on from Alan Jope being appointed to the position of chief executive, taking over from outgoing exec Paul Polman.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Weed said in reports: &amp;ldquo;I have had a hugely enjoyable time with the company, with a range of positions in different countries.&amp;nbsp;As the world&amp;rsquo;s second largest advertiser, we have been able to leverage our scale for effectiveness and efficiencies, and we have also been able to leverage our scale for good, leading for greater responsibility, transparency and accountability in the advertising and digital industry.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Weed joined Unilever in 1983. He was appointed to the role of chief marketing and communications officer in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Over the last few years, Weed along with P&amp;amp;G&amp;#39;s Marc Pritchard,&amp;nbsp;has been working with agencies and platforms to stop advertisers losing money to issues like ad fraud and opaque digital measurement. This year&amp;nbsp;at Cannes he&amp;nbsp;called for&amp;nbsp;the industry to put a stop to influencer fraud.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/fs_69361.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing-news/pepsicos-change-the-game-offers-students-chance-to-win-100000-grant-93316.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>06/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>PepsiCo’s ‘Change the Game’ offers students chance to win $100,000 grant</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;As part of their journey to attract talent and empower the youth, PepsiCo India has conceptualised a campus challenge called &amp;lsquo;Change the Game&amp;rsquo;. The initiative, now it its third edition, provides young talent a platform to share creative solutions to real-life problem situations, with a chance to work with the company. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;This year, PepsiCo&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Change the Game&amp;rsquo; challenge has become bigger as the India winners will compete with winners from other regions for a chance to meet and present their business case to PepsiCo&amp;rsquo;s CEO Ramon Laguarta and the global leadership team in New York, the company said in a statement. Additionally, PepsiCo will also grant the winners a fund of $100,000 for bringing the winning idea to life, along with an international job offer.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Speaking about the initiative, Suchitra Rajendra - VP Human Resources India region, PepsiCo India, said, &amp;ldquo;The main objective of the &amp;lsquo;Change the Game&amp;rsquo; challenge is to spot the brightest sparks of talent by inviting them to develop sustainable and viable solutions to real issues. This year&amp;rsquo;s challenge is focussed on finding creative solutions to attaining PepsiCo&amp;rsquo;s Performance with Purpose goals for sustainable plastic packaging and recycling. We have already received an overwhelming response from India and continue to be impressed with the diverse range of creative business plan submissions we have received. We hope deserving talent from India will go on to win at the next level too.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;The third edition of &amp;lsquo;Change the Game&amp;rsquo; has received a phenomenal response &amp;ndash; with 11,000 students from top B schools in India putting their minds to make the world a better place by presenting solutions for sustainability. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;The challenge is open to undergraduate and postgraduate individuals, as well as working professionals with up to three years&amp;rsquo; experience, giving them an opportunity to make their mark globally. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="m7694586341267703927msonospacing" style="text-align:justify; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;The winning teams from the three PepsiCo regions -- India Region, Asia Pacific Region (Philippines, Korea, Thailand and Pakistan) and Middle East &amp;amp; North Africa Region (Egypt, Jordan, Lebanon, Kingdom of Saudi Arabia and UAE) -- will be eligible to travel to Dubai where they will compete at the finals. They will also get a year-long international experience or a two-month international internship.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:2.0pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;The regional first runners up will receive either a local job offer or an opportunity to &amp;lsquo;Shadow a Senior Business Leader&amp;rsquo; for a week. Regional second runners up will receive an opportunity to shadow a senior business leader for a week.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93316-pepsicoMain.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing-news/amazon-invests-rs-22-billion-of-new-funds-in-india-marketplace-93304.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>06/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Amazon invests Rs 22 billion of new funds in India marketplace</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;E-commerce giant Amazon has injected Rs 22 billion of new funding into Amazon Seller Services, its marketplace unit, according to media reports. This takes the overall funding in the unit to Rs 75 billion so far in this fiscal year.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The new funding comes at a time when it is believed that Amazon India is almost on par or has outdone&amp;nbsp;its domestic rivals in terms of gross sales on its platform.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;However, the burn rate continues to remain at a higher level as e-commerce giants have set their aim to conquer the underpenetrated tier-II and tier-III type of markets that require a different approach.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93304-amazonlogo.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing-news/saregama-carvaan-a-lesson-in-listening-to-the-consumer-93291.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>06/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Saregama Carvaan: A lesson in listening to the consumer</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;The Saregama Carvaan is 55-year-old Archana Singh&amp;rsquo;s primary music listening device. She listens to bhajans in the morning and evergreen melodies of the 60s and 70s while having her evening tea. Last Diwali her children gifted it to her and her husband. And over the past year, Carvaan has become her prized possession. What&amp;rsquo;s more, Singh&amp;rsquo;s friends who have experienced Carvaan at her home have also bought the portable music player.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Scepticism was rife 16 months ago when legacy music licencing company Saregama (erstwhile HMV) announced the launch of its digital music player that resembled an old fashioned radio. Who would pay to buy a device that stores 5,000 songs when everything is freely available on sites like YouTube, most&amp;nbsp;wondered. But people like Archana Singh and her friends are testimony to the consumer insight that drove Saregama to rethink how people listen to music.&amp;nbsp;People wanted a device that is convenient to use. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Positioned for people in the 40-plus age bracket, Carvaan delivers a lean-back listening experience in a world where people need to proactively create playlists of their liking and decide what song they want to listen to next.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;The scepticism about a product like Carvaan stems from people, and sometimes even marketers, getting stuck inside an echo chamber of people just like them. The success of Saregama Carvaan teaches marketers to never lose touch of the needs of the end consumer.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Vikram Mehra, Managing Director of Saregama Carvaan, says, &amp;ldquo;As marketers we start thinking that the whole of India or the world is like us. It need not be so. There are a large number of people in this country who still want things that are comfortable.&amp;rdquo; He says that marketers must not lose touch with what the end consumer wants. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Calling Saregama Carvaan unique and unconventional, brand guru Saurabh Uboweja said, &amp;ldquo;This is a simple product that is packaged around a need that was not serviced.&amp;rdquo; At a time when all marketers are chasing the millennials, &amp;ldquo;Carvaan targeted a market that is largely ignored by brands,&amp;rdquo; Uboweja pointed out.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Mehra said he was surprised to learn that people thought that Saregama was not sharing its huge library of music even though all the songs from the Saregama stable were available on all leading streaming platforms and YouTube for free. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Consumer research also revealed that the fear of technology gets stronger among people as they age. In addition to the 40+ demographic from non-metro cities and towns, Saregama spoke to people in the 65+ age group in Mumbai to learn their sentiments. They asked this group of people what they feared the most; the response the company was expecting was &amp;ldquo;dying.&amp;rdquo; Instead, this urban group said what it feared the most was &amp;ldquo;being dependent on children.&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Armed with this consumer insight, the company set out with a clear vision to create a product for people who grew up listening to iconic singers like Lata Mangeshkar, Asha Bhonsle, Kishore Kumar, Mukesh, and Mohd. Rafi. Positioning typically defines the target audience for a product. &amp;ldquo;It is also important to know who we are not positioned for,&amp;rdquo; says Mehra. He and his team is not targeting this product for a 21-year-old and they are clear about it.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;The Saregama team designed Carvaan to have a familiar user interface that triggers nostalgia. In the early version of the Carvaan, the buttons were activated on touch. &amp;ldquo;People got back saying with touch they were not sure of having pressed the button. So in the later models we introduced mechanical buttons,&amp;rdquo; explains Mehra.&amp;nbsp;Nostalgia-inspired products like Paper Boat&amp;rsquo;s drinks have been making a comeback in a huge way. Tapping into the nostalgia element through design and the selection of music has been a winning strategy for Carvaan and helped the product gain entry into the living rooms of people.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;The latest version of the product is also large in size because of the feedback that some perceived the product to be fragile. Mehra lifts the metallic Carvaan Gold to prove that it is light, though the appearance of the product makes it look robust.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/1544069291_XKwTG2_units-sold.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;All the attributes of the Saregama Carvaan, including its creative communication that positions it as a gift that youngsters can give their parents and grandparents have hit the right notes. The product has sold one million units since its launch and contributes to nearly half of Saregama&amp;rsquo;s music revenue. The company has just scratched the surface of its potential market size - 25 million homes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/1544069213_8OQLu4_music-share.jpg" style="width: 350px; height: 345px;" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Mehra could not be more proud of the product and what it stands for. &amp;ldquo;Biggest feather in our cap is that we not just created a new product but a new category and new concept that too from a brand that is not into retail.&amp;rdquo; As per Saregama&amp;rsquo;s internal studies, Carvaan is played for around 7.5 hours on average every day in a home where there is at least one person above the age of 60. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Mehra says that Carvaan will see many further iterations as feedback flows back into the company. He reiterates that the core insight that made Carvaan a success will always inform every stage of development. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&amp;ldquo;Carvaan is not just giving music but memories connected to music along with the convenience of listening to music,&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;he says. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93291-carvaan.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing-news/industry-experts-from-reliance-industries-and-jsw-steel-to-speak-at-iprccc-2018-93303.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>06/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Industry experts from Reliance Industries and JSW Steel to speak at IPRCCC 2018</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;The ninth edition of exchange4media&amp;#39;s India PR &amp;amp; Corporate Communications Awards 2018 is&amp;nbsp;the most extensive and exhaustive awards to recognise the contribution and success of the PR Industry. With five&amp;nbsp;categories and 22 sub categories, IPRCCA 2018 is the path breaking initiative to salute and recognise the contribution of PR Consultancies and Corporate Communications.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The event is scheduled to be held on December 13 at The Leela Ambience in Gurugram.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The event will also witness an all-day India PR &amp;amp; Corporate Communications Conference 2018. The theme for the conference this year is &amp;lsquo;The importance of integrated communications and its challenges&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The topic for the second session of the conference is on &amp;lsquo;Crisis management and Brand management two edged sword&amp;rsquo;, wherein our esteemed speakers will discuss how corporate contain and manages the crisis, especially when social media channels spread information like fire, how do brand contain information sensitivity and consumer sentiments. How to make brand communication most friendly for the media and consumers. How to tackle fake news, trolling shaming and manage brand image. Market risk are synonym with brand loyalty. Stakeholders are key influencers in business growth and it is imperative to mitigate risk factor. Especially in crisis situation, what should be the communication strategy for stakeholders to dovetail their decision making factor and market sentiments?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;To answer the above questions will be our esteemed speakers Rohit Bansal, Group Head of Communications, Reliance Industries and Jitendra Vashistha, Head- Corporate Communications, JSW Steel.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Bansal is a media leader and influencer. He is an alum of Harvard Business School and St Stephen&amp;rsquo;s College. He is a multiple TEDx speaker and a Distinguished Fellow at India&amp;#39;s premier think tank, the Observer Research Foundation (ORF). He serves on the National Executive of the Federation of Indian Chambers of Commerce &amp;amp; Industry (FICCI) and three national committees of the Confederation of Indian Industry (CII) on i) services, ii) skill development iii) media and entertainment.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Bansal is a British Chevening scholar. He has undertaken short professional programmes at University of Westminster, The Times Centre for Media Studies, and The European Journalism Centre, Maastricht. He served on the boards of Network18 Media &amp;amp; Investments, TV18, IBN Lokmat TV, Viacom18, HS18, Panorama, Prism, and News Broadcasters Association; Fellow, Institute of Competitiveness; Mentor, JioGenNext; as Resident Editor of The Financial Express, New Delhi; Managing Editor (and later COO) of Independent News Service; Editor-Business, Zee News; Special Correspondent, Television 18; and Senior Business Correspondent, The Times of India.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;In collaboration with law firm Hammurabi &amp;amp; Solomon, Bansal advised CEOs across the spectrum on policy and the media. He served as Treasurer of The Editors Guild of India and the Foundation of Media Professionals, was on the board of a hospital company and two start-ups in Essel Group. He served as Trustee, St Stephen&amp;#39;s Alumni Foundation Trust. His expertise is at the intersect of Government and Regulation, Media/Social Media, Reputation, Corporate Communications, Strategy, Alliances, and Legal Affairs.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Jitendra Vashistha spearheads Corporate Communications function for India&amp;#39;s largest integrated steel plant - JSW Steel Ltd. and is based at their flagship plant of Vijayanagar, Karnataka. He possesses comprehensive multi-industry experience in the areas of Corporate Communications &amp;amp; PR, encompassing internal &amp;amp; external communication, marketing communications, and CSR for over two decades with the multinational and blue-chip organisations in the industries covering FMCG, Financial Services, IT, Manufacturing and Telecom. He&amp;rsquo;s a seasoned corporate communications&amp;#39; professional with hands-on exposure, experience, and expertise in leading strategic communications for the leading multi-national brands in the likes of Fidelity, RPG Enterprises, Amway, Fidelity, HSBC, and Vodafone.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Vashistha has cut his teeth in the entire gamut of corporate communications in establishing &amp;amp; developing communication function, mentoring teams, relationship building and strategic engagement with external and internal stakeholders for delivering strategic, effective &amp;amp; measurable communication in a global change-environment.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;He was the first communication executive from India to earn a seat at HSBC&amp;rsquo;s Executive Council &amp;ndash; EXCO, of Global Technology. He was instrumental in partnering &amp;amp; deploying one of the largest Change Communications&amp;#39; programmes of HSBC Group, impacting over 30K employees worldwide. He curated and led some interesting PR properties at Amway Corporation, which helped him steer the challenging &amp;amp; intriguing crisis communications management programme. At the moment, his primary thrusts are on safety communication and to find inclusive communication threads to build employee and media relations in an era; engulfed by social media, digitalisation and disruptive interventions.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Ad Factors is the presenting partner of the IPRCCA and is co-Powered by Media Mantra &amp;amp; MSL. The gold partner is Kaizzen, PR Pundit &amp;amp; AvianWe. The urban mobility partner is Uber. The dgital media partner is Media Value works. Policy Bazaar is the knowledge partner and is co-partnered by Text 100, The Publicist &amp;amp; Kommune. The lifestyle PR partner is ActiMedia, TV partner is NewsX, creativity partner is Webershandwick. The partner For IPRCCC is Pearl Academy.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;To know more, click here: &lt;a href="https://e4mevents.com/iprcca-2018/"&gt;https://e4mevents.com/iprcca-2018/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93303-IPRCCCMain.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
</urlset>
