<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9" xmlns:image="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-image/1.1" xmlns:news="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-news/0.9">
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/mediaradio/big-fm-ups-core-market-ad-rates-by-12-15-this-festive-season_92373.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>04/10/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Big FM ups core market ad rates by 12-15% this festive season</news:title>
      <news:description>With markets stabilizing post demonetisation and the implications of GST, BIG FM has spiked its national as well as region specific rates for the upcoming festive season. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Parallelly, BIG FM is also looking at partnering with advertisers for deep integration, long tenure and sponsorship sales. The radio network is invariably looking at providing a clutter free experience by reducing ad inventory in key markets. The radio network intends to increase rates by approximately 12 – 15 % in core markets and a rate correction Rs. 25 – 35 / 10 secs in smaller stations. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commenting on the same, Asheesh Chatterjee, CFO, BIG FM, says, "The idea is to offer our advertisers with unique value proposition by providing plethora of festival spikes, unique integration restricting cloud burst and providing extremely good ROIs for advertisers. With 90% of our stations ranked amongst the top stations as per IRS 2017, we look forward to seamlessly serving our advertisers and listeners with interesting and exciting content.”&amp;nbsp;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src="https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/1538653774_O7xhQP_gfx3.jpg"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Radio penetration has showed a growth of nearly 100% across India between 2014 and 2017 as per a report by IRS. Only 35% of Indians have access to the internet as compared to broadcast radio which has access to 99% of the Indian population. Radio medium also holds far stronger position over internet in priority states including Bihar, MP, Tamil Nadu, UP, West Bengal, Orissa etc.  &lt;/div&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/article/article_large_image/1538653382_vQ1FTm_BIG-FM-logo.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/mediaradio/ram-week-36-fever-fm-leader-in-mumbai-and-delhi-again_92277.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>27/09/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>RAM Week 36: Fever FM leader in Mumbai and Delhi again</news:title>
      <news:description>In Week 36 of the RAM ratings, Fever FM continued to retain its leadership position in Mumbai and Delhi. Radio City and Radio Mirchi retained the top positions in Bangalore and Kolkata, respectively.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Mumbai, in a universe of 12.2 million listeners, Fever FM ruled with 17.3 per cent share, followed by Radio Mirchi and Radio City with a 13.5 per cent and 13.1 per cent share, respectively. Early morning followed by mid-morning and afternoon time band observed highest listenership on total radio. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fever FM continued to lead in Delhi as well, with 18.7 per cent share&amp;nbsp;in a universe of 16.5 million listeners. Radio City and Radio Nasha with 12.7 per cent and 12 per cent share held the second and third positions, respectively. Evening followed by mid-morning and  afternoon time band observed highest listenership on total radio.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Bangalore, in a universe of 5.3 million listeners, Radio City maintained its leadership with 25.3 per cent share, followed by Big FM and Radio Mirchi. Both retained their spots with 19.4 and 17.1 per cent share, respectively. Afternoon followed by mid-morning and evening time band observed highest listenership on total radio.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Radio Mirchi retained its number one position in Kolkata in a universe of 9.5 million listeners, with a share of 19.3 per cent, followed by Fever FM in the second spot and Big FM in the third with 17.9 per cent and 17.3 per cent share, respectively. Afternoon time band, followed by mid-morning and morning observed the highest listenership on total radio.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/article/article_large_image/1538013034_weolMG_radio_final.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/mediaradio/ram-ratings-week-34-fever-continues-to-lead-mumbai-and-delhi_92054.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>13/09/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>RAM ratings Week 34: Fever continues to lead Mumbai and Delhi</news:title>
      <news:description>In Week 34 of the RAM ratings, Fever FM continued to retain its leadership position in Mumbai and Delhi. The channel has been the leader for the past seven weeks. Radio City and Radio Mirchi retained the top positions in Bangalore and Kolkata, respectively. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Mumbai, in a universe of 12.2 million listeners, Fever FM ruled with 16.1 per cent share, followed by Radio Mirchi and Radio City with a 13.8 per cent and 12.5 per cent share respectively. Early morning followed by mid-morning and morning time band observed highest listenership on total radio.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Fever FM continued to lead in Delhi as well, with an improved share of 19.2 per cent in a universe of 16.5 million listeners. Radio Mirchi and Radio City, with 13.4 per cent and 13.1 per cent share held the second and third positions, respectively. Mid-morning followed by early morning and night band observed highest listenership on total radio.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Bangalore, in a universe of 5.3 million listeners, Radio City maintained its leadership with 25.2 per cent, followed by Big FM and Radio Mirchi. Both retained their spots with 18.1 and 17.4 per cent, respectively. Afternoon followed by night and mid-morning time band observed highest listenership on total radio. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Radio Mirchi retained its number one position in Kolkata in a universe of 9.5 million listeners, with a share of 19.8 per cent, followed by Fever FM in the second spot and Big FM in the third with 17.8 per cent and 17 per cent share, respectively. Afternoon time band, followed by mid-morning and morning observed the highest listenership on total radio.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/article/article_large_image/1515551597_Mcyl7K_big_(1).jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/mediaradio/ram-week-33-fever-continues-to-lead-mumbai-and-delhi_91930.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>06/09/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>RAM Week 33: Fever continues to lead Mumbai and Delhi</news:title>
      <news:description>In Week 33 of the RAM Ratings, Fever FM continued to retain its leadership position in Mumbai and Delhi for the past seven weeks, while Radio City and Radio Mirchi retained the top positions in Bangalore and Kolkata market respectively. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Mumbai, in a universe of 12.2 million listeners, Fever FM ruled this market with a 16.7 per cent share, while Radio Mirchi and Radio City clinched the second and third positions with a 13.7 per cent and 12.2 per cent share respectively. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Early morning, followed by morning and mid-morning time band observed the highest listenership in total radio.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fever FM continued to lead in Delhi in Week 33 as well, with an 18.4 per cent share in a universe of 16.5 million listeners. Radio Mirchi and Radio City, with a 12.7 percent and 12.5 per cent share held the second and third positions respectively. Early-morning, followed by mid-morning and evening time band observed the highest listenership on total radio.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Bangalore, in a universe of 5.3 million listeners, Radio City dominated with a 24.7 per cent share, while Big FM held the second position with an 18.4 per cent share, followed by Radio Mirchi in third with a 17.1 per cent share. Evening, followed by afternoon and mid-morning time band observed the highest listenership on total radio.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Radio Mirchi continued to retain its number one position in a universe of 9.5 million listeners, with a 17.7 per cent share, followed by Fever FM in the second spot and Big FM in the third with a 16.4 percent share. Afternoon time band, followed by mid-morning and morning observed the highest listenership on total radio.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/article/article_large_image/1515551597_Mcyl7K_big_(1).jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/mediaradio/no-unified-measurement-so-how-does-the-radio-industry-work_91745.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>27/08/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>No unified measurement: So, how does the radio industry work? </news:title>
      <news:description>Radio Mirchi’s second channel Mirchi 95 pulls in 9.6 lakh listeners in Bengaluru &amp;amp; Hyderabad, and Red FM has more than 35 per cent market share in Kerala. Thanks to the Indian Readership Survey (IRS) launched this year, these detailed breakups of the listenership data are now available with radio channels. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Undoubtedly, such&amp;nbsp;insights from&amp;nbsp;IRS&amp;nbsp;data&amp;nbsp;based on listener profile, demographics, frequency&amp;nbsp;and timeband come in extremely handy for the radio industry, which does not have a unified measurement in place. And in the absence of a unified system, most players take help of third-party agencies, commission independent researches or subscribe to Radio Audience Measurement (RAM) data by TAM Media Research. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To each his own&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Take, for instance, ENIL-led Radio Mirchi. Prior to the launch of IRS, which they have now adopted as their currency, the radio station worked with IPSOS, the third largest market research company in the world to gather listenership data from 2015-17. The channel had initially subscribed to RAM data, but pulled out of it in 2015.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to GG Jayanta, National Marketing Head, Radio Mirchi, IRS 2017 is an “excellent tool”. &lt;br&gt;“It shows the importance of radio as a medium and category. The penetration of radio has increased by 15 percentage points in urban areas, from 15% to 28%, representing a growth of 87% in listenership,” he shared.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another big player, Red FM, follows IRS to a certain extent, especially for tier-II and III towns. However, the station, depending on the need, conducts qualitative study in different markets from time to time. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nisha Narayanan, COO &amp;amp; Director, RED FM &amp;amp; Redtro and CEO, Digital Radio, shared, “To enhance the product and marketing,&amp;nbsp;we do an internal research that&amp;nbsp;we mostly keep to&amp;nbsp;ourselves. But the industry needs a unified radio measurement system.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Homegrown international players such as Radio One measure consumer behaviour through an internal tool called ‘The International Indian Monitor.’ It helps them track the&amp;nbsp;unique upscale audience digitally using social media. &lt;br&gt;Vineet Singh Hukmani, MD &amp;amp; CEO, 94.3 Radio One, mentioned, “For reach quantitative measurement of radio, the annual IRS study is good. But the radio industry needs to understand that advertisers want engagement data, and reach is not enough.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;However there are stations, such as My FM, that neither follow IRS nor RAM. My FM, which operates out of 30 tier-II and tier-III cities, follow their own currency for product purpose.&lt;br&gt;Rahul Namjoshi, Business Head, MY FM, shared that they work with an agency called Karvy. They conduct quarterly survey with 200 respondents as sample size in top 12 cities each. &lt;br&gt;“The idea is to improve our product and see where we stand. It gazes the listenership preferences on RJs, music and timeband,” Namjoshi said. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Let's talk sales&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;The advertising revenue of the industry is estimated to grow by 10 per cent in 2018 to stand at Rs 2,063 crore. But in an industry governed by advertising revenue and somewhat challenged by the lack of a unified measurement currency, how does the stations sell their inventory?  &lt;br&gt;In most cases, advertisers take a 360-degree approach that goes beyond FCT to digital and on-ground properties. Moreover, some are of the opinion that radio is not sold on measurement but on engagement, impact, reach and frequency.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to Narayanan, radio inventory is sold based on brand perception. As a result, they are part of most of the media plans, especially if the planner wants to reach out to the younger audience.&lt;br&gt;Talking about the strategy followed by her channel, Narayanan said, “We don’t restrict to FCT as we believe in a 360-degree approach. There are different verticals for revenue generation such as digital and events. Content monetization is another area we focus on. It can be combined based on client requirement (event, digital supported with on-air).”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Radio Mirchi uses IRS 2017 as its currency to sell its inventory to the advertisers. Jayanta shared, “They (advertisers) are looking for a full suite of solutions beyond radio, encompassing integration with all or any of our concerts, events, digital and web series. Our business has grown on the back of ideas, innovation and partnership with the client.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;My FM works on their “client’s business challenges”. Namjoshi claimed that their approach is different from others.&lt;br&gt;“We propose media solutions (such as on-ground activation) which can address business challenges.” &lt;br&gt;The station has been working with national and local brands (such as Lotus Electronics store in Indore) for the past 11 years, he said.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But Asheesh Chatterjee, CFO, Big FM, is of the opinion that radio is sold more as a medium with “high-impact, high-frequency reach.” &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Big FM, one of the subscribers to RAM, operates more on the ‘hero, hub, hygiene’ model. The station has worked with more than 1,800 brands. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chatterjee explained, “Heroes are the bigger tentpole properties with highest brand recall such as Big Golden Voice. In hub, comes our real estate, gadget and movie review shows which have a narrow TG. These unique formats offer rich content integration. This makes the brand recall much better as the client message is passed across in a far more meaningful and clutter-breaking manner. Big FM looks at platform agnostic solutions. Some solutions get augmented in radio and are amplified on digital property.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meanwhile, even media planners feel challenged as the medium suffers from a lack of sufficient reliable and regular data. Ashish Bhasin, Chairman &amp;amp; CEO of South Asia Dentsu Aegis Network - Aegis Group, shared, “There isn’t sufficient radio research in India. It is a challenge for media planners as they have to evaluate based on their judgement, intuition and the paltry available data. As a result, it has remained a relatively smaller medium.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Advertisers like KidZania, who has Radio City as their radio partner, look at RAM figures given by agencies and stations. Tarandeep Singh Sekhon, Marketing Director, KidZania, said, “I am making do with what’s available. With a mix of qualitative feedback, we mostly do FCT and bigger activation.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;So while different stations resort to different ways to measure their audience, industry experts feel that it is absolutely necessary for the category to have a unified audience measurement system. Well, the good news is that AROI and MRUC are currently working on such a system.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where’s RAM heading&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;RAM subscribers keep a track of their weekly data from four main markets based on physical diary-entry method. But the methodology will soon transition into digital medium as TAM Media Research is testing a software that captures in-mobile listening. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;L V Krishnan, CEO, Tam Media Research, explained, “With&amp;nbsp;listening to audio&amp;nbsp;content getting more skewed to the&amp;nbsp;mobile platform, it is only imperative that measurement moves in the same direction. Hence, we are testing a measurement software that picks up the audio bits of the content for that specific frequency. The software encrypts whatever is getting transmitted or listened by the audience. At the second level, it reports which station and&amp;nbsp;what respondents listen to. It’s all real time basis. It’s the stage one of going digital.” &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“With no hardware needed in this method, the measurement is scalable in nature and can be expanded to remaining markets. Also, this fits into our overall vision of measuring not just radio, but audio as well. In this manner, we will also be able to measure audio streaming apps and podcasts on mobile device. Thus one can measure the interplay between various audio platforms,” Krishnan added.&lt;br&gt;For the process, Tam Media Research has roped in Vtion as their software partner and field agency Kantar. The research agency plans to unveil the new system for some markets this year-end.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;So, till the new unified measurement system takes shape and TAM’s digital measurement comes to form, the current state of affairs with regards to measurement and selling, it seems, will continue.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/article/article_large_image/1535338459_Rsh7DG_Radio.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/mediaradio/abraham-thomas-moves-out-of-radio-city-ashit-kukian-joins-in-as-ceo_91742.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>24/08/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Abraham Thomas moves out of Radio City, Ashit Kukian joins in as CEO</news:title>
      <news:description>Abraham Thomas has stepped down as the CEO of Radio City after serving nearly three years. Ashit Kukian will be taking over his position according to industry sources. This is his second stint with Radio City where he will report to Apurva Purohit,&amp;nbsp;President, Jagran Prakashan.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kukian was earlier with iTV Network as COO-NewsX &amp;amp; CRO-iTV Regionals, Entertainment &amp;amp; Sports Businesses. Kukian was President – Revenue for Times Network. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prior to joining Times Network, Kukian was the President and Chief Operating Officer at Radio City from 2005-15. His leadership, industry insights and operational expertise had strengthened Radio City's performance in the radio industry through traditional and non-traditional revenue.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/article/article_large_image/1532489034_bfKsai_radio-city_final.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/mediaradio/continuous-consumer-engagement-has-helped-us-differentiate-ourselves-head-friends-fm_91528.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>09/08/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Continuous consumer engagement has helped us differentiate ourselves: Head, Friends FM</news:title>
      <news:description>With projected margins of about 20 per cent in FY 17-18, Kolkata-based Friends FM is riding high. Jimmy Tangree, Head, Friends FM tells us how the focus on continuous consumer engagement has been a key to their success and has helped the station differentiate itself from other players.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How has the year been so far for Friends FM? What kind of growth are you witnessing? How is the medium doing overall?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the past four years, we have been improving our line. Our margins Y-o-Y have been going up – 15 per cent in FY 15/16, 18 per cent in FY 16/17 and a projected 20 per cent in FY 17/18. So we are growing. What makes Radio different is that it gives you a direct engagement profile like no other medium. We can engage with the audience, get full demographic data, have consumer participation or innovative integrations, all in one hour. And at the end of that one hour, results are out, then and there. Today, if a client does something at night, he has the entire data detail by the next morning. So its instantaneous, live and responsive. Today radio is surrounded by ancillaries like Digital, on-ground activations and events, FB live etc. The Digital medium has also helped bring about a sense of new business because when you bundle, it adds to the top-line. Radio is the only entertainment platform that can give you a 360 degree solution. So overall business is looking good for Radio. But the crux to good business is a lot of innovation and introspective engagement. Innovation with a combination of Digital and on-ground is going to take Radio way ahead. The mantra for Radio is simple, connect and you will be successful. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The station started off being a retro Bengali music FM station but has now transformed into a much younger, fresher offering. How difficult was the transition?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four years of being a part of the Ananda Offset Pvt Ltd (AOPL) has been an amazing experience. The kind of freedom and encouragement we got from the the higher ups gave us an opportunity to do a lot, we experimented a lot and did a lot of new things that were unheard of from a radio station. Who would have thought that an eight year old retro Bengali music channel could change over and do well. Initially we would do a lot of Bengali music but now it's a blend of Hindi, Bengali and English shows with a lot of engagement.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is your primary target audience the youth?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are primarily targeting people between the age of 18 to 45. Our goal is to target those who are young and also the ones that are young at heart. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Friends FM has been acquired by Music Broadcast Limited. What kind of changes can we expect to see at Friends FM as a result of this acquisition?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To be very honest, we don’t really have much to update right now. Yes the acquisition has happened, subject to a clearance from the Ministry of Information and Broadcasting. So people are just waiting for the clearance to come through. For now, there has been no change in the way we were running. We are still Friends FM.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For a market like Kolkata, the festive season is very critical with a large part of business coming in during those few weeks. What are your plans for this year?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last year we did a 100 Durga puja tie-ups, 91 VIP entries, 18 activations, 3257 live updates and brought close to 199 celebs live on air. We have already started gearing up for the festive season this year. We will have all that we did last year but we’ll have a lot of innovation both at the station and on-ground. We’ll be connecting, participating and engaging with the festivities. Our aim is to make people feel like they are celebrating puja when they tune in to our station even if they are not on ground.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Innovation is a big part of the work that you do with brands. Do you have a dedicated innovation team?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;We don’t have a separate team. All our teams, be it the sales and marketing teams or the programming teams, sit together, discuss client briefs, brainstorm, and come up with innovative client solutions. Content which engages is the finest content on air. And that’s where we score. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What differentiates Friends FM from other FM players?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are a 24x7 live station. Night time is also super prime for us. We are the only station that is live through the night and that makes a difference because we are always connected, not just on our stations but through SMS, WhatsApp messages, Facebook etc. That is a huge differentiator and has helped us reach where we are today.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/article/article_large_image/1533782174_EMDShE_JimmyTangree_Head_FriendsFM.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/mediaradio/farhan-akhtar-launches-international-radio-station-kool-104-in-hyderabad_91495.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>07/08/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Farhan Akhtar launches international radio station Kool 104 in Hyderabad</news:title>
      <news:description>Kool 104, Hyderabad’s first international radio station, officially announced its launch in the city on Tuesday at an event which was attended by actor-director Farhan Akhtar.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The music on Kool 104 comprises latest international chartbusters with some evergreen hits in the afternoon. According to the company, this is an FM station for those who crave for the best of English pop music and who follow contemporary international sensations such as Justin Bieber, The Chainsmokers, Rihanna, Coldplay, Ariana Grande, Maroon 5, Dua Lipa and Selena Gomez.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The RJs on the station are ‘Kool Sana’ who comes on from 7am to 12 noon and is available on Instagram @sanakool104; ‘Kool Deep’ who comes on-air from 12 noon-4 PM; ‘Kool Savio’ who does the evening drive show from 4 PM-9 PM and is available on Instagram @saviokool104; and the host of the night show Kool Paran, who takes to the airwaves from 9pm-12 midnight.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The launch event saw Farhan Akhtar take to the stage to unveil the logo of Kool 104 in front of the audience. When asked about the event, Akhtar said, “I have grown up listening to classic bands and artists from the 70s, 80s and 90s. Most of them have influenced my song writing and music. So I’m sure Hyderabad’s first international station – Kool 104 - will keep everyone entertained with the best international hits!”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tapas Sen, Chief Programming Officer, ENIL, commented, “We are very happy to be launching an international radio station in Hyderabad. With this new station, we now cover all three languages in the city, Telugu with Mirchi 98.3, Hindi with Mirchi 95 and English with Kool 104. As with all our stations, the product was devised after a lot of research and we hope that people love the content on Kool as much as we loved coming up with it!”</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/article/article_large_image/1533626587_z13OZd_farhan_akhtar_image.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/mediaradio/radio-mirchi-expands-in-gujarat-new-station-opens-in-bharuch_91464.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>06/08/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Radio Mirchi expands in Gujarat; new station opens in Bharuch</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Radio Mirchi recently kicked off its expansion in Gujarat with a new station in Bharuch, inaugurated by the Hon’ble Chief Minister of Gujarat, Vijay Rupani.&lt;br&gt;He was also the first guest on the station and the first segment on Mirchi 92.3 in Bharuch was a direct message to the people of Bharuch from the CM.&lt;br&gt;Mirchi already has six stations in Ahmedabad, Vadodara, Surat and Rajkot (including Mirchi Love). As part of the expansion, Mirchi is entering six new cities in Gujarat including Bharuch, Junagadh, Jamnagar, Palanpur, Mehsana and Bhavnagar. &lt;br&gt;Speaking on this occasion, Vijay Rupani, Gujarat CM, said, “I am extremely happy that Radio Mirchi is setting up stations in so many new locations in Gujarat. I wish them the very best and am sure that it is only a matter of time before it becomes as much a part of the social and cultural fabric of all these towns as it is in Ahmedabad, Baroda, Surat and Rajkot already!”&lt;br&gt;Bithindra Biswas, Cluster Head - Gujarat, Radio Mirchi, commented, “We are extremely happy to be expanding into so many new cities. With the launch of Bharuch and the upcoming five more locations, we will be present in 10 cities across the state. We always strive to provide the best content everywhere we go and this is our plan for these new cities as well. We hope the audience enjoys what we put on-air as much as we enjoyed devising it.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/article/article_large_image/1533535384_7P9Ldr_radiomirchiguj.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/mediaradio/superhits-935-red-fm-introduces-new-short-series-short-cuts_91448.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>04/08/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Superhits 93.5 Red FM introduces new short series- Short-cuts&#13;
&#13;
</news:title>
      <news:description>Pushing the wave of creative narrative to a new height, 93.5 Red FM has initiated an original series of quick story-telling sessions titled Short-cuts, which will wrap up within 2 mins, but not without a twist at the end. Sticking to the taut and intense feel of multiple award-winning shows on Red FM such as - Ek Kahani Aisi Bhi and The Headphone Show, Short-cuts also promises to keep listeners glued to the station. Narrated by RJ Praveen, whose visceral narration in Ek Kahaani Aisi Bhi brought him the prestigious award at the New York Radio Festival for Best Innovation and Best Narration in 2015 &amp;amp; 2016. Short-cuts will be played across the Red FM network, along with a video narrative of each story being put up on social media pages of Red FM.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/1533353300_gRNZ0N_Creative-1.jpg" style="width:443px;height:162px;vertical-align:middle"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commenting on the programme, Nisha Narayanan, COO, Red FM, says “Storytelling and audio narratives are back with a bang and listeners are looking forward to exciting story telling formats on radio. Our previous story telling programmes like ‘Ek Kahani Aisi Bhi &amp;amp; The Headphone Show’ being widely appreciated by our listeners, we thought of innovating in the story telling format with “Short-cuts. With most listeners running behind their busy schedules, this time we have tweaked the story-telling format to a swift one, accompanied by short films for every story on digital platform. The two minutes stories will have twisted and exciting endings.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It is all about creating meaningful content which aims to revive the golden days of radio, when it was the ultimate medium of entertainment. Short-cuts is an inventive way of story-telling in digital age where both on-air and online mediums will be utilized for effective narrative. Harnessing the ingenuity of our creative resource we promise to deliver the most thrilling experience to our audience.”, said RJ Praveen, who has conceptualised the entire initiative along with Ranjit Pathak, the national creative head at Red FM.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/1533353300_2U8xVb_Creative-2.jpg" style="width:443px;height:162px;vertical-align:middle"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shortcuts has already begun enticing the audience with its compelling fictional story plot that have been made utmost graphic with experimental voice modulation, appropriate sound effects, and ambient background music. In addition to that, every on-air narrative has been adapted into short film with precise representation. The listeners will be served with 2 fresh stories every week. This is the first time, a radio property will release narratives on-air and on digital platforms at the same time. 93.5 Red FM hopes to keep its listeners entertained with more innovative ways that add to the glorious legacy of radio.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/article/article_large_image/1533353346_wUkIwV_Red-FM_(1).jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/mediaradio/magic-1064-fm-appoints-apeksha-mehta-as-station-head_91361.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>31/07/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Magic 106.4 FM appoints Apeksha Mehta as Station Head</news:title>
      <news:description>Magic&amp;nbsp;106.4 FM, the brand-new radio station that recently hit Mumbai airwaves, has appointed Apeksha Mehta as the Station Head.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prior to joining Magic 106.4 FM, Apeksha has worked with popular brands in the entertainment industry. She began her career with MTV and also worked with Zee Entertainment Enterprises Limited for eight and a half years, handling marketing for channels Zee TV and Zee Cinema, as well as the OTT platform, Ditto TV. Apeksha has worked as DVP Digital Marketing and Strategy and spearheaded their digital initiatives. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apeksha previously worked with Amazon Bangalore, with the Amazon Seller Services team and took care of Marketing, PR and special projects for Amazon Sellers. At Amazon she spearheaded the project for the empowerment of women entrepreneurs on the platform, along with working on several award-winning marketing campaigns.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commenting on her new role at Magic&amp;nbsp;106.4 FM Apeksha Mehta says, "I am very excited to head the station for Magic 106.4 FM. For me this switch acts as a catalyst for change in my career graph. It is a young brand and given my experience in entertainment with television, I look forward to working with radio now. Magic&amp;nbsp;is a promising brand and there is a lot of creativity which can be explored to reach our listener base. With the brand proposition of ‘Jee Le Zara’ there is a lot we have in store for the station and I cannot wait to get started on making this brand a successful one.”</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/article/article_large_image/1533030211_UIL9jf_Apeksha-Mehta-MAGIC-FM---1-(1).jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/mediaradio/music-broadcast-limited-reports-245-hike-in-net-profit-for-q1fy19_91232.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>25/07/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Music Broadcast Limited reports 24.5% hike in net profit for Q1FY19</news:title>
      <news:description>Music Broadcast Limited&amp;nbsp;(MBL),&amp;nbsp;which owns and operates FM radio stations under the &lt;em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;Radio City,   reported 24.5 per cent increase in net profit for its Q1FY19 to&amp;nbsp;Rs 13 crore, up from&amp;nbsp;  from Rs 10 crore&amp;nbsp;in Q1FY18.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company also reported&amp;nbsp;improvement in operating profit by 17.5 per cent YOY. Topline is up by 8 per cent to Rs 75.7 crore from Rs 70 crore.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The key highlights were hike in rate in all core markets, improvement in utilization in Phase III Markets with a positive contribution to EBITDA and 34.4 per cent operating margin delivery testimony of fixed costs and operating leverage playing. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Talking about the results,&amp;nbsp;Apurva Purohit, Director of&amp;nbsp;MBL, said,&amp;nbsp;“I am pleased to inform you that our company continued its trend of delivering stronger than expected EBITDA margins, with this quarter’s margin being 34&amp;nbsp;per cent. Our topline showed a growth of 8 per cent, on the back of rate hikes in all 12 core markets and improved utilizations in the Phase III stations in accordance with our strategy formulated for the year."&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Our PAT growth, which is more than three times of the top line growth at 25%, reiterates the fixed cost nature of our business as well as validates the strategic choices we made while bidding, i.e. to expand our geographic footprint, rather than deepen it at unviable costs,"&amp;nbsp;Purohit added.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/article/article_large_image/1532489034_bfKsai_radio-city_final.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/mediaradio/943-radio-one-and-fever-fm-radio-nasha-propose-merger_91114.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>19/07/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>94.3 Radio One and Fever FM-Radio Nasha propose merger  </news:title>
      <news:description>Next Radio Ltd (94.3 Radio One) and HT Media Ltd (Fever and Radio-Nasha) are proposing a merger to take advantage of a larger combined metro play  subject to the approval of shareholders, legal bodies and the Ministry of Information &amp;amp; Broadcasting.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;While Radio One is a pioneer in the international format space, Fever &amp;amp; Radio Nasha are exceptional leaders in the Hindi CHR &amp;amp; Retro radio space respectively. This proposed coming together allows the merged entity to offer enhanced value for listeners and advertisers by offering them clearly segmented high value products. 7 stations of  Fever FM + Radio Nasha (Delhi-2, Mumbai-2, Bangalore, Kolkata &amp;amp; Chennai) and all 6 stations of Radio One (Delhi, Mumbai, Bangalore, Kolkata, Chennai, &amp;amp; Pune) will aim to come together in a proposed merged entity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Both radio companies, will currently continue to operate ‘independently’ as before since the proposed merger is subject to government approval. Once the merger has all the requisite approvals, HT Media and its shareholders will hold 74% and Next Radio shareholders will hold 26% in the merged entity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vineet Singh Hukmani MD &amp;amp; CEO Radio One &amp;amp; Harshad Jain, CEO Fever FM will continue to function in their respective leadership roles. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sales teams of both companies will continue to function independently as before and will not sell any combination products</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/article/article_large_image/1531911141_n7k3yk_collage_(30).jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/mediaradio/ram-ratings-week-26-fever-fm-continues-to-lead-in-mumbai-and-delhi_91073.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>18/07/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>RAM Ratings Week 26: Fever FM continues to lead in Mumbai and Delhi</news:title>
      <news:description>In Week 26 of the RAM Ratings, Fever FM continued to retain its leadership position in Mumbai and Delhi, while Radio City retains the top position in Bangalore and Radio Mirchi continues to dominate in Kolkata.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Mumbai, in a universe of 12.2 million listeners, Fever FM continued to rule in the top position with a 16.4 per cent share, while Radio Mirchi clinched the second position with a 14 per cent share and Big FM took the third spot with a 13 per cent share.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Early morning, followed by morning and mid-morning time band observed the highest listenership in total radio.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fever FM continued to lead in Delhi in Week 26 as well, with a 19.5 per cent share in a universe of 16.5 million listeners. Radio city, with a 13 percent share held the second spot, while Radio Mirchi took the third position.&lt;br&gt;Mid-morning, followed by night and afternoon time band observed the highest listenership on total radio.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Bangalore, in a universe of 5.3 million listeners, Radio City dominated with a 25.1 per cent share, while Big FM held the second position with a 19 per cent share, followed by Radio Mirchi in third with a 17 per cent share.&lt;br&gt;Evening, followed by afternoon and mid-morning time band observed the highest listenership on total radio.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Radio Mirchi continued to retain its number one position in a universe of 9.1 million listeners, with a 19.2 per cent share, followed by Fever FM in the second spot and Big FM in third with a 17 percent share.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Afternoon time band, followed by evening and morning observed the highest listenership on total radio.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/article/article_large_image/1515551597_Mcyl7K_big_(1).jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/mediaradio/ram-ratings-week-24-fever-fm-retains-lead-position-in-mumbai-and-delhi_90873.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>05/07/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>RAM Ratings Week 24: Fever FM retains lead position in Mumbai and Delhi </news:title>
      <news:description>Week 24 of the RAM ratings saw Fever FM continue in the leading position in Mumbai and Delhi, while Radio City and Radio Mirchi continued to lead in Bangalore and Kolkata, respectively.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Mumbai, in a universe of 12.2 million listeners, Fever FM remained at the top spot with a share of 16.4 per cent, followed by Radio Mirchi in the second spot with 13.8 per cent. Big FM climbed to third spot with 12.5 per cent. Radio City slipped to fourth spot with 12.4 per cent while Radio Nasha took the fifth spot with 10.7 per cent. Early Morning, followed by mid-morning and morning time band observed the highest listenership in total radio.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fever FM also held the top position in Delhi, with 19.3 per cent share in a universe of 16.5 million listeners. Radio City followed in the second spot with a 12.5 per cent share, while Radio Mirchi held on to the third position with a 12.3 per cent share. Radio Nasha and AIR FM 2 Gold took the fourth and fifth spot with 12.2 and 10 per cent share respectively. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mid-morning, followed by morning and early morning time band observed the highest listenership.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Bangalore, Radio City retained its No.1 position with a 24.5 per cent share out of a universe of 5.3 million users. This was followed by Big FM in the second spot and Radio Mirchi in third with 17.8 and 17.1 per cent, respectively. Fever and AIRFM 1 Rainbow stood fourth and fifth with 14 and 6.5 per cent share respectively. Evening followed by mid-morning and night time band observed the highest listenership in total radio.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Radio Mirchi dominated in Kolkata with 19 per cent share in a universe of 9 million listeners. Fever FM held the second spot with 18 per cent, while Big FM took 17.7 per cent share at the third spot. Aamar FM and Red FM ranked fourth and fifth with 9.5 and 9.2 per cent share respectively. Afternoon, followed by mid-morning and morning time bands observed the highest listenership on total radio.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/article/article_large_image/1529980662_DH0DI2_radio_final.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/mediaradio/935-red-fm-raises-inr-8551lacs-in-association-with-kailash-satyarthi-childrens-foundation_90800.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>29/06/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>93.5 RED FM raises INR 85.51lacs in association with Kailash Satyarthi Children’s Foundation</news:title>
      <news:description>Superhits 93.5 RED FM&amp;nbsp;under its annual CSR initiative - Bajao for A Cause this year partnered with Kailash Satyarthi Children’s Foundation. Bajao for a Cause is an annual campaign. This year RED FM took up the cause of child protection against child labour, forced prostitution, trafficking, and sexual abuse. Every year RED FM takes up a cause of social significance to raise awareness and funds, and to act as the mouthpiece of those voiceless minor sections of our society who remain unrepresented.&lt;br&gt;The Kailash Satyarthi Children’s Foundation (KSCF) on the other hand envisions a world where all children are free, safe, healthy and have the opportunity to realize her/his potential. Their mission is to end slavery and child labour and ultimately end violence against children. To make this a reality, the foundation is scaling Satyarthi’s almost 4 decades of work at both the grassroots and global policy level. His lessons learned guide the Foundation’s work to engage children and youth as part of the solution, build greater collaboration between governments, business and communities, ensure effective national and international laws, scale know-how and successful practice and create partnerships with key stakeholders.  &lt;br&gt;The campaign kick-started on the 12&amp;nbsp;June, 2018 on World Day Against Child Labour with&amp;nbsp;Kailash Satyarthi visiting the RED FM stations in Mumbai, Kolkata and Delhi NCR. The joint campaign by Kailash Satyarthi Children’s Foundation and RED FM aimed to raise funds for Surakshit Bachpan Fund to provide immediate medical, legal, and psychological assistance to child victims of child labour, sex crimes and abuse.&lt;br&gt;During the campaign the Foundation along with RED FM RJ Raunac had also conducted 5 LIVE raids in Delhi where a total of 63 children were rescued. Through this collaboration with RED FM, The Kailash Satyarthi Foundation aimed to escalate their mission amongst the masses through the power of radio.&lt;br&gt;Summing up the initiative Nisha Narayanan, COO RED FM, said, “‘Bajao for a Cause’ is deeply imbibed in RED FM’s DNA and we conduct CSR campaigns every year in all the major markets. Our aim is to take up a cause that is affecting the nation widely and using radio as a medium to appeal to our listeners to raise funds to combat the situation. We believe our collaboration with Mr. Satyarthi’s ‘Surakshit Bachpan’ initiative, will bring a positive change in the lives of young souls. The reach of radio is far and wide and will help percolate the message to stop child labour and child exploitation by educating and mobilizing the masses. We have received an overwhelming response from our listeners and encourage them to keep supporting us in our endeavour to making this country a better place.”&lt;br&gt;Kailash Satyarthi said, “Radio was a tool for my activism when I started my fight against child labour.  Radio as a broadcast medium has a far-reaching impact and the ability to reach out to the most remote areas. I am happy that the message of Safe Childhood could reach the masses. I thank RED FM and all their listeners for supporting the cause.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The collaboration between RED FM and Kailash Satyarthi Children’s Foundation was a success through multiple interactions with the media and On-Air discussions with the Nobel Prize For Peace Winner. RED FM called upon their listeners to donate a minimum amount of INR 1,000/- towards the cause which will be exempted from income tax under section 80G. Through this campaign&amp;nbsp;an amount of INR 85, 51,428 was raised.&lt;br&gt;Process of rehabilitation: For all child victims of trafficking, the CWC will issue rehabilitation card to monitor the progress made on their individual care plan. The rehabilitation card should be updated by the PO/CWO of the concerned CCI or the authority providing rehabilitation at the district. CWC to make an individual care plan (with information on health and nutrition needs, special needs, educational, training, emotional, psychological, restoration, follow up, social mainstreaming, life skills, protection from all kinds of exploitation and abuse). This has to be reviewed after three months and modified as per progress. For children whose home verification reports are not approved they may be placed in a, (i) Children’s home (ii) Fit facility (iii) Fit person (iv) Foster Care till they are 18 years old, with periodic monitoring of the CWC through the individual care plan. Subject to conditions under section 45 of the JJ Act such child maybe provided sponsorship. After the child attains 18 years under section 46 of the JJ Act she or he may be provided with further financial support. In case a woman victim who cannot be repatriated, she may be given shelter under the Ujjwala scheme shelter and enrolled in a skill training program by the Government till such time that she finds a suitable job opportunity and can be reintegrated into society.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/article/article_large_image/1530255203_tszYMv_nishafunds.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/mediaradio/suhaana-safar-with-annu-kapoor-turns-5-on-big-fm_90785.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>28/06/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Suhaana Safar with Annu Kapoor turns 5 on BIG FM</news:title>
      <news:description>BIG FM's&amp;nbsp;longest running show, Suhaana Safar with Annu Kapoor has&amp;nbsp;completed 5 years on June 24. Annu Kapoor's&amp;nbsp;personality has gained immense credibility for the show which airs on all weekdays entertaining millions across the country.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Celebrating the occasion, the radio network hosted an FB live with the icon,&amp;nbsp;who addressed his fans while reminiscing his remarkable journey so far.  Interestingly, the live session garnered a massive reach in a short span of time. A special show was also conducted where Annu Kapoor was seen interacting with young budding singers sharing meaningful insights on the art of music. Adding to the engagement, BIG FM, throughout the week will also be conducting contests.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaking on the occasion, a BIG FM spokesperson said, “Suhaana Safar With Annu Kapoor has received a wide acceptance since its inception, and is rated as the No. 1 radio show. Annu Kapoor’s profound knowledge and penchant towards Hindi cinema has led to its success and earned credibility amongst listeners. The show not only appeals to the mature generation, but is a huge attraction with youngsters as well. It is a moment of pride to witness Suhaana Safar With Annu Kapoor complete five great years, scale to such great heights and it is an honour to have a personality as incredible as Annu Kapoor to be a part of the BIG family.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commenting on the successful completion of 5 years, Annu Kapoor said, “I fall short of words to express how gratifying it is to see this show run so successfully and reach where it has reached today. It gives me great pleasure in bringing listeners closer to the world of cinema by narrating unheard anecdotes. It has been an exciting 5 years with BIG FM and our association has only strengthened over the years given that we share the same ideology to deliver excellent content to our music loving audience. My dedicated team of writers and researches have been instrumental in contributing to the show’s success. I hope to continue the legacy of the show and also engross the millennial generation in these enthralling tales.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The show has also received various accolades -&amp;nbsp;Best Radio programme under Hindi category and RJ of the year at IRF and Golden Mikes, respectively to name a few.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/article/article_large_image/1499231011_iY2Mi5_69529.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/mediaradio/radio-city-joins-fight-to-ban-plastic-with-sonu-nigam_90782.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>28/06/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Radio City joins fight to ban plastic with Sonu Nigam </news:title>
      <news:description>Radio City 91.1FM&amp;nbsp;has&amp;nbsp;launched the Kar Mumbaikar initiative in Mumbai to give back to the society by pledging for plastic ban. Radio City kick started this initiative by creating awareness on the plastic ban which was recently implemented by the Maharashtra government. In an evening full of entertainment, Radio City invites Mumbaikars to come together to pledge against the use of plastic along with Sonu Nigam and popular duo of RJ Salil &amp;amp; Archana. Radio City has organized a music concert with Bollywood’s singer Sonu Nigam who has joined the rally and is gearing up to perform live for the cause.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As part of the Kar Mumbaikar campaign, Radio City commenced a week long activity across Mumbai to spread awareness about Plastic Ban. To aid in the transition of using environmental friendly materials, Radio City is distributing cloth bags to shopkeepers, fruit, vegetable and&amp;nbsp;flower vendors and fellow Mumbaikars. This campaign was initiated at&amp;nbsp;Dadar Phool Market in the presence of Radio City’s popular RJ Salil &amp;amp; Archana, social activist Afroz Shah, Consul General of Norway in Mumbai Ann Ollestad, BMC Deputy commissioner Nidhi Choudhari and will continue for a week at various touch points across Mumbai.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Urging Mumbaikars to Rally for the Cause, Playback Singer Sonu Nigam said, “Plastic causes widespread destruction to our environment and its ban in Maharashtra couldn’t have come sooner. Kudos to Radio City for launching the Kar Mumbaikar campaign and taking up this cause in such a compelling manner. I urge Mumbaikars to root for this by completely eliminating its usage in their day to day lives. I hope all my fans will rally for this cause by joining me on Friday, in a musical evening dedicated towards bringing a positive change.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details of Kar Mumbaikar concert:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·         Venue - Phoenix Market City, Dublin Square&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·         Date and Time – Friday,&amp;nbsp;June 29,&amp;nbsp;2018, 7pm onwards&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;·         Tickets on Bookmyshow</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/article/article_large_image/1506067809_Mfym5g_70635.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/mediaradio/ram-ratings-week-23-fever-fm-retains-lead-position-in-mumbai-and-delhi_90712.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>26/06/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>RAM Ratings Week 23: Fever FM retains lead position in Mumbai and Delhi </news:title>
      <news:description>Week 23 of the RAM ratings saw Fever FM continue in the leading position in Mumbai and Delhi, while Radio City and Radio Mirchi continued to lead in Bangalore and Kolkata, respectively. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Mumbai, in a universe of 12.2 million listeners, Fever FM held the top position with a share of 15.6 per cent, followed by Radio Mirchi in the second spot with 13.6 per cent and Radio City in the third with 13 per cent share. &lt;br&gt;Early Morning, followed by mid-morning and morning time band observed the highest listenership in total radio.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fever FM also held the top position in Delhi, with 18.6 per cent share in a universe of 16.5 million listeners. Radio City followed in the second spot with a 13.9 per cent share, while Radio Mirchi held on to the third position with a 12.2 per cent share.&lt;br&gt;Mid-morning, followed by night and afternoon time band observed the highest listenership.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Bangalore, Radio City retained its No.1 position with 25.6 per cent share out of a universe of 5.3 million users. This was followed by Big FM in the second spot and Radio Mirchi in third with 17.8 and 17.6 per cent, respectively.&lt;br&gt;Evening followed by mid-morning and afternoon time band observed the highest listenership in total radio.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Radio Mirchi dominated in Kolkata with 19.4 per cent share in a universe of 9 million listeners. Fever FM held the second spot with 18.3 per cent, while Big FM took 17.9 per cent share at the third spot.&lt;br&gt;Afternoon, followed by mid-morning and morning time bands observed the highest listenership on total radio.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/article/article_large_image/1529980662_DH0DI2_radio_final.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/mediaradio/red-fm-launches-new-radio-station-in-srinagar-on-eid-al-fitr_90542.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>15/06/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>RED FM launches new radio station in Srinagar on Eid al-Fitr&#13;
</news:title>
      <news:description>India’s private radio network 93.5 RED FM celebrates Eid al-Fitr with the launch of its new radio station in Srinagar. The network continues to strengthen its presence in the North market. As a part of their phase III expansion RED FM launched its station today, aligned to the brand philosophy and attitude that is ‘Bajaate Raho!’. The station will have CHR (Contemporary Hit Radio) format for the city, playing Hindi superhit music. The radio network won the Best&amp;nbsp;FM Network&amp;nbsp;2018 at the India Radio Forum.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaking about the station expansion, Nisha Narayanan, COO, RED FM said, “RED FM’s constant effort has been to create meaningful and innovative content formats for everyone. We have been waiting to enter Srinagar for a long time now and we intend to bring our entertaining intellectual properties to this market. The team has invested a lot of time to create the content for this market, keeping in mind the sentiments of the listeners. Having said that, the entry into such sensitive markets is a major step for the growth of FM in India.” &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new radio station promises to be more than just music and aims to create a strong emotional touchpoint for the citizens of Srinagar.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/article/article_large_image/1529047925_NJldSS_RED-FM-launch-in-Srinagar.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/mediaradio/big-fm-appoints-tarun-katyal-as-business-head-metros_90541.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>15/06/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>BIG FM appoints Tarun Katyal as Business Head, Metros </news:title>
      <news:description>Indian radio network, BIG FM, in its process of increasing volume in building strategic partnerships has appointed Tarun Katyal as Business Head – Metros. After his successful stint of two years at the organization, Katyal rejoins the BIG network to lead business associations for key markets and scale up the inventory. He will report to Asheesh Chatterjee, Chief Financial Officer, Reliance Broadcast Network Limited.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Katyal said, “BIG FM’s working culture has always been a positive ground to explore and cultivate one’s strengths to the maximum. I feel great to be a part of the network again. I look forward to working towards developing and strengthening productive business partnerships across regions along with the team.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaking about the appointment, Chatterjee said, “We are positive that Tarun will steer the vertical to build lucrative business partnerships in key regions and add to the network’s ‘Shared Purpose’ strategy.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Katyal has over 17 years of experience in developing sales strategies across industry sectors. He has been functional in amplifying the business and growth strategy of various organizations. He has rich exposure in project management, sales and delivery of large scale solutions at Pan India level including ad sales for radio and television.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/article/article_large_image/1529045728_sR3zW4_Tarun-Katyal_Big-FM.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/mediaradio/ht-media-board-approves-rs-400-crore-investment-in-its-radio-business_90444.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>12/06/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>HT Media Board approves Rs 400 crore investment in its Radio business&#13;
</news:title>
      <news:description>The Board of Directors of HT Media Limited has approved the proposal to invest Rs 400 crore to fund expansion and growth&amp;nbsp;opportunities in its FM Radio business vertical.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It should be noted that the FM radio business of the media giant is held under its&amp;nbsp;wholly-owned subsidiary company, HT Media and Entertainment Company Limited.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“This is to inform you that the Board of Directors of the Company at its meeting held on June 6, 2018 (commenced at 11. 00 A.M and concluded at 12 Noon) has approved the proposal to invest an amount up to Rs. 400 Crore in one or more tranches, in its wholly-owned subsidiary company namely, HT Music and Entertainment Company Limited to fund expansion/growth opportunities in its FM Radio business vertical,” HT Media informed the&amp;nbsp;BSE.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fever 104 FM is the company’s premium radio station currently operational in Delhi, Mumbai, Bangalore and Kolkata and the other radio station it operates is Radio Nasha 91.9 FM that&amp;nbsp;is operational in Mumbai and Delhi.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/article/article_large_image/1519907595_x0OWxw_ht_media.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/mediaradio/ram-ratings-week-21-fever-fm-continues-to-dominate-in-mumbai-and-delhi_90465.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>12/06/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>RAM Ratings Week 21: Fever FM continues to dominate in Mumbai and Delhi</news:title>
      <news:description>Week 21 of the RAM ratings saw Fever FM continue in the leading position in Mumbai and Delhi, while Radio City and Radio Mirchi continued to lead in Bangalore and Kolkata, respectively. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Mumbai, in&amp;nbsp;a universe of 12.2 million listeners, Fever FM held the top position with a share of 17 per cent, followed by Radio Mirchi in the second spot with 14 per cent and Radio City in the&amp;nbsp;third with 13 per cent share. &lt;br&gt;Early Morning, followed by Morning and Mid-Morning time band observed the highest listenership in total radio. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fever FM also held the top position in Delhi, with 18.6 per cent share out of a universe of 16.5 million listeners. Radio City followed in the second spot with a 13 per cent share, while Radio Mirchi held on to the third position with a 12 per cent share.&lt;br&gt;Night, followed by Mid-Morning and Afternoon time band observed the highest listenership.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Bangalore, Radio City retained&amp;nbsp;its No.1 position with 26 per cent share out of a universe of 5.3 million users, this was followed by Big FM in the second spot and Radio Mirchi in third with 18 and 17 per cent, respectively.&lt;br&gt;Evening followed by Afternoon and Mid-Morning time band observed the highest listenership in total radio.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Radio Mirchi dominated in Kolkata with 19.3 per cent share in a universe of 9 million listeners. Fever FM held the second spot with 18 per&amp;nbsp;cent, while Big FM took an 18 percent share at the third spot.&lt;br&gt;Morning, followed by Mid-Morning and Afternoon time bands observed the highest listenership on total radio.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/article/article_large_image/1515551597_Mcyl7K_big_(1).jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/mediaradio/ram-ratings-week-20-fever-fm-leads-in-mumbai-and-delhi_90399.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>07/06/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>RAM Ratings Week 20: Fever FM leads in Mumbai and Delhi</news:title>
      <news:description>In Week 20 of the RAM ratings, Fever FM continued to dominate Mumbai and Delhi, while Radio City and Radio Mirchi maintained the top positions in Bangalore and Kolkata respectively.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Mumbai,&amp;nbsp;out of&amp;nbsp;a universe of 12.2 million listeners, Fever FM held the first position with a 17 per cent share, followed by Radio Mirchi with 13 percent in the second spot and Radio City in the third with 13 per cent. Early Morning, followed by Morning and Mid-Morning time observes the highest listenership.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Dehli, in a universe 16.5 million listeners, Fever FM also held the top spot with a 18.1 percent share, followed by Radio City in the second spot with 13 per cent share and Radio Mirchi in the third with 13 per cent. In Delhi, Mid Morning, followed by Afternoon and Night time observed the highest listenership.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Radio City dominated in Bangalore in a universe of 5.3 million listeners with a 25 per cent share. Big FM held a 18 percent share in the second position, while Radio Mirchi followed in the third position with a 17 per cent share. Evening time band, followed by Afternoon and Mid-Morning observed the highest listenership overall.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Kolkata, Radio Mirchi led with a 18.8 percent share of a total universe of 9 million listeners, followed by Fever FM and Big FM in the second and third spots respectively with an 18 per cent share. Morning, followed by Mid Morning and Evening time observed the highest listenership.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/article/article_large_image/1514341617_vAmrcF_big_(41).jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/mediaradio/radio-city-collaborates-with-united-nations-environment-programme-to-beat-plastic-pollution-in-india_90252.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>30/05/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Radio City collaborates with United Nations Environment Programme to ‘Beat Plastic Pollution’ in India</news:title>
      <news:description>Radio City, India’s leading radio network announced its association with the United Nations Environment Programme (UNEP) as the radio partner for the World Environment Day initiative to be held in India to control plastic pollution. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;UNEP is an agency of United Nations to coordinate environmental activities, assisting developing countries in implementing environmentally sound policies and practices. Every year, United Nations chooses one country to be a global host to spread environmental awareness, and this year it’s India. Radio City’s consistent effort towards addressing societal issues by leveraging the reach and power of the medium has made it an unrivaled partner for UNEP to amplify this noble cause. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Versova beach in Mumbai has been selected to drive the campaign ‘Beat Plastic Pollution’, by the United Nations and Indian Government to kick start the cleanup drive. Radio City initiated proceedings on 27th May with a beach cleanup drive in Versova, as a build up to the World Environment Day to be held on 5th June. The launch event hosted by popular Radio City RJ Archana, witnessed participation from high profile dignitaries including the UN environment Chief Erik Solhiem, Aditya Thackrey, actresses Diya Mirza and Pooja Bhatt. An awareness generating video featuring RJ Archana was also unveiled at the event to create awareness on various measures to be taken to beat plastic pollution.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commenting on the association with UNEP for World Environment Day,Mr. Abraham Thomas, CEO, Radio City said,“Radio has the power to influence mindsets and bring about a positive change in the society. We are proud to partner with UNEP to work towards this greater cause. At Radio City, we strongly believe in maintaining a right balance in the environment where we all co-exist. The Versova beach cleanup is one of the many activities that we intend to drive this year with the objective of highlighting the importance of protecting our environment for the future generations.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/1527685843_f2S0Dc_1_%283%29.jpg" style="width:443px;height:332px;vertical-align:middle"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It's fantastic to get the support of partners like Radio City to get the World Environment Day message out across India," said UN Environment Chief Erik Solheim. “During my visit to Mumbai, I witnessed first-hand, the damage marine plastic pollution is causing. It will require a step forward from each one of us to do what we can to reduce our own plastic footprint, and of course we must. I am delighted that a booming economy like India is the global host of World Environment Day 2018 and will be leading the push to save the oceans and the planet. Every single environmental challenge we face can be solved by innovation. It's simply a case of getting the message out and inspiring as many people as possible to join forces and take a stand for the planet and look forward to Radio City's help to amplifying the same."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Radio City’s RJ Archana, expressing her thoughts on the cleanup drive said, “Mumbai is known for its beaches and it is extremely sad to see the condition of the beaches with plastic getting deep rooted. I have always been taken aback by the amount of plastic waste that is dumped on the streets and the beaches of Mumbai. Being a Mumbaikar, I feel a sense of responsibility to make this city pollution free and a better place to live in. I urge all Radio City listeners and all Mumbaikars to contribute towards conserving our environment and keeping it pollution free.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a part of the campaign Radio City along with Afroz Shah, the UN environment ambassador takes the drive on air and on ground by creating awareness amongst Mumbaikars of how they could replace, reuse plastic thereby avoiding plastic pollution. Radio City will go on ground to various locations in Mumbai where plastic pollution is high and continue to drive the awareness of beating plastic pollution with volunteers from schools, colleges and fellow Mumbaikars.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/article/article_large_image/1506067809_Mfym5g_70635.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
</urlset>
