<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9" xmlns:image="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-image/1.1" xmlns:news="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-news/0.9">
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/media-tv-news/thanthi-tv-editor-in-chief-rangraj-pandey-steps-down-93410.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>12/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Thanthi TV Editor-in-Chief Rangaraj Pandey steps down</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Rangaraj Pandey, who was the Editor-in-Chief of Thanthi TV, has quit from his post, with effect from Monday. Pandey announced his decision to step down in an emotional video, where he thanked the viewers and said that he wanted a break from his daily routine. He added that he also wanted to give space and opportunity to the next generation of journalists. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/c0KWyKkSznY" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;Pandey, who has 22 years of experience in journalism, began his career with Tamil newspaper Dinamalar. &lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;He started the well-known satire column &amp;ldquo;Doubtu Dhanabalu&amp;rdquo;, a fictional character who mocks the day-to-day political discourse in Tamil Nadu and pan-India.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:6.0pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:6.0pt; margin-left:0cm; text-align:start; -webkit-text-stroke-width:0px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:inherit"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-ligatures:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-caps:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="orphans:2"&gt;&lt;span style="widows:2"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-style:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-color:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="word-spacing:0px"&gt;His interviews with famous personalities made him a popular television face. He hosts talk show &amp;ldquo;Kelvikku Enna Badhil&amp;rdquo; (What is the answer to the question?). Pandey also hosted a prime-time news debate programme &amp;lsquo;Ayutha Ezhuthu&amp;lsquo;. He is renowned for his simple and spontaneous questioning style. Pandey, who hails from North India, is a post graduate in Tamil from Madurai Kamaraj University. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93410-Pandey.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/media-tv-news/mib-calls-for-meet-to-discuss-broadband-services-through-cable-tv-networks-93400.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>11/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>MIB calls for meet to discuss broadband services through cable TV networks</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;The Ministry of Information and Broadcasting (MIB) is organising a conference of cable TV industry representatives (MSOs) on December 18 to discuss providing broadband services through cable TV networks.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;The meet will discuss various issues, including feasibility, affordability, ubiquity, infrastructure, modalities of payment and segregation of revenue earned from broadband activities. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;According to a ministry notice, detailed deliberation will be held on: (i) willingness of the operators to invest in the infrastructure required. ii) The payment of 8 per cent Adjusted Gross Revenue (AGR) as the fee to DoT, whether to be paid only on the broadband services or on overall revenue earned in respect of both the businesses. iii) Whether separate entity needs to be created for the broadband activities for segregation of the revenue earned on it. iv)All other issues related to the delivery of broadband services through cable TV network.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;The notice mentions that the conference will be held at Gulmohar Hall, Habitat Centre, Lodhi Road, New Delhi, and will see participation from major MSOs, officials from MIB, DoT, TRAI and Broadcast Engineering Consultants India Limited (BECIL).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/92873-MIBLogo.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/media-tv-news/discussion-on-barc-india-suspending-ratings-for-2-months-is-premature-industry-experts-93391.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>11/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Discussion on BARC India suspending ratings for 2 months is ‘premature’: Industry experts</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Amidst speculations of BARC (Broadcast Audience Research Council) not releasing ratings for two months in the backdrop of TRAI rating order, industry sources told exchange4media a concrete decision on this is expected in a meeting of stakeholders later this month.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Senior industry sources also confirmed that there were &amp;quot;premature&amp;quot; discussions around it during meetings held few weeks ago. However, nothing concrete has been decided as of now. &amp;quot;It was discussed as one of the possible options to deal with the scenario as most of us are trying to find ways to tackle the issue,&amp;quot; said a senior industry source.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Industry veterans however emphasized on the need for creating public awareness on the TRAI order for its better implication.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;A senior executive said, &amp;ldquo;The meeting was scheduled to take place tomorrow. However the meeting has been rescheduled because many board members were not available. Only in that meeting we will come to know whether it&amp;#39;s going to happen or not. Also there is no mention of this in any agenda. As of now this is only word of mouth.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Another senior industry expert said, &amp;ldquo;The suggestion has some logic because when there will be disruption of this magnitude nobody should be in a position to take advantage showing ratings in this phase.&amp;rdquo; Going by the information the meeting will happen in next 15 days.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;This kind of a blackout has happened twice - in 2012 when the government had asked for the mandatory switch from analogue to digital cable and second time in 2015 when the industry moved from TAM to BARC.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;As per our sources, there is a lot of uncertainty on the implementation of the Tariff order post January 1, 2018, due to the pending petitions in court and DTH/cable operators expecting to get a stay order; there is a higher probability that the implantation date of this order will be pushed ahead further.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The order&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Early this year, Star had approached the Apex court questioning TRAI&amp;rsquo;s jurisdiction to frame tariff order on the grounds that the authority has no jurisdiction on content as that actually comes under Copyright Act and not TRAI Act.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The appeal was filed against the fractured judgement passed by a two-judge Bench of Madras High Court comprising Chief Justice Indira Banerjee and Justice M Sundar. The bench had given a split verdict. Justice M Sundar had ruled in favour of Star. Commenting on the judgement delivered by Justice M Sundar, the Supreme Court order stated, &amp;ldquo;I am unable to agree with the conclusion of M. Sundar, J. that the provisions of the impugned Regulation and the impugned Tariff Order are not in conformity with the TRAI Act. In my view the impugned provisions neither touch upon the content of programmes of broadcasters, nor liable to be struck down.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;However, the clause putting cap of 15% to the discount on the MRP of a bouquet is arbitrary. The said provision is, in my view, not enforceable. In my considered view, the challenge to the impugned Regulation and the impugned Tariff Order fail,&amp;rdquo; the order read further.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The 2017 Regulations prevented the mixing of pay channels and free to air channels in a single bouquet. &amp;nbsp;The Regulations restricted placing high definition format and ordinary format of the same channel in the same bouquet. &amp;nbsp;Another restriction was that a bouquet of pay channels should not contain any pay channel where the Maximum Retail Price is more than Rs 19.&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93324-BARClogo.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/media-tv-news/telangana-news-broadcasters-spike-rates-by-25-80-ahead-of-assembly-elections-93392.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>11/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Telangana News broadcasters spike ad rates by 25-80% ahead of election results</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;The results of assembly election in Telangana along with four other states, Madhya Pradesh, Rajasthan, Mizoram, Chhattisgarh will be announced today. The election results are considered to be the semi-finals to the 2019 Lok Sabha elections.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;A grand alliance of Congress, Telugu Desham Party (TDS), Communist Party of India (CPI), Telangana Jana Samithi (TJS) named Prajakootami &amp;nbsp;(People&amp;rsquo;s front) was formed with an objective of defeating the ruling TRS in the elections. Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP), All India Majlis-e-Ittehadul Muslimeen (AIMIM) are the two other parties on the battlefield. Sixty is the magic number required to form the government in the 119 member Telangana assembly.&amp;nbsp;The state recorded a turn out of 73.2 per cent of voters and if the numbers are in favour of TRS, then K Chandrashekar Rao will return to power and form the government.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The various news organisations have released exit poll survey results prior to the counting day.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;CNX - Times Now, India TV, Axis My India - India Today and Aaj Tak, Republic Jan Ki Baat, CVoter - Republic TV are few of the exit poll surveys and these surveys have revealed mixed results for Congress and BJP.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The channels across the country have lined up extensive programs for the counting day with live updates and in-depth analyses of the election results.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;CNN-News18 launched numerous shows to bring latest developments throughout the elections &amp;ndash; the campaigning phase and the polling day.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Under the channel&amp;rsquo;s programming&amp;nbsp;&amp;lsquo;Reporters Project&amp;rsquo;, their&amp;nbsp;reporters travelled across Telangana to capture the ground realities, assess issues and record the sentiments of the people at the center of the story.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;With comprehensive reportage to bring the fastest and most accurate results, first reactions and a 360-degree view of the final picture, the programming will commence at 6 AM on CNN-News18. Offering a combination of live coverage, real-time updates on seat tally, the programming on the channel will not only keep a close track of the trends but also provide in-depth analyses and implications of the results. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;With the entire News18 Network&amp;rsquo;s team of journalists across the states bringing in up-to-the-minute updates on the results, the channel will bring to the viewers unparalleled access to the latest happenings.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;On CNN-News18,&amp;nbsp;Executive Editor Bhupendra Chaubey along with Deputy Executive Editor Zakka Jacob&amp;nbsp;and Deputy Executive Editor Anand Narasimhan&amp;nbsp;will also be joined by a panel of the prominent journalists and the finest political analysts like&amp;nbsp;Swapan Dasgupta, Sanjaya Baru, Vir Sanghvi, Surjit Bhalla, Ajoy Bose, Rasheed Kidwai and Advaita Kala&amp;nbsp;to bring a comprehensive analysis of the results of the assembly elections.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The regional players in Telangana have also lined up programs for the state&amp;rsquo;s D-Day. The channels also have hiked their advertisement rates for the day. On the other hand, a few channels are planning to go for limited advertisement space telecast.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;According to industry experts based in Hyderabad, the channels have raised their advertisement rates by 20-80%. &amp;ldquo;The channels have come up with premium package for the advertisers on the counting day. There will be a huge rise in the advertisement rates and there will a high demand for advertisement space in the morning slots. There will be a spike of more than 20-60 % from the actual advertisement rate,&amp;rdquo; said a senior media planner based in Hyderabad.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Talking to exchange4media, Srinivas Murthy, VP, Marketing TV5 News Network said, &amp;ldquo;TV5 will be starting live telecast from 6 am. We have deployed 50 OB vans and reporters covering all the counting centres. There will be a change in screen layout for tomorrow and we are doing a 360-degree coverage of the counting day.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;There will be a huge rise in the TV viewership today. The viewership on the counting day will double than compared to the normal days,&amp;rdquo; added Murthy.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The channel will be conducting an in-depth analysis of the election results.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;We have a premium package for advertisers for the day and have hiked the advertisement rates by 25%,&amp;rdquo; said Murthy.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Another major player in South India TV9 is providing&amp;nbsp;non-stop coverage of the counting day with special bulletins and live telecasts. The channel started their live telecast at 6 am.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Today we will be allotting very limited advertisement space and there are premium advertisement packages for today,&amp;rdquo; said Clifford Pereira, Director, TV9. &amp;ldquo;The TV viewership will be phenomenal and a rise of 100% in terms of viewership will be achieved easily today,&amp;rdquo; added Pereira.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The Telugu News channel NTV is also doing an extensive coverage of the counting day. &amp;ldquo;We are doing a marathon live on this D-Day. We have deployed reporters and contributors across the counting centres. The advertisement space will be limited for today at the same time we expect a rise of 80-90% increase in terms of viewership,&amp;rdquo; said Hari Krishnan, Chief Copy Editor, NTV News.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;The Telangana elections are very crucial for the political parties and the channels also reap benefits during the election period in terms of revenue and viewership. The high amount of competition in the TV space will force the players to provide unbiased reportage of the events. In terms of advertisement rates, there will be a spike of almost 80%. In terms of viewership, the local channels will have a massive rise,&amp;rdquo; concluded, a senior media planner.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93392-TelanganaMap.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/media-tv-news/barc-india-bags-most-innovative-company-award-93374.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>10/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>BARC India bags ‘Most Innovative Company’ award</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;BARC India was adjudged the &amp;lsquo;Most Innovative Company in Service &amp;ndash; Medium Enterprise Category&amp;rsquo; at the CII Industrial Innovations 2018 Awards. The company has also been recognised as one of the &amp;lsquo;Top 25 Most Innovative Companies in India&amp;rsquo;. The announcement was made in a ceremony of the 5th&amp;nbsp;CII Industrial Innovation Awards 2018 held in New Delhi on December 3, 2018.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The Industrial Innovation Awards identify and celebrate innovative Indian enterprises across various sectors. The award has been instituted by the Confederation of Indian Industry (CII), and is one of the most coveted innovation awards in India, BARC said in a statement on Monday.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The winners have been decided after a four-stage process, spanning across eight months. This also included an assessor visit to understand BARC India&amp;rsquo;s robust technology set up on the back of some path-breaking innovations and a presentation in front of an eminent jury.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The company said that the award is a validation of the rigorous and credible measurement system that BARC India has established&amp;nbsp;in a short span of three years. With its robust methodology and constant tech innovations, BARC India has developed a world class system for the TV industry. It can also be recalled that BARC India&amp;rsquo;s BAR-O-Meters were developed indigenously at 1/6th&amp;nbsp;the cost of globally available meters. This ensured scalability as well as ensured that the meters could handle the weather/power/telecom fluctuations which is unique to the Indian market, the statement mentioned.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The other innovation which has helped BARC India achieve the status of Most Innovative Companies is the Panel Management System (PMS). This indigenously developed system has helped in bringing efficiency in the field force that installs, manages and trains the panel homes. This has played an important role in ensuring reporting from the panel homes at par with global standards.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The third innovation is the BIO suite of products which is a visualization tool that provides interactive UI, 90 per cent reduction in output time and helps in faster and better decision making.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Shashi Sinha, BARC India Technical Committee Chairman and CEO, IPG Mediabrands, said, &amp;ldquo;BARC India was set up with the aim to give the industry a measurement system that it deserved, and this could not have happened without having a strong technology backbone. The team at BARC India has been able to give the industry a technology marvel which is capable of providing the industry a representative data that helps them take better business decisions. The CII Industrial Innovation Award is proof of the great work done by the team.&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;BARC India Chairman Nakul Chopra added, &amp;ldquo;BARC India has been a key-change agent in the viewership measurement space, and its initiatives have already started to redefine the industry. Since its inception, BARC India has tackled several challenges. But, considering we work in a dynamic industry, these challenges are never-ending. The key to success is to constantly keep innovating and be the change-maker. BARC India has been successful in doing so. We are now looking at implementing some key future projects such as Unified Video Measurement and Return Path Data, which will bring another paradigm shift in the industry.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;BARC India CEO Partho Dasgupta said, &amp;ldquo;In future, technology will disrupt every single business, be it cement, retail, telecomm, e-comm or media. It is therefore important to keep pace with the changing technology. As is said, in tomorrow&amp;rsquo;s world, the big fish will not eat the small fish, but a fast fish will eat the slow one. We at BARC India firmly believe that innovation is imperative and not a choice. We also believe that it is important to be the fearless first to inspire change and not be a mere follower. I am delighted to see that our efforts have been recognised by CII. We shall continue to empower the industry with our robust measurement.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93324-BARClogo.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/media-tv-news/radaan-media-works-offloads-24-stake-to-jbcg-advisory-to-raise-rs-35-cr-93369.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>10/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Radaan Media Works offloads 24% stake to JBCG Advisory to raise Rs 3.5 Cr</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Radaan Mediaworks,&amp;nbsp;promoted by actress Raadhika Sarathkumar, has decided to offload nearly 25% stake to former Stanchart head honcho, Jaspal Singh Bindra&amp;rsquo;s M/s. JBCG Advisory Services Private Limited, say reports.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;As per the deal, Radaan will issue 17.5 million equity shares of Rs.2/- face value on preferential basis to at a price of Rs.2/- per share to JBCG Advisory that is aggregating to Rs.3.5 Crore.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Radaan Mediaworks was founded as a proprietary concern in the early 90s and converted into a listed entity in 1999.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The Company is&amp;nbsp;launching television soap, &amp;lsquo;Chandrakumari&amp;rsquo;, being aired in all four South Indian languages starting with Tamil version on Sun TV from&amp;nbsp;December 10, 2018.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93369-raadan.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/media-tv-news/our-focus-areas-for-2019-are-south-rural-cinema-ashish-sehgal-zeel-93364.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>10/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Our focus areas for 2019 are south, rural &amp; cinema: Ashish Sehgal, ZEEL</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Last month, Zee Entertainment Enterprises Ltd (ZEEL) promoted Ashish Sehgal (former Chief Operating Officer of ZEE Unimedia) to the position of Chief Growth Officer, ZEEL. The change of designation came following the dissolution of Zee Unimedia, a vertical that was set up by the broadcast network in 2016 to boost ad sales monetisation.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Before being shifted to Zee Unimedia, Sehgal, who has been associated with the network for over a decade, handled sales at ZEEL as the Chief Sales Officer .&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;exchange4media caught up with him to talk about the dissolution of Zee Unimedia, Trai tariff order, key focus areas for 2019 and more. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Excerpts:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Why exactly was Zee Unimedia dissolved within two years of its creation?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Zee as an organisation is gearing up to the take the next leap in the media &amp;amp; entertainment space as a &amp;lsquo;global media-tech player&amp;rsquo;.&amp;nbsp; Hence, we are consolidating all our units.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;From a business point of view, the objective of Zee Unimedia was to offer a synergistic solution across ZEEL, ZMCL &amp;amp; the digital business. And this continues in the new scenario. Hence, effectively, there is no change in the functioning of the team.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;What are the key challenges before you in the new role as Chief Growth Officer?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;As market leaders, the key challenge is to not only grow the market but also garner higher shares in this highly fragmented &amp;amp; cluttered environment. Hence, as the Chief Growth Officer, it is imperative that we evolve newer modes of revenue opportunities that provide effective &amp;amp; efficient solution to the brands as well as help us maintain above-the-market advertising revenue growth rates for ZEEL &amp;amp; ZMCL, which currently is at 20 per cent &amp;amp; 30 per cent, respectively. In this endeavour, our core focus would be to proliferate newer segments of advertisers across the length &amp;amp; breadth of India.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;How will the new TRAI tariff order impact the industry?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;The demand-supply equation has shifted in the favour of consumer.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Hence, brands that are constantly evolving, connecting &amp;amp; delivering compelling content and satisfying the entertainment needs of the consumer will sustain in the long run. Having said that, it&amp;rsquo;s too early to predict the impact as it&amp;rsquo;s a challenge for broadcasters, LCOs, MSOs &amp;amp; DTH players to educate the consumer about this new beneficial structural change. The backend for this change is a huge challenge for all distribution platforms.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;When it comes to business, I don&amp;rsquo;t think it will have an impact in the near term. In the long term, it will only help me grow my advertising revenue. How? While BARC will keep giving its ratings, I, through distribution, can find out which channels are in demand. Also, it will benefit niche channels. My assumption is that this may finally lead the conversation towards CPT. Eventually, then the advertising industry will grow.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;How has 2018 been for the industry?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;The year has been good. The industry has grown in double digits; I think 13-14 per cent. However, my perspective is that the overall industry could have grown better.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;What are your plans for 2019? How does the next year look like for the broadcast industry? Going forward, what will be the key focus areas for you?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;2019 looks like a great year. It will be another year of growth as there are three big properties&amp;mdash;state elections, general elections &amp;amp; cricket world cup. This will attract advertisers and increase the TV advertising pie.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;From our perspective, our key focus areas for 2019 are very clear- south, rural &amp;amp; cinema genre.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;We are seeing a change in market focus from pan-India to region specific. Advertisers are creating customised market-specific communication plans. South as a region has seen high economic growth, fuelling consumption across categories. Television medium is at an advantage with almost 100 per cent penetration. As a dominant player, it will be our endeavour to correct the price point in line with the economic contribution to the national GDP.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Cinema genre continues to be undervalued in comparison to GEC, despite closing the gap in terms of the impressions delivered. We believe, there is ample room for growth.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Thirdly, the rural viewer is under-indexed compared to his urban counterpart in terms of advertising rates. This is despite significant growth in his personal consumption &amp;amp; contribution across categories.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93364-AshishSehgal.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/media-tv-news/always-want-to-be-a-pro-people-channel-power-tv-ceo-93362.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>10/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Always want to be a pro-people channel: Power TV CEO</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 10pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Verdana&amp;quot;,sans-serif"&gt;Powersmart Media Pvt Ltd launched its Kannada News channel, Power TV,&amp;nbsp;in October. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 10pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Verdana&amp;quot;,sans-serif"&gt;&amp;ldquo;We are positioning ourselves as a channel which brings truthful and unbiased news to the people of Karnataka. Delivering&amp;nbsp;accurate, uncompromised news to the audience will be our top priority,&amp;rdquo; said Manjunath TR, CEO, Power TV. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 10pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Verdana&amp;quot;,sans-serif"&gt;&amp;ldquo;We always want to be a pro-people channel, whether it is about&amp;nbsp;bringing&amp;nbsp;social issues to the forefront or&amp;nbsp;taking people&amp;rsquo;s might and plight to the lime light,&amp;rdquo; he added. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 10pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Verdana&amp;quot;,sans-serif"&gt;He said that the channel&amp;rsquo;s programmes&amp;nbsp;are designed with utmost passion to cater to all&amp;nbsp;sections of society. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 10pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Verdana&amp;quot;,sans-serif"&gt;&amp;ldquo;A dedicated young team is well equipped to work industriously to reach out to the people of Karnataka,&amp;rdquo; said the CEO. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 10pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Verdana&amp;quot;,sans-serif"&gt;&amp;quot;Just like the name, Power TV will always thrive hard to empower, protect and educate women, youth and people of all walks of life. &amp;nbsp;After all, credibility and our people matter the most to&amp;nbsp;us.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 10pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Verdana&amp;quot;,sans-serif"&gt;The channel telecasts programmes&amp;nbsp;namely Power Yoga, Power Caf&amp;eacute;, Ladies Power, Filmy Power, Chintus Power, to name a few.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 10pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:10.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Verdana&amp;quot;,sans-serif"&gt;Available on all MSOs (Multiple System Operators),&amp;nbsp;by the end of 2018 it will be available on 3 DTH platforms. Viewers&amp;nbsp;can also watch live updates on &lt;span style="color:#548dd4"&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.powertvnews.in" rel="nofollow" style="color:blue; text-decoration:underline"&gt;www.powertvnews.in&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 10pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 10pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 10pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93362-Power-TV-Logo.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/media-tv-news/sony-pictures-network-indias-channels-back-on-tata-sky-93349.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>07/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Sony Pictures Network India's channels back on Tata Sky</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Early October, Direct to Home (DTH) operator Tata Sky removed SPNI&amp;#39;s 22 channels along with TV Today Network&amp;rsquo;s channels which were officially distributed by SPNI.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;SPNI spokesperson confirmed the news and said, &amp;ldquo;Yes, the Sony Pictures Networks channels are back on Tata SKy&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;The operator had faced a lot of backlash by its subscribers on social media after removing the broadcaster&amp;#39;s channels. Tata Sky requested its subscribers to bear with them and assured that they are committed to working in the interest of its subscribers.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&amp;ldquo;Commercial negotiations with the broadcasters broke down as what they were seeking would have forced us to hike our prices. Hence we have had to drop a few channels while keeping the popular ones on. We request our subscribers to bear with us, as we are doing this in their best interest,&amp;rdquo; said Harit Nagpal, CEO &amp;amp; MD of Tata Sky said in October.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93349-SonyPicturesNetwork.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/media-tv-news/india-aus-series-third-match-gets-highest-viewership-of-181-million-93327.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>07/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>India-Aus series: Third match gets highest viewership of 18.1 million</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;The third match of the ongoing India- Australia cricket series has garnered the highest viewership so far. The November 25 face-off, which was won by India by six wickets, recorded 18.1 million impressions, according to BARC data.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The first and second matches had recorded 14.8 million and 13.3 million impressions, respectively&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The matches&amp;nbsp;are&amp;nbsp;being aired on five channels-- Sony Six HD, Sony Six, Sony Ten 3, Sony Ten 3 HD and DD Sports. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The series, being telecasted with English and Hindi commentaries on Sony Ten 3, started on November 21, 2018 and will go on till January 18, 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;In Week 48 of BARC data, Star Sports First bagged the first slot in the sports genre with 115 million impressions, followed by Sony Ten 3 on the second spot with 110 million impressions and Star Sports 1 Hindi on the third position with 79.0 million impressions. Sony Ten 1 and Sony Six grabbed the fourth and fifth spots with 75.2 and 75.1 million impressions respectively.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93327-match.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/media-tv-news/our-future-course-will-be-determined-more-by-values-than-commerce-sudhanshu-vats-93318.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>06/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Our future course will be determined more by values than commerce: Sudhanshu Vats</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Sudhanshu Vats, Chairman of National Committee on Media &amp;amp; Entertainment and Group CEO &amp;amp; MD, Viacom18, spoke at CII Big Picture Summit 2018 on Thursday. Vats delivered the theme address on &amp;lsquo;Changing M&amp;amp;E landscape - from convergence to transformation&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s his full speech:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Namaskar&amp;nbsp;ladies &amp;amp; gentlemen, many thanks for investing your valuable time with us at the CII Big Picture Summit. It is my privilege to host all of you, over today and tomorrow to discuss, debate and deliberate on the rapidly changing media and entertainment landscape in this country.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The first CII Big Picture event I attended was in&amp;nbsp;2012, I believe it was also the first edition of the event.&amp;nbsp;As a regular&amp;nbsp;learner&amp;nbsp;at these events, I can say with utmost certainty that a lot of the issues we discussed back then &amp;ndash; ambitious revenue targets, radio auctions, TV measurement, digitization and so on &amp;ndash; a large chunk of it &amp;ndash; while still relevant &amp;ndash; are in various stages of development today. And that&amp;rsquo;s only fair &amp;ndash; such is the nature of the beast we ride. Also, this trend of convergence and consolidation &amp;ndash; the 2 &amp;lsquo;Cs&amp;rsquo; &amp;ndash; is a universal one &amp;ndash; taking place all over the world. That brings me to the theme of this edition of Big Picture &amp;ndash; from convergence to transformation.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;This is an interesting thought, convergence is a reality &amp;ndash; one that is here to stay. It&amp;rsquo;s being driven by consumer needs and industry&amp;rsquo;s response to those needs &amp;ndash; meaning that it&amp;rsquo;ll be a long-lasting phenomenon. Transformation is a much bigger &amp;ndash; and more daunting &amp;ndash; phenomenon. That said, what do we mean by &amp;lsquo;transformation&amp;rsquo;? &amp;nbsp;It&amp;rsquo;s a big word. I&amp;rsquo;m going to do what my professor at university used to do when we asked her the meaning of a &amp;lsquo;big word&amp;rsquo; &amp;ndash; throwback two bigger words &amp;ndash; MORAL DILEMMAS.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;On a serious note, I want to take this precious opportunity to share a point of view that may not make headlines like aggressive industry targets do, but is, in my humble opinion, even more important.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;If you step back and introspect about all that is happening with our industry across the world, you will agree that we are battling several changes - and most of them are a result of moral dilemmas and our response to them. If we can tackle these dilemmas successfully (and defining success is the hardest part), we can believe that we have transformed.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, our rich cultural heritage is a treasure trove of insights when it comes to handling moral dilemmas. I recently had a young director from the South approach me with what he called was a &amp;lsquo;modern adaptation of the Mahabharata &amp;ndash; told from the perspective of the Kauravas&amp;rsquo;. It was an interesting thought and we&amp;rsquo;re testing it - but that&amp;rsquo;s beside the point. We all know about Dharamraj Yudhishtira and his half-lie &amp;ndash; when he told Drona&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- on Krishna&amp;rsquo;s counsel - that Ashvathama is dead. Yudhishtira was referring to an elephant who had died in battle &amp;ndash; knowing that Drona would mistake Ashvathama to be his son of the same name. On hearing that &amp;lsquo;Ashvatahama is dead&amp;rsquo;, Drona put down his arms and was killed by Dhrishtadyumna. Was Yudhishitra right in doing what he did? It&amp;rsquo;s a debate that divides many till date.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;I gave this example to showcase the greyness of moral dilemmas. Let&amp;rsquo;s look at our industry and the moral dilemmas we will have to face or are facing &amp;ndash;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;ul&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li&gt;How do we deal with the power we have? What do we do if we find out that our reach and credibility is being used to influence electoral processes across the world?&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
	&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li&gt;How do we ensure fairness in the terms of availability of our content to our consumers and parity across distribution platforms? Especially in a foreseeable future when convergence is going to dial up vertical integration across value chains.&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
	&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li&gt;As consumption moves online, our access to data will increase. In many ways, data will be a competitive advantage and drive advertising revenues and personalized user experiences &amp;ndash; what processes do we put in place to ensure it is not misused &amp;ndash; how and where do we draw the line differentiating personalization versus privacy?&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;ul&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li&gt;Human resources &amp;ndash; our people- are our biggest asset &amp;ndash; on screen and off it &amp;ndash; how do we react when their individual, personal behaviour questions the fabric of the society we want to create? Think of this especially in light of the recent issues around diversity and inclusion that we&amp;rsquo;ve experienced.&amp;nbsp;It&amp;rsquo;s important for everyone, but especially so for our industry.&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The list of moral dilemmas is endless. We need to be cognizant of these dilemmas &amp;ndash; as organizations, industry bodies, policymakers and governments - as we look to scale up our businesses.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve always been an ardent supporter of data and its importance in driving decision making. In this address, I have not used a single data point &amp;ndash; because I believe that the course we take over the next decade will be determined more by these fundamental issues of values and how we tackle moral dilemmas than just commercial considerations. Driving consensus will be difficult yet more important than ever before. This is even more so given that India is today amongst the world&amp;rsquo;s largest &amp;lsquo;open&amp;rsquo; media markets and home to a multitude of players from all over and of all sizes.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Yudhishtira had to spend a day in hell to make up for his half-lie. He was willing to spend a lifetime there to atone for his sins. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure that we are as brave as him. We must tread carefully, follow our dharma in the toughest of times and be patient. Only then will we have truly transformed.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93318-Vats.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/media-tv-news/doordarshan-launches-educational-channel-dd-roshini-93311.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>06/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Doordarshan launches educational channel DD Roshini</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Public broadcaster Doordarshan on Thursday launched an educational channel, DD Roshini, on the DTT platform. The channel was launched by Karnataka Chief Minister H D Kumaraswamy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;DD Roshini debuts as a pilot on Digital Terrestrial Platform of DD in partnership with Microsoft and Bruhat Bengaluru Mahanagar Palike (BBMP).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;The channel will be available on DD FreeDish, Airtel Digital TV, Dish TV, Big TV, Tata Sky, VideoconD2h and Sun Direct.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93311-DD.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/media-tv-news/mtvs-ryan-mendonca-appointed-at-bang-bang-as-director-93314.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>06/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>MTV's Ryan Mendonca appointed at BANG BANG as Director</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 10pt;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12px;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;MTV&amp;rsquo;s Ryan Mendonca signs with BANG BANG as Director. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Armed with over a decade of experience in the world of advertising, Mendonca started his filmmaking career at MTV, where he was National Creative Head until last month, leading the team at MTV and MTV Beats, pushing creative boundaries with branded communications across digital and branded content. Prior to this, he was Group Creative Director at Ogilvy &amp;amp; Mather, where he developed iconic campaigns for Unilever, Cadbury, BCCI and more and rose rapidly to Group Creative Director.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 10pt;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12px;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;His experience has earned him many accolades like Copywriter of the Year and Social Thinker of the Year by &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;The Advertising Club of India. His other laurels include winning at Cannes, The One Show, London International, Spikes Asia, Promax Asia, WARC, Effies (India and Asia), AMEs, Kyoorius, and Young Guns to name a few.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 10pt;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12px;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;Mendonca says,&amp;nbsp;&amp;ldquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Goes without saying I&amp;rsquo;m excited to be partnering Roopak and the team at BANG BANG. The plan is no different from what it&amp;rsquo;s been so far&amp;ndash; to try and tell big stories, beautifully. Except this time around I&amp;rsquo;ll be directing them as well. Can&amp;rsquo;t wait to start.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin: 0cm 0cm 10pt;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12px;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;Roopak Saluja, Founder &amp;amp; Chief Executive Officer &amp;ndash; The 120 Media Collective, comments,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&amp;ldquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:115%"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;Sometimes you just know someone&amp;#39;s going to make a kick*** Director; they tend to exude a special storytelling ability and a keen eye for detail. I&amp;#39;ve known Ryan over the years and have always been a fan of his abilities. He&amp;#39;s definitely that guy. Watch out world, here comes Ryan Mendonca!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93314-Ryan-Mendonca.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/media-tv-news/star-plus-retains-leadership-spot-in-urban-market-barc-week-48-93308.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>06/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Star Plus retains leadership spot in urban market: BARC week 48</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;meta charset="utf-8" /&gt;Zee Anmol continued to lead the overall market with 873 million impressions, followed by Zee TV on the second slot with 761 million impressions and Star Bharat on the third spot with 734 million impressions, according to Broadcast Audience Research Council (BARC) India Week 48 data.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Zee Anmol&amp;rsquo;s Kumkum Bhagya bagged the first slot with 14.8 million impressions followed by Zee TV&amp;rsquo;s Kundali Bhagya and Kumkum Bhagya on second and third spot with 12.6 million impressions and 12.327 million impressions. Colors&amp;rsquo; Naagin-3 slipped to&amp;nbsp;number four from the second slot with 12.325 million impressions. Star Bharat&amp;rsquo;s Radhakrishn stood at number five with 11.2 million impressions.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hindi GEC Urban &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Star Plus retained its leadership position this week with 507 million impressions followed by Zee TV on the second slot with 468 million impressions and Sony Entertainment Television on the third slot with 432 million impressions. Colors and Star Bharat stood at number four and five with 384 million impressions and 366 million impressions respectively.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Colors&amp;rsquo; Naagin 3 continued to dominate the list of top five programmes in the urban market with 8.1 million impressions. Zee TV&amp;rsquo;s Kundali Bhagya bagged the second spot with 8&amp;nbsp;million impressions followed Sony Entertainment Television&amp;rsquo;s Indian Idol on third spot with 7.6 million impressions. Zee TV&amp;rsquo;s Kumkum Bhagya grabbed fourth spot with 7.5 million impressions whereas Star Plus&amp;rsquo; Kulfi Kumar Bajewala stood at number five with 7.2 million impressions&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hindi GEC Rural&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Zee Anmol continued to lead the rural market with 708 million impressions, followed by Sony Pal on the second spot with 450 million impressions and Star Utsav on the third with 423 million impressions. Star Bharat and Dangal TV stood on the fourth and fifth positions with 368 million and 356 million impressions, respectively.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Zee Anmol&amp;rsquo;s Kumkum Bhagya continued to lead the list of top five programmes with 12.4 million impressions followed by Mahek on the same channel with 8.5 million impressions on second slot and Dangal TV&amp;rsquo;s Ramayan &amp;nbsp;stood on three with 7.5 million impressions. Zee Anmol&amp;rsquo;s Ek Main Aur Ek Tu and Sony Pal&amp;rsquo;s Taarak Mehta Ka Ooltah Chashma bagged fourth and fifth spots with 7.15 mn and 7.10 million impressions respectively.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93308-barcbiglogo.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/media-tv-news/kabaddi-comes-home-to-ap-and-telangana-on-star-sports-1-telugu-93310.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>06/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Kabaddi comes home to AP and Telangana on Star Sports 1 Telugu</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p class="Default" style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Star Sports has launched Star Sport 1 Telugu, which will offer multiple sporting events in Telugu, starting with the VIVO Pro Kabaddi League. The channel launch is In-line with Star Sports&amp;rsquo; commitment to foster a multi-sports culture in the country while bringing fans closer to the sporting ecosystem. Providing live and non-live content, Star Sports 1 Telugu will have onboard, experts, commentators and players building a strong compelling offering for Telugu speaking sports audiences.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="Default" style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="Default" style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Superstar Rana Daggubati, the ambassador for VIVO Pro Kabaddi in Andhra Pradesh and Telangana features in the new TVC, where he compares sports to action packed cinema. He draws parallels on the similarities between sports and cinema, emphasizing on the ability each of them possess to capture audience attention always. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;Speaking at the launch of Star Sports 1 Telugu, a Star Sports spokesperson said, &amp;ldquo;Andhra Pradesh and Telangana are unique markets with a substantial demand for specific language content and have distinct viewing habits, this has helped us at Star Sports understand the pulse of the Telugu sports fan. Star Sports 1 Telugu is a unique product offering catering to core Telugu sports fans in the region and outside. With the launch of Star Sports 1 Telugu, we are exemplifying our endeavor of providing relevant regional sports content to fans across the country. We are committed to constantly strengthen our portfolio across markets, with the growing number of diverse requirements, Star Sports 1 Telugu launch is a key milestone in that journey to curate a compelling offering for fans across regions.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;On the caravan moving to Andhra Pradesh, Anupam Goswami, League Commissioner, VIVO Pro Kabaddi League, said, &amp;quot;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;he initiative with Star Sports 1 Telugu exemplifies the value created by Star India for sports in the country, with its belief and commitment to take it deep into the lives of fans across India in their own language.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;VIVO Pro Kabaddi has been a big gainer owing to the role created by the broadcaster; the launch of Star Sports 1 Telugu will deepen great following that the League has in both Andhra Pradesh and Telangana.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;Present at the press conference was, Rahul Chaudhari, Telugu Titans &amp;ndash; Leading Raider, who said, &amp;ldquo;Over the past few seasons we have received immense support from fans in the region, they have cheered for Telugu Titans and been there to support us for every match. The affection we receive in the region has been unmatched so far. I thoroughly enjoy watching sports in Hindi, and with this new destination, I am confident Star Sports 1 Telugu will make fans come together to watch their favourite sport in their language, starting with our home games here.&amp;rdquo; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;Star Sports 1 Telugu will feature live and non-live content packaged into a line-up with distinguished Telugu hosts and commentators from the sports fraternity including, Venkatpathy Raju, Venkatesh, Kalyan Krishna and Kaushik Nallan Chakravarthy for Cricket and Madhavi Bhandari, Radhika Reddy and Kalyan Kollaram for Kabaddi. Star Sports 1 Telugu will be available on leading DTH and Cable Operators across Andhra Pradesh and Telangana as well as the rest of India. The channel will be LIVE December 7, 2018 onwards.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US" style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;Fans can catch the VIVO Pro Kabaddi action LIVE, 7:30 pm onwards, on Star Sports 1 Telugu, the Star Sports Network and Hotstar. Fans can also watch the match live at Rajiv Gandhi Indoor Stadium, Vizag, starting December 7, 2018 onwards. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/RMAN2V5A3l0" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93310-sportsteluu.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/media-tv-news/key-media-people-movements-of-2018-93180.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>05/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Key Media People Movements of 2018</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;meta charset="utf-8" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;As the year 2018 comes to an end, we at exchange4media look at the key people movements that took place in the year across television and OTT industry.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Television Industry&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The big news that was announced this month was Raj Nayak leaving Viacom 18 as COO. Known for his creative and business acumen, Nayak steered Viacom18 flagship brand Colors to the leadership position as its CEO for over seven years. With a career spanning over 25 years, Nayak has turned around the fortunes of several media companies in the television industry.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Before joining Viacom18, Nayak formed Aidem Ventures, an independent media consulting and sales &amp;amp; marketing company. Prior to forming his own venture, Nayak was the CEO of NDTV Media Limited for a period of over seven years. He was the founding member of the Star TV Group in India, where he spent close to 10 years.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Another big movement in television industry was that of Karan Bajaj quitting Discovery Communications India in September. Bajaj joined Discovery India in 2016 as head of India and South Asia at Discovery Networks. He passionately led a bold wing to create a new type of purpose driven GE channel in India with Jeet. Prior to this, Bajaj has worked with Kraft Foods Group, The Boston Consulting Group and Procter &amp;amp; Gamble in the past. Bajaj has also written three books such as &amp;#39;Keep off the Grass&amp;rsquo; (fiction), &amp;lsquo;Johnny Gone Down&amp;rsquo; (fiction) and &amp;lsquo;The Yoga of Max&amp;#39;s Discontent/The Seeker&amp;rsquo; (fiction).&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Reliance Broadcast Network Limited, one of India&amp;#39;s largest network appointed Abraham Thomas as its Chief Executive Officer in October. The industry veteran has leveraged his deep insights into the multi-media platforms to drive and sustain the network&amp;#39;s vision of being a leading platform-agnostic radio player. Thomas comes with more than two decades of experience and has a proven track record of propelling businesses across print, radio, TV and digital to newer heights in India, China and South Asia.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;On 25 May, 2018, the Board of Balaji Telefilms approved the appointment of Sunil Lulla as Group Chief Executive Officer (CEO). Lulla brings with himself nearly three decades of experience in media, entertainment, technology and broadcast industry. In the early stages of his career, he was with JWT in various positions. In the 1990s, he was General Manager, MTV India. He had also worked with HMV India in the early 1990s. In 1999-2000, he was CEO of indya.com, a global internet venture of Microland. Prior joining Balaji, he was serving as the Chairman and Managing Director in advertising agency Grey Group India.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Joy Chakraborthy, Forbes India CEO and President (Revenue), Network18 Media &amp;amp; Investments, resigned from his post in November. A media veteran, Chakraborthy joined Network18 in May 2016. Before Network 18, Chakraborthy worked with BCCL as Director. He has also worked with TV Today as CEO and Zee Entertainment Enterprises as Executive Director (Revenue).&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Ashok Venkatramani, former CEO of ABP News Network, joined Zee Media Corporation Ltd (ZMCL) as Managing Director in the month of May. Venkatramani brings with him an experience of over 25 years in FMCG and broadcasting sectors. Prior to joining ZMCL, he also worked with ABP for over eight years. He joined ABP in 2008.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OTT Industry&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Ajit Mohan who was instrumental in making Hotstar one of India&amp;rsquo;s leading OTT services, created headlines when he was appointed by Facebook India as Managing Director and Vice President in September. He will join the social media giant early next year. He will be responsible for aligning teams and driving Facebook&amp;rsquo;s overall strategy in the country.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Former Chief Executive Officer of Voot Gaurav Gandhi quit Viacom18 Digital Ventures in March to join Amazon Prime Video India. Gandhi was with Viacom right from 2010 and initially worked with IndiaCast, the distribution company of TV18 and Viacom18 before moving to Voot.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;In May, Tarun Katial joined ZEE5 India, its digital arm, Zee Entertainment Enterprises Limited (ZEEL) as the CEO. He had already taken up additional responsibilities at ZEEL which included TV and digital content production in April 2017 besides heading BIG FM as its COO-CEO, which he had found 12 years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;In October, ZEEL roped in Taranjeet Singh for its OTT service ZEE5 India as Chief Revenue Officer and Business Head &amp;ndash; New Projects. Prior to this he was already well known in the digital ecosystem as social media platform&amp;rsquo;s Twitter&amp;rsquo;s Business Head where he served for more than three years.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Global streaming giant Netflix made headway in India appointing Swati Mohan as Director (Marketing) in May. Mohan&amp;#39;s last role was that of Country Head of National Geographic and Fox Networks Group, India since April 2015. Between January 2012 and March 2015 she was spearheading the programming and content portfolio for the bouquet of channels as the Vice President of Content and Programming at Fox International Channels, India.&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93180-yearender_(1).jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/media-tv-news/poll-programming-news-channels-line-up-special-shows-93231.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>05/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Poll Programming: News channels line up special shows</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;The Election season in the country is just around the corner. Five states including Rajasthan, Chhattisgarh, Madhya Pradesh, Mizoram and Telangana will vote for a new government&amp;nbsp;this month, and this will be followed by general elections next year. The BJP and the Congress are in direct fight in the states of Chhattisgarh, Madhya Pradesh and Rajasthan. In the&amp;nbsp;states of Mizoram and Telangana a multi-cornered fight is expected.&amp;nbsp;No wonder then news channels are having a field day, showing all possible details and debates on the political scene. With an aim to attract maximum viewers, most of the channels have lined up special election shows.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;According to the Broadcast Audience Research Council (BARC) India, the state elections in India hold special importance in the national politics affecting all major political parties. Broadcasters aim to cover it as it is a scheduled event and has lot of eagerness among viewers. &amp;ldquo;We will analyse this event in depth as we have previously seen that state elections have consistently led to viewership spikes,&amp;rdquo; said a BARC representative.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The news genre contributes 8 per cent to the total TV viewership. It was the third biggest genre on television in terms of viewership in 2017, as per BARC India data. In the past state elections in Kerala, West Bengal, Tamil Nadu and UP (state elections from 2016 and 2017) - the growth was highest for Kerala on the result day as compared to the pre-election days, and the least in UP.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;According to the data, interestingly, the importance of Election Day and Result Day varies across markets. The difference in viewership for pre-election weeks and Election Day was the maximum for TN/ Pondicherry, indicating the importance and impact of the poll-day for this market, while the other markets were predominantly result-oriented.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;In 2017, the Gujarat assembly elections saw a huge interest from viewers. On the day of the counting, the Hindi news genre grew by 130 per cent, while the English news saw a growth of 272 per cent (as per the BARC data). This clearly shows the interest of viewers in news, especially during elections. During the recently held Karnataka elections, Hindi news viewership increased by 25-30 per cent in that week (as per BARC data) despite the regional nature of the news. And so, expecting a similar surge in viewership during the upcoming elections won&amp;rsquo;t be wrong.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;News18 India has launched a slew of new shows and has ramped up its existing ones. For instance, two of the most popular shows on News18 India, &amp;lsquo;Lapete Mien Netaji&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Bhaiyaji Kahin&amp;rsquo; are travelling to Rajasthan and MP.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking about the programming on elections, Priyanka Kaul, President &amp;ndash; Marketing &amp;amp; Special Projects, Network 18, said, &amp;ldquo;Elections clearly drive a strong spike in viewership of news channels. In a democratic polity such as ours, people at large retain a key interest in politics.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;She further said, &amp;ldquo;As a network, we have always prided ourselves in our coverage of elections. Over the years, we have developed a reputation of being the most accurate and the first to call elections. Given our national and regional reach, we have the ability to not only track key stories across the length and breadth of the country but also evaluate the likely impact of the same. In terms of our brand strategy, we have always believed that there is no real alternative to Network18 when it comes to elections and hence we centre much of our promotion on the thought of elections.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Similarly, with Mandate 2019, Times Now has been claiming to be at the forefront of tracking the assembly elections in five states. Through engaging properties, Times Now promises to make the election coverage more exciting and captivating for its viewers. The channel also has programmes such as Pre-Poll Surveys (aired every Thursday from 6 pm to 8 pm) which broadcast a set of opinion polls through its association with CNX Media for an in-depth analysis of data on voting, public opinion, and political participation. Inside: A weekend magazine show at 11:30 am brings viewers close to the heat and hustle of the elections with the candidates in the fray dwelling in detail about the issues in each of the five states. Also, there is &amp;lsquo;Contest: A weekend debate show&amp;rsquo; anchored by Rahul Shivshankar. Some other poll shows of the channel are &amp;lsquo;Frankly Speaking&amp;rsquo; with Navika Kumar and &amp;lsquo;India Upfront&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Exit Poll&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Mirror Now too is geared to present extensive ground reports from the polling states. According to the channel, its reportage will focus on people&amp;rsquo;s issues such as aspirations of the youth vis-&amp;agrave;-vis jobs, a deep-dive into the agrarian distress in these states, a status check on the implementation of welfare schemes, access to healthcare, urban infrastructure, civic woes, and women&amp;rsquo;s safety.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Talking about ABP News&amp;rsquo; election coverage plan, Avinash Pandey, COO, ABP News Network, shared, &amp;ldquo;Desh Ka Mood, the leading election programme of ABP News, released the survey results on November 2. Done by CVoter, the timeline of the survey was October 2018 with over 15463 respondents spread pan India. All the channels under the network are doing election coverage, starting from monthly poll. Regional channels broadly do daily election coverage around 5pm and 8pm every day.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Taking the highest election recall programme of ABP News- &amp;lsquo;Kaun Banega Mukhyamantri&amp;rsquo; forward, the network launched &amp;lsquo;Siyasat Ka Sensex&amp;rsquo;. The one- hour show is hosted by anchor Neha Pant from Monday-Friday between 8pm and 9pm. The show will aim at giving viewers opinion poll data of Madhya Pradesh, Chhattisgarh and Rajasthan during the upcoming elections. &amp;ldquo;Siyasat Ka Sensex is like a daily poll in these states,&amp;rdquo; said Pandey.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Aaj Tak, meanwhile, plans to have a show, Panchayat, in three states each along with opinion polls. The channel also aired &amp;lsquo;Chunavi Dangal&amp;rsquo;, a weekly discussion show which was aired from September 8 to November 24. Show &amp;lsquo;Raj Tilak&amp;rsquo; is all about ground report of almost all election issues through packages, conversation with voter and local leaders.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;According to the channel, the purpose of the programme is to show what people expect from the political parties. &amp;lsquo;MP Ajab Hai&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Rajasthan on Wheels&amp;rsquo; are among the other election special shows on the news channel.&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93231-elections.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/media-tv-news/lokmat-to-come-up-with-hindi-channel-next-year-93269.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>05/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Lokmat to come up with Hindi channel next year</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Marathi media group Lokmat is all set to launch a Hindi news channel next year.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;It has been learnt that the preparations for the launch are in the final stages. Highly placed sources have also confirmed that senior journalist Punya Prasun Bajpai, whose recent resignation from ABP News caused quite a stir, could be the face of the channel. Bajpai has worked with Lokmat before also.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Lokmat along with Network18 is already running a Marathi news channel.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;This is so far the third channel that would be launched in 2019. The other two being Republic Bharat and TV9.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93269-LokmatLogo.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/media-tv-news/rejuvenating-indian-television-looking-beyond-trp-93273.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>05/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Rejuvenating Indian television: Looking beyond TRP</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Chairman of Prasar Bharati Dr. Surya Prakash on Tuesday released a book written by Founder Chairman of CMS Dr. N Bhaskara Rao, &amp;lsquo;TRP Trick: How Television in India was hijacked&amp;#39;. Kiran Karnik, former CEO of Discovery Channel, introduced the book at the event held in New Delhi.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;The book release was followed by a panel of esteemed speakers discussing the topic &amp;lsquo;Rejuvenating Indian Television&amp;rsquo;. The panel comprised&amp;nbsp;Ashok Venkatramani, Managing Director, Zee Media (News);&amp;nbsp;Anuradha Prasad, Chairperson, BAG Network;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#545454"&gt;veteran journalist and&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#545454"&gt;Padam Shri&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Alok Mehta; Sunil Gupta, Secretary, TRAI; and&amp;nbsp;K G Suresh, Director General, IIMC.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Moderating the session was P N Vasanti, Director General, CMS, who brought up the topic of how to make the medium of television more meaningful to our culture and society. &amp;nbsp;She said, &amp;ldquo;Compared to television, demand for content is growing higher on video, digital, mobile and YouTube etc. In such times, how are we shifting gears to meet both business and content sides of the TV industry? How can the entire eco-system be made more sensitive to the diverse interest of our audience?&amp;rdquo; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Commenting on it, Ashok Venkatramani said, &amp;ldquo;Today, it&amp;rsquo;s a conspiracy of convenience where broadcaster, advertiser, regulator all are happy with the status quo. While this is the reality, it isn&amp;rsquo;t actually a happy situation. I strongly believe that there is space for every single medium in this country. There&amp;rsquo;s enough headroom for growth, be it television, print or digital. India is a young country with high chances of growth in all domains. I don&amp;rsquo;t think there&amp;rsquo;s a need to worry about television being in a bad shape. &amp;nbsp;The key challenge for TV is about making itself relevant in the changing eco-system today.&amp;nbsp; Television companies are realising very fast that the news and the way it&amp;rsquo;s conveyed is crucial, the platform or the medium isn&amp;rsquo;t. &amp;nbsp;TRPs are not relevant at all, if companies are really interested in creating brand equity or credibility.&amp;rdquo; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Anuradha Prasad, Chairperson, BAG Network, shared the manner in which BAG Network managed its business and content.&amp;nbsp;&amp;ldquo;It is very easy to discern, dissect and condemn but difficult to survive and be the one executing it out all. I started my news channel with the tagline &amp;lsquo;news is back&amp;rsquo;. I promised myself that I&amp;rsquo;d remain true to my journalism ethics that taught me to show news and not TRP-favouring shows. But then, the ratings came as -4. I then spoke to authorities at TAM and I was told that I must telecast shows of a certain kind in order to get high TRPs. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t in agreement with what I was told,&amp;rdquo; she said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&amp;ldquo;But even then I survived. And it was only because of the passion, commitment and cause. You decide come what may, I would stick to my ethics. I wish there&amp;rsquo;s a competition to TAM and BARC, but sadly there&amp;rsquo;s none. I wish we had set up distribution platforms earlier. If TRAI today announces that there will be no TRP in India, you will see how the content paradigm will shift,&amp;rdquo; Prasad said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Adding to the argument, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Alok Mehta, said, &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s crucial to build an eco-system that goes beyond this number-driven practice and is more of citizen-committee driven. Everyone is watching television. What the industry needs to work on is to make sure that media gets to be self-disciplined. Hence I request all media organisations and media schools to make this book a part of their curriculum. The issue with TRPs needs to be resolved.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Explaining the purpose of the consultation paper issued by TRAI on Monday &amp;amp; the authority&amp;rsquo;s vision for the broadcasting sector in India, Sunil Gupta,&amp;nbsp;said, &amp;ldquo;When private channels started increasing their operations in India, the primary focus shifted from educating people to making as much money as you want through this business. The mindset of broadcasters and other stakeholders has not changed and customers are not ready to choose from the price options available. When Hindi-speaking viewers are watching an English channel and you count those Hindi viewers as your audience, you as an English channel are modifying the TRPs, which is wrong. While this is happening at a huge scale, the question is who is to be blamed for this. Again, world over, the concept of impression is being adopted to see what is the weightage of a channel. We are fully aware of the incidences of tampering and influences happening around. Once industry reforms and consumers have choices, TRP ratings will not be of consequence any longer.&amp;rdquo; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Discussing the future of the television medium in our society, K G Suresh, Director General, IIMC, said, &amp;ldquo;In media, I think we are not sure, whether we are a leader or a follower. If I am a leader, I will have to develop a niche, I cannot be following the mob. The concept of TRP goes for a toss here itself. In a country like India, we can surely develop a taste for good content. &amp;nbsp;I don&amp;rsquo;t think the domain of market research in our industry has been discovered entirely before planning the programming. Good content alone can give you audience. Here TRP does not come into the picture. Today, on social media, people are going to rate you and also demolish you if you don&amp;rsquo;t present good content. It&amp;rsquo;s social media that is driving news agenda today and not television. Topics that go viral on social media end up becoming the 9 pm debate subjects.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;h1 style="margin: 0cm 0cm 0.0001pt;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h1&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93273-Book.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/media-tv-news/icc-womens-world-t20-india-vs-australia-match-garners-24-mn-impressions-93253.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>04/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>ICC Women’s World T20: India v/s Australia match garners 2.4 mn impressions</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;meta charset="utf-8" /&gt;The India v/s Australia match of ICC Women&amp;rsquo;s World T20 garnered 2.4 million impressions in week 47 of the Broadcast Audience Research Council (BARC) India data.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The series started from November 9 and was telecast&amp;nbsp;on Star India&amp;rsquo;s sports channels including Star Sports 1, Star Sports 1 Hindi, Star Sports 1 HD, Star Sports 1 Hindi HD and Star Sports Tamil 1.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;In week 47, Sony Ten 3 leads the sports genre with 141 million impressions followed by Star Sports First in the second position with 119 million impressions and Sony Ten 1 on third with 117 million impressions. Sony Six and Star Sports 1Hindi bagged the fourth and fifth spots with 112 and 90.7 million impressions.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The tournament was scheduled to be held between 9 and 24 November 2018 in three venues in the Caribbean - Guyana, Antigua, and St Lucia.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The ten participating teams are Australia, England, New Zealand, India, Bangladesh, South Africa, Sri Lanka, Pakistan, West Indies, and Ireland.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93253-ICCWomenT20.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/media-tv-news/india-today-group-group-ceo-quits-93237.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>03/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>India Today Group CEO Vivek Khanna quits</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Vivek Khanna, Group Chief Executive Officer, India Today Group, has put down his papers after a year with the comapny to pursue other professional opportunities. Khanna confirmed this to exchange4media. He will be serving his notice period as per the terms of his appointment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;In the transition period, all of Khanna&amp;#39;s direct reportees will report to Kalli Purie and Dinesh Bhatia. Everything else will remain unchanged, the company said in a statement. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: Calibri, sans-serif; font-size: 11pt;"&gt;Khanna has over 27 years of experience with stints at Hindustan Media Ventures Ltd, HT Media and Aviva. An alumnus of IIM Ahmedabad, he started his career with Hindustan Unilever and Aviva Life Insurance. He moved to HT Media in 2008. He has a successful track record of launching new businesses, turning around and rapidly growing businesses, building passionate teams, and leading large teams in media, insurance and FMCG sectors.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93237-Vivek.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/media-tv-news/sun-directs-fy18s-revenue-shot-by-13-spike-to-rs-1367-cr-93236.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>03/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Sun Direct's FY18's revenue shot by 13% spike to Rs 1367 cr</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Direct-to-home (DTH) operator Sun Direct&amp;rsquo;s revenue for the fiscal ending March 31, 2018, witnessed a spike of 13.25 per cent to Rs 1367 crore, as against Rs 1207 crore in the previous fiscal, according to media reports.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Its net profit recorded at Rs 45 crore, a slight increase compared to Rs 44 crore in the previous fiscal. The company&amp;rsquo;s PAT margin dropped to 3.3 per cent compared to 3.7 per cent in the previous fiscal.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Reports mentioned that the DTH operator&amp;rsquo;s long and short-term bank facilities were recently reaffirmed by rating agency Crisil. Sun Direct&amp;rsquo;s long-term bank facilities were reassigned &amp;lsquo;Crisil BBB+/Stable&amp;rsquo; while the short-term ratings were reassigned &amp;lsquo;Crisil A2&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Sun Direct, among the top five DTH operators in India, has a 40 per cent market share in South India with a subscriber base of 13.92 million and a net subscriber base of 6.99 million as on 31 March 2018.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;It currently has close around 70 HD channels, making it one of the biggest distributors of HD content in India. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93236-sundirect.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/media-tv-news/umesh-kumawat-joins-news18-lokmat-as-managing-editor-93210.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>30/11/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Umesh Kumawat joins News18 Lokmat as Managing Editor</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;Network18 on Friday announced the appointment of Umesh Kumawat as Managing Editor of News18 Lokmat.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;News18-Lokmat is a joint venture of Network 18&amp;rsquo;s TV18 Broadcast Ltd. and the Lokmat Media Pvt Ltd. It is a 24-hours Marathi news channel. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;Speaking on the appointment,&amp;nbsp;Kumawat&amp;nbsp;said, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m delighted to be leading the team at News18 Lokmat and being a part of Network18 Group, which is one of the most renowned media houses in India. It is an honour to be a part of such a well-respected media house that comprises an incredibly talented team. I look forward to bringing authentic, speedy and reliable news and stories to our audience. It is my goal to make the channel an essential part of the viewer&amp;rsquo;s everyday life.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;Kumawat comes with close to 19 years of experience in journalism. Prior to Network18, he was Senior Editor with ABP News for 14 years. Previously, he has been a part of leading media brands such as Aajtak, Zee News and TV 9.&amp;nbsp; He has also been honoured with many awards in the field of journalism.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93210-UmeshKumawat.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/media-tv-news/media-has-always-been-one-of-the-most-brand-sensitive-businesses-mk-anand-93197.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>29/11/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Media has always been one of the most brand sensitive businesses: MK Anand</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Times Network MD &amp;amp; CEO MK Anand delivered a keynote address at Shared Value Summit 2018 on &amp;#39;Role of Media in Creating Resilient Democracies&amp;#39;.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;He began the address saying, &amp;ldquo;We in media consider it our fundamental right to discuss and debate about everything around us, somewhere we either escape attention or sidestep the issue. Or maybe we simply avoid it.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Below is his speech:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Media or specifically news media is far too important to be left to a small bunch of us news professionals to conduct. While I believe news operations and its ethical conduct are safe with our community, the general functional relevance and strategic impact of news must be firmly at the centre of discourses such as this. This is the second time in a month that there has been a request for me to talk about the role of news media in society. And if that&amp;rsquo;s a pattern, I think it&amp;rsquo;s good.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The news is continuing education. It basically works to standardize social awareness and thus makes communicating, transacting and living with each other possible. If our news contexts are congruent, we relate. If they are not, we can&amp;rsquo;t see eye to eye. News, therefore, is a prerequisite for democracy.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Media business has a natural and instinctive affinity for democracy. In fact, it cannot exist without democracy. In non-democratic regimes, news media are mouthpieces supported by regimes or vested interests. They cannot be called independent businesses at all. As such, market forces have ensured that news media in democracies have by and large overtly or covertly worked to strengthen democracy. It has been a virtuous cycle.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;There can be no democracy if there is no shared purpose. And there cannot be shared purpose without shared context. News media starts with reporting events. And theoretically, the context is set by the events themselves. However, the choice of which news gets highlighted and what sequence it is reported in, the choice of words, visuals and innuendo means that news media ends up setting the context. How and for what this power is used determines how much contribution media makes to strengthen democracy.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Corporate media, like all consumer product businesses, face competing products, evolve brands, espouse values and work in self-interest. The temptation to use the power of setting context arises due to competitive self-interest in the short term. While some amount of this is permissible in the form of advertising or agenda led editorial called advertorial, anything beyond that distorts social awareness. Studying the long-term behaviour of news brands will clearly indicate that misuse of the power to set the context eventually leads to brand erosion and is bad for business. From a competition point of view, therefore, short-term gains by currying favours works against the news media brand itself. Contrary to popular imagination, corporate media is not besieged by powerful vested interests and no one really arm twists anyone. If someone alludes to that, it&amp;rsquo;s good to remember that it always takes two&amp;nbsp;to tango.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;In my experience, values-led context setting is permissible. And fidelity to such values is appreciated by consumers. In an age when event information is a commodity due to the ubiquitous nature of screens, news media brands do need to be opinionated to choose and pursue target groups. Mass news media brands can be biased to a set of values and democratic at the same time, just as honest political leaders are. Leading news brands like ours actually lead the nation as much as the political leadership does.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;News media management, therefore, is also about management of this power for the larger good. We are in a unique position to choose public good agendas and put our force behind them to accelerate change and aid in development. We have a few striking examples of this in our company such as Remonetise India, India for Kerala, India Development Debate, The Urban Debate, End VVIP Racism and Path to Life. Jan Nivesh by ET Now and AMFI cross&amp;nbsp;the targeted one million pledges within six months of activity. World&amp;rsquo;s largest investor education programme.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The only corporate self-interest in all these cases is to do good, to be known as good from a brand point of view. The importance of brand equity cannot be ever overstated in media business. Media is a trust product and has always been one of the most brand sensitive businesses. And the seismic changes that have been unleashed on media industry, which forever faces new competition due to evolving technology, has only raised the importance of brand. These forces work towards ensuring that media brands that don&amp;rsquo;t work for their consumer interest or are compromised will not survive.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;While designing the content architecture and broad theme for Times Now and Mirror Now, we rely a lot on consumer research and data from sample surveys. We stand for values that large consumer groups believe in. Our digital platforms give us instant feedback on what the mood of the nation is on issues. Our content line up then reflects that. Its pure market forces at work. The end result of all this is audience aggregation.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;So much about corporate media. Any discussion today on news and democracy will be incomplete without touching upon the impact that digital and particularly social media has on society.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The Internet converts every device on it into a potential server. And without realising, each one of us is a broadcaster. The positive side of this ability to publish is the opportunity it offers individuals to directly reach out to others, without the cumbersome and sometimes limiting filter of media platforms. Mass outreach is today possible without courting major media platforms. Donald Trump has 55 million followers on Twitter, which gives him the strength to brush aside global news brands. Narendra Modi&amp;rsquo;s social media reach is larger than the social media reach of the top three Indian digital English news platforms --TOI, NDTV and Times Now-- put together. This obviously is a great source of power for these leaders. This strengthens democracy as it offers individuals immense potential. While the new medium comes with this major potential, there is a dark side to it. Fake news, deliberate and unintended, has grave consequences. It&amp;rsquo;s all the more dangerous when we realise that the news consumer is still driven by an almost 200-year-old habit of trusting the published word. While publishing technology has leap-frogged, the same cannot be expected of the consumer&amp;#39;s brain. Branded media could lose its business, net worth and the shirt off its back if they did a hoax piece and got caught. What do anonymous social media jockeys or address fewer bloggers and opinion websites have to lose? Worse still is the propagation by message apps, with no address of the source. Regulation and consumer education have to urgently adapt.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;In the context of digital news, the other critical issue besides fake news that needs to be confronted is the concentration of power and therefore the potential threat that search and social intermediaries and platform owners can pose. As a news practitioner, I can tell you one thing. Ensuring that my news gets to your screen is not as simple as it looks. Behind your seemingly &amp;lsquo;in control&amp;rsquo; act of choosing my channel and staying tuned, is a highly complex data-driven activity. Your choice is always influenced by a series of invisible steps that broadcasters take in placement, distribution, visibility, etc. And I am talking about traditional broadcast. We call it reach-optimisation. This power gets magnified when the medium through which you access stories, the algorithms that decide which story to place in front of you when you search, is owned and operated by corporations that may not be easily regulated. I am not blaming them for wilful subversion at all. They have robust systems to ensure fair play. But concentrating power of this nature can have unintended disastrous consequences. Today, search rules on such platforms can overnight change which news brand gets watched over others. A third-party platform that wields such absolute power that determines survival itself for news players can be dangerous to democracy.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93197-MKAnandKeynote.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/media-tv-news/mona-jain-gets-additional-charge-at-zee-93196.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>29/11/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Mona Jain gets additional charge at Zee</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Corrigendum: The story filed by exchange4media pertaining to Mona Jain&amp;#39;s exit from ZEE Entertainment was incorrect. Mona Jain is very much a part of ZEE Entertainment and has successfully led the English, Hindi HD and Brand Solutions vertical as Principal Cluster Head. She&amp;nbsp;has also very recently taken additional charge of &amp;amp;TV and the FTA cluster (Zee Anmol, Big magic, Anmol Cinema and Music). Along with this, Jain&amp;nbsp;is also responsible for the branch revenue of the North zone.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93196-Mona-Jain-ZEE.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
</urlset>
