<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9" xmlns:image="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-image/1.1" xmlns:news="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-news/0.9">
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/out-of-home-news/posterscope-launches-digital-ooh-ad-exchange-rooh-93278.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>05/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Posterscope launches Digital OOH Ad Exchange, ROOH</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;Posterscope India, the out-of-home specialist from Dentsu Aegis Network, has announced the launch of ROOH (Real Time Out Of Home), a unique planning-buying platform (including programmatic) for digital OOH inventories. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;With billings from digital OOH estimated to grow at a rate of 60% by 2019-end, this latest tool will only help Posterscope to further strengthen and bolster its real-time capabilities in India.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;Based on the extensive use of APIs (application programming interface), Posterscope&amp;rsquo;s ROOH uses a wide variety of data feeds to create customised and targeted advertising. This, in turn, allows advertisers to exercise direct control over the content that is being played on screens without the need to access the media owner systems, individually.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;Most of the screens are cloud-based that enables ease and flexibility in campaign management. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;Now, with the launch of ROOH, Posterscope India has collated and brought together more than 60,000 digital screens on a single platform. This tool not only uses analytics around the screen when consumers frequenting the location but also exploits Dentsu Aegis Network&amp;rsquo;s research, insights and planning tool &amp;ndash; CCS (Consumer Connections Study Planner) along with Dan Explore (a tool that examines consumer passion points) to arrive at the right screen mix for the brand to help optimise the plan. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;Haresh Nayak, the Group MD, Posterscope Group South Asia, said, &amp;quot;The ability to deliver dynamic content in real time, driven by highly relevant data and optimised to audience type and audience mindset, represents an enormous leap in the power of the OOH medium. I am certain that it will attract new advertisers to the medium, particularly those that need highly flexible and agile brand communication.&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;Deepak Kumar, Senior Vice President, ROOH, said, &amp;ldquo;Over the last two years, we have worked across 2500 towns, dealing with over 50 key media owners, to develop this tool. This has helped us in understanding and curating ROOH. The flexibility of ROOH will enable some interesting campaigns and will make OOH truly a dynamic medium. The Posterscope Group predicts that the year 2020 will be a defining year for Real Time Out Of Home.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;Currently, BFSI, mobile, ecommerce and automobile categories are at the forefront of usage of this tool. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;Also, only accessed by its planning team now, Posterscope will soon extend ROOH&amp;rsquo;s access to its clients and partners. ROOH will provide insights and data to them - right from the brief stage juxtaposed against consumer analytics that will help then detect and decipher the apt triggers for their campaign. Human intervention, then, will be limited and utilised only if necessary. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93278-rooh.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/out-of-home-news/we-still-love-tv-and-ooh-for-their-emotional-impact-karthi-marshan-kotak-mahindra-93254.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>04/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>We still love TV and OOH for their emotional impact: Karthi Marshan, Kotak Mahindra</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;BFSI sector brand Kotak Mahindra is rapidly increasing its focus on digital media in the last few years. The brand hired actor Ranveer Singh as the face of the brand and is also the crowd puller for the #IndiaInvited campaign.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The brand was recently in the news for its latest campaign &amp;lsquo;Card Mila Kya&amp;rsquo; amidst the wedding of Singh and actor Deepika Padukone. The campaign was applauded for its humour and creative idea.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;In an interview with exchange4media, Karthi Marshan, Chief Marketing Officer, Kotak Mahindra Group, spoke about the role of brand ambassador in communication, idea behind the &amp;lsquo;Card Mila kya&amp;rsquo;, overall marketing strategy and more.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hiring a brand ambassador in banking sector is very difficult because it&amp;#39;s all about &amp;lsquo;Trust and Faith&amp;rsquo;. Do you think Ranveer Singh fits the bill here?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Banking is about trust and faith, this much is absolutely true. But that is not a task we can abdicate to a brand ambassador, the brand itself must answer for that, by its conduct, and the conduct of its leadership as well as its foot soldiers, in every single interaction it has with its stakeholders. A brand ambassador for us has a very different responsibility. It is his job to espouse the brand&amp;rsquo;s values, bring them alive and guarantee attention of the prospective consumers. If the ambassador&amp;rsquo;s public persona and the brand&amp;rsquo;s values are in sync, that&amp;rsquo;s a huge bonus for the brand, as every sighting of the ambassador will be tantamount to a sighting of the brand. For instance, we recently launched a teaser campaign for our Ranveer Singh Debit card which has no Kotak logo on it, and yet social media was abuzz with talk about Kotak&amp;rsquo;s coup.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When you incorporate humour and creativity in marketing, the results are definitely going to grab eyeballs and the same happened with the recent campaign &amp;lsquo;Card Mila Kya&amp;rsquo;. How did the idea come about?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s a clich&amp;eacute; about good luck happening when opportunity meets preparation. I think in this case it was definitely so. We were on track and fully prepared to launch a Debit Card with images of Ranveer Singh on it, when news came of his wedding. Social media was already in hyper drive discussing all aspects of the imminent nuptials. When we saw the couple publish their wedding announcement card on Twitter, and then share pictures with the select invitees receiving their invitation card, we thought it was too good an opportunity to miss. We quickly (practically overnight) revised the creatives to reflect the idea of a humorous take on the Wedding Card that was in reality the announcer for our Debit Card, and it really grabbed the imagination of the viewing public.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Being a financial brand, how you define your target audience on digital and how do you strategize to reach out to them?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Everybody has a relationship with money, and in that sense everybody is a target customer for us. However, everybody&amp;rsquo;s money needs are somewhat different, and that is where customisation and segmenting comes in. On digital, it is possible to precise target consumers not only based on their demographics but also their interests, needs and burning questions. This is what we use effectively to target multiple micro-segments on digital.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is your media mix? What has been the role of digital medium in communicating with the consumers? What part of your marketing spends are allocated to the digital medium?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;We still love traditional media like TV and OOH for the emotional impact they have. We use digital selectively for buzz and engagement, and we also use digital dominantly for performance campaigns. We communicate on digital with prospects, to persuade them to consider our products, and we also communicate with customers already banking with us, persuading them to consider other products that are relevant and appropriate for them at various points in time.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;What role does outdoor medium play in the overall marketing strategy?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Traditionally, outdoor has been approached as a reminder medium, one that encapsulates a brand campaign&amp;rsquo;s message into one visual, one line and the brand&amp;rsquo;s logo. At Kotak, we have never limited its utility to that. We have very often used outdoor for its unique ability to be topical, hyper local, impactful etc. We have done bold things like run ads on hoardings minus the brand logo, confident that the message would reflect the brand on its own. We have gone hyper local with messages on bus shelters and hoardings in the vicinity of our branches, inviting customers of neighbouring banks to cross the road to get more for their money. During our Kona Kona Kotak campaign, we deliberately switched around visuals, celebrating the Guntur customers in Mumbai, Bangalore customers in Ranchi, Goa customers in Cuddapah and so on. This seeming incongruity got people&amp;rsquo;s attention, and we got a lot of messages about how we must have made mistakes in dispatching the wrong artworks to various cities. But slowly, the penny dropped, and Mumbaikars appreciated that if we had branches in places like Guntur, we probably had branches in many places of India.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do you see greater reason to drive OOH advertising for deepening your brands consumer connects?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Absolutely. OOH has enormous flexibility because we can change messaging based on location, as well as based on topical relevance. So sites near our branches can have one kind of message, while sites near the competitors can have another. Sites relevant to my category like malls and cinemas can have a specific type of message. Outdoor is a lot like finely targeted digital advertising. We also believe good outdoor design is a nuanced craft. David Ogilvy prescribed &amp;lsquo;12 words or less&amp;rsquo;. Most billboards tend to have a lot more clutter. Kotak actually operate with the maxim of 6 words or less.&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93254-KarthiMarshan.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/out-of-home-news/india-uses-ooh-in-a-really-quirky-and-fun-way-david-payne-93015.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>20/11/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>India uses OOH in a really quirky and fun way: David Payne</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Former CEO of WPP Kinetic David Payne recently took over as Global Head of strategy &amp;amp; operations at independent international out of home media company Mediakeys, owned by Comkeys. Comkeys has now entered into a strategic alliance with Laqshya Media Group (LMG) to launch Mediakeys in the Indian market.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Payne was in India recently and exchange4media caught up with him to talk about the alliance with Laqshya Media, India&amp;rsquo;s OOH market and much more.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Watch the video here or read the edited excerpts&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/AD6SoE2qFM8" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;On strategic partnership with Laqshya Media&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;We work with brands all over the world, delivering solutions for them largely in the world of out of home (OOH), although we do cover all media. So, for us, it&amp;rsquo;s quite a narrow and small market. But we are the biggest in that sector. So, on the international scale, India is becoming increasingly attractive for us.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;There is obviously an increase in the number of Indian brands that are looking to talk to consumers outside India. So, India is becoming more important for us in terms of sales and outbound. Also, it&amp;rsquo;s becoming more important for us as brands that work with us globally want to come into India. We have been thinking long and hard about our strategy for the Indian market. We wanted to accomplish something where we get to work with the best in class, both in sales and execution. And we bring exactly the same to India as well. It&amp;rsquo;s a complementary relationship where we can work with them to drive sales from India, and we can bring business for them into India.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s just two like-minded companies working together to jointly invest in the future of the business.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;India vs global OOH industry&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;I have come to India many times in my career and I am always fascinated by the out of home scene here. It has a huge potential as many changes that we have seen in other parts of the world have not taken place here.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;It is prime for consolidation and capital investment. If you match that with what&amp;rsquo;s going on in this country from an infrastructure point of view (with new airports, new roads, new railways and new metros), there is a huge potential for development. Actually, India is yet to establish itself alongside more established &amp;amp; developed markets such as Germany, UK and France. But I think once that acceleration starts, it&amp;rsquo;s going to be a much quicker transition.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;There is no real measurement here yet and so it&amp;rsquo;s not quite as accountable. But it&amp;rsquo;s still quite dynamic and creative. What we are yet to see in India is real use of data to bring audiences. But I think that&amp;rsquo;s coming quite fast.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Digital impact on OOH industry globally&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;I think it&amp;rsquo;s a competitive threat, particularly in India where digital is highly accessible. Smartphone penetration has bypassed all aspects of larger screen penetration and it&amp;rsquo;s very high. Therefore, digital mobile is very accessible and it&amp;rsquo;s measurable and accountable. And that is what outdoor is not yet here in India.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s a big competitive threat to a number of media channels in India. It&amp;rsquo;s also a really nice business opportunity because out of home in other markets is becoming increasingly technology-driven, where you have digital screens. However, to talk about programmatic buying of digital screens will be a stretch.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Also, it&amp;rsquo;s very interesting to see non out of home media companies beginning to acquire out of home businesses, something that you are not seeing here. But certainly it&amp;rsquo;s a big trend in the US and the UK at the moment, and possibly in Germany where you are seeing the likes of Google, and Ali Baba in China.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;On Indian OOH market&amp;rsquo;s creativity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;India is really progressive in that. I think India uses out of home in a really quirky and fun way. It is often used as a backdrop in special events or for special demonstrations or activations. I have always felt that India does that quite well.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;What India needs is to carry on doing what they are doing well and invest in capital expenditure and infrastructure. Work in partnership with government and public authorities so that the quality of out of home does not just benefit the advertiser but benefit the community.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Future projects&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Mediakeys is agile and quick-moving. We make decisions quickly on our strategy. We are able to test and get things done fast, and we are very entrepreneurial. I am looking for the 2019 immensely. We have got a lot of exciting things happening next year, and a couple of major global announcements. We will be able to talk about it after Christmas.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/93015-david.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/out-of-home-news/headsail-rolls-out-ooh-campaign-for-bbc-news-across-south-asia-east-africa-92955.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>14/11/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Headsail rolls out OOH campaign for BBC News across South Asia &amp; East Africa</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;BBC&amp;nbsp;News, along with its OOH agency Headsail Media Services Pvt. Ltd. rolled out an&amp;nbsp;innovative campaign in&amp;nbsp;Pakistan,&amp;nbsp;Bangladesh&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;Kenya in September 2018.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;The key objective of the campaign is to drive reach and position the BBC News as a news provider that offers something unique for audience in their local language&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;showcase how&amp;nbsp;BBC news helps people make more of their world compared to other news providers. The key message was that BBC News has expanded in new languages, offering the knowledge and&amp;nbsp;perspective that helps audiences to progress and grow in life.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The campaign shone&amp;nbsp;a light on&amp;nbsp;the BBC&amp;rsquo;s unique offering and gave&amp;nbsp;a positive voice in a country buoyed by progress.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;A&amp;nbsp;key challenge was to get the attention of audience and understand that BBC News with its new languages is the go-to destination for news and information.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;The OOH plan was spread across&amp;nbsp;South Asia&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;East Africa&amp;nbsp;- 6 major cities across 3 countries - Pakistan (Lahore, Karachi, Islamabad &amp;amp; Rawalpindi), Bangladesh (Dhaka) and Kenya (Nairobi). Larger-than-life digital screens/billboards and wall wraps were deployed across markets at main arterial routes, nodal junction, key connectors and trade areas, which created significant interest and impact.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;Also, this year India was the host country for the World Environment Day summit &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;and it was&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;particularly&amp;nbsp;relevant for BBC World Service to make a huge splash on the day and mark the launch of their &amp;lsquo;Make More of Your World&amp;rsquo; brand campaign.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&amp;nbsp;An on-ground marketing event campaign was developed in-house by BBC Creative, who worked in partnership with the renowned graffiti writer turned artist INSA. As part of the campaign in India, the BBC Marketing commissioned the task to manage this on-ground event to Headsail Media.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:11.25pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Tejash Kothari &amp;ndash; Marketing Manager Asia Pacific (BBC News), said&amp;nbsp;&amp;ldquo;This is a key campaign for us at BBC News and we wanted to align all our efforts to effectively reach out to our global audience. The campaign was spread across demographics, geographies and time zones and we wanted to activate the campaign on all media platforms on the same day across all the 4 countries. We are extremely glad we were able to successfully execute the campaign with support from Headsail Media Services and team.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:11.25pt; text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Vijay Jain - Founder &amp;amp; CEO, (Headsail Media Services Pvt. Ltd), said, &amp;ldquo;We took a data-backed approach on OOH and used heatmaps of cities to create dominance through Digital Billboards keeping the essence of creative into consideration. Our footprint in South Asia and East Africa enabled us to plan and flawlessly execute a campaign of such scale which transcended international boundaries.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Team Credits:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="color:null;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;Client Servicing &amp;ndash; Viral Gohil&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="color:null;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;Media Planning &amp;ndash; Kavita Sabherwal&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="color:null;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;Creative Director &amp;ndash; Rajesh Khanna&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="color:null;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;Media Execution &amp;ndash; Smita Patade&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="color:null;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;Buying &amp;ndash; Chirag Jain&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/92955-bbcnews.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/out-of-home-news/when-kotak-mahindra-bank-played-its-cards-right-with-campaign-featuring-ranveer-singh-92924.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>13/11/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Card Mila Kya? Ranveer Singh asks with folded hands</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;meta charset="utf-8" /&gt;If you have crossed certain key areas across Mumbai you just can&amp;#39;t miss&amp;nbsp;hoardings of Bollywood star Ranveer Singh with folded hands,&amp;nbsp;asking, &amp;quot;Card Mila Kya?&amp;quot; And no, he is not talking about his wedding card. With Singh&amp;#39;s&amp;nbsp;wedding to longtime girlfriend Deepika Padukone just around the corner, this ad by Kotak Mahindra Bank first needs applause for its impeccable timing. What the&amp;nbsp;bank has done is featured its brand ambassador Singh in its limited edition debit cards.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The celebrity image debit card, a first-of-its-kind in the country, gives the bank&amp;#39;s customers and fans of the actor the option to choose from six images of the Bollywood star. The card will be available for customers to order for a limited period till December 31, 2018.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Puneet Kapoor, Senior Executive Vice President, Kotak Mahindra Bank, said, &amp;ldquo;This limited edition debit card gives Ranveer Singh&amp;rsquo;s legion of fans a fantastic opportunity to own a personalised card featuring the actor. We are very conscious of the fact that our customers have diverse interests and our approach at Kotak is to offer a range of exclusive, customised and innovative products and services that provide both emotional and transactional value to our customers.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The OOH duties are&amp;nbsp;being&amp;nbsp;handled by Kinetic India and Madison OOH. This teaser campaign in Mumbai has been executed by Madison OOH.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Ranveer Singh came on board&amp;nbsp;as Kotak Mahindra Bank&amp;rsquo;s brand ambassador in June 2018 and is the face of&amp;nbsp;its #IndiaInvited campaign. The campaign champions inclusive banking and features people from all walks of life, across age, gender, profession, religion, physical appearance, including an acid attack survivor, among others, alongside Singh.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The Singh-featured debit card is linked to a savings account which comes with a number of benefits including up to 6 per cent p.a. interest. In addition, customers get a host of attractive offers/discounts on the debit card across a select set of merchant establishments and ecommerce sites. Furthermore, based on their card spends, customers also stand a chance to meet the superstar.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/92924-cardkotak.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/out-of-home-news/south-ooh-industry-in-doldrums-hopes-pinned-on-hyderabad-chennai-to-drive-spends-92745.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>29/10/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>South OOH industry in doldrums; hopes pinned on Hyderabad, Chennai to drive spends</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;The festive spirit has set in all across India and the media industry is getting busier day by day be it TV programming, increased ad spends and even new campaigns just to coincide with the season&amp;rsquo;s joyous mood. But, the same can&amp;rsquo;t be said about the South OOH industry. Hindrances faced by them started with Onam when Kerala was distressed due to floods and now comes the recent ban of&amp;nbsp;hoardings in Bangalore.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&amp;ldquo;For us this Diwali period is lull and compared to last year, there is a significant downturn. Though we are seeing some very positive consumer sentiments elsewhere, which is translating to good revenues, South has suffered overall and, this festive season is not good for us&amp;nbsp;and I am sure it is the same for others too,&amp;rdquo; said Naresh Bhandari, COO, OMI, the OOH agency arm of Laqshya Media Group. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;Double whammy: Kerala floods and BBMP bylaw&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;The OOH industry in Kerala has been adversely affected by the floods, which wreaked havoc across the state. Just in the months of July-August alone the state&amp;rsquo;s OOH industry suffered a loss of almost&amp;nbsp;Rs 60 crore.&amp;nbsp; According to experts, the industry is estimated to have incurred a loss of Rs 200 crore overall as it is taking a few months now for the business to be back on track completely. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&amp;ldquo;The market is bad and around 45% of the inventories are vacant this Diwali season, this is because the advertisers have a perception that Kerala is totally devastated after the floods. We are now on revive-mode,&amp;rdquo; said &lt;span style="background:white"&gt;Chithra Prakash of Chitra Painters, an OOH player based in Kerala. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;The OOH players in Kerala are hopeful that with Christmas season approaching and the state of Kerala getting back to normalcy, they can bring down, if not completely obliterate, the losses by getting back to business as soon as possible. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;Coming to Bangalore, the BBMP (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="background:whitesmoke"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;Bruhat Bengaluru Mahanagara Palike)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;council has approved a new draft advertising policy titled &amp;lsquo;BBMP Outdoor Signage and Public Messaging, 2018&amp;rsquo; that calls for a ban on all illegal commercial billboards and hoardings in the city. &lt;span style="color:black"&gt;The proposed advertisement policy seeks to benefit advertisers using bus shelters, gantries and skywalks by banning all other sorts of outdoor advertising. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&amp;ldquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;The ban has affected all of us as the move came in during the onset of festive season which would have otherwise contributed us well. The matter is still in court and we aren&amp;rsquo;t very clear on the way forward,&amp;rdquo; said Bhandari. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;Lukewarm hopes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;Diwali is a time of cheer everywhere in South but it&amp;rsquo;s even more prominent in Bangalore due to the cosmopolitan crowd. The recent BBMP ban has hampered the festive spending which is typically around 30-40% of most of the brand&amp;rsquo;s annual budget. During Onam, Kerala gets high on brand visibility and spends, which unfortunately wasn&amp;rsquo;t great this year because of floods. So, it is now Hyderabad and Chennai that would be hopefully driving spends of OOH in South India this Diwali.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;Speaking about expectations this Diwali season, Bhandari said,&lt;b&gt; &amp;ldquo;&lt;/b&gt;Our expectations aren&amp;rsquo;t high because Bangalore contributes the maximum to South revenues and this move by BBMP has hit the South OOH Industry at large. Onam, which is another big occasion, turned sour because of the floods. Chennai with media assets restricted to street furniture would not be very successful to add a fortune to the total South industry pie. Hyderabad seems to be in action but, not sure how would it compensate the losses faced by Bangalore and Kerala. So, overall, our expectations are low.&amp;rdquo; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&amp;ldquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;Our festive specific strategy is to be visible at all key shopping hubs for our retail brands and we also have created customized festive creatives for their OOH campaigns. We have been doing consumer experiential festive campaigns at the Hyderabad Airport too,&amp;rdquo; said Bhandari, speaking on festive strategies given the double whammy of floods and BBMP ban.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:normal"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/92745-bbmpfloods.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/out-of-home-news/mtv-creates-live-billboards-for-ace-of-space-and-elovator-pitch-92685.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>24/10/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>MTV creates live billboards for Ace of Space and Elovator Pitch</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Building on its quirk, wit, and innovation,&amp;nbsp;MTV recently launched a clutter-breaking concept based marketing campaign for two of its latest shows, Ace of Space and Elovator Pitch.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Conceptualised in house and executed by Zenith Outdoors, the billboards bring to life the shows&amp;rsquo; content theme and gives the audience a sneak-peek of what to expect when they tune-in.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking about concept-based outdoors, Ferzad Palia, Head &amp;ndash; Youth, Music and English Entertainment, Viacom18 said, &amp;ldquo;Innovation is core to MTV and It&amp;rsquo;s a way of life for us. With both Ace of Space and Elovator Pitch, we have pushed the envelope for innovative content. Hence, for marketing these unique shows, we have built a concept-based advertising campaign and utilised the high impact medium of billboards that stand out and give a real-life slice of the show&amp;rsquo;s content.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;For the show Ace of Space, the live billboards showcase real people enacting the scenes of being trapped in a small room. Specially designed to bring alive the uniqueness of the show, the billboards went live on October 19 between 5-9 pm and 4-6pm on Sunday at a strategic location in Mumbai.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The hoardings have the anchor Vikas Gupta, shrinking the room with the press of a button causing panic and mayhem amongst the contestants, much like the show &amp;lsquo;Ace of Space&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The billboard for Elovator Pitch anchored by Gaelyn Mendonca makes for an interesting and thought-provoking visual as well. In line with the show&amp;rsquo;s concept where 10 boys try to woo one girl with quick creative thinking while riding a lift between two floors, the hoarding features Cyrus Sahukar in different avatars across each level. Sahukar is a visual reflection of the 10 participants who fight it out for their dream girl&amp;rsquo;s attention.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/92685-mtv.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/out-of-home-news/ooh-has-the-capability-of-driving-online-activity-coo-laqshya-solutions-92542.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>16/10/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>OOH has the capability of driving online activity: COO, Laqshya Solutions</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;DOOH is growing in double digits in other developed countries but, in India it&amp;rsquo;s still at&amp;nbsp;a very nascent stage,&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;says Amarjeet Singh Hudda- COO, Laqshya Solutions, an outdoor agency arm of Laqshya Media Group. According to him, OOH has never demanded a larger pie of the overall advertising chunk primarily because of the inadequacy of audience measurement tools in the industry.&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
In a chat with exchange4media, Hudda&amp;nbsp;spoke about how audience measurement tool increases the accountability of an agency towards a brand, challenges and if the&amp;nbsp;digital medium could be a threat to OOH in the long run. Edited Excerpts:&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are your thoughts on the effectiveness of audience measurement tools and the way in which it is&amp;nbsp;increasing the accountability of an agency towards brands?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Over the years, OOH has never got a larger pie of the advertising chunk primarily because of the lack of&amp;nbsp;audience measurement in this industry. Agencies with in-house tools now are in a better position to&amp;nbsp;offer OOH media solutions and reach advertisers. The measurement tool addresses the brand&amp;rsquo;s&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
objective of reaching out to their desired TG with minimum wastage. They are also equipped to offer&amp;nbsp;them the efficacy of the plan in terms of eye-balls met.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;strong&gt;Do you see OOH increasing its share of the total advertise pie in the coming year? How is Laqshya&amp;nbsp;leading the OOH industry?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Yes. We are hopeful of the change. Research backed strategic plans offered by specialist&amp;nbsp;agencies&amp;nbsp;have given advertisers the confidence on the ROI front which had always been a concern for marketers.&amp;nbsp;Laqshya has been offering such research based scientific plans to our existing clients. Timely monitoring&amp;nbsp;of campaigns and updates to the clients along with regular maintenance of our own media assets are all&amp;nbsp;adding to factors differentiating us from the rest.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;strong&gt;What are your views on digital OOH? Do you think it will make OOH advertising more engaging?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
DOOH is growing in double digits in other developed countries but&amp;nbsp;in India it&amp;#39;s&amp;nbsp;still is in a very nascent&amp;nbsp;stage. Digital Outdoors with content -first approach engages viewers better as compared to a Static&amp;nbsp;Billboard. Having said that, Digital OOH is definitely the growth driver for outdoor. Ambient spaces like&amp;nbsp;airports and malls have been experimenting with DOOH successfully and the results are great.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;What particular challenges is the OOH industry&amp;nbsp;facing and what needs to be done to transform the&amp;nbsp;landscape?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Unlike&amp;nbsp;online ads,&amp;nbsp;Digital OOH does not cause inconvenience to consumers. In fact, a very&amp;nbsp;good creative can be a visual&amp;nbsp;treat for them; with the use of technology it can create innovations to&amp;nbsp;further amplify a&amp;nbsp;brand&amp;rsquo;s communication. Customizing and changing the content to target TG comes in handy with DOOH and, an advertiser can pick their slots as per their budgets wherever possible. DOOH campaigns are far more compelling than a static billboard. Globally, a lot of Innovation using&amp;nbsp;technology such as&amp;nbsp;facial recognition etc has been harnessed to make DOOH far more&amp;nbsp;engaging.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Could the Digital medium&amp;nbsp;be a threat to OOH in the long term?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Digital Medium isn&amp;rsquo;t a threat to the OOH Industry. And, OOH has the capability of driving online activity.&amp;nbsp;OOH coupled with online works well for brands. This has been proved according to a Nielsen study&amp;nbsp;done globally too. Digital is definitely the future, but in a country like ours, it still needs time. A&amp;nbsp;fragmented industry like ours cannot shift to Digital so soon. The change will happen gradually. But, a lot of marketers&amp;nbsp;seeing the value it brings to their brands,&amp;nbsp;will&amp;nbsp;vouch for it and, this&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
demand could soon prove to be&amp;nbsp;a game changer.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/92542-Laqshya.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/out-of-home-news/ooh-festive-spends-expected-to-rise-15-18-from-last-year-92529.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>15/10/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>OOH festive spends expected to rise 15-18% from last year</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;The festive season in India has begun with full gusto, first with&amp;nbsp;the arrival of Ganesh Chaturthi, followed by Navratri,&amp;nbsp;Durga Pujo&amp;nbsp;and Diwali. Right after monsoon ends, this is the time when roads&amp;nbsp;all over the country are adorned with colourful and creative ads&amp;nbsp;in order to grab consumers&amp;rsquo; attention.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;Pleasant weather and celebratory mood among consumers triggers an urge to shop&amp;nbsp;and brands leave no stone unturned to extract maximum value out of this season&amp;nbsp;by promoting their festive offerings and&amp;nbsp;heavy spends on marketing campaigns. In such a scenario, OOH plays a significant role in a brand&amp;rsquo;s communication and this is exactly why OOH business particularly thrives in the last quarter of the year.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;Unlike the previous year, the OOH industry is expecting a huge surge in traffic this year. This can be a great relief for the industry, which is looking to compensate for the losses of last year due to GST and demonetisation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;Amarjeet Singh, COO, Laqshya Solution, said, &amp;ldquo;Today&amp;nbsp;OOH goes where most other media can&amp;rsquo;t go.&amp;nbsp;OOH is everywhere consumers are. The fact that India has one of the highest chunks of millennial population and&amp;nbsp;approximately&amp;nbsp;70% of their waking hours is spent outside, just makes OOH more lucrative for advertisers.&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&amp;ldquo;Marketers heavily ride on the festive fervour&amp;nbsp;and OOH works well to connect them to their TG by&amp;nbsp;being visible at congregations that are relevant to them. OOH follows them at B2B pockets, residential&amp;nbsp;clusters, to the journey to and fro along with all destination points they can possibly visit- be it main&amp;nbsp;arterial roads, malls, movie theatres, coffee shops, airports, and even golf course and&amp;nbsp;grocery shopping. So OOH offers a customised media plan for different TGs,&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;added Singh. Alok Gupta, Graphisads, said, &amp;ldquo;Festive season means&amp;nbsp;traffic snarls, outdoor as a medium always has had an&amp;nbsp;impact value. 2-3 hours of forced viewing helps brands to create an immediate recall value, which leads&amp;nbsp;to impulse purchase decisions.&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;When asked as to how much a&amp;nbsp;brand&amp;rsquo;s marketing spends usually increases during the festive season, he added,&amp;nbsp;&amp;ldquo;Many brands keeps aside as much as 15-20% of their annual budgets for this specific period. You would&amp;nbsp;see many clients that&amp;nbsp;are not visible during the year&amp;nbsp;suddenly come up at the time of festive&amp;nbsp;season.&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;According to Rohan Srinivasan, Chief Marketing and Communication Officer, Vyoma Media, &amp;ldquo;The OOH Industry will hope to get 30-40% of its total revenues this festive season alone. (Country wide) Spends are expected&amp;nbsp;to be&amp;nbsp;significantly up&amp;nbsp;from last year. The very nature of&amp;nbsp;festivals has&amp;nbsp;people gathering together in one place to celebrate, which brands use to their advantage&amp;nbsp;and hence focus on this season in particular. The opportunity to target a vast audience, increased visibility for products by localising content&amp;nbsp;reaps&amp;nbsp;rewards by transforming into&amp;nbsp;eventual sales.&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;&amp;ldquo;We are very optimistic and are looking at a sizeable growth when compared to last year. Previously, the&amp;nbsp;whole industry was affected by GST and demonetisation,&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;he added.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;quot;OOH is the only impact creation option in the entire communication chain&amp;quot;, said&amp;nbsp;Charanjeet Singh&amp;nbsp;Arora, CO-CEO- India, Kinetic India. &amp;ldquo;No other media delivers the impact which OOH can deliver because&amp;nbsp;of its size, and OOH is always the last mile media in consumer marketing so, if you plan and place OOH&amp;nbsp;well, it helps brands with higher ROI,&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;he pointed out.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
A brand&amp;rsquo;s marketing spend&amp;nbsp;purely depends on the brand&amp;#39;s priorities and product. &amp;ldquo;Like for automobile,&amp;nbsp;white goods, jewelry, clothing and lifestyle products, Diwali is the peak sales period. All brands keep&amp;nbsp;aside a festival budget&amp;nbsp;for this&amp;nbsp;period depending on&amp;nbsp;specific priorities for instance&amp;nbsp;which region matters&amp;nbsp;more&amp;nbsp;for which festival and then, brands spend likewise. All brands keep a consistency of presence in target&amp;nbsp;priority markets and they create spike of media presence during big festivals. Spending goes up as high&amp;nbsp;as even 100% for few product categories,&amp;quot; explained Charanjeet Singh Arora.&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;ldquo;Typically consumer-focused brands hike their spends substantially. There are brands that spend&amp;nbsp;30-40%&amp;nbsp;of their annual budget specifically during OND (October, November, December)&amp;nbsp;quarter,&amp;quot; said Amarjeet Singh.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;The industry at large believes that this festive year will be positive for them in terms of budget. Gupta&amp;nbsp;said, &amp;ldquo;This year, we are hoping that the outdoor industry shall recover the losses of past 2-3 years of sluggishness. Availability issues for&amp;nbsp;getting key locations&amp;nbsp;for clients have begun. Since outdoor media is so&amp;nbsp;location-specific, important areas have already been booked.&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Fira Sans;"&gt;Since media occupancy is going up, Gupta&amp;nbsp;expects an overall 20-25% spurt in the top line this year, as compared to&amp;nbsp;the last year. Haresh Nayak, Managing Director, Postercope, said, &amp;ldquo;Historically we have seen a&amp;nbsp;10-12% increase during festivities. Given that last year spends were adversely affected due to the policy&amp;nbsp;changes, we see a possible increase of 15-18% as compared to last year.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;ldquo;We should see a healthy double-digit growth. An overall growth of&amp;nbsp;approximately 10% compared to last year is what we all expect,&amp;quot; said Amarjeet Singh.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/92529-festival_logo.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/out-of-home-news/vyoma-media-wins-digital-outdoor-advertising-mandate-for-tvs-victor-92377.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>04/10/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Vyoma Media wins Digital Outdoor Advertising mandate for TVS Victor</news:title>
      <news:description>Vyoma Media, the out of home digital solutions company, has won the Digital Outdoor Advertising mandate for TVS Victor.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;TVS Victors new model will be the first bike in its segment to feature a unique Daytime Running Lamp (DRL), along with a host of other class leading features. Vyoma Media will aim to build on the massive affinity towards the TVS brand by engaging consumers through their smart dispays at ticket counters across the Kolkata Metro and Bihar railway stations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first phase of TVS Victors Badi Bhi Badhiya Bhi campaign will be for a duration of two months and then will be seen across other markets.&lt;br&gt;The multi-lingual creatives, in English, Hindi and Bengali, will play simultaneously across locations and will allow consumers a chance to win the brand new TVS Victor bike.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This campaign will take content localisation to the next level by not only displaying content in the three languages but also delivering the resulting SMS on the viewers mobile phones in the same language as shown in the creative they have responded to. Further consumer engagement will be ensured when the consumer is redirected to the brands Facebook page to participate in a contest to win more goodies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kendraj Joshi, Head  Commuter Motorcycles Marketing, said, We wanted to come up with a unique campaign with a focus on interactive and localised creatives. This initial phase, with Vyomas intelligent displays at eye-level at the ticket counters, allows us to integrate and amplify the brands campaign across two key markets. It will also ensure our brand loyalists are aware of our new innovative bike features and help us maintain our unrivalled market presence. The second phase of the campaign will be across cities in Karnataka, Maharashtra and Telangana.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1538659496_P6TNCI_TVS_Victor_Campaigns_on_Vyoma_Displays.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/out-of-home-news/edelweiss-leverages-ooh-media-forbeunlimited-campaign-92227.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>24/09/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Edelweiss leverages OOH media for #BeUnlimited campaign</news:title>
      <news:description>Edelweiss is going&amp;nbsp;all out in OOH media using innovations to drive its recent campaign themed #BeUnlimited"&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commenting on the campaign, Shabnam Panjwani, Head Marketing &amp;amp; Communication, Edelweiss Group, said, The objective was to bring out the #BeUnlimited spirit of the athletes that resonates with Edelweiss. Every time these athletes play in the world arena, they play as one team, for one country, with one vision. Through this outdoor campaign based on the theme - &lt;em&gt;koi bhi limit, limit nahi hoti &lt;/em&gt;Edelweiss salutes the untiring spirit of Team India.&amp;nbsp;We firmly believe that OOH, if done innovatively, commands attention, while building on overall campaign memorability specially for multimedia campaigns. OOH innovations are a marketers weapon and have been used by brands across product categories. Clutter-breaking innovations help drive buzz, create awareness, build brand recall and make a concept come alive, especially in sporting events like the Asian Games  full of action, glory and pride. The right innovation can give a fillip to ones campaign And Team Headsail Media Services Pvt Ltd. has proved it by conceptualising and executing the innovations for Edelweiss."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vijay Jain  Founder &amp;amp; CEO of Headsail Media Services Pvt. Ltd., says, "Marketing is not always about doing ad extensive campaign, sometimes you must break the shackles, come up with some breakthrough innovative strategy and execution. The future of OOH will be defined by innovations, So we came up with path-breaking innovative campaign. The idea was to give life to the creative that would relate to professional sports of the athletes, innovatively on the billboard. It is delighted to have the opportunity to work with such renowned brand like Edelweiss."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Credits:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Client Servicing Director  Kavita Sabherwal &lt;br&gt;Creative Director  Rajesh Khanna&lt;br&gt;Media Planning  Smita Patade&lt;br&gt;Buying &amp;amp; Execution  Chirag Jain&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://we.tl/t-jHFgeZSiEc</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1537786157_m7b4J5_Edelweiss.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/out-of-home-news/kerala-floodsooh-industry-faces-loss-of-rs-200crneed-6-months-to-recoverexperts-91958.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>10/09/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Kerala Floods: OOH industry faces loss of Rs 200cr, need 6 months to recover: Experts</news:title>
      <news:description>The state of Kerala and its economy is limping back to normalcy after the floods which devastated the state just few days ago. Reportedly, the disaster claimed around 400 lives and the state has incurred a loss of about Rs 21,000 crore overall. As a result of the flood, all the industries and businesses in the state have been affected quite adversely, that it was the Onam festive season, when advertising spends are at peak, made things even worse. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Onam, which marks the beginning of festive season in the country, is also a time when the entire marketing focus of not just local but even national brands shifts to Kerala. The advertising spends by brands witness a considerable rise during this season. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the most widely affected media industries during the flood in Kerala was the Out Of Home (OOH) industry as there was severe loss of ad inventory and devastation of infrastructure across the state.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to industry experts, the OOH industry has incurred a loss of almost&amp;nbsp;Rs 60 crore, just during the months of July-August. Overall, industry is estimated to incur a loss of Rs 200 crore as it will take 4-6 months for things to normalise. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;K Vijayakumar, President, Kerala Advertising Industries Association said, Onam season is a peak time for the OOH industry in terms of revenue and this year due to heavy rainfall and floods about 50 per cent of the campaigns were cancelled. Most of the hoardings remain vacant in the city. But the losses incurred by the OOH industry is due to clients backing off and campaign cancellations and not because of the destruction of properties. In fact, the hoardings and billboards are intact as there was less wind in the flood affected areas.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sreekumar PV, Secretary, Kerala Advertising Industries Association said, The flood has hit he OOH industry very severely and it will take minimum 4-6 months to resume business. Clients backed off from the campaigns as it doesnt seem sensible to run an advertisement campaign when the whole state of Kerala is suffering. But they have promised that they will come back to us when the state attains normalcy. The industry loss approximately will be Rs 200 crore, as the industry will be idle for another 4-6 months.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Firstly, it is very unfortunate that the state of Kerala has gone through a disaster like this, which claimed several lives. In terms of business, its a tough time for the OOH industry in the state as most of the spends in Kerala happens during the festive season. 50-60 % of spends happens during the months of August-September alone. Campaigns got postponed due to the calamity and an approximate loss of Rs 50-60 crore has occurred in these last two months alone, said Haresh Nayak, Regional Director, Posterscope APAC &amp;amp; Managing Director, Posterscope Group.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Kerala OOH industry has a turnover of almost Rs 350 crore per year of which Onam season alone accounts 45 per cent. &lt;br&gt;  &lt;br&gt;Speaking to exchange4media, Chithra Prakash of Chitra Painters, one of the initial players in the OOH industry in Kerala, said, The flood has affected the OOH industry of the state very badly. When the intensity of rain increased, and the situation was going out of hands, most of my clients backed off from the Onam campaigns. My firm alone incurred a loss of Rs 5-6 crore.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;OOH within the city limits were not affected by the rains. But places like Perumbavoor, Aluva, Paravoor, Thodupuzha, Chengannur, Ranni etc were severely affected by the rains and this has reflected in the OOH campaigns as well. The areas surrounding the Cochin International Airport is another important spot for the OOH industry in the Ernakulam district, and the closing down of airport for a few days also turned out to be a prime reason for cancelling of OOH campaigns by the clients. My estimate is that the OOH industry in Kerala has to face an approximate loss of Rs 150-200 crore, added Prakash. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even when the OOH industry is badly affected, the players didnt stop themselves from helping the flood victims, they were actively involved in flood relief activities. The Kerala Advertising Industries Association has distributed around 2000 essential food kits to the flood victims in Alapuzha district and is also involved in other flood relief work, added Sreekumar. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state is now slowly limping back to normalcy. According to me the state and the OOH industry is slowly getting back on track, added Nayak&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to all industry experts we spoke with, the OOH industry in Kerala will now take minimum 4-6 months to get back to its feet. Now the OOH players are pinning their hope on the Christmas season, which accounts to about 25-30 per cent of the revenue for the year.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1536550573_Ye8Ec7_Kerala_Flood.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/out-of-home-news/need-of-the-hour-is-a-national-ooh-policycharanjeet-aroraceokinetic-advertising-91922.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>07/09/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Need of the hour is a national OOH policy: Charanjeet Arora, CEO, Kinetic Advertising</news:title>
      <news:description>Kinetic India recently promoted Charanjeet Arora and Rachana Lokhande as new Co-CEOs of Kinetic Advertising&amp;nbsp;India Pvt. Ltd.. This follows the resignation of Suresh Balakrishna, CEO, South Asia and Middle East. Arora has been working with Kinetic Advertising&amp;nbsp;India since November 2017.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We spoke to him about his views on the OOH medium, measures companies must take to promote programmatic digital OOH across markets and growth of DOOH in the near future.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Edited Excerpts:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OOH as a medium to connect in non-metro cities:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arora says, OOH has always been a key media in local markets and has played a vital role. Telecom, Retail, Education, Real Estate, Automobile sectors have always used OOH as the key media in non-metros. There are many advantages of OOH in non-metros, which has always encouraged brands to advertise in OOH space."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The reasons for this he says is Low cost of media, Contextual placement and Customised communication at key touch points. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Majority of brands use OOH in non-metros to promote sales schemes, which immediately converts into numbers, so, in a way non metro clients understand the power of media well and believe in ROI," he says.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Programmatic digital OOH across markets&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to him, programmatic will help media owners to earn maximum revenue and utilisation of inventory. Automation is the future of every business and technologies across the globe are redefining business and enhancing efficiencies. It is high time for large OOH media owners to automate availability and publish card rates on their sites," Arora says.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Changes needed in the OOH space&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;He perceives digital formats as the future of OOH business, but highlights that the present method of printing flex is not eco-friendly and whatever is not eco friendly is not going to be there for long."&lt;br&gt;Digital media will ensure transparency; speed of execution and digital formats are definitely more dynamic and can accommodate multiple creatives.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;He sees regularisation and standardisation of OOH formats across markets, and says, theres more transparency in OOH business. He also admits, There is a possibility of national OOH policy, which is the need of the hour."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Major OOH companies are partnering in infrastructure growth of India through BOOT models and working with governments and to build a smarter India by creating international design BQS and more public facilities in Tier 1 and Tier 2 towns," he adds.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How Kinetic ensures high ROI&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arora explained how Kinetic ensures maximum ROI to the buyer on their platform. Data, Technology and Content are the future of the media business. Kinetic uses its patented global tool Aureus, in planning, which is scientific and ensures most accurate planning and therefore, maximum return of investment. Kinetic uses AIM scoring to select the best sites for brands, based on brand requirements and the market."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Because of the sheer size and volume, we get best the deals in the OOH space and we ensure we pass on the benefits to our esteemed clients. We are transparent to the core and ensure fair dealing at all levels; the idea is to deliver best to our clients. We believe in creating values for brands associated with us," says Arora.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DOOH as a medium of the future&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;When asked as to how he sees the growth of DOOH as a medium in the future, he says, DOOH would grow at high pace in the coming years and this will help in better digital integrations. Consumer behaviours are changing fast and the way consumers consume media is also changing rapidly. Mobile has become a major media and digital OOH would help brands connect with consumers on mobile by using smart integrations and through innovative OOH+ Mobile interface."</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1536286248_GISJSH_Charanjeet.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/out-of-home-news/technology-will-secure-the-future-of-oohchairman-mdselvel-one-91899.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>06/09/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Technology will secure the future of OOH: Chairman &amp; MD, Selvel One</news:title>
      <news:description>There are hardly any brands that do not advertise on OOH, says Noomi Mehta, Chairman and Managing Director of Selvel One. The new LED screens add the touch of glamour to a medium that has long been the workhorse of the advertising world, he says.&amp;nbsp;Technology is a friend to OOH. It adds flexibility and gives a creative boost to the medium. Technology will secure the future of OOH around the world. &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a conversation with exchange4media, Mehta talks about the various aspects of OOH advertising and why it is crucial for brands.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Edited excerpts:&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;What are your views on digital OOH? Do you think it will become a huge growth driver for the OOH industry?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;All over the world, digital has taken a disproportionate share of the OOH media pie. And this has not happened by cannibalising&amp;nbsp;the classic OOH media, but through a quantum jump in the share of OOH in the overall media pie. I see no reason why the India story should be any different. In fact, given the density of population in cities, the growth story should be even more dramatic. By and large, just&amp;nbsp;5 to 7 per cent of&amp;nbsp;digital OOH expenditure&amp;nbsp;is equivalent to&amp;nbsp;nearly&amp;nbsp;50 per cent of the total OOH expenditure. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What changes do you think technology will bring about in the OOH landscape?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Technology has been a disruption for media. Newspapers and magazines all over the world have suffered a sharp decline in their hard copy formats and subsequently their advertising support, and have been forced to adapt IoT as they moved online. Television too has come under enormous pressure. Channels are suffering as players like Amazon, Netflix, Facebook, YouTube and Hotstar have become the preferred medium for viewing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Technology is a friend to OOH. It adds flexibility, colour and immediacy via latest hardware and helps place advertisements better by automatically changing products and creatives to match the audience. It has given a creative boost to the medium.&amp;nbsp;Studies have shown that the efficacy of digital advertising increases substantially when bolstered by on OOH campaign. The medium cannot be zapped, switched or silenced as it cannot be manipulated by bots, clicks and automation. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The efficiency of buying OOH has increased dramatically with the use of technology. Technology can give an idea of the reach, frequency and likelihood of seeing as cameras capture eye movements, pauses and even smiles when ads are viewed. Predictive analysis on movements, passageways and destinations make it possible to pinpoint the ads that have&amp;nbsp;actually influenced people&amp;nbsp;and contributed to sale. This gives the marketers an invaluable ally and tool in evaluating and allocating market spends. This may take a while to percolate into the Indian market, but when it does catch on, it will spread like wildfire. Yes, technology will secure the future of OOH around the world.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Is the OOH domain bringing more brands into its fold? What is your particular experience in this regard?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are hardly any brands that do not advertise on OOH. The new LED screens add the touch of glamour to a medium that has long been the workhorse of the advertising world. The final barrier of resistance to OOH will crumble with the drama, effect and impact that giant LED screens can provide. Once clients get to experience the effectiveness of the medium, the market will explode.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What do you think is the impact of advertising on the street?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fact that all other media uses OOH&amp;nbsp;shows its impact. When you think of the world's largest brands, you automatically remember their OOH campaigns -- Coca-Cola, Pepsi, Google, Samsung, Apple, and Amazon. In fact, Netflix has bought off OOH companies along the West Coast of USA to advertise their own programmes! Need we say more?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How does Selvel provide leverage to brands in terms of visibility, reach and recall?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Visibility and reach are in-built in every location that we own. Over the years, we have pioneered almost every size and format in OOH-- from monopoles to backlit, to halogen lighting and then to metal halides. We put up street lamps, created parks and even engineered and financed a traffic signal system in a major city. We pioneered LED screens 15 years ago to provide reach and visibility with a variety of options.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Any challenges that you face in the Indian OOH scenario? &lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;The problems we face are the same as others in different parts of the country. There is a belief that billboards cause danger to motorists. Sadly not a single study has ever proven any link, even casually, between OOH media and accidents. In fact, the major accidents in the country are on highways! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We at IOAA are trying to get a model code approved by the Ministry of Urban Affairs so that the basic guidelines can be universally adapted with changes for local peculiarities. Every municipal corporation interprets OOH differently with some by-laws that govern our business dating back to the days of our independence! And of course every commissioner who takes charge automatically knows everything there is to know about OOH without even bothering to study the industry. So changes keep happening in rules and regulations every time there is a change in the top executive of a municipal body. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;New OOH needs time and this requires stability and long-term contracts. Given proper encouragement, OOH can contribute substantially to the city infrastructure. We have already proven that we are better than the government in maintaining civic infrastructure entrusted to us on BOOT basis. Smart cities need smart OOH and that means large investments.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1536204547_6TfZ1g_Noomi-Mehta.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/out-of-home-news/time-outdoor-monitoring-analyses-category-trends-for-the-first-two-quarters-of-2018-91795.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>28/08/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Time Outdoor Monitoring analyses category trends for the first two quarters of 2018</news:title>
      <news:description>Third party data is the cornerstone for all OOH companies and brands in getting scientific analysis and measurement. Third party monitoring agency, Time Outdoor Monitoring, tracks OOH spends, monitors outdoor campaigns and tracks the effectiveness of spends. The report is based on PAN India analysis across 42 cities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When analysing OOH spends, it is important to understand which categories are competing in the OOH market. Be it direct or indirect competition, one can obtain a fair perspective regarding the activities of various categories in the OOH space. It can be used as a tool and can be applied in many contexts and at many scales, and may be applied to an individual brand as well as the whole category.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top categories which highlight themselves in first two quarters as per spends and share of space are showcased below:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TOP 20 CATEGORIES IN THE MONTH OF JANUARY TO MARCH 2018&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/files/1535454894_D4CsJx_Graph-01.jpg"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/files/1535454894_tQgKUz_table-01.jpg"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;The data does not cover transit media airport, malls, inside railway stations and kiosks. Rates are indicative figure and subject to negotiation.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the above data chart and table all the categories mentioned are competing in terms of spends and share of space.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Share of expenditure&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Real estate and builders category with their huge budget is leading the first quarter of the year 2018 with spends of Rs 1456.85 million and with share of space 96,82,131 square feet. Jewellery/Jewellery Shops category taking second spot with spends of Rs 428.95 million and share of space of 31,30,139 square feet. Showrooms/Shopping malls category in third spot with 416.33 million and share of space of 32,74,849 square feet.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smartphone users are on the rise in India. This has interested a lot of mobile companies around the globe to highlight themselves in the form of OOH media and this is especially true in case of Xiaomi Corporation, one of the most popular Chinese brand among smart phone users in India have never used the OOH medium to market their products and only recently have moved into the OOH space owing to their sheer popularity and customer base in India. Similarly, there is huge customer base for all the car segments from luxury to mid-size to compact cars. Given the vast number of people travelling on road today gives four wheeler companies an opportunity to introduce their new car models or highlight the already popular ones through OOH medium to reach the masses. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;January to March being the final quarter of the financial year makes salaried individuals and business houses file their tax returns. This period witnesses a significant increase in life insurance and mutual fund investments. No wonder, life insurance and mutual fund companies maximise their spends during this period.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall there are many emerging categories and regular players in the first quarter.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Share of Space (Square feet)&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As compared to share of expenditure, we can see similar trend followed by categories in the Share of Space segment. Real estate category leads in top position and Showrooms/Shopping malls category taking second position with little more coverage in terms of square feet than Jewellery category.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Remaining category rankings stay more or less similar compared to their share of expenditure.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TOP 20 CATEGORIES IN THE MONTH OF APRIL TO JUNE 2018&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/files/1535454894_E8asTS_graphh-02.jpg"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/files/1535454894_rrykfG_table-02.jpg"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;The data does not cover transit media airport, malls, inside railway stations and kiosks. Rates are indicative figure and subject to negotiation.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Compared to previous quarter&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spends of the current quarter (Apr-Jun) has slightly decreased from the previous quarter but still in both quarters Real Estate category reclaims its first spot. June being prime time for all the school and colleges to reopen, the education institute category maximises its spends taking a huge leap from ninth to second position moving ahead of Jewellery/Jewellery Shops category from the previous quarter. April and May being the vacation months in India, all shopping malls and showrooms are the frequently visited hence it has retained its third position from the earlier quarter.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Air conditioner/Air cooler, Apparels/Garment, Soft drink, Undergarments and Footwear categories are the new entrants in the list for the second quarter of the year. Political party, film ads, Housing finance, Hotels/Resort and Mutual fund category did not make it to the list.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1535455332_uRNZw7_Time_Outdoor_Monitoring.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/out-of-home-news/unreasonable-pricing-is-a-big-challenge-for-ooh-industrydirectorgraphisads-91757.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>27/08/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Unreasonable pricing is a big challenge for OOH industry: Director, Graphisads</news:title>
      <news:description>Alok Gupta, Director of OOH agency Graphisads, believes that there are ample opportunities to transform the OOH&amp;nbsp;sector&amp;nbsp;now as traditional media owners have finally started looking at digital aspect of the domain. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to Gupta, one the biggest challenges that the medium faces is unreasonable pricing. Gupta says that Delhi has become too expensive a market for a client to execute outdoor campaigns. exchange4media caught up with him to talk about the changes that one can see in the OOH landscape in the near future, his views on DOOH and more.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here are the edited excerpts:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are the major changes that you expect to see in the OOH landscape with the advent of new technologies?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is a lot of correlation between digital and out of home as both are hyper local in nature. In future, we can see a lot of social media companies integrating with outdoor advertising agencies and offering new opportunities to client for interacting with end consumers. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Is the OOH domain bringing more brands into its fold? What is your experience in this regard?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indeed, a lot of new clients are coming into outdoor. But, at the same point, a lot of clients have also started to leave the industry because of unreasonable pricing. For instance, Delhi has become too expensive a market for clients to execute outdoor campaigns. Somewhere down the line, media owners need to realise that clients budget is not increasing. Only media owners payments to the authority have increased. At our end, we try and pick outdoor media at judicious prices and offer the same to our clients at reasonable rates. Further, we also&amp;nbsp;struggle with the fact that there is no data about outdoor medium. It is an irony that in a market with more than 10 crore televisions,&amp;nbsp;  20,000 BARC boxes (sample size of .000002%) help media planners and buyers decide on a budget of more than Rs 30,000 crores per annumm.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are your views on Digital OOH? Going forward, do you think it will become a huge growth driver for the OOH industry?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is actually digital 2.0 scenario for out of home industry. Ten years ago, many players, including OOH media, tried to offer digital to clients but could not succeed. However, with new clients coming in with a lot of global perspective, digital is gaining ground. At the same time, traditional media owners have also started to look at digital media opportunities and even authorities are willing to offer long-term contracts. Over a period of decade, we could expect a significant movement towards digital out of home.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tell us about Graphisads journey so far? What interesting things can we see this year?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our journey at Graphisads has been great. We have always had a decent market share in Delhi and offer media to our clients at economical rates. The first turning point for our organisation was the 2010 Commonwealth Games, wherein we bagged a project to create street furniture infrastructure in Delhi that helped us get noticed in the industry. Now again, we have some new projects lined up-- one of which is for the creation of public cycle sharing system in New Delhi. We are hoping that this project will become the talk of the town. At the same time, we are expanding to other markets such as Bhopal, UP, Haryana. Primarily, we're looking at long-term projects on BOT basis.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Any tips youd like to give to the clients for outdoor campaigns?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are some factors that clients should keep in mind while doing outdoor campaigns. Since the time is very limited, the creative for outdoor should be different from other mediums. We still see a lot of clients making the mistake of cut-copy-paste print ads in outdoor. For example, digital outdoor is a specialised domain and clients should consult with outdoor specialists, be it media owner or media agencies, who are experienced enough to handle their budgets. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a media vehicle, outdoor is always open to experimentation and innovations. Hence, we always try and suggest our clients to keep 10-15 % of the budget aside for innovation as it can double the impact of the campaign. Last but not the least, clients need to shed their know-it-all persona and be willing to learn more about this industry. For instance, in Delhi market, we still see that a lot of campaigns either happen in South Delhi or Gurgaon. But Delhi&amp;nbsp;today is much different from what it was 20 years ago. The spending capacity of people in North-West-East Delhi is much more than South now! We need to move out from perceptions and look at ground realities. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where do you see the OOH industry in India five years from now? Do you think digital media has affected the domain?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;I see a lot of consolidations happening,&amp;nbsp;as many&amp;nbsp;smart cities are coming up now. Outdoor is being seen as a serious revenue generation opportunity. It shall also help the industry since contracts are expected to be for longer period. However, it implies that there shall be some sort of consolidation wherein 80 per cent market will be controlled by 20 per cent players and vice versa. We aim to be one of the 20 per cent players. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I dont think that digital media has affected our domain, but I do think that when digital outdoor will come into play, there shall be great synergies with digital media and we will be able to cater to a lot of new clientele in future.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1535338527_Fj1ogt_graphisads_image.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/out-of-home-news/digital-ooh-is-hot-cake-and-everybody-wants-itharesh-nayakposterscope-india-91676.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>21/08/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Digital OOH is hot cake and everybody wants it: Haresh Nayak, Posterscope India</news:title>
      <news:description>Posterscope India has completed 10 years in the country and coincidentally Haresh Nayak, Regional Director, Posterscope Asia Pacific, Managing Director, Posterscope Group India has also completed 10 years with the company. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nayak currently heads operations under the Dentsu Aegis Network (DAN) umbrella for Posterscope (OOH), Brandscope (OOH), Ambient OOH, Hyperspace (Retail), InDeed (CSR Advisory) and C-LAB (Celebrity &amp;amp; Sports Management).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Watch the video here or read the excerpts below&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/jqC23JREzyg" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;On the 10-year journey &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nayak joined the company on 25 August 2008. When I joined Posterscope India, Ashish Bhasin and I weren't even aware of how things would be. The journey was little rough at the start during the 2008 global financial crisis, but the journey has been remarkable and it's largely due to the kind of people we have and my mentor- Ashish Bhasin, Nayak shared. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;He further added, In 2009, we launched Hyperspace and later in 2013, we launched InDeed services. Today, we have services across retail, ambient, out of home, sports, celebrity management, CSR and smart city solutions. The latest entrant would be digital out of home as a separate service within the Posterscope Group Network." &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two values that I really imbibed during this journey is being agile and constantly reinventing yourself. I think as a company we made a brand relevant for the industry, for the clients and our media partners. We started Posterscope India with 11 people and today we have 180 people on board. The company is continuously growing on an average of 30-40 percent year on year for last ten years. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Challenges in the OOH space&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nayak believes that there are quite a few challenges that agencies face such as, data, numbers and accuracy. The larger issue that the industry is facing today is professionalism as there are no trade barriers, unlike television and print. He mentioned, We need larger players and investment into the domain which will bring professionalism, quality, and analytical capabilities. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We started an initiative way back in 2014 and in 2016 where we cracked the entire piece on how to bring in ROI and data into the industry. We are little ahead from our competitors when it comes to giving the ROI in the out of home business. Today we have global software and tools which can tell you where your target audience is, what they are searching and what kind of media options you need to take, shared Nayak.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Out-of-home is one of the oldest mediums and Nayak thinks that the industry has great scope to evolve and grow. Yes we started with out-of-home advertising, but today we position ourselves as location-based marketing specialists. Because the moment I became a location-based expert the horizon actually broadened. In Asia, where the market is growing between 7-10 per cent, globally, the industry is growing at 2-3 percent. I think we are in a much better space when it comes to the medium. In 2013, we bought Milestone, that itself talks about our group's belief in the medium.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Size of OOH industry in India &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The size of the outdoor industry is dependable because there are various numbers which keep floating. Official numbers talk about Rs 3000 crore industry but our report and analysis say that the industry size is around 5000 crore and it is continuously growing and that's a great space to be in and it will grow 7-8 percent year on year. Though our advertising industry is small. Chinas OOH industry is equaled to Indias OOH industry. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Future of Digital OOH&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nayak believes that Digital OOH is "hot cake" and everybody wants it, but he thinks it is important to first understand what digital OOH is. He elaborated, For us, digital out-of-home is not just about digital screens. Apart from the display, it is also important to have engagement. If you look at the overall digital market, in the last two years time, the screens have grown from 15,000-20,000 to 70,000 screens. The number of screens have gone up."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;From non-connecting screens, around about 5 percent to almost 60 percent screens are connected today. So, programmatic becomes another avenue for our clients to explore, that is why as an agency we are taking some position there and connecting the screens and making a platform for everyone to use programmatic.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Programmatic advertising will bring accuracy and optimisation in spends. That's the area which will grow in the next three years. I believe in the next 5-10 years, the digital OOH industry would grow the fastest and it will roughly be around 20-25 per cent of the overall industry pie. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Next for Posterscope India&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nayak believes that today Posterscope India positioned as a location-based marketing specialist, gives them an immense opportunity to grow. "In the next 10 years, I see a growth at 30-40 per cent. I see a bright future in Smart City Solutions given the government's initiative to modernise the cities. There is a lot of opportunity in digital OOH. It is an initiative we are taking globally and also in India. I believe we are a little ahead of the curve, because we are connected to 28,000 screens out of those 70,000. The third area of growth is optimisation of OOH and bringing in data and technology into the business and I think automation is driving our business to a very large extent. Three key factors that are going to drive the business are data, technology, and infrastructure," he said.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1534821388_H57ZAN_haresh_Nayak.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/out-of-home-news/posterscope's-campaign-for-brand-behrouz-is-a-lesson-in-quick-but-intensive-marketing-91659.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>20/08/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Posterscope's campaign for Brand Behrouz is a lesson in quick but intensive marketing</news:title>
      <news:description>Don't blame Delhiites if they suddenly stop in the middle of the roads, even in the midst of bustling traffic. It is to be blamed on tempting posters of Behrouz Biryani that have been put up across various locations in the national capital by Faasos Foods. The campaign has been executed by Posterscope India and was rolled out on several commercial routes, and lip-smacking biryani pictures can largely be seen on billboards, bus shelters, gantries and metro pillars. The campaign tagline conveys the message, A Biryani that was worth a war, is definitely worth a try."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Haresh Nayak, CEO, Posterscope, says, The purpose of the campaign was to improve brand awareness and communicate the 2000-year-old legacy of the brand. The target group was NCCS A/B in the age-group of 28-45. The sites selected were best-suited to cater to this demographic."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the campaign in its second week, the agency used certain creatives for further promotion. Given the regal positioning of the brand, we used a Persian setup for our ads. The theme was that of a royal decor with the product at the centerpiece. We used our bestsellers  Dum Gosht Biryani, Lazeez Bhuna Murgh Biryani and Zaikedaar Paneer Biryani- in our creatives," says Nayak on the appealing visuals.The agency also adopted a few innovations before the roll out of the campaign, which helped them to embellish the message. For instance, the brand used Product Focused Innovations- smoke emitting out of a biryani plate to demonstrate the hot and fresh aspect and Brand Focused Innovations to backlit the brand logo on billboards and illuminated brand punch line placed above the bus shelters. Various innovations were executed. In addition to on-ground impact, these innovations helped us create an impact on social media. We were trending on Twitter for three days during the campaign said Nayak. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The agency is now assessing the impact of the campaign through its proprietary tool, OOHZONE. "The campaign has been received exceedingly well in the market. We have seen a 5x growth during the campaign period, which has sustained since then. We have moved a step towards associating biryani with the Behrouz brand. As a result, Behrouz search volumes are now larger than biryani search volumes in the campaign markets," added Nayak.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1534737322_didfIw_Nehru-Place.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/out-of-home-news/smart-movenetflix-uses-existing-sacred-games-billboards-to-promote-next-original-&#13;
-91641.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>17/08/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Smart move, Netflix!: Uses existing Sacred Games billboards to promote next original &#13;
</news:title>
      <news:description>After setting&amp;nbsp;benchmark with Sacred Games, Netflix India is all set to launch its second&amp;nbsp;original series Ghoul on August 24.&lt;br&gt;As a run up to the airing, Netflix is&amp;nbsp;going all out&amp;nbsp;with&amp;nbsp;its promotions now, particularly with OOH. The online streaming service&amp;nbsp;has used Sacred Games billboards to promote the&amp;nbsp;upcoming horror miniseries. 'The Bloody Ghoul' symbol has been sprayed on Sacred Games billboards across the city.&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/files/1534475228_Xbxhke_ghoulinside.jpg" style="width:400px;height:265px;float:right"&gt;Kinetic India is the OOH agency for Netflix while&amp;nbsp;its digital creative mandate is handled by&amp;nbsp;The Glitch.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ghoul is a&amp;nbsp;horror mini-series created by Patrick Graham. It stars Radhika Apte and Manav Kaul. &lt;br&gt;Jason Blum is serving as producer through his banner, Blumhouse Productions&amp;nbsp;and Anurag Kashyap is producing it under his banner, Phantom Films. In February 2018, Netflix acquired the film and turned it into a miniseries. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The story revolves around a newly-minted military interrogator who arrives at a covert detention center to discover that some of the terrorists held there are not of this world.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;iframe frameborder="0" height="315" src="https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/zg0N4L4mwFk?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" width="100%"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;iframe frameborder="0" height="315" src="https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/Kwqayc6tDPY?rel=0&amp;wmode=transparent" width="100%"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1534475199_tW8xCN_Netflix-GHOUL.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/out-of-home-news/nescafe-romances-mumbaikars-with-new-ooh-campaign-91421.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>02/08/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Nescaf romances Mumbaikars with new OOH campaign</news:title>
      <news:description>Nescafe&amp;nbsp;coffee is back to make a statement yet again with its new OOH campaign 'Badal Life Ki Raftaar this monsoon.&amp;nbsp;Cliched it might be, but rains, romance and a hot cuppa coffee always go hand-in-hand.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/files/1533212513_BXM5OY_Kim.jpg"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Executed by Street Talk, this time the&amp;nbsp;brand solely chose&amp;nbsp;the OOH medium,&amp;nbsp;considering its TG. The objective of the innovation was to spread the message that You cant guzzle a hot drink, it has to be taken slowly (making it the perfect way to measure out breaks) and while youre sipping and blowing and waiting for that optimum comfortable drinking temperature, you can inhale the warmth of the aromatic vapours.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/files/1533212491_oTzrB7_Cycle.jpg"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lot of insights were put in place to arrive at the pockets that would have the best impact on the potential consumers. The agency studied the best permutation and combination with media price, site visibility potential and the best of site characteristics to arrive at the media placements specifically addressing the right TG.&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/files/1533212501_aWywNK_Umbrella.jpg"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The highlight of the campaign was the innovative steaming Cup of Coffee, strategically placed at high traffic zones across multiple locations to attract significant eyeballs. The billboard featured a coffee mug,&amp;nbsp;emulating steam from a freshly brewed cup of coffee.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;The cluster approach at key junctions aided immediate buzz and high visibility for&amp;nbsp;Nescafe.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/files/1533212529_m5bfEx_Laptop.jpg"&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1533293499_bwqoHp_Nescafe.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/out-of-home-news/wpp's-kinetic-india-promotes-rachana-lokhande-and-charanjeet-singh-arora-to-co-ceos-91264.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>25/07/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>WPP's Kinetic India promotes Rachana Lokhande and Charanjeet Singh Arora to Co-CEOs</news:title>
      <news:description>Kinetic India has promoted&amp;nbsp;Rachana Lokhande and Charanjeet Singh Arora to Co-CEOs.  They replace Suresh Balakrishna who&amp;nbsp;resigned earlier this month.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before the announcement, Lokhande&amp;nbsp;was serving as VP Trading and Operations of Kinetic India. Previously she worked for IPG and RK Swamy BBDO. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arora&amp;nbsp;has been with Kinetic India since November 2017 as Senior VP for clients. Prior to joining Kinetic India he worked for Posterscope, IPG and Reliance Broadcast.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marc-Antoine de Roys, Kinetic&amp;nbsp;Global CEO said: I want to thank Suresh for his great work at Kinetic.  It is because of his leadership and succession planning that we are in a position to have consistency as he transitions out of the organisation. Rachana and CJ are proven leaders at our company who have earned the trust and respect of our employees, vendors and clients.  Their service, history, and accomplishments made this an easy decision.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1532522632_6UisBW_wpptwo.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/out-of-home-news/cars24-and-milestone-brandcom-launch-massive-ooh-campaign-in-bangalore-91203.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>23/07/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Cars24 and Milestone Brandcom launch massive OOH campaign in Bangalore</news:title>
      <news:description>Milestone Brandcom, the out-of-home agency from Dentsu Aegis Network, has rolled out a massive OOH campaign for Cars24, a platform that makes selling of second-hand cars an easy, fair and a quick experience. Currently launched in Bangalore, the campaign focuses on inviting customers to sell their cars at the citys Cars24 branch in their very first visit.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The campaign is based on the insight that, in the current times, the selling of second-hand cars in India is an extremely complex process. In this market, car owners have to visit or meet a number of buyers before making the sale; and Cars24, a focused and specialised player in this domain, intends to make this technique easy with its unique process that allows the sellers to get the right price for their cars in their very first visit.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/files/1532345701_VAOxFU_Dairy_Circle_%283%29.jpg" style="width:443px;height:238px;vertical-align:middle"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spread across a massive area of more than 70,000 square feet, the OOH campaign encompasses large format billboards, bus shelters, buses, unipoles and gantry. With an aim to design a successful campaign, Milestone Brandcom has selected strategic locations, including arterial routes, corporate areas, market areas, and motor garage to reach out to the brands core TG.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/files/1532345699_lgCGUe_airport_road_towords_yelanka.jpg" style="width:443px;height:347px;vertical-align:middle"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gajendra Jangid, VP- Marketing, Cars 24 said, we aim to provide a quick and convenient way for car owners to sell car in India. The campaign was strategically placed to test the OOH medium and to understand its impact to convey the brand communication to wider audience. This quarter of the year is always good for the used car market and we wanted to create a huge noise before the festive season.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/files/1532345699_J92Rvd_Boman_Innovation.jpg" style="width:443px;height:430px;vertical-align:middle"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commenting of the campaign, Nabendu Bhattacharyya, CEO &amp;amp; Managing Director, Milestone Brandcom said, We got an opportunity here to introduce Cars24 to its core group of consumers through OOH and we have left no stone unturned to create a high impact campaign for the brand. The idea here remains to create buzz and drive home ample curiosity for customers to visit the store and get a first-hand experience on the value of their cars.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Its a delight to witness such an outstanding response to this campaign. The planning of each site was done using detailed understanding of the citys traffic pattern and showroom locations. Each site that has been chosen is a high-impact zone, ensuring maximum visibility. The innovation has already generated extensive exposure and significant buzz, he added. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/OAcTSQ8JN0E" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1532344767_zZrCfs_Cars24-Milestone-Brandcom.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/out-of-home-news/suresh-balakrishna-ceo-kinetic-worldwide-steps-down-90955.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>10/07/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Suresh Balakrishna CEO Kinetic Worldwide Steps Down</news:title>
      <news:description>Suresh Balakrishna, CEO South Asia and Middle East, Kinetic Worldwide has stepped down. He joined the WPP agency in January 2016. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Confirming the news with exchange4media Balakrishna&amp;nbsp;said that he will be on leave for few months after serving his last day on July 13, 2018. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Under his leadership the agency won many accolades. The agency swept the the recently concluded NEONS Awards 2018&amp;nbsp;and bagged the Agency of the Year award. On the same awards night Balakrishna&amp;nbsp;was honoured with the  OOH Person of the Year title.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prior to Kinetic, he was CEO Initiative, BPN/ Rapport. He spent four years with the IPG Mediabrands agency. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Balakrishna&amp;nbsp;had rejoined Lintas media in 2012, from his previous stint at Mail Today as COO which he quit in 2011.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 2005, he had joined Zee Entertainment Enterprises Ltd (ZEEL) as Executive Vice-President, Marketing, but was moved to DNA when ZEEL joined hands with the Bhaskar Group to launch DNA in Mumbai.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Balakrishna&amp;nbsp;had quit Lowe Lintas Initiative Media as EVP and GM in 2003 to join The Hindustan Times as VP - Media &amp;amp; Marketing.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1531202814_cQVujm_collage.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/out-of-home-news/netflix-india-creates-buzz-through-ooh-for-sacred-games-90856.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>04/07/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Netflix India creates buzz through OOH for Sacred Games&#13;
</news:title>
      <news:description>Netflix India, the popular online streaming platform is all set to launch its first original series in the country based on Vikram Chandras novel Sacred Games. The series will premiere on 6 July 2018. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to industry sources, Netflix India is&amp;nbsp;spending approximately Rs 5-6 crores on Out Of Home(OOH) advertising. The billboards can be seen across the roads and flyovers of the Western Express Highway, Juhu Circle and Bandra Linking Road, with an aim to create&amp;nbsp;buzz for its first original series in India. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/files/1530672366_VSQGCv_IMG_20180629_154711-001.jpg" style="width:443px;height:369px;vertical-align:middle"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A senior media planner said, "When Amazon Prime launched its second original web series, Breath, they spent close to Rs 10 crores which was much more than any fiction and non- fiction show. He said, Since it is Netflix Indias first series, they will not compromise on the advertising. It's an on-going campaign, Netflix must be spending nothing less than Rs 5-6 crore on OOH. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to international media reports, Netflix is planning to own up to 35 billboard displays in Hollywood. Netflix is not just a heavy advertiser on billboards in Hollywood, but also in India. Kinetic India has been the OOH agency for Netflix India. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/files/1530672364_EvLN1Z_IMG_20180629_153649-001.jpg" style="width:443px;height:413px;vertical-align:middle"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the OOH campaign, spends will be somewhere around Rs 4-5 crores which is lesser than its earlier campaigns done for The Crown and Strange, which were around Rs 6-7 crores, another media planner shared on the condition of anonymity. He also said,  Due to the monsoon, the spends can be lesser, as&amp;nbsp;the industry witnesses 10-15 percent dip.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When contacted,&amp;nbsp;Netflix India refused&amp;nbsp;to comment. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/files/1530672365_RFfbLn_IMG_20180629_153651-001.jpg" style="width:443px;height:396px;vertical-align:middle"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Based in Mumbai, the series revolves around a contemptuous Mumbai city cop Sartaj Singh (Saif Ali Khan) who is tipped off on the location of crime lord Ganesh Gaitonde (Nawazuddin Siddiqui). As the lives of these two men collide, it exposes the trappings of a game bigger than both of them. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This eight-part series, helmed by acclaimed filmmaker Anurag Kashyap and Vikramaditya Motwane, stars popular actors such as, Saif Ali Khan, Nawazuddin Siddiqui and Radhika Apte.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/28j8h0RRov4" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1530672455_Llw8by_Sacred-Games-main.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/out-of-home-news/digital-ooh-is-opportunity-for-growthmd-media-24x7-90769.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>02/07/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Digital OOH is opportunity for growth: MD Media 24X7</news:title>
      <news:description>Rajendra Kumar, Managing Director of Media 24X7, is very excited about his latest project for the Airports Authority of India.&amp;nbsp;In early June the OOH&amp;nbsp;firm acquired the advertising rights of Khajuraho and Kullu airports from the Airport Authority of India. The company won exclusive rights to sell the advertising space, both in static as well as digital formats. Media 24x7 now plans to build media infrastructure at both the airports to ensure value proposition for the advertisers.  &lt;br&gt;Kumar spoke to exchange4media about the new project and more. Edited excerpts:&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;On the Kullu and Khajuraho Project:&amp;nbsp;We are really excited about the new project. Over the years, Media24x7 has earned the reputation of being one of the most reliable and comprehensive outdoor media solution providers in North India. We have always been striving hard to offer more efficient and modern media infrastructure to our clients and by acquiring space at these two airports, we feel, we have taken a giant step in that direction. Regional or small&amp;nbsp;airports play a vital role in brand communication. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Growth of Airport OOH:&amp;nbsp;Over the past couple of years, regional airports have been achieving exponential growth, both in terms of flight connectivity and passenger count. Our aim is to provide premium advertising media platforms to advertisers or brands so that they can reach out to a larger audience at an affordable cost. We are building a high-quality and aesthetically appealing media inventory that will truly compliment premium brands. We have already started building the inventories and hope to make them live at both the airports by the first week of August.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Potential of OOH for Civic Authorities:&amp;nbsp;The domain is anticipating a paradigm shift in the way the outdoor advertising is perceived and carried out in India. Civic authorities have started recognising the potential of outdoor media as a mainstream revenue earner.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Challenges in OOH Market: Lack of proper guidelines governing the industry. The market has been flooded with too many unregulated and illegal media. This has not only created clutter but has also diminished the effectiveness of OOH as a media format. We sincerely hope that civic authorities&amp;nbsp;soon formulate proper guidelines. Once that happens, the focus will shift from the prevailing highly cluttered OOH space to delivering high-quality and effective media solutions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Future:&amp;nbsp;A&amp;nbsp;change that we anticipate in the near future is the increase in digital formats in OOH space. Share of digital formats in OOH space is less than 5% in India, which is abysmal when compared to the global average of more than 40%. We see this as an opportunity for growth and anticipate that the DOOH market will grow exponentially over the years to come.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1530494917_X1YD2T_Media-24x7-logo.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
</urlset>
