<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9" xmlns:image="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-image/1.1" xmlns:news="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-news/0.9">
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing-news/wpp-to-cut-3500-jobs-93414.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>12/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>WPP to cut 3,500 jobs as part of restructuring</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;WPP&amp;rsquo;s radical evolution plan laid down at the Investor Day on Tuesday indicates that following the hiring freeze, the network will be cutting jobs globally. It was revealed that WPP&amp;rsquo;s restructuring will include shutting 80 offices globally and combining operations of a further 100 in locations where business is slow.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&amp;ldquo;Fewer businesses make it easier to manage, but unfortunately there will be job losses from bringing businesses together,&amp;rdquo; said Mark Read, CEO, WPP, during his presentation. The company is said to cut 3,500 of its 1,34,000 global workforce. WPP has 400 ad businesses in more than 3,000 offices in 112 countries.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Responding to a question from an analyst about further consolidation in the WPP group of companies, Read clarified that WPP will not be looking at more mergers for now. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Over the last three months, WPP has reviewed and restructured agencies that make up for 23 per cent of its revenue. Read called the mergers of VML with Y&amp;amp;R and Wunderman with JWT &amp;ldquo;tough choices&amp;rdquo; and added that the merged companies should be able to provide more integrated solutions to clients. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&amp;ldquo;There is nothing worse than running a company in a so-called traditional area that is doomed forever to the client,&amp;rdquo; he said.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;In this new radical phase of WPP, Read said, he is banning the use of the word &amp;ldquo;digital&amp;rdquo; and veering more towards technology. WPP is positioning itself as a &amp;ldquo;creative transformation company&amp;rdquo; that uses &amp;ldquo;creativity as differentiator and technology as growth engine,&amp;rdquo; Read said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&amp;ldquo;Any company that is not deeply investing in technology will not be successful in the next 5 or 10 or 25 years. I think it is incumbent on us to do that in the right way,&amp;rdquo; he added.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Talking about the mergers that WPP has undertaken recently, Read said the artificial difference between analog and digital is not helpful in understanding the world. &amp;ldquo;Removing those distinctions helps you get to the answer better,&amp;rdquo; he said. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Making a reference to ex-CEO Sir Martin Sorrell&amp;rsquo;s reference to Google and Facebook as frenemies, Read said those companies should be treated as &amp;ldquo;technology partners not as frenemies; as partners and also increasingly and interestingly as clients.&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;He further said that WPP&amp;rsquo;s technology strategy is to become a developer of technology and not just an integrator. &amp;ldquo;We cannot compete with Google or Adobe in terms of technology, but we can leverage the spend of many large partners and stitch their systems together to give us what we need.&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>93414-read.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing-news/we-aim-to-be-in-top-3-brands-in-the-water-heater-category-by-2020-rakesh-kaul-hsil-ltd-93413.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>12/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>We aim to be in top 3 brands in the water heater category by 2020: Rakesh Kaul, HSIL Ltd</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Water heater brand Hindware Atlantic, part of the sanitaryware company HSIL, recently released its first TVC campaign for the Ondeo Series &amp;lsquo;Fresh Hot Water Saalon Saal&amp;rsquo;. The TVC highlights the industry-first and Patented O&amp;#39;Pro Protection Technology and Titanium Core Shield of the Ondeo range which prevents internal corrosion, thereby enhancing the life of water heaters. In 2015, HSIL had entered the home appliances segment with a collaboration with Groupe Atlantic of France.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the insight&amp;nbsp;behind the TVC for its water heater brand Hindware Atlantic, Rakesh Kaul, President and Chief Executive, Consumer Products Division &amp;amp; CEO EVOK Retail, HSIL Limited says, &amp;ldquo;We wanted to bring a campaign to help consumers understand what is happening inside their water heaters as they are not aware of the corrosion and dirt deposits that are formed inside the tank over the years. Thus the first ad campaign focuses on our water heaters equipped with the Patented O&amp;#39;Pro Protection Technology and its Titanium Core Shield helps protect the tank longer from corrosion. The &amp;lsquo;Fresh Hot Water&amp;nbsp;Saalon&amp;nbsp;Sal&amp;rsquo; campaign emphasizes the prolonged life of Hindware Atlantic water heaters as compared to any other ordinary water heaters.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Conceptualized and created by DDB Mudra, the film captures how corrosion and dirty deposits impact the longevity of a water-heater in a light-hearted neo-mythological format. Speaking on the brief given to the creative agency, Kaul says, &amp;ldquo;Our brief to the agency was to voice the aforementioned insight in a humorous and light-hearted manner. Hindware Atlantic Ondeo series comes with patented technology which prolongs the life of the product,&amp;nbsp;our&amp;nbsp;ask from the agency was to keep this messaging at the heart of the commercial while creating an ad that is not just engaging but also entertaining.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Hindware has taken a multi-pronged marketing approach for the commercial through various platforms such as Electronic and Digital. For a wider reach, the TVC is being aired on key regional channels in languages like Bengali, Kannada, Tamil, and Telugu including prominent Movies and News channels. Kaul says, &amp;ldquo;We&amp;#39;ve kept a sizable budget for the TV&amp;nbsp;campaign&amp;nbsp;so that it&amp;#39;s well tailored to reach out to our target audience.&amp;rdquo; Talking about ad-spends he says, &amp;ldquo;We will spend up to Rs 50 crores this financial year on marketing to build our brands across categories. The majority of the spends will be on digital marketing and advertising during festival season.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking about the company&amp;rsquo;s growth Kaul says, &amp;ldquo;We have grown phenomenally in all the categories we are present in over the years. In the chimney segment, we are already among the Top 3 players with a 15-16% market share. Our water heaters category is doing extremely well and in a span of 24 months, we have grown 165% more than last year and currently have 6-6.5% market share in this category.&amp;rdquo; Looking ahead he adds, &amp;ldquo;We aim to be amongst the top 3 brands in the category of water heaters by end 2020 and similarly be amongst the top 3 in the water purifiers category in next 5 years and are working to extend our distribution and retailer network, after sales network and introduce tech led variants in the categories to ensure we achieve our target.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Campaign video:&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/0K5lDBjI5l4" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>93413-RakeshKaul.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital-news/2019-will-be-the-year-of-regional-content-tarun-katial-zee5-93411.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>12/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>2019 will be the year of regional content: Tarun Katial, ZEE5</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;2018 has been a rather action-packed year for ZEE5 and the upcoming year or two will only see things getting bigger and better for ZEEL&amp;rsquo;s OTT platform with more investments being pushed in that direction. Punit Goenka, MD &amp;amp; CEO of ZEEL, had mentioned earlier in one of his interviews that the streaming service is their next big bet when it comes to investment and cornering incremental and additional viewers. With increasing investment he is expecting the business to break even in three to five years.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:8.0pt; text-align:start; -webkit-text-stroke-width:0px; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-ligatures:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-caps:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="orphans:2"&gt;&lt;span style="widows:2"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-style:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-color:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="word-spacing:0px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;Tarun Katial, CEO, ZEE5, talks to e4m about the future plans and how the past year has been for the OTT platform, including the reception, region specific subscription pack and original content. Excerpts:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:start; -webkit-text-stroke-width:0px; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-ligatures:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-caps:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="orphans:2"&gt;&lt;span style="widows:2"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-style:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-color:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="word-spacing:0px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;Innovative pricing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;span style="font-size:11.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;Apart from bringing in regional content, ZEE5 played around with the pricing and introduced special subscription packs for Tamil, Telugu and Kannada audience. This enables users to access premium language content at half the price (Rs 49/month).&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Katial shared that the reception to these region specific packs has been &amp;lsquo;great&amp;rsquo; as they are offering live TV, regional original content, digital movie premieres and early access to regional shows even before TV. &amp;ldquo;So it&amp;rsquo;s a healthy bouquet of content with lot of depth for Tamil, Telugu and Kannada consumers. After South, we will take a break for a quarter and go East,&amp;rdquo; revealed Katial. &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
2018 saw original regional content really taking off with OTT players eyeing growth from tier II and III cities. But that, says Katial, was just the tip of the iceberg. &amp;ldquo;2019 will be the actual year of language (regional) content, the big proliferation of original content and digital movies in India. The uptake of original content will move 3-4 times,&amp;rdquo; he said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-bottom:12.0pt; text-align:start; -webkit-text-stroke-width:0px; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-ligatures:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-caps:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="orphans:2"&gt;&lt;span style="widows:2"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-style:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-color:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="word-spacing:0px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;Katial also mentioned the launch of a premium brand around ZEE5. &amp;quot;It&amp;rsquo;s in the process of being created. SVOD section will be branded separately. It&amp;rsquo;s a different experience than AVOD subset. Several features will be added to it.&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:start; -webkit-text-stroke-width:0px; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-ligatures:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-caps:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="orphans:2"&gt;&lt;span style="widows:2"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-style:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-color:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="word-spacing:0px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;Content game strong&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;Right from its launch, ZEE5 has kept its content game strong especially for originals and movie acquisition. It came out with 15 originals across six languages including the big-budget &amp;lsquo;Karenjit Kaur&amp;rsquo; and big digital premieres of popular titles such as Mulk, Parmanu, Stree and Veere Di Wedding. The strategy of movie premieres particularly worked as it was one of the major consumption drivers. &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
It&amp;rsquo;s now looking to launch over 90 originals in FY2019 and reach 150+ digital premiers in the next 18 months. Katial mentioned that audience sees value in original content as it&amp;rsquo;s a big differentiator. This explains the deep investment. &amp;ldquo;Original movies did well, case in point being &amp;lsquo;Tiger&amp;rsquo; (Emraan Hashmi) We have &amp;lsquo;Rangbaaz&amp;rsquo; coming up next month with Saqib Saleem which is as big as &amp;lsquo;Karenjit Kaur&amp;rsquo; for us. Then there will be big original shows in Tamil, Telugu, Bengali and Marathi. We will amp up in 2019. A slate of 40-50 big shows will come up over the next two quarters,&amp;rdquo; Katial added.&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
AVOD is not getting overshadowed as Katial sees TV shows and their characters being big drivers. &amp;ldquo;We have content beyond the general shows like character journeys and best scenes. Lot of content is created outside the core content. We will continue to invest behind that as well.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;&amp;quot;Language original content, shows around specific themes and relevant topics will continue to resonate well with Indian consumers. You will see off-take in subscription,&amp;quot; says Katial.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:start; -webkit-text-stroke-width:0px; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-ligatures:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-caps:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="orphans:2"&gt;&lt;span style="widows:2"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-style:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-color:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="word-spacing:0px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;Distribution&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;span style="font-size:11.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;Like any other OTT streaming platform, ZEE5 hasn&amp;rsquo;t left any stone unturned to reach the consumer.&amp;nbsp; This goes beyond the regular tie-ups with telecom service providers, digital wallets and smart TVs. For instance, for travel start-up RailYatri customers, ZEE5 had introduced a sachet subscription which gets bundled with the bookings. Similar partnerships with Oyo, MakeMyTrip and RedBus among others are aimed at travel-loving consumers by offering them discounts. &amp;ldquo;Sachet consumers come for a short period of time and want entertainment on the go.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:start; -webkit-text-stroke-width:0px; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-ligatures:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-caps:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="orphans:2"&gt;&lt;span style="widows:2"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-style:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-color:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="word-spacing:0px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;All this and more is definitely working as the ZEE5 app garnered 41.3 million Monthly Active Users in Sep&amp;rsquo;18, a whopping 190% growth since Apr&amp;rsquo;18, according to data provided by ZEE5. And they have just about begun.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>1526893051_UNDgGs_Tarun-Katial.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/media-tv-news/thanthi-tv-editor-in-chief-rangraj-pandey-steps-down-93410.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>12/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Thanthi TV Editor-in-Chief Rangaraj Pandey steps down</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Rangaraj Pandey, who was the Editor-in-Chief of Thanthi TV, has quit from his post, with effect from Monday. Pandey announced his decision to step down in an emotional video, where he thanked the viewers and said that he wanted a break from his daily routine. He added that he also wanted to give space and opportunity to the next generation of journalists. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/c0KWyKkSznY" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;Pandey, who has 22 years of experience in journalism, began his career with Tamil newspaper Dinamalar. &lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;He started the well-known satire column &amp;ldquo;Doubtu Dhanabalu&amp;rdquo;, a fictional character who mocks the day-to-day political discourse in Tamil Nadu and pan-India.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:6.0pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:6.0pt; margin-left:0cm; text-align:start; -webkit-text-stroke-width:0px"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:inherit"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-ligatures:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="font-variant-caps:normal"&gt;&lt;span style="orphans:2"&gt;&lt;span style="widows:2"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-style:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration-color:initial"&gt;&lt;span style="word-spacing:0px"&gt;His interviews with famous personalities made him a popular television face. He hosts talk show &amp;ldquo;Kelvikku Enna Badhil&amp;rdquo; (What is the answer to the question?). Pandey also hosted a prime-time news debate programme &amp;lsquo;Ayutha Ezhuthu&amp;lsquo;. He is renowned for his simple and spontaneous questioning style. Pandey, who hails from North India, is a post graduate in Tamil from Madurai Kamaraj University. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>93410-Pandey.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing-news/our-purpose-is-to-bring-value-not-kill-competition-bhaskar-bhat-md-taneira-93389.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>12/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Our purpose is to bring value, not kill competition: Bhaskar Bhat, MD, Titan</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Titan Company Ltd, which has successfully launched many lifestyle brands over the years-- Titan, Tanishq, Fastrack, Xylys, Raga, Skinn (fragrances), has now entered the textile category with its new offering Taneira.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The company might be a late entrant in the category, but it plans to draw on its strong brand appeal to build its presence across the country.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;At the launch of Taneira&amp;rsquo;s first flagship store, Bhaskar Bhat, Managing Director, Titan Company Limited, spoke about Titan&amp;rsquo;s new offering and the changing retail landscape in the country.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Excerpts:&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What was the thought behind launching this new category?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;See where I sit,&amp;nbsp;which is as the head of the company,&amp;nbsp;it has to be a combination of&amp;nbsp;inspiration and business sense.&amp;nbsp;We have what is known as a sandbox,&amp;nbsp;it&amp;#39;s called the Titan hexagon,&amp;nbsp;which we apply to look at the future.&amp;nbsp;One of the important sides of this hexagon is the under-served and underpenetrated&amp;nbsp;and under-organized.&amp;nbsp;Any category which has two out of three of these,&amp;nbsp;we would like to explore.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;So in that process, we found this (Taneira) as one, and we have several others.&amp;nbsp;And as we explored more and more, we realized&amp;nbsp;that it has&amp;nbsp;a significant proportion of unorganized. We also realized that this is a category where we can bring more value,&amp;nbsp;and it is a very big category.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Looking at the size of this category and given our ability to transform the category combined with our strong retail play is a big strength that we have. Also, branding in this category has not happened so often in the past, and branding is something we bring to the table&amp;nbsp;apart from retail expertise.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In a world which is betting big on digital and considers mobile as the future, how would you contextualize this big investment in offline retail?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t think offline will ever go away for categories where&amp;nbsp;standardization is not the driver of the demand.&amp;nbsp;Anything which has touched and feel has a very strong offline component.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;But&amp;nbsp;the marriage of the two is what we do,&amp;nbsp;which is called Omni, and we are doing that very well, for example in the eyewear category.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Would you call yourself a late entrant in this category? How do you plan to take on players who have been in this business for a long time?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Our impulse is never to compete, our impulse is to serve. I&amp;#39;m not saying this in any philosophical manner. We have found great value and inspiration in being&amp;nbsp;totally driven by the consumers.&amp;nbsp;So consumer insight is a very important function&amp;nbsp;in the company.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;In every store, we listen to our customers and&amp;nbsp;we are driven by the customers. That is what has brought us size and scale,&amp;nbsp;and what happens to the competitors&amp;nbsp;in a way is not our problem. Our purpose is not to kill the competition; our purpose is to bring value. I believe we will create so much value&amp;nbsp;that people would want to come to us.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You have &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;helmed&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt; the success of Titan across categories, what would you call the enablers of this success story?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Fundamentally, customer-centricity; we are driven by the customers;&amp;nbsp;fantastic people orientation in the company. We have a theory about people-- which is unconditional positive regard.&amp;nbsp;It means people first before any other stakeholder. So we are totally people focused. The other factor is design.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How do you see the future of retail panning out in India over the next few years?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;I think it will be Omni&amp;nbsp;and the relevance of&amp;nbsp;brick and mortar stores will continue.&amp;nbsp;As I said,&amp;nbsp;for standard products and technology led products,&amp;nbsp;it will&amp;nbsp;become less and less relevant&amp;nbsp;but there will be flagship stores,&amp;nbsp;which will be less for sales and more for showcasing.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>93389-BhaskarBhat.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements-news/wpp-takes-on-new-identity-to-push-its-radical-evolution-plan-93412.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>12/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>WPP takes on new identity to push its ‘radical evolution’ plan</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;WPP CEO Mark Read on Tuesday announced a three-year plan for &amp;ldquo;radical evolution&amp;rdquo; of the company to deliver improved performance. To reflect the new strategic direction of the company, WPP has launched an evolution of its brand identity.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;Superunion and Landor have collaborated to create the new identity which represents WPP as a creative transformation company that is dynamic, connected and organised around the needs of its clients, according to information available on the agency&amp;rsquo;s site.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;The logo is made up of many parts that combine to form the whole &amp;ndash; a representation of WPP&amp;rsquo;s people, agencies, capabilities and markets that work together as one for clients. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;On-screen, the logo is designed to have a continuously changing form and colour, symbolising creative transformation in itself. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;Talking about the idea behind the new logo, Jim Prior, Global CEO, Superunion, said, &amp;ldquo;Our ambition was to present WPP with the same energy and creativity that we offer to our clients right across the company. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of pride and ambition in WPP that is now united under a strong and dynamic brand identity.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;Jane Geraghty, Global CEO of Landor, said, &amp;ldquo;WPP has always been transformative &amp;ndash; bringing together the best people and ideas to meet the needs of our clients. We now have an evolved brand and expression of purpose that better reflects who we are as a company, our collective capabilities, and what we offer.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;According to WPP, the Superunion/Landor team worked alongside WPP&amp;rsquo;s central team on the new positioning as a dynamic, forward-thinking company with creativity and technology at its heart, and the core purpose of creating better futures for its clients and people.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>93412-WPP.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing-news/delivery-boy-eating-customers-food-will-the-viral-video-brew-trouble-for-zomato-93408.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>12/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Delivery boy eating customers' food: Will the viral video brew trouble for Zomato?</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Online food ordering and restaurant reservation platform Zomato found itself at the receiving end of public ire after a video showing one of its delivery boys consuming food out of its boxed orders appeared on social media. In the two-minute video, the boy was then seen re-sealing the packages, which were likely to be delivered, and putting them back into the delivery bag. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;The video has gone viral and has &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;prompted widespread outrage on social media, with people questioning the brand and its credibility. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-lang="en"&gt;&#13;
&lt;p dir="ltr" lang="en"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/deepigoyal?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;@deepigoyal&lt;/a&gt; Hope you are doing something to repose the trust on your brand &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Zomato?src=hash&amp;amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;#Zomato&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://t.co/Z6LuSL3cGW"&gt;pic.twitter.com/Z6LuSL3cGW&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&amp;mdash; Samrat Ghosh (@SamratYokel) &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/SamratYokel/status/1072381186125774849?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;December 11, 2018&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#13;
&lt;script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-lang="en"&gt;&#13;
&lt;p dir="ltr" lang="en"&gt;What is this &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/Zomato?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;@Zomato&lt;/a&gt; I just placed an order, should I cancel it? &lt;a href="https://t.co/L6izWHajpO"&gt;pic.twitter.com/L6izWHajpO&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&amp;mdash; Ankita (@Miss_Takken) &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/Miss_Takken/status/1072150302592253952?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;December 10, 2018&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#13;
&lt;script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-lang="en"&gt;&#13;
&lt;p dir="ltr" lang="en"&gt;It&amp;#39;s not fault of employee but it is d biggest mistake of Brand name &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/Zomato?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;@Zomato&lt;/a&gt; who made it&amp;#39;s packing so that employee can unpack it thn repack it &lt;a href="https://t.co/yLlIi16uWz"&gt;https://t.co/yLlIi16uWz&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&amp;mdash; ONK (@omkak55) &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/omkak55/status/1072212529575645184?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;December 10, 2018&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#13;
&lt;script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-lang="en"&gt;&#13;
&lt;p dir="ltr" lang="en"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/Zomato?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;@Zomato&lt;/a&gt; Here is what I received on Whatsapp!! Please attend to it or it can damage the Brand really badly. &lt;a href="https://t.co/fpoLk49iLW"&gt;pic.twitter.com/fpoLk49iLW&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&amp;mdash; Ajay Sharma (@itz_aj) &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/itz_aj/status/1072207501901381632?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;December 10, 2018&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#13;
&lt;script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-lang="en"&gt;&#13;
&lt;p dir="ltr" lang="en"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/Zomato?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;@Zomato&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/ZomatoIN?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;@ZomatoIN&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/zomatocare?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;@zomatocare&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
What the heck is this .. Customers trust the brand blindly and this is what we get in return . Cant dare to believe that we are being served such kind of food . ?? &lt;a href="https://t.co/4O85PEz6nb"&gt;pic.twitter.com/4O85PEz6nb&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&amp;mdash; James Chacko (@JamesChacko1984) &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/JamesChacko1984/status/1072196597658894336?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;December 10, 2018&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#13;
&lt;script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;The question that now arises is will the brand be impacted due to this? What&amp;rsquo;s interesting is that Zomato&amp;rsquo;s competitor Swiggy recently rolled an ad communication asking consumers to empathise with delivery partners, as they, like each one of us, have a name and unique identity that they would like everybody to acknowledge. Will this incident then jeopardize Zomato&amp;rsquo;s image and give its competitors an edge over it? Or will Zomato be able to reclaim itself just right post the fiasco?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Kiran Khalap, Co-founder &amp;amp; Managing Director, Chlorophyll&amp;nbsp;Brand &amp;amp; Communications, calls this a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;classic crisis and contends that besides sacking the delivery boy, the brand will have to engage directly with the end-consumer to explain putting into place processes that will prevent recurrence of such incidents. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&amp;ldquo;Hopefully Zomato has a crisis management manual. It is the same with the Cadbury&amp;rsquo;s or the Nestle Maggi crisis: telling the truth always helps! It is difficult, but it can be done. And if done well, Zomato will regain its lost goodwill,&amp;rdquo; reasons Khalap. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="MsoNoSpacing" style="margin:0cm; margin-bottom:.0001pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Brand expert Gaurav Gulati opines that the video has surely damaged the brand reputation and is a lesson that even others in the category should pay heed to. &amp;ldquo;This surely is going to create a lot of trouble for the brand. Moreover, people might start poking the brand and Zomato delivery boys with sarcasm and prefer to use the services of their competitors instead. But it is high time for all these brands to take food tampering and hygiene very seriously.&amp;rdquo; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Gulati adds that Zomato recently raised fresh funding of $210 million from Alibaba&amp;rsquo;s Ant Financials for payment solution, but as things have changed, they should probably utilise most of the funds on image building and fixing brand reputation. After all, it&amp;rsquo;s the matter of existence now.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Harish Bijoor, brand guru &amp;amp; founder of Harish Bijoor Consults Inc, remarks that pulling one delivery boy off roster does nothing and is a big hit not only to Zomato in terms of &amp;nbsp;consumer-imagery and impression, but to the entire food and beverage delivery category altogether. &amp;ldquo;When a brand outsources literally everything it does, issues such as these are bound to be a constant bother. It is important to make food handling and delivery totally tamper-proof. Packaging can play a crucial role here,&amp;rdquo; says Bijoor.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="background:white"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;Meanwhile, responding to the criticism, Z&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;omato released an official statement, saying that it will soon introduce tamper-proof packaging.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;&amp;quot;In our commitment towards mitigating any possibility of tampering with food,&amp;nbsp;Zomato will soon introduce tamper-proof tapes and other precautionary measures to ensure we safeguard against any chances of tampering of food. Zomato has a zero tolerance policy for tampering of food.&amp;rdquo; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:8.0pt; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#222222"&gt;&amp;ldquo;We have found that the video was shot in Madurai. The person in the video is a delivery partner on our fleet. We have spoken to him at length - and while we understand that this was a human error in judgement, we have taken him off the platform. This incident only makes our commitment to fleet training, scheduling and process even stronger. We stand behind our extensive fleet who do the right thing across many hours of the day,&amp;rdquo; the statement said further.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>93408-zomato.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital-news/learning-a-thing-or-two-from-the-mumbai-police-about-upping-the-social-media-game-93403.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>12/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Learning a thing or two from the Mumbai Police about upping the Social Media game</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Lately, the woman behind the famed Mumbai Police department&amp;rsquo;s Twitter handle (@MumbaiPolice) finds herself catching up on the latest binge-worthy shows, viral memes and Twitter trends whenever she finds the time.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;From Game of Thrones and Stranger Things to Twitter memes like GharSeNikalTeHi, Sunchika Pandey and her team is thinking content round the clock and tries to never miss a social media opportunity for the Mumbai Police. Over the last three years, the Mumbai Police Department&amp;rsquo;s Twitter handle has become every Mumbaikar&amp;rsquo;s go-to channel for latest updates on law and order related happenings in the city, to register complaints, all while being treated to social media memes on the side. The social media strategy is a prime example for consumer facing brands that are trying to establish a strong social media presence.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seeing Content Everywhere&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Content has become a state of mind for the Mumbai Police social media team. &amp;quot;If I see a glass lying around on the table, I wonder how to use it as content!&amp;quot; she says. But she is not cued into all the millenial themes and trends, so she&amp;nbsp;generally gets all her&amp;nbsp;references checked with her&amp;nbsp;team of youngsters.&amp;nbsp;&amp;quot;But now I am also watching all the popular shows,&amp;rdquo; confesses Pandey, who is&amp;nbsp;the Group Director of its Citizen Initiatives &amp;amp; Government division at independent digital agency, Gozoop.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s not just Pandey, even the policemen who run the Twitter operations for the department have begun looking at the world around them through the lens of &amp;ldquo;content.&amp;rdquo; This is the result of the Mumbai Police department&amp;rsquo;s innovative attempt at reaching out to the citizens of Mumbai through the micro-blogging platform three years ago.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Every brand is talking the language of content, and there is no reason&amp;nbsp;the Mumbai Police should be found lagging. &amp;ldquo;What ticks with the readers now-a-days is content. Content that is quirky, trendy, timeless, resonating...&amp;nbsp;the list goes on. Mumbai Police has ticked all the boxes.&amp;nbsp;Messages about safety, social &amp;amp; traffic discipline, celebration, respect for martyrs, cyber security, and all such occasions are so very well weaved into different engaging formats of content. By default you end up consuming these pieces and the point is driven home,&amp;rdquo; says Shekhar Mhaskar, EVP Isobar India, decoding the success of the Mumbai Police&amp;#39;s social media game.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;The first tweet we ever put out was : Why should the police station be the only place where we meet? Let&amp;rsquo;s meet here every day,&amp;rdquo; recollects Pandey. Hers and her&amp;nbsp;team&amp;rsquo;s efforts to make the police department more approachable and less fearful for&amp;nbsp;the citizens has earned the department the moniker Meme-bai Police and Amul of Government departments.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Response Engenders Trust&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Hidden under the satirical content and prompt informative responses from the department is a lesson for all marketers who are trying to create a social media persona for their brands. To Pandey the lesson is very simple: a clear vision plus knowledge of target audience complemented by fulfilment of brand promise = success.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Even Pandey knows this is easier said than done. Social media handles of most consumer facing companies are inundated with complaints from disgruntled consumers every day. These complaints are mostly met with automated responses that only irk consumers further.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;There are instances when a disgruntled consumer feels a loss of trust with the brand because of a negative experience and cannot be assuaged by following documented response matrices. This is where a brand can elevate itself to the next level of sophistication &amp;ndash; with their ability to humanise interactions and setting up of strong internal processes that speak with different departments to effectively act upon their customer commitments,&amp;rdquo; says Sakshi Arora, Strategy Director, Digitas India.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Anticipating the citizen outpouring, at least eight policemen and two senior police officers monitor the Mumbai Police and Police Commissioner&amp;rsquo;s Twitter handles at any given point. The policemen monitor the tweets and direct messages sent to these two handles until 3-4am every day. &amp;ldquo;The clear mandate when we started out was that we must respond to every single tweet,&amp;rdquo; Pandey says.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kidding, but seriously...&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The mission of the Mumbai Police was to utilise Twitter as yet another touchpoint where the department could interact with the citizens. &amp;ldquo;It was not in our plan to make it iconic in the way that it has become,&amp;rdquo; says Pandey with humility.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;We wanted to make people smile and that&amp;rsquo;s how we thought about using humour in our posts.&amp;rdquo; At the same time as the Twitter handle of the police department the content had to always adhere to a certain high moral and ethical code. &amp;ldquo;As Mumbai Police we needed to maintain the dignity of the officers and the uniform. That is why we chose satire.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Mumbai Police has resonated with the citizens of Mumbai by &amp;ldquo;challenging the status quo on the type of online personality an administrative body should have,&amp;rdquo; says Arora. This dark humour coupled with healthy engagement with citizens gives Mumbai Police its clutter breaking social presence and huge organic following.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Brands typically monitor their social media handles but worry that saying something edgy will get them trolled. Typically BFSI, healthcare, and B2B brands are uncomfortable about using humour on social channels. But the Mumbai Police is okay with taking a stance and even responding to citizens. Now the mental impression of Mumbai Police has improved because of the social media presence of the department,&amp;rdquo; says Siddharth Hegde, MD &amp;amp; Founder, Ethinos Digital Marketing.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;All of these factors have made Mumbai Police a social media case study that other police departments across the country have begun to emulate. The Bangalore and Kolkata City Police engage with their citizens on social media very successfully. &amp;quot;Even the UP Police has launched a Twitter account and that has helped the department improve its image,&amp;quot; quips Pandey. As the&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Group Director of its Citizen Initiatives &amp;amp; Government division at Gozoop, Pandey wishes to work with more government bodies, helping them engage in a healthy manner with citizens.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>93403-mumbaipolice.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing-news/tech-mahindra-announces-key-leadership-appointments-93407.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>11/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Tech Mahindra announces key leadership appointments</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Tech Mahindra announced key leadership appointments to drive the organization&amp;rsquo;s growth and lead the digital transformation journey. The leadership changes will be effective from &amp;nbsp;January 1, 2019.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Jagdish Mitra, currently the Chief Strategy &amp;amp; Marketing Officer, will be in charge of the Enterprise Business. With his experience in the digital space, he will drive growth across Enterprise Business Verticals and Strategic Business Units. He will also drive Strategic Partnerships and Alliances for Tech Mahindra. Sanjeev Nikore, currently leading Strategic Initiatives, will now take over as the Head of Marketing at Tech Mahindra.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Manoj Chugh, who is currently the Enterprise Business Head at Tech Mahindra, will take over as President, Corporate Affairs at Mahindra &amp;amp; Mahindra Group.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;sans-serif&amp;quot;"&gt;CP Gurnani, Managing Director and Chief Executive Officer, Tech Mahindra said, &amp;ldquo;I wish everyone a great success in their respective roles. This will help the organization accelerate the digital transformation journey, as part of the TechMNxt charter. I am confident that this team will propel Tech Mahindra&amp;rsquo;s growth globally.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>92770-techmahindra.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/industry-briefing-news/innovation-takes-the-lead-in-abp-newsroom-93406.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>11/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Innovation takes the lead in ABP newsroom</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;With the vision to keep #Deshkorakheyaagey, ABP news created first-of-its-kind reporting set-up to lift the exuberance and excitement of the dynamic movement of the election results. An innovative 360-degree setup was organized on Tuesday to help viewers understand the ground zero of elections across India.&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
The innovative live view of ABP newsroom included an interesting Virtual Reality set-up which gives an overview of the entire newsroom. A thematic graphical representation of data projecting city graphics data over innovative bulletin train. An active data LED wall was also installed with colour codes and alignments to help understand the dynamic movements on the results.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Talking about the initiatives, Avinash Pandey, COO, ABP News Network, said, &amp;ldquo;Time and again, we have set a benchmark in creating new standard when it comes to innovation in newsroom. With the changing consumer behaviour, we have tried to make our today&amp;rsquo;s programming more innovative, interactive and engaging for our viewers. Our all &amp;ndash; new &amp;amp; first- of-its-kind initiatives like active data LED wall and Virtual reality initiative, kept the viewers engaged during the game changing numbers of the election results.&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
He added, &amp;ldquo;On digital front, we have yet again taken a lead today in the Hindi genre segment receiving the highest concurrent visitors on desktop and mobile platforms.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Some other initiatives like LIVE Result coverage on LED screens (outdoor) for our viewers was also installed in Delhi - Connaught Place, Kolkata - Top n Town news market, Jaipur - Near Alberta Museum, Raipur - Jaistambh Chowk along with extensive outdoor coverage.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>93406-ABPMain.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/industry-briefing-news/lux-golden-rose-awards-marks-3rd-year-in-collaboration-with-mindshare-india-star-tv-93405.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>11/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Lux Golden Rose Awards marks 3rd year, in collaboration with Mindshare India &amp; Star TV</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p class="Default" style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;The 3rd edition of Lux Golden Rose Awards (LGRA), which was recently held at NSCI Dome in Mumbai, congregated B-town&amp;rsquo;s biggest and brightest stars across eras to extend their support for UN&amp;rsquo;s HeForShe campaign and to stand in solidarity for gender equality in a one-of-its-kind extravaganza celebrating female cinematic legends of the silver screen. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="Default" style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="Default" style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Mindshare Fulcrum anchored the entire event with Star TV and Hotstar for content creation and broadcasting of the main award ceremony. The company also partnered with Hindustan Times, Fever 104 FM, Pinkvilla, Facebook and BeBeautiful for ancillary content creation. Celebrities such as Varun Dhawan, Ayushmann Khurrana, Aparshakti Khurrana, Guru Randhawa, Karan Tacker, Karan Kundrra, Nakuul Mehta and Mohit Malik joined the country&amp;#39;s first and one-of-its-kind &amp;quot;I am HeForShe&amp;quot; movement. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="Default" style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="Default" style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;The ceremony was a grand affair and was graced by some of the most legendary and popular faces of the fraternity such as Shah Rukh Khan, Akshay Kumar, Varun Dhawan, Karan Johar, Rekha, Alia Bhatt, Madhuri Dixit Nene, Aishwarya Rai Bachchan, Kareena Kapoor, Karisma Kapoor, Jacqueline Fernandez, Kajol, Hema Malini, Zeenat Aman, Helen and many more. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="Default" style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="Default" style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;The performers entertained audiences with their mesmerizing and colorful jigs, and the novel combination of hosts had all in splits throughout the evening. Shahrukh Khan&amp;rsquo;s evergreen wit combined with Varun Dhawan and Akshay Kumar&amp;rsquo;s hilarious dramatics was very well received and appreciated. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="Default" style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="Default" style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;B Town regulars and other spectators for the evening were in for a memorable surprise as they watched leading B-town male celebrities pay tribute to some of the most loved divas of Bollywood for their immense contribution in their professional and personal lives. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="Default" style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="Default" style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Kareena Kapoor Khan, as usual left audiences spell-bound being her vivacious self as she performed on superhit tracks of her male co-stars. Charming superstar, Varun Dhawan&amp;rsquo;s performance was a tribute, celebrating the gorgeous women he has had the chance to share screen space with. The evening also housed a sizzling performance from this year&amp;rsquo;s star debutants, the lovely &amp;lsquo;Dhadak&amp;rsquo; pair Janhvi Kapoor and Ishaan who performed on hits like Dhadak, Jugni, Kar Har Maidan Fateh and the chartbusting Zingaat but the star performance of the night was by none other than the Dhak-Dhak girl of Bollywood Madhuri Dixit, who performed to Hema Malini&amp;rsquo;s Dreamgirl and to Helen&amp;rsquo;s Yeh Mera Dil. She is also seen dancing to late actress Sridevi&amp;rsquo;s Hawa Hawai and her own song, Tamma Tamma Loge. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;The night ended on a high note with the ruling men of Bollywood &amp;ndash; The Badshah and Khiladi along with the super charming Varun Dhawan who came together to celebrate these iconic women and the women of the country &amp;ndash; the Lux HeForShe finale.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="Default" style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Amin Lakhani, President- Client Leadership, Mindshare India, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;said &amp;lsquo;With LGRA in its third consecutive year, we take immense pride in saying that with each passing year it has not only turned out to be a stronger but an even more successful association with brand Lux. In our three years of being associated with this project, we have only seen it grow in terms of grandeur and scale and what better than supporting the UN initiative HeForShe for an even more purposeful cause.&amp;rsquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="Default" style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Harman Dhillion, GM &amp;ndash; Skin Cleansing, Hindustan Unilever Limited, mentioned&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;, &amp;ldquo;For 90 years, Lux has been the beauty secret of iconic Bollywood superstars. This year, we used the grand stage of the Lux Golden Rose Awards to celebrate these women, and it was done in great style by the men of Bollywood paying an ode to their ladies. It was truly a pleasure to witness the Lux divas across generations being celebrated and a once in a lifetime experience.&amp;rdquo; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="Default" style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="Default" style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="color:black"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;Premjeet Sodhi Senior Vice-President Mindshare Fulcrum South Asia, said, &amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;LGRA has always been a project that we at Mindshare hold in high regard. We feel extremely honoured by the fact that over the past three years, we have been able to bring Lux&amp;rsquo;s grand vision to life, with each edition being even more&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
well-received than the last. This year, in particular, has been a matter of extreme pride, with a purpose-driven association in the form of HeForShe. The incredible success of this project would not have been possible without the tireless work and dedication of our Content+, Exchange, and Client Leadership teams, who performed extraordinarily, and delivered excellence.&amp;quot; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p class="Default" style="margin:0cm 0cm 0.0001pt"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Calibri,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12.0pt"&gt;&lt;span style="line-height:107%"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;serif&amp;quot;"&gt;The award ceremony created a platform for a larger- than-life celebration of the divas of Bollywood.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>93405-mindsharemain.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements-news/madisons-hiveminds-wins-google-premier-partner-awards-2018-for-search-innovation-93404.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>11/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Madison’s HiveMinds wins Google Premier Partner Awards 2018 for Search Innovation</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Hiveminds, the newly acquired Search specialist digital agency of Madison World, has won the Search Innovation Award for their work on Curefit, at the 2nd edition of the Google Premier Partner Awards 2018, India.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The Google Premier Partner Awards honours innovation in digital marketing across Search, Mobile, Video, Display, Shopping and Growing Businesses Online. Google Premier Partner Award in search innovation is given for expertise and innovation with Google search ads. Examples include creative uses of auto-bidding or optimizing beyond the last click to help clients achieve their goals online. Out of 300+ Google Premier Partners in India, only six agencies were shortlisted for the award.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Curefit is an FMCG-health &amp;amp; fitness solutions provider, founded by former Flipkart executives Mukesh Bansal and Ankit Nagori. For Curefit, HiveMinds through its continuous effort and stacked approach, has been able to deliver 6X improvement in conversions and helped acquire new users consistently, the company said in a statement.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Hiveminds also used:&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;ul&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li&gt;Hyper localized ads to personalize messaging based on user data signals using Google&amp;rsquo;s smart business feed platform&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li&gt;Compelling ad formats like countdown feature, pin-code based bid adjustments&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li&gt;Smart remarketing strategies&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;All this helped the brand deliver 6X increase in conversions, as well as a 30 per cent drop in overall customer acquisition costs.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Talking about the award, Jyothirmayee JT, Founder &amp;amp; CEO, Hiveminds, said, &amp;ldquo;HiveMinds is arguably one of the strongest performance marketing agencies out of India. Winning this award from Google in the core category of search innovation is very encouraging for us. What&amp;#39;s more special, is the award was for our work with another ambitious startup, growing multifold every month and are destined to be an industry leader like many of our clients whom we have engaged at an early stage&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;HiveMinds specialises in providing end-to-end digital marketing solutions like SEO, Performance &amp;amp; Paid Campaigns, Analytics, Social Media, Digital Branding and Creative &amp;amp; Content services, for leading brands and startups in India, US and the Middle East. HiveMinds handles key clients such as bigbasket, Teabox, Sonata Watches, Portea, Zoomcar and Cloudnine Hospitals.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>93404-awardfinal.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements-news/ajay-gahlaut-to-join-publicis-93372.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>11/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Ajay Gahlaut to join Publicis</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Ajay Gahlaut, who recently quit as Chief Creative Officer of Ogilvy North and Deputy Chief Creative Officer of Ogilvy India, is believed to be joining Publicis.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Galaut is expected to succeed Bobby Pawar, who quit Publicis to join Havas Media. Pawar was the Managing Director and Chief Creative Officer, Publicis Worldwide South Asia.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The development has been confirmed to exchange4media by highly-placed sources. We reached out to Gahlaut for a confirmation, but are yet to get a response.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;At Ogilvy, Gahlaut&amp;nbsp;worked on brands such as Pernod Ricard, BMW, KFC, Taco Bell, Dabur, Perfetti Van Melle, Mother Dairy, Pizza Hut, Sprite, Best Foods, HT Mint and Philips.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Gahlaut worked with Ogilvy as a creative consultant between 2001 and 2005, after which he left. He re-joined the agency in 2007 and had been with it ever since. He has previously worked with agencies such as McCann, Saatchi &amp;amp; Saatchi (then Sista Saatchi &amp;amp; Saatchi), among others.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>92572-Ajay-Gahlaut-pic.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/media-tv-news/mib-calls-for-meet-to-discuss-broadband-services-through-cable-tv-networks-93400.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>11/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>MIB calls for meet to discuss broadband services through cable TV networks</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;The Ministry of Information and Broadcasting (MIB) is organising a conference of cable TV industry representatives (MSOs) on December 18 to discuss providing broadband services through cable TV networks.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;The meet will discuss various issues, including feasibility, affordability, ubiquity, infrastructure, modalities of payment and segregation of revenue earned from broadband activities. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;According to a ministry notice, detailed deliberation will be held on: (i) willingness of the operators to invest in the infrastructure required. ii) The payment of 8 per cent Adjusted Gross Revenue (AGR) as the fee to DoT, whether to be paid only on the broadband services or on overall revenue earned in respect of both the businesses. iii) Whether separate entity needs to be created for the broadband activities for segregation of the revenue earned on it. iv)All other issues related to the delivery of broadband services through cable TV network.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;The notice mentions that the conference will be held at Gulmohar Hall, Habitat Centre, Lodhi Road, New Delhi, and will see participation from major MSOs, officials from MIB, DoT, TRAI and Broadcast Engineering Consultants India Limited (BECIL).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>92873-MIBLogo.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/marketing-news/quaker-launches-the-last-meal-film-as-part-of-its-feed-a-child-initiative-93402.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>11/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Quaker launches 'The Last Meal' film as part of its Feed a Child initiative</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;As part of the Quaker Feed a Child initiative that aims to create awareness for the issue of hunger amongst children, Quaker India&amp;nbsp;has released a new, thought-provoking digital film &amp;lsquo;The Last Meal&amp;#39;. Produced in association with Culture Machine, the video takes an authentic social experiment route to bring forth the dichotomy of the world we live in, where the privileged masses take access to food for granted, versus the underprivileged who struggle for each meal.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Capturing a real-life social experiment conducted on the streets of Mumbai, the new digital film for Quaker Feed a Child shows people talking about their love for food and yet struggling to remember their most recent meal. In contrast, the film moves to show children from underprivileged backgrounds immediately recalling their last meal, with some even stating sadly that they hadn&amp;rsquo;t eaten anything. The film ends poignantly with some of the children requesting for a meal, as they are hungry. The film also features celebrated&amp;nbsp;Michelin starred Chef Vikas Khanna making a call to action to all viewers to make their new year special by feeding a hungry child.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking about the initiative, Nobel Dhingra, Brand head - Quaker, PepsiCo India, said, &amp;ldquo;It is disturbing that less than one-third of children in India receive adequate nutrition. Quaker Feed a Child is a social initiative based on a powerful thought that urges us all to make every festival or occasion more meaningful by simply pledging a fistful of nutrition to feed a child. With the new year approaching, we hope that people will choose to share their festive cheer by taking a pledge to feed a child.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Commenting about his association with the initiative, Chef Vikas Khanna, Michelin-starred Chef said, &amp;ldquo;The problem of hunger and malnutrition in India cannot be solved overnight. If each of us take a step forward to help the underprivileged children, I believe we can take a big leap towards ensuring no child goes to bed hungry. I am happy to be a part of Quaker Feed A Child to raise awareness for this important and heart-wrenching issue.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Sharique Khan, Vice President- Brand Solutions, Culture Machine added,&amp;nbsp;&amp;ldquo;One of the most unfortunate facts today is that most children in our country do not have access to timely meals to satiate their hunger; which is the most basic necessity to any life form. It is our duty and responsibility, as humans and own beings , to create an awareness and also to do whatever we can in our small way to end this, one child at a time. Culture Machine in association with Quaker, urges its viewers to take a pledge and do their bit for this humane cause.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Quaker&amp;rsquo;s new digital film will feature on Culture Machine&amp;rsquo;s digital platform, Being Indian, and aptly captures how the value of a single meal could differ for those who are food secure and those deprived of food. The film reiterates the vision of the Quaker Feed a Child initiative, that aims to raise awareness for the problem of hunger amongst children, given India has one of the highest rates of hunger among children where one in five children go hungry each day. Till date, Quaker Feed a Child has supported over half a million meals for underprivileged children through Smile Foundation.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Video:&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/x0KshTHkgWY" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>93402-TheLastMeal.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements-news/himanshu-shekhar-promoted-to-ceo-groupm-indonesia-93401.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>11/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Himanshu Shekhar promoted to CEO, GroupM Indonesia</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;GroupM has announced that Himanshu Shekhar will be taking over from Ed Thesiger as the CEO of GroupM Indonesia, effective January 1, 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Shekhar has been based in Indonesia since March 2010 when he joined as the Managing Director for Mindshare&amp;rsquo;s business with Unilever. He was later promoted to CEO of Mindshare Indonesia in December 2011.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;While at the helm of Mindshare Indonesia, he consistently delivered strong growth for the agency and positioned Mindshare as the market leader in digital transformation. In January 2015, Shekhar was promoted to his current position, CEO of Mindshare South East Asia, the company said in a statement.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Thesiger, CEO GroupM Indonesia and Vietnam, will be relocating to the UK at the end of March 2019 to set up his own consulting business.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the appointment, Mark Patterson, CEO GroupM APAC, said, &amp;ldquo;Indonesia continues to be a key growth market for us, and I am delighted that we have been able to promote from within for this important leadership position. Himanshu has a proven track record with a depth of experience and industry relationships that is second to none in that market.&amp;nbsp;I would also like to thank Ed for his energy, passion and outstanding leadership over the past seven years.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;We are sorry to see him leave the region and wish him every success on his new venture back in the UK.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Amrita Randhawa, CEO Mindshare APAC, added, &amp;ldquo;Himanshu has built Mindshare into a titan of an organisation in Indonesia and driven its strength, reputation and leadership stature across South East Asia. His knowledge of Indonesia and our clients&amp;rsquo; core needs in the market is unparalleled and therefore there is no one better suited to step into the GroupM leadership position. We are rooting for Himanshu&amp;rsquo;s success in this next chapter of his career and are confident that he will continue to be an incredible partner for Mindshare and our client&amp;rsquo;s growth story in Indonesia.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking of his promotion Shekhar noted, &amp;ldquo;Leading GroupM Indonesia is a massive responsibility. Across our agencies, Mediacom, Mindshare, Wavemaker and Essence, we have some of the brightest minds working with super successful brands on creating media for business growth. I am thankful to our leadership and teams for building trusted partnerships with clients, media and tech ecosystems over the years.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Today, Indonesia&amp;rsquo;s media is among the most vibrant globally. We have global innovation originating here and best practices taking shape in some areas. Our global networks have been deeply committed to this already, and I am excited to add my efforts to this journey. I am thankful for the trust, and look forward to working together with our wonderful teams and partners.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Thesiger added, &amp;ldquo;It has been an absolute privilege leading such a talented group over the past 7 years. Himanshu has been a cornerstone of the team for the duration of my tenure and I look forward to seeing him drive the business on to the next level in the coming years.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Ed will work closely with Himanshu to ensure a smooth transition over the coming weeks.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Details of Ed&amp;rsquo;s successor in Vietnam and Himanshu&amp;rsquo;s successor will be the subject of separate communications in due course, the company said.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Shekhar will continue to be based in Jakarta with his family and will report directly to Mark Patterson.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>93401-himanshu.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements-news/the-thick-shake-factory-announces-its-new-board-of-advisors-93399.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>11/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>The Thick Shake Factory announces its new Board of Advisors</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;India&amp;rsquo;s first premium thick shake brand and one of the fastest growing QSR chains in the country &amp;ndash; The Thick Shake Factory - is proud to announce a stellar panel of industry stalwarts joining its board of advisors headed by serial entrepreneur Dr. Anurag Batra, chairman of BW Business World and founder of media group exchange4media. The advisory board consists of mavericks like Dr. Velumani Arokiaswamy, the founder of the Rs 3000 crore valued healthcare Thyrocare, Jayant Kocchar the ex MD, Founder of Lacoste India, Barista, India&amp;rsquo;s 1st Coffee Caf&amp;eacute; chain, Sagar Daryani of Wow! Momo, Srinath Sridharan, the head of Group Chairman&amp;rsquo;s office of Wadhawan Global Capital, which manages $22 billion in assets, Rohit Bayana Co-founder of Lumis Partners, a Private equity fund and Preeti Vyas Chairwoman &amp;amp; founder of VGC - one of India&amp;rsquo;s top design agencies.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking on the announcement, M. Yeshwanth Nag Mocherla, Co-Founder of The ThickShake Factory, said, &amp;quot;All of the newest Board members embody the spirit of entrepreneurship and bring immense experience, expertise and energy to the table. We are very fortunate to have them by our side as we continue on our journey and aim to become a large international consumer brand. With such eminent personalities to guide us, we are confident of executing our vision.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the occasion, Ashwin Mocherla, Co-Founder, The ThickShake Factory said, &amp;ldquo;We currently are operational across 20 cities and two countries with more than 50 outlets in the pipeline to be opened in the coming months. Our vision is to have over 500 outlets in the next three years. We are a profitable bootstrapped company and have continued to grow via internal accruals since our inception five years ago&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking on his inclusion into the Board of Advisors, Jayant Kochar said, &amp;ldquo;With our hectic, stressful, abstemious lifestyles, I think we all deserve a bit of indulgence and joy from time to time. There are very few things that match the sheer bliss of a delicious Thick Shake, and I am pleased to help Yeshwanth and Ashwin spread their flavours of happiness across the country&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Velumani added, &amp;ldquo;As long as the product is really good, packaged well, priced honest &amp;amp; promoted aggressively, there are enough customers to consume in an emerging market like India&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The Thick Shake Factory was founded by Yeshwanth Nag Mocherla and his brother Ashwin Mocherla.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/YeshwantandAshwinMocherla.png" style="width: 300px; height: 300px;" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Yeshwanth Nag Mocherla and his brother Ashwin Mocherla, Founders of The Thick Shake Factory&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Yeshwanth is an engineer from JNTU and completed his Post Graduate Diploma in Management from Xavier Institute of Management, Bhubaneswar &amp;amp; IESEG School of management, France, post which he worked with Tata Consultancy Services for one year before plunging into entrepreneurship. The driving force for him is to create more jobs &amp;amp; add value to the economy.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Ashwin is an engineer from JNTU and had studied his Post Graduate Diploma in Management from Goa Institute of management &amp;amp; Antwerp management school, Belgium, prior to which he had worked with United Health Group for one year &amp;amp; plunged into entrepreneurship right after his post-graduation. The driving force for him is his passion towards the Food &amp;amp; beverages sector.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Yeshwanth and Ashwin are seen as industry leaders in the F&amp;amp;B sector &amp;amp; have been speakers at multiple forums including but not limited to: Women Economic Forum 2018, Food &amp;amp; Beverages Conclave &amp;amp; Expo, 2017, SME Growth Leadership Conclave, 2017, India Food Forum, 2018, T Hub, Hyderabad (India&amp;#39;s biggest Start-up Business Incubator), Jagriti Yatra (World&amp;rsquo;s longest train journey for entrepreneurship), Utkarsh Yatra (Entrepreneurship journey) etc. to name a few.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The New Board Members:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/AnuragBatra.jpg" style="width: 300px; height: 300px;" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Anurag Batra&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Anurag Batra is a serial entrepreneur, media mogul, a journalist and an eternal optimist rolled into one. He is a first generation entrepreneur having acquired the iconic business media &amp;amp; magazine brand BW Business World, and also serves as the Chairman and Editor-In-Chief of exchange4media group. He mentors many budding entrepreneurs and enjoys the process of reverse mentoring of learning from the entrepreneurs.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/DrAVelumani.jpg" style="width: 300px; height: 300px;" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Dr. A. Velumani&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. A. Velumani is maverick entrepreneur. He is the founder, chairman and managing director of Thyrocare Technologies Ltd., an industry leader and a brand worth over Rs. 3000 Crore. A visionary &amp;amp; an able business administrator, Dr. Velumani proves amply clearly to the industry that, &amp;ldquo;Focus gives success&amp;rdquo;. A first generation entrepreneur, he is an infectious motivator &amp;amp; by his unique way, transformed intimidating problems to opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/JayantKochar.jpg" style="width: 300px; height: 300px;" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Jayant Kochar&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Jayant Kochar is one of the pioneers of organized retail in India; an authentic &amp;ldquo;start-up&amp;rdquo; specialist. After a long stint with automobile major Mahindra&amp;rsquo;s, he pioneered the entry of organized retail by launching the French apparel brand LACOSTE in India. He created not just a great brand, but an entirely new category when he conceptualized and built the pioneering chain of espresso bars in India &amp;ndash; Barista. Having also led the Images Group, he now heads India&amp;rsquo;s leading retail consulting practice &amp;ndash; GO FISH. He recently conceptualized &amp;amp; curated an innovative retail strategy conference &amp;ndash; unBox Retail.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/SrinathSridharan.jpg" style="width: 300px; height: 300px;" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Srinath Sridharan&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Srinath Sridharan is the head of the Group Chairman&amp;#39;s Office and convenor of the Group Management Council at the Wadhawan Global Capital which manages $22 Billion in assets. An expert in strategy and a business visionary, he anchors the growth of Wadhawan Global Capital&amp;rsquo;s businesses with one key focus &amp;ndash; robust value creation. Srinath is known to provide unique perspectives that blend consumer-driven strategy, financial acumen &amp;amp; risk management in a seamless manner.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/PreetiVyas.jpg" style="width: 300px; height: 300px;" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Preeti Vyas&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Preeti Vyas, an independent entrepreneur with humble beginnings, has created some of India&amp;rsquo;s most iconic brand stories and redefined the design landscape. She is counted among the 50 most influential women in India according to Business Today, Impact and Verve magazines, and ranked as one of the top creative minds by The Economic Times.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/SagarDaryani.jpg" style="width: 300px; height: 300px;" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sagar Daryani&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Sagar Daryani is the founder of one of the fastest growing QSR chains; the 300 Crore valued brand - Wow! Momo. A graduate of St. Xavier&amp;rsquo;s Kolkata, he along with his partner started Wow! Momo immediately after graduation at the age of 21. A passionate speaker with active Oratory skills, Sagar has given business &amp;amp; motivational talks at various Business Schools &amp;amp; Entrepreneurship Cells across the country.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/RohitBayana.jpg" style="width: 300px; height: 300px;" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Rohit Bayana&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Rohit Bayana is the Managing Partner and coFounder of Lumis Partners, a Private equity Fund. Rohit brings to bear strong experience in building, leading &amp;amp; scaling asset-light businesses while balancing Demand-Supply, working on both strong organic growth as well as acquisition led growth. Before Lumis Partners, Rohit was at GE, and in his last position, he was CEO of GE Software Solutions (later merged with Genpact). Rohit is a postgraduate from the London School of Economics and an Engineer in Computer Science from Delhi University.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>93399-TheThickShakeFactory.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements-news/wpp-outlines-strategy-for-growth-93398.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>11/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>WPP to spend £300m over three years for restructuring</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;WPP has announced the results of its strategic review, setting out a new plan to return the business to grow. The strategy reflects a new vision for WPP as a leader in creativity and technology. It incorporates a simpler, improved offer designed to capture the opportunities of a changing marketplace, and a streamlined structure built around the needs of clients. It also includes additional investments in creativity, technology and talent to enhance WPP&amp;rsquo;s proposition to clients and drive top-line growth.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;WPP expects to deliver organic growth (defined as like-for-like revenue less pass-through costs growth) in line with its peers at a headline operating profit margin (excluding associates) of at least 15% by the end of 2021 as a result of the strategy. The company will incur cash costs for restructuring of &amp;pound;300m over the next three years to deliver estimated annual savings of &amp;pound;275m by the end of 2021, approximately half of which will be reinvested in the business.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking about the announcement, Mark Read, Chief Executive Officer of WPP, said&amp;nbsp;&amp;ldquo;What we hear from clients is very consistent: they want our creativity, and they want us to help them transform their business in a world reshaped by technology. This is at the heart of what we do. &amp;ldquo;We are fundamentally repositioning WPP as a creative transformation company with a simpler offer that allows us to meet the present and future needs of clients. This more contemporary proposition has already helped us to win new business, including Volkswagen&amp;rsquo;s creative account in North America.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;He continued, &amp;ldquo;The restructuring of our business will enable increased investment in creativity, technology and talent, enhancing our capabilities in the categories with the greatest potential for future growth. As well as improving our offer and creating opportunities for clients, this investment will drive sustainable, profitable growth for our shareholders.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;We describe our approach as &amp;lsquo;radical evolution&amp;rsquo;: radical because we are taking decisive action and implementing major change; evolution because we will achieve this while respecting the things that make WPP the great company it is today&amp;quot; he added.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;WPP is hosting a presentation for investors and analysts&amp;nbsp;at its new headquarters in London.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Key points of the presentation, which will also be webcast, include:&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Opportunities in a Changing Industry&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Technology is rapidly reshaping our sector, presenting challenges but also opportunities. We believe the industry is facing structural change not structural decline. WPP is adapting at speed to capture these opportunities and to become even more client-centric than it is today.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Vision, Purpose and Identity&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;WPP&amp;rsquo;s vision is to be a creative transformation company, bringing together creativity and expertise in technology and data &amp;ndash; with the purpose of building better futures for its people and clients. This competitive positioning was developed in consultation with our people and clients, and is supported by a refreshed brand identity created by WPP agencies Superunion and Landor.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Simpler, Improved Offer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;WPP&amp;rsquo;s future offer will cover four areas: communications, experience, commerce and technology. Each of these areas is critical to success for modern clients, and by bringing them together the company will better serve clients&amp;rsquo; needs as they react to the changing marketplace, and expand WPP&amp;rsquo;s own business in high-growth sectors.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Communications focuses on advertising, content, media, public relations and public affairs, and healthcare.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Experience reflects the growing need of clients to create a new brand, product and service experiences.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Commerce allows WPP to expand its growing omnichannel commerce business and its work with brands to help them succeed in marketplaces such as Alibaba and Amazon.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Technology underpins WPP&amp;rsquo;s work with both CMOs and CIOs to build and operate marketing technology that supports their consumer- and customer-facing activities.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The areas of experience, commerce and technology already represent approximately one-quarter of WPP&amp;rsquo;s revenue.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Renewed Commitment to Creativity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;WPP&amp;rsquo;s most important competitive advantage is its creativity. It is what makes WPP special and what differentiates it from other professional services firms. WPP has significant creative strengths, having won the &amp;ldquo;Holding Company of the Year&amp;rdquo; award at the Cannes Lions International Festival of Creativity for seven consecutive years between 2011 and 2017 &amp;ndash; but the business must invest more in this area. As part of this strategic review, WPP is making a renewed commitment to creativity, investing an incremental &amp;pound;15m a year for the next three years in creative leadership, with a particular focus on the United States.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technology, Data, Partners &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;and&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt; Platforms&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Alongside creativity, the company will accelerate and promote its technology and data capabilities as clear sources of competitive advantage to WPP. They will follow a consistent approach across WPP by adopting a common technology strategy, leveraging the strengths of our unique technology partnerships, and making our significant existing capabilities in marketing and advertising technology available to all WPP companies for the benefit of our clients.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Simpler Structure&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;WPP has become too unwieldy, with too much duplication. As a result, it is not always as focused or as a fleet of foot as it needs to be to satisfy the needs of clients around the globe. Therefore, central to the new strategy is a simpler structure, built around the needs of clients, to allow easier access to WPP&amp;rsquo;s many resources. The structure is based on three principles:&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Clients: we will become a more client-centric organisation in order to deliver the best of WPP.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Companies: we will have fewer, more integrated companies equipped to adapt to a changing market.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Countries: we will integrate further at a country level to leverage our strengths in individual markets.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kantar&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;As previously announced, the Board of WPP has decided to develop Kantar with a potential strategic or financial partner, with WPP retaining a significant minority interest and strategic links with Kantar. Proposals will be evaluated on their financial and strategic benefits and if a transaction is agreed it is likely to be announced in the second quarter of 2019. Preparations are well underway and we have received numerous unsolicited expressions of interest.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Leadership, Talent and Culture&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;For the first time, WPP has established an Executive Committee drawn from both corporate and company leadership. This Executive Committee will work together to implement the new plan, and we will review the company&amp;rsquo;s incentive arrangements to align with the strategy. To make WPP the natural home for the best and brightest, and to attract the next generation of talent, we will champion a culture across WPP characterized by the values of openness, optimism and a commitment to extraordinary work.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Progress to Date:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Since April this year, the company has made consistent progress towards our goals. This includes the creation of the integrated networks VMLY&amp;amp;R and Wunderman Thompson; the alignment of our US healthcare agencies with integrated agency partners; and the elimination of the sub-holding company WPP Health &amp;amp; Wellness. VML, Y&amp;amp;R, Wunderman, J. Walter Thompson and WPP Health &amp;amp; Wellness collectively account for 23% of WPP revenue. WPP has also disposed of 16 non-core investments and associates, raising &amp;pound;704m to reduce our debt.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2018 and 2019 Outlook:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;WPP anticipates reporting full-year results in line with consensus expectations, with full-year like-for-like revenue less pass-through costs growth now expected to be closer to -0.5%. The company is beginning a multi-year improvement programme and 2019 will be a year of investment in the business with the execution of our cost-savings programme and further actions taken to return the company to long-term sustainable growth.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Previously announced account losses will create the anticipated headwind, particularly in the first half of the year.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Restructuring and Investment:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The company will incur cash costs for&amp;nbsp;of &amp;pound;300m restructuring over the next three years, reflecting actions to position the company for growth, address under-performing units and streamline our operations. The actions include:&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; The integration of VML and Y&amp;amp;R, and Wunderman and J. Walter Thompson.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Right-sizing and disposal of under-performing businesses.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Closure of unsustainable operations.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Further development of Campus co-locations.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Establishing a consistent, shared service infrastructure to support 30 countries over the next five years.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The annual savings from the actions are anticipated to be &amp;pound;275m by the end of 2021. WPP will reinvest approximately half of these savings into 2019 to 2021.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Future Capital Allocation Policy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The company has made good progress on its divestment of non-core assets, raising &amp;pound;704m from 16 disposals to date. We continue to target a reduction in average net debt to EBITDA ratio to within our revised target range of 1.50-1.75x by 2021. Over the next three years, WPP will prioritise the dividend over share buy-backs and will balance targeted M&amp;amp;A with divestments. The Board anticipates declaring a final dividend of 37.3p at the Preliminary Results to deliver a full-year dividend for the current financial year of 60p which it intends to maintain.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Medium-Term Financial Targets&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;As part of the strategic review, WPP has set out new medium-term financial targets that will allow the company to invest in talent and technology, improve its competitive position and deliver sustainable long-term growth rates. These are as follows, to be achieved by the end of 2021:&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Organic growth (defined as like-for-like revenue less pass-through costs growth) in line with peers&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Headline operating profit margin (excluding associates) of at least 15%&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull; Free cash flow conversion1 of 80%-90%&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>93398-wpp.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/announcements-news/harsh-rai-resigns-as-vp-and-general-manager-of-sales-pepsico-93397.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>11/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Harsh Rai resigns as VP and General Manager of Sales, PepsiCo</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Harsh Rai, VP and General Manager of Sales, PepsiCo has resigned from his post according to media reports. It has also been reported that Ajit Dheer, Managing Director of the Tata-PepsiCo joint venture company NourishCo, will succeed Rai. Rai has been with the company for more than a decade.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Rai has been a member of PepsiCo India&amp;#39;s executive committee since 2014 and has worked across functions, including general management, sales and distribution, and business model transformation. He was also responsible for the snacks business, beverages business and also worked as the CEO &amp;amp; MD for NourishCo Beverages.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Prior to his work at PepsiCo, he worked with Wipro Consumer Care and Lighting as General Manager.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>93397-HarshRai.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/account-news/kurl-on-awards-creative-mandate-to-fcb-ulka-93396.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>11/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Kurl-on awards creative mandate to FCB Ulka</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;FCB Ulka has partnered with&amp;nbsp;Kurl- on for their creative mandate. FCB Ulka will service the iconic brand from the Bangalore office. FCB Ulka was awarded the mandate following a multi-agency pitch. Kurl-on is India&amp;#39;s leading brand of mattresses, furniture and furnishing products in India. The company was founded in 1962 by Ramesh Pai. With state-of-the-art technology, Kurl-on endeavors to improve standards in the Indian mattress and furniture industry besides being in tune with the changing needs of the Indian consumer. The brand is available across India through 7000+ multi-brand outlets, 920+ franchise outlets, and 35 exclusive brand outlets across the country today.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The company manufactures mattresses in 126 different configurations. Pan-India, they have partnered with a network comprising more than 10,000+ dealers, 72 branch &amp;amp; stock points and 10 strategically located manufacturing facilities across Karnataka, Orissa, Madhya Pradesh, Uttaranchal and Gujarat. The company was formerly known as Karnataka Consumer Products Limited and changed its name to Kurl-on Limited in 1995.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking on the occasion, Ashutosh Vaidya, CMO, Kurlon, said, &amp;ldquo;Kurlon is a brand undergoing an immense transformation from being known as India&amp;rsquo;s largest selling mattress brand to becoming a leader in cutting edge technologically driven home comfort products. We wanted an agency that could understand this vision and work with us through the journey of achieving collaborative success. We met many agencies through a pitch process, but FCB Ulka stood out in their ability to translate our market ambitions with a clear strategy, differentiated creativity and a unique understanding of the digital ecosystem. We are confident of this partnership and look forward to meeting milestones together&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the win, Theresa Ronnie, Vice President, FCB Ulka- Bangalore said, Kurl-on is a great brand with an impressive presence in the Indian market. They wanted an agency partner who understood their business aspirations. We, in turn, were very impressed with their ability to understand and seek the differentiation that good creativity brings to brand growth. We are encouraged by the quality of the partnership thus far and hope to build a new chapter for Brand Kurl-on together&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Adding to this, Romit Nair, Creative Head, FCB Ulka- Bangalore, said, &amp;lsquo;&amp;rsquo;I believe this is the start of something big and beautiful. We are really excited to partner Kurl-on on the next phase of their journey and hope to create a strong relationship that leads to some beautiful work.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>93396-KurlonFCBUlka.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital-news/most-viewed-videos-of-2018-93300.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>11/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Most viewed videos of 2018</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;The power of social media is so huge that it requires no time to make one become famous. It recognises true and unrecognised talents and has given them a platform to display their unique skills. The year 2018 witnessed a bunch of videos going viral making the person depicted in it, famous. From winking girl to daily wager, who is a singing sensation, the list of people who became famous through social media never ends.&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at some of the videos that went viral in the&amp;nbsp;year 2018.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Winking Girl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Priya Prakash Varrier took the internet by storm by a wink. The 19-year model-actress from Kerala was seen winking in a 30 second clip from a song from the movie &amp;lsquo;Oru Adaar Love&amp;rsquo;. It didn&amp;rsquo;t take much time for Varrier to become global sensation. Meltwater, the global media intelligence company, tracked and analysed mentions of the film and of Varrier across online, editorial and social media. According to reports, &amp;lsquo;Oru Adaar Love&amp;rsquo; and Varrier were mentioned 2,723 times on editorial media and 89,785 times on social media globally, in the second week of February.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Varrier has around 6.5 M + followers on Instagram and 6 lakh+ followers on Facebook. The song has garnered 82 +Million views on YouTube. She was signed for Nestle Munch advertisement and a South Indian shopping mall, even before her first movie release.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/W0fKl43QmIE?rel=0&amp;amp;wmode=transparent" width="100%"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dancing Uncle&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Sanjeev Shrivastava fondly known as Dancing Uncle became a sensation overnight with his &amp;lsquo;Govinda&amp;rsquo; dance moves. A video of Shrivastava dancing at a wedding has gone viral in the month of June.&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Bajaj Allianz Life Insurance capitalised on Shrivastava&amp;rsquo;s popularity and quickly roped him for their latest announcement of a one-time special bonus for their policyholders. The video saw him dancing to Bajaj Allianz Life&amp;rsquo;s new jingle &amp;lsquo;Samjho Ho Gaya&amp;rsquo; that captures the essence of the brand&amp;rsquo;s new philosophy &amp;lsquo;Life Goals. DONE&amp;rsquo;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;His Twitter account @Dabbuthe dancer has 8.2K followers.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/dvQb76sRR2E?rel=0&amp;amp;wmode=transparent" width="100%"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Singing Baby from Andhra Pradesh&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;In the month of November, Baby, a native of East Godavari district of Andhra Pradesh &amp;nbsp;was seen in a viral video singing &amp;lsquo;O Cheliya&amp;rsquo; from the movie Premikudu, Telugu version of A R Rahman&amp;rsquo;s popular song &amp;lsquo;Ennavale&amp;rsquo; from the movie Kadhalan. Rahman himself shared the video captioned &amp;lsquo;unknown, anonymous, beautiful voice&amp;rsquo;. The video got millions of shares and likes in no time. She has got her Tollywood break in the&amp;nbsp;movie &amp;#39;Palasa 1978&amp;#39;.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe frameborder="0" height="476" rel="nofollow" scrolling="no" src="https://www.facebook.com/plugins/video.php?href=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.facebook.com%2Farrahman%2Fvideos%2F524106481413224%2F&amp;amp;show_text=0&amp;amp;" style="border:none;overflow:hidden" width="261"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The daily wager who caught Shankar Mahadevan&amp;rsquo;s attention&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;In the month of July a daily wager went viral with his song &amp;lsquo;Unai Kaanadhu Naan Indru Naal Illaye&amp;rsquo; from actor Kamal Haasan starrer film &amp;lsquo;Vishwaroopam&amp;rsquo;. The video was shared by singer Shankar Mahadevan who sang the original song asking people to help him to identify the singer in the video. The person was identified as Rakesh Unni, a daily wager from Kerala who sang during break from his work has met Kamal Hassan and sang for the actor. &amp;nbsp;Unni is soon to get a break in play back singing.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" rel="nofollow" src="https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/ZzRqbwiC914?rel=0&amp;amp;wmode=transparent" width="100%"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>93300-PriyaVarrier.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital-news/sir-martin-sorrell-has-shopping-plans-in-india-93394.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>11/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Sir Martin Sorrell has plans to buy agencies in India</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Sir Martin Sorrell is in India with plans to shop for agencies in content, data, and media planning space. According to Sorrell, these three sectors are the main focus areas of S4 Capital and he will be interested in pure independent digital agencies and agencies that have broken away from networks and large agencies. Sorrell hopes that his company S4 Capital is seen as a new kid on the block with a different strategy.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Speaking at an event in Mumbai on Monday evening, Sorrell said that version 3.0 of his avatar will be all about technology. &amp;ldquo;The 10 most important companies right now are Google, Facebook, Amazon, Tencent, Alibaba, Apple, Microsoft, Oracle, Salesforce, and Adobe. I would like S4 to be a royalty of the growth of all those companies.&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Calling Google, Facebook, Amazon, Tencent, Alibaba, Apple, and Microsoft &amp;lsquo;seven sisters&amp;rsquo;, he said the last time a group of companies was referred to as &amp;lsquo;seven sisters&amp;rsquo; was with the oil giants. &amp;ldquo;Jeff Bezos is like the John D Rockefeller of today,&amp;rdquo; he said. Sorrell noted that the last bunch of &amp;lsquo;seven sisters&amp;rsquo; were regulated and the same might happen to the current &amp;lsquo;seven sisters&amp;rsquo;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Sorrell broadly spoke about the pressures on the agency business and the disruptions that are shaping the market. He said that agencies are mainly suffering because of pressure from clients and not only because of &amp;lsquo;frenemies&amp;rsquo; like Google &amp;amp; Facebook, competition from consulting companies, and in-housing.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Sorrell felt that mergers of legacy agencies with digital agencies like in the case of JWT with Wunderman and VML with Y&amp;amp;R may affect the brand and image of the older and more established agency. &amp;ldquo;JWT is more well-known in India than Wunderman. Now if people call it Wunderman, there could be a problem. I do believe in the strength of the brands and they have value,&amp;rdquo; he said.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;In the face of the large-scale mergers that WPP has initiated over the last few months, Sorrell said that the senior management of a multinational company like WPP should visit other markets. &amp;ldquo;The senior management of WPP has not visited Latam and Asia in the last six months. If you are going to make structural changes that result in losing 7,500 jobs out of the 135,000 jobs you have, there is a responsibility to visit those places and explain the decision.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Prior to his India trip, Sorrell&amp;rsquo;s S4 Capital bought San Francisco ad tech company MightyHive. It was his second acquisition since leaving WPP and setting up S4 Capital. He made his first acquisition in July with a &amp;euro;300m deal to buy Dutch company MediaMonks.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Before Sorrell arrived in Mumbai, he attended the pre-wedding celebrations of Mukesh Ambani&amp;rsquo;s daughter Isha Ambani in Udaipur.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>93394-MartinSorrell.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/advertising-news/why-the-sudden-rise-in-ccos-quitting-and-switching-jobs-93390.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>11/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Why the sudden rise in CCOs quitting and switching jobs?</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;The last two weeks have witnessed a number of Chief Creative Officer (CCO) movements. Ajay Gahlaut recently quit as chief creative officer of Ogilvy North and deputy chief creative officer, Ogilvy India. Gahlaut is expected to&amp;nbsp;join Publicis, replacing Bobby Pawar who is slated&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;to join Havas Media in January.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Ashish Chakravarty quit Contract India to join McCann India as creative head while Sagar Mahabalaleshwarkar has taken on Chakravarty&amp;rsquo;s place at Contract.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The question here is,&amp;nbsp;what has changed all of a sudden&amp;nbsp;to lead to such a large-scale churn? As per the owner of a manpower search agency specializing in ad and media hiring, &amp;ldquo;It is a result of ad firms trying to reinvent themselves to keep pace with the rise of digital, which have upended the marketing business.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;With digital coming in, creativity has become&amp;nbsp;far more complicated than it used to be. Agencies, regardless of their respective sizes, need to keep reviewing how they are coping (or not) with the digital wave.&amp;nbsp;Hence, overhauling existing creative teams is one of the priorities, points out a former CCO turned independent ad-man. &amp;ldquo;Digital has, of course, changed a lot. Agencies are now creating hundreds, if not thousands pieces of creative, a month. This rise of social media and platforms in general has meant that creativity is more targeted than ever. So most large agencies are constantly re-evaluating the positions and talent pool.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Sandeep Goyal, former President of Rediffusion and ex Chairman of Dentsu India remarks that there is paucity of talent at that level. &amp;quot;Most creative directors of certain seniority and stature set up creative shops of their own in recent years leaving fewer and fewer talent available for employment by agencies. &amp;quot; Goyal opines that the bigger problem is that these creative satraps also invariably carry some creative followers into their new agencies. So a lot of attrition and turmoil all around. &amp;quot;Network pressure today is simply how many global awards you pocket, how much new biz you win. Earlier it was not easy to quantity and compare. Now it is. Laggards are always under pressure. Quitting &amp;lsquo;for better prospects&amp;rsquo; is the easy way out,&amp;quot; he explains.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The job-list of a CCO entails&amp;nbsp;supervising the creative team, directing their output, developing design concepts that further the company&amp;rsquo;s identity to anticipating the future direction of the industry using research and insight and bringing the company in fore of that trajectory.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Industry sources share that one of the biggest shifts has been the network-pressures, which can also be attributed to the high churn rate. &amp;ldquo;Agencies today are angling to ingrain themselves deeper within client&amp;rsquo;s businesses, to centralize themselves closer to the bottom line. The revenue streams are being attacked on various fronts which does lead to cost-cutting. One being given the polite exit signal under a cost-cutting mission is the &amp;lsquo;new&amp;rsquo; normal in the business,&amp;rdquo; shared an ad-agency co-founder on condition of anonymity.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Another source argues that in case anything goes wrong, a CCO is one of the most visible heads. Besides, a CCO who merely handles ad campaigns and branding consistency is a missed opportunity. &amp;ldquo;CCOs today end up being easier scapegoats if the business isn&amp;#39;t doing too well. Infact, this person needs a seat at the table when executive business plans are being created and the leverage to present big interruptions and lead the team through strategic brainstorming too. This remains one reason they&amp;#39;re likely to want to quit or switch their work culture,&amp;quot; said the source.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>93390-cco.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/digital-news/facebook-and-twitters-public-policy-experts-root-for-addressing-digital-addiction-93361.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>11/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Facebook and Twitter’s public policy experts root for addressing digital addiction</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:10.0pt; margin-left:0cm; text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;While the rise of social media has given us countless benefits, the flip side of it is gradually becoming the new focus area. Issues such as trolls, data safety and digital addiction are being spoken about more vocally than before and social media platforms such as Facebook and Twitter are taking due cognizance to address these concerns.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:10.0pt; margin-left:0cm; text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;At a recent event in New Delhi, Ankhi Das, Public Policy Director, Facebook -India, South &amp;amp; Central Asia; and Mahima Kaul, Head, Public Policy &amp;amp; Government Partnerships, Twitter India; spoke about the issue of &amp;lsquo;digital revolution and social challenges&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:10.0pt; margin-left:0cm; text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Answering a question on the increasing addiction to social platforms like Facebook and the way to deal with it, Ankhi Das said, &amp;ldquo;We are creating a &amp;lsquo;time spent&amp;rsquo; dashboard and it will&amp;nbsp;help to self-regulate.&amp;nbsp; Also I think it is the responsibility of all of us as a society&amp;nbsp;to address it. We have created a network of safety partners and mental health&amp;nbsp;experts,&amp;nbsp;including institutions like Tata Institute of Social Sciences, to tackle it.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:10.0pt; margin-left:0cm; text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Das also spoke about Facebook&amp;rsquo;s thrust on promoting regional languages and reaching out to people beyond the big cities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:10.0pt; margin-left:0cm; text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&amp;ldquo;Facebook has been upgraded to be available in 16 Indian languages. A lot of consumption is happening in the local languages. If you look at the way media is getting consumed, the patterns of consumption are changing in terms of being more visual and more towards video.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:10.0pt; margin-left:0cm; text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;She also spoke about the collapse of information barriers, something that social media platforms like Facebook have enabled.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:10.0pt; margin-left:0cm; text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&amp;ldquo;The way we access information has changed drastically.&amp;nbsp; People, especially youngster students, don&amp;#39;t have barriers to information today,&amp;rdquo; said Das.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:10.0pt; margin-left:0cm; text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Mahima Kaul of Twitter spoke about the correct use of the micro blogging platform and how the government has made it an effective tool to reach out to public at large.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:10.0pt; margin-left:0cm; text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;&amp;quot;If you see, the government is using Twitter in the most efficient way. You can find all the ministries on this platform and they share important information through this platform&amp;rdquo;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:10.0pt; margin-left:0cm; text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;Answering a question about the rampant issue of trolling and safety on social media platforms, Kaul said, &amp;quot;There are many product features within the platform that can tackle these issues and most of the users don&amp;#39;t know about them. And when they do, it becomes easier to&amp;nbsp;deal with trolls and address other such concerns.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-top:0cm; margin-right:0cm; margin-bottom:10.0pt; margin-left:0cm; text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:12pt"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;,serif"&gt;The event was organised by&amp;nbsp;Jagran Group.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin:0cm 0cm 8pt; margin-right:0cm; margin-left:0cm"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>93361-Jagran-event-pic.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/people-movement-news/freakout-appoints-narayan-murthy-ivaturi-to-its-board-of-directors-93395.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>11/12/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>FreakOut appoints Narayan Murthy Ivaturi to its Board of Directors</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;FreakOut, the global marketing technology company, part of FreakOut Holdings, has appointed Narayan Murthy Ivaturi to its Board of Directors. FreakOut has also elevated Ivaturi to the role of Global Chief Operating Officer for its adtech&amp;nbsp;business.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The appointment is in recognition of Narayan&amp;rsquo;s pivotal contributions to FreakOut&amp;rsquo;s strategic growth, including launching the next wave of FreakOut&amp;rsquo;s digital solutions and building out key programmatic partnerships across both the supply and demand sides.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;In his expanded remit, Narayan will lead the newly consolidated adtech business across all 16 markets where FreakOut is currently present. He will work on enhancing local and international product partnerships with publishers, strengthening supply partnerships and orchestrating M&amp;amp;A in line with FreakOut&amp;rsquo;s expansion agenda.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the appointment, Yuzuru Honda, CEO and President &amp;ndash; FreakOut Holdings, Inc.&amp;nbsp;said, &amp;ldquo;We are delighted to have Narayan join the board as our adtech business enters the next phase of its growth strategy. We believe the refreshed board and management team are committed to achieving outstanding performance and maximizing our corporate value.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The consolidation of FreakOut&amp;rsquo;s adtech business is poised to deliver immense value to advertisers and publishers by streamlining product lines and technologies. As a result, clients will have access to FreakOut&amp;rsquo;s multi-faceted product portfolio in Japan, including Programmatic SSP with native in-feed display and video formats. The diverse product access, coupled with FreakOut&amp;rsquo;s network of 3000 premium publishers, will enable clients to maximize the global reach of their marketing campaigns.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking on his new role, Ivaturi said: &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m really excited to be part of a team that shares my passion and vision. I&amp;rsquo;m very grateful to FreakOut&amp;rsquo;s board and am looking forward to building a formidable global offering, and making FreakOut the first choice for advertisers and publishers.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Ivaturi&amp;rsquo;s role is effective immediately.&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>93395-NarayanMurthyIvaturi.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
</urlset>
