<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9" xmlns:image="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-image/1.1" xmlns:news="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-news/0.9">
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/spotlight-news/why-tv-continues-to-be-the-first-love-of-advertisers-92122.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>18/09/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Why TV continues to be the first love of advertisers </news:title>
      <news:description>Digital has become quite the buzzword for advertisers in the last couple of years. Almost all big brands are now present on online platforms and no marketing strategy is considered complete without the inclusion of digital. In fact, according to recent KPMG report&amp;nbsp;'Media Ecosystem: The wall falls down',&amp;nbsp;digital advertising revenues registered a growth of 35 per cent in FY18 to reach Rs 11,600 crore. Television, meanwhile, had a relatively subdued year in FY18, with the overall revenue growing at a slower rate of 9.5 per cent to reach Rs 65,200 crore. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;While there is no doubt that digital has become a must-have for brands today and is growing fast, it is also no secret that television is still the preferred medium for advertisers. So, what is it that keeps the advertiser-television relationship going strong? Also, going ahead, will TV continue to be the first love of advertisers or will the digital push change the equation? We spoke to some experts for the answers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to Sanjiv Mehta, CEO &amp;amp; MD, HUL, television is and will remain relevant in the country for many decades to come.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Today technology enables us to design digital communication and geo-target with personalised plans. However, some things will not change. The marketing fundamentals will remain the same. The consumer will remain at the heart of marketing. New-age content will take us to the art of new storytelling. But it would be seriously immature to write the obituary of television. Television is and will remain relevant for many decades to come in the country. But what makes people succeed in the art of being ambidextrous is balancing the online with the offline,” says Mehta.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayank Shah, Category Head, Parle Products, says that TV is the preferred medium for brands&amp;nbsp;mainly because of its sheer reach. He feels that it makes sense for brands to advertise on TV as it ensures mass targeting. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“There is no doubt that digital is growing and it is also an important medium. But when it comes to reach, especially for mass brands such as FMCG or daily need items, TV works better. For some time, TV will continue to have an edge over digital. Digital is the platform for brands that want to target a certain segment of audience,” he explains.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Neel Kamal Sharma, COO-Buying, Madison World, says that despite losing 1 per cent share last year, television tops the advertising chart.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Yes, digital advertising revenues have been growing in India and the trend will continue. However, television is still sitting on the top of the advertising revenue pie despite losing 1 per cent share last year,” he says. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sharma adds, “Since total advertising is growing at 12 per cent and digital at 25 per cent, well-established mediums such as TV and print are likely to lose their share in the future. But the relevance of television remains. TV is the first love of FMCG players, the biggest advertising category. Also, digital-skewed categories such as smartphone, travel and even OTT platforms use TV to drive their growth.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Categories such as FMCG, telecom, BFSI, real estate and e-commerce are the main growth drivers for digital media, but some of these have a big presence in the traditional media as well. With an increase in the consumption of content such as news, entertainment and sports on digital platforms, consumers, especially the younger generation, have drifted away from traditional media and so many TV-heavy categories such as FMCG and telecom are now also using digital platforms extensively.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chandramohan Mehra, Chief Marketing Officer, Bajaj Allianz Life Insurance, feels that the two mediums will continue to co-exist, for the next 3 to 5 years at least.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Firstly, the selection of media is the function of strategic objectives. Choice of TV or digital depends on the task at hand. Largely, for brands, an integrated approach is far more effective. TV can deliver reach while digital can deepen brand engagement. At least for the next 3 to 5 years, both the mediums will continue to co-exist despite the exponential growth rate of digital,” Mehra says.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As per the KPMG report, mature TV and digital markets like the US are witnessing a shift of viewers from TV to digital-only consumption on the back of price arbitrage and strong digital infrastructure. But in India, TV offers a strong proposition in terms of price and content along with continued headroom for growth. Also, there is a lack of depth in digital infrastructure, especially fixed-line internet. As a result, digital consumption appears to be largely complementary to TV, enabling latent individual viewing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to Ravish Kumar, Head– Regional TV Network, Viacom 18, TV is the single largest and cost-effective medium for reaching out to consumers. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;He says, “TV is measured very beautifully. Hence, you know exactly how much you are getting in terms of measurement. In that way, digital has a long way to go. In terms of content, the two are complementing each other, but digital has a lot to learn from TV and vice- versa. However, overall, TV remains the preferred medium for brands.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vidhu Sagar, National Director - PointNine Lintas at MullenLowe Lintas Group, also believes that it is always different strokes for different folks. He thinks that one general approach can’t be applied to all kind of audience. &lt;br&gt;Sagar says, “The kind of media fragmentation that is taking place today, you can’t have the same old approach of going with one broadcast medium and carrying one large creative message and letting everything else follow. In a way, such kind of an approach doesn't work anymore because things have drastically changed in the last 10 years. However, even in this changed reality, any brand that is launching cannot do without television and in many cases even print.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“You can have video assets for some segments of the market on digital, but if you want to impact the overall structure and want a business of big magnitude, you will need television. If you want to add a qualitative aspect to your brand, in terms of stature, respect and credibility, you must go with the broadcast media,” he adds.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The KPMG report states that&amp;nbsp;digital advertisements have become mainstream in India, with digital ad spends expected to cross Rs 40,000 crore in FY 2023.1. In FY 2017, digital advertising contributed Rs 86.2 billion and is expected to grow at a rapid pace with a compounded annual growth rate (CAGR) of 30.9 per cent until 2023.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sagar mentions, “Digital has grown very rapidly, but the overall advertising budget hasn't grown in that manner for most advertisers. And so, clearly, digital is earning its revenue cutting into the share of other media. Most noticeably, it's happening at the cost of weaker media like radio, cinema, OOH and to some extent also print. Magazines are almost dead now, and also television, in some cases, may be getting impacted. But knowing that television has its own threshold cost of entry, it's not that the client will suddenly cut television and get on digital.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Indian OTT industry is currently driven by AVOD or a freemium model and SVOD is still at a nascent stage, with 2-2.4 million subscribers having directly subscribed to OTT platforms, in addition to the ones who are considered paid subscribers through telco-based access. While such telco-based subscriptions have increased in the last year, advertisement revenues have faced challenges with falling CPM rates on account of increasing ad inventory and lack of a standardised, third-party validated digital measurement tool. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Girish Menon, Partner and Head, KPMG, explains, “At the moment, CPM at digital is lower. India’s CPM is much lower than what others get on digital. That's one of the reasons why digital struggles. What you earn from digital is less than what you earn for a one-page advertising in print. Hence, that's why you need ROI and measurement to come through before the CPM starts increasing.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meanwhile, according to the KPMG report, from a relatively subdued run in FY’18, the television is expected to bounce back and continue on the growth trajectory it has been on for the last few years. The growth in TV consumption across most of the genres, coupled with traction on live and catch-up TV being viewed on digital platforms, points to the fact that television is likely to continue being the dominant mode of media consumption in India. &lt;br&gt;Television is expected to grow at a CAGR of 12.6 per cent because of growing penetration, strong advertising demand on the back of domestic consumption and major events (two cricket world cups and general elections in the next five years) and support from better distribution realisations due to digitisation.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1537240350_fXu93V_spotlight.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/spotlight-news/inside-the-changing-world-of-pr-corporate-communications-91662.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>20/08/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Inside the changing world of PR &amp; Corporate Communications</news:title>
      <news:description>The landscape of communications industry has undergone a major shift over the years. Traditionally, PR agencies have been into media releases,&amp;nbsp;client management and media relations. Now, in its re-imagined form, PR is not just about media relations and employee communication, but it is also&amp;nbsp;being used increasingly for customer relations, strategic communication, crisis management and brand building. PR has now evolved into a high-level management profession that deals with the core values of an organisation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/files/1534734393_zSDNti_spotlight_graphic.jpg" style="width:278px;height:496px;float:right"&gt;We spoke to some communications professionals who have seen the industry go through a cultural and contextual shift to understand the changing dynamics. According to Kunal Kishore, Founder Director, Value 360 Communications Pvt Ltd, the PR industry has become more comprehensive today than ever before. &lt;br&gt;He said, “It would be an understatement to say that the PR industry has seen a strategic shift over the years. In my opinion, the evolution of the domain can more aptly be called paradigmatic. From being heavily invested in one-way communications via the print and broadcast media, the space has become more comprehensive today with the advent of the digital. Two-way conversations have become de rigueur to engage with new-age audiences who have a voice of their own and robust channels to express the same.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kishore feels that brands can no longer afford to simply talk at their target customers. “They need to engage in conversations that are meaningful and relevant by effectively leveraging digital media, offline activations, and traditional media. The rise of social influencers has further changed the game of branding and marketing, in a way obliterating the practice of hard selling. Brand messages need to be far more subtle and yet far more compelling today than ever before. Shareability and likeability have become critical parameters for brand communications,” added Kishore.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lavang Khare, Senior VP, Adfactors-PR, believes that PR has seen an interesting onward journey in India and has undergone a complete metamorphosis. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;She says, “PR plays an extremely important role in marketing and is the fifth ‘P’ that sits in the board rooms in India (along with price, product, promotion and place). The Indian PR industry is still about earned media, but is not restricted to journalists. The influencers are now bloggers, analysts, industry experts and many other stakeholders who matter in any industry.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“In the current context, in India therefore, the strategic shift is clearly seen in the presence of communications people in C-suite meetings and the way they influence and drive the corporate strategy. The big change is the way content is curated for social media and how it is strategically leveraged,” said Khare.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kishore also thinks that while digital has opened up a world of possibilities and made the PR function more critical than ever, it has also made the branding exercise more complex and competitive. “PR campaigns can no longer be planned in isolation and can no longer revolve around putting across the brand's message alone. They need to be contextual and nuanced. They need to place the customer at the core of the communications. This has challenged all the practitioners to be more creative, innovative and strategic, while also making the entire domain of PR more exciting than it has ever been,” he explains.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to Seema Siddiqui, AGM &amp;amp; Head, PR and Corporate Communication, Schneider Electric-India, “Smart mobility and digitisation have disrupted the PR space dramatically. With it has changed the way organisations are managing their reputation and brand image with their stakeholders and beyond. More often than not, speed is of essence in corporates’ engagement with individuals and other businesses --not just in crises but also for regular inflow of information that can be impacted if the so called ‘stitch’ is not made in time.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“As we navigate the rough and tumble of real time and the without-filter engagement, the one great outcome has been the way in which corporates have become real and reachable and as much invested in social commitment and politics of the day as an individual. There has hardly been a time as interesting as now to do PR, neither as challenging,” said Siddiqui. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Independent communication consultant Anup Sharma believes that the role of PR firms and in-house corporate communication teams has changed from being a support function to being a key function in developing and implementing strategies to control the narratives and manage truth-trust-transparency. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Today PR firms are working on programmes not only to create awareness, protect and improve reputation but also to produce revenues.  With digital (social) media being the communication channel of choice, now the power to control message has moved directly in the hands of stakeholders, including the competition/haters. So, PR is moving from a broadcast model to an engagement model and PR firms are now working on integrated communication models to share knowledge and findings and create engaging content,” believes Sharma.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1534732231_7V5Iz9_PR_industry.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/spotlight-news/margin-pressures-push-industry-to-find-solutions-to-pitch-discount-issue-91580.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>13/08/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Margin pressures push industry to find solutions to ‘pitch discount’ issue</news:title>
      <news:description>“In a free market, only demand and supply determine prices,” said the head of a leading agency when asked to respond to the concerns raised by the Indian Broadcasting Foundation (IBF) on ‘pitch discount rates’. Last week, IBF Director Punit Goenka sent an email to all agency heads asking them to abstain from the practice of offering discounts to clients on behalf of broadcasters without prior approval from them. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mail, a first-of-its-kind initiative by an industry body, intends to put a halt to a practice that has been discouraged vehemently during several IBF meetings in the last one year. Though the practice hurts the agencies that work primarily on commissions, it hurts broadcasters more.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Industry experts unanimously claim that with increasing competition and technology playing a larger role than talent, pricing is the biggest factor driving pitches.&amp;nbsp;Another factor that has worked against the business is the growing role of consultancies. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to a&amp;nbsp;senior agency head, “Consultants are increasingly putting pressure on clients to cut on advertising margins, which puts further pressure on our pricing. They have also contributed significantly in reducing the trust we shared with our clients. Brands are calling pitches sooner than before. There have been times when we were forced to quote a lesser price than our previous pitch held three years ago, just because we wanted to retain our client.” &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;While everyone in the industry is concerned about and affected by diminishing profit&amp;nbsp;margins, will a mail, merely asking the agencies to abstain from offering discounts, work as a solution to a larger problem that the industry is grappling with for the last few years?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Raj Nayak, COO -Viacom18, lauded IBF’s initiative but said that it needs two hands to clap. “Broadcasters are equally responsible. We need to find a solution within ourselves too. Just an agreement in letter and spirit among even the top five-six networks, that they will not reduce the rate given to an incumbent agency when the account shifts, itself will solve the problem. At the end of the day, it is broadcasters who are succumbing to pressure because of lack of unity and the advertiser is taking advantage of this.” &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I don’t blame the agencies because they have no skin in the game and they will do anything to retain a client or acquire new business. Having said this, there should also be a stringent punishment which could even mean cancelling the agency’s accreditation if they continue to disregard the IBF guidance on pitching for new business and work in a manner that is against the overall growth of the industry,” Nayak told exchange4media &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ashish Sehgal, COO of Zee Unimedia, however, believes that the problem is much more complex. The industry needs to introspect the need to shift its focus back on quality, he said. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Media is being commoditised and pitching is not at all focused on strategy to capture relevant target audience thereby right media mix, but only on pricing. From a specialist role, it has moved to the role of procurement where the sole objective is to put more and more pressure on the marketing heads to reduce budgets.” &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“However, what needs to be understood is that with the fragmentation and segmentation of the market, creation of content as well as marketing have not only become challenging but also expensive. Hence, it is critical that we get right pricing from the advertisers, else the industry will eventually collapse," he adds.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Agency heads, however, bring the issue back to the principles of economics.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We are perfectly fine with broadcasters fixing whatever rates they want to, but then there should be unity. If the industry shows a positive growth, we all will benefit from it. At the end of the day, our purpose is to drive the business,” said an agency head.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another agency head added that the issue needs to be resolved by tripartite discussions among&amp;nbsp;broadcasters, agency heads and marketers. All three need to sit together and form a consensus in the larger interest of the industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We all have our own compulsions driving our decisions. It’s a free market. I have to protect my business and hold my clients back and win new clients. I have every right to get them the lowest price. If not me, someone else will. Therefore, the solution will only come from a discussion among all three verticals of the industry,” said the agency head.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nayak, meanwhile, added that another area IBF needs to put its foot down is the long-pending issue of CPT. “We have been dragging this for too long. With the universe expanding, the broadcasters are not getting fair value but the content &amp;amp; other input costs are going up. We cannot keep procrastinating this anymore,” he said.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;THE PRINT SAGA&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;The issue of ‘pitch discount rates’ has affected the print industry alike. Hormusji N Cama, Chairman, of Indian Newspaper Society (INS) has already raised the issue with the Advertising Agencies Association of India (AAAI) and would soon be taking it with each agency one on one.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We jointly took the decision that the agencies would not do it. And in case they do, INS henceforth will take action,” he told exchange4media. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When asked if the action could include something as serious as cancellation of accreditation of agencies, Cama said that in extreme cases, the association may even consider that.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The owner of a leading publishing house also raised his concerns over diminishing margins. “In many cases, we told the agencies to bear the loss on committing a lesser rate on our behalf. Why should I suffer the loss,” said the publisher.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another publisher complained that agencies are pushing the ads from print to digital where the margins are higher. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Digital gives a commission ranging from 20-30% whereas print only gives you 2-3%. Therefore, there is an ongoing movement against publishers and towards digital. I am not saying that digital is not growing, but the projections are hyped as compared to print by agencies to get higher margins,” said another leading publisher.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1534127974_q9pWbX_spotlight_collage.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/spotlight-news/newsprint-price-spike-may-burden-print-industry-with-over-rs-4-600-cr-additional-cost-91333.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>30/07/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Newsprint price spike may burden print industry with over Rs 4,600 cr additional cost</news:title>
      <news:description>Despite the death&amp;nbsp;of print media in most parts of&amp;nbsp;the world, newspapers in&amp;nbsp;India&amp;nbsp;have not only managed to survive but have also shown growth. However, with the recent spike in newsprint price, some feel the doomsday might not be far. The rise in newsprint price would mean an annual burden of more than Rs 4600 crore for&amp;nbsp;the print industry in India. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why the Situation?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;With an increase in raw material cost, downfall of Indian rupee against US dollar and China imposing a ban on import of paper waste, the&amp;nbsp;newsprint price has sky-rocketed. The situation looks worrisome for the industry because newsprint, which is the major raw material and represents nearly&amp;nbsp;30-40% of the overall spend, has seen a spike of over 50% in its price. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last year around the same time, the rate of US dollar was Rs 64.16 while today it is Rs 68.62. In August 2017, the price of newsprint was around Rs 36,000 per tonne, while now the price has reached around Rs 55,000 per tonne. Annual demand in India for newsprint is around 2.6 million tonnes. The difference in these&amp;nbsp;prices&amp;nbsp;show an over 50% hike in the price of newsprint. At this rate, the industry is estimated to lose more than Rs 4600 crore annually (some&amp;nbsp;waste newsprint is returned by the publishers).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pauly, General Manager, Metro Vaartha, a Malayalam language daily newspaper published from Kochi, told exchange4media, “Previously, the price was around Rs 36-37 per kg, now it has increased to Rs 55-56 per kg. Imported newsprint price in August 2017 was Rs 35,000/tonne, which has increased to Rs 55,000-56,000k/tonne.” &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaking about the situation the industry is stuck in, Jwalant Swaroop, former CEO of Sakal and Lokmat publications, said, “With dollar becoming expensive, those using more foreign newsprint will be impacted adversely. Largely, English dailies.” &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The impact of newsprint price was also quite visible on HT Media’s Q1FY19 statement that showed a net profit drop of around 86%.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;“Our operating performance was also impacted by higher newsprint prices,” Shobhana Bhartia, Chairperson and Editorial Director, HT Media Ltd and Hindustan Media Ventures Ltd, had said in her statement.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In addition to the spike in newsprint price, lack of clarity on the actual user of newsprint in India has also created an issue. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to a member of the Indian Newsprint Manufacturers’ Association, earlier, only registered mills and publishers could avail concessional taxes. However, after the implementation of GST, third parties are also buying newsprint (which was earlier sold to them as other grade paper). This ambiguity has allowed them to manipulate the GST rates. (There is 5% GST on newsprint while 12% GST on other grade paper). The purchasing of newsprint by third parties&amp;nbsp;causes shortage of supply for publishers. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Impact on Industry&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;“As far as newsprint prices are concerned, it is locked for almost everybody this year. Because the newsprint orders go about 6-9 months in advance.&amp;nbsp;The higher cost of implication is already baked into the P&amp;amp;L financials of everybody. And hence, some may even go into losses on account of newsprint costs alone. That is the reality of the industry,” Pradeep Dwivedi, Chief Executive Officer, Sakal Media Group, told exchange4media.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;With input cost increasing by over 50% and no definite means to compensate it, the impact on the industry has been estimated to be around Rs 4600 crore a year.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A top management official from another leading paper&amp;nbsp;told exchange4media, “The newsprint that we use to buy for $500 per tonne in 2017 is now costing around $750-$780. And we can’t increase the cover price. Also, there is no increase in ad rates. There is nothing that can be seen as a sign of relief. Our newspaper will lose around Rs 250 crore in a year. So newspapers larger than ours, such as the&amp;nbsp;Times of India and Hindustan Times, that use mostly imported newsprint will suffer higher losses.” &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pauly added, “We are spending almost Rs 40 lakh extra every month, but we will never reduce the circulation as it will affect our image.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaking on the condition of anonymity, a senior industry person from a large regional publication in southern India, told exchange4media, “The spike in cost is around 50-60% per cent if you take into consideration the devaluation of the Indian rupee. It is definitely a very difficult time, especially because advertising is not growing.” &lt;br&gt;He added that because of the price hike, the publication would be spending around Rs 80-90 crore more annually. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Cutting cost is one of the things we are looking at. In fact, we increased the cover price increased by Re1. It will bring some relief, but definitely not complete relief. The cover price rise can only compensate around 35-40% of the inflation,” the industry veteran further revealed to us. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Interestingly, speaking about the situation, Paresh Nath, Publisher, Delhi Press, had very clear views. While Nath accepted that the situation is severe, he also pointed out that if publishers correct the cover price and stop giving the content for free, it wouldn’t be such a big crisis. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Irrespective of the recent spike in newsprint price, the cover price should be kept decent. We should not give content this cheap to the reader. It is almost free,” he said. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On being asked if DAVP could do anything about the ad rates to calm the situation down, he said, “One page of government ad is enough to purchase 5 pages of newsprint. In any newspaper, there are only 5-7 ads from DAVP. There are around 70-80 ads from other departments. These are not ads from DAVP, but these ads are given at DAVP rates. So what DAVP spends is less than 5% of the total ad spent. Everybody has been misled about the ads by the industry deliberately.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What Can Be Done?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dwivedi, CEO Sakal Media Group, says, “Adex volumes are not growing as much as we would like. And cost pressures, especially on newsprint, have an adverse bearing for almost everyone in the industry.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dwivedi further brought the attention towards limited print ad revenue, which he said, “has grown only&amp;nbsp;by 5%-7%.” &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first quarter of this year, while the data of listed companies is in public domain, some unlisted companies are either flat or have around low single digit growth on top-line, he added.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The coming festive season of three months is going to be the most critical time. Everyone is hoping that the period will bail them out with stronger adex growth. If the revenue grows, the ability to absorb the cost gets better. That’s when we are expecting a lot more money to come in. In any case, print companies are continuing to focus on digital, activations and event solutions to shore up the revenue,” he added.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Our partners in the advertising industry should empathise with the newspaper industry. There is a great amount of reluctance from the industry to take up rates. The rates have remained unchanged for the last 4-5 years. It is the only industry probably which sees almost 60% hike in the input cost and still advertisers want lower rates,” an industry veteran said.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jwalant Swaroop, CEO of Happinessinfinite Solutions, feels that the usual ways to bear the pressure of newsprint prices are cutting down on the number of pages, and opting for compact size rather than broadsheet needs. This needs to be supported by raising the cover price substantially and a serious effort on ad rates. He insisted that these solutions can be opted for only if the industry comes together united.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“No single publisher can individually make that decision in such a competitive environment,” he said.  &lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Parts pertaining to unconfirmed numbers on&amp;nbsp;loses to organisations&amp;nbsp;have been edited)&lt;/strong&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1532919269_ub7ujZ_newsprint_collage.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/spotlight-news/with-rise-of-localised-content-creationkids-genre-to-grow-by-12-14in-2018-89572.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>23/04/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>With rise of localised content creation, kids genre to grow by 12-14% in 2018</news:title>
      <news:description>Even though the kids genre in the country is still under indexed,&amp;nbsp;it still&amp;nbsp;has the potential to grow beyond limits. Industry experts believe&amp;nbsp;that owning the IPs and localisation of the content is going to be a way forward for the category which is&amp;nbsp;expected to grow by 10-14 per cent in 2018. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nina Elavia Jaipuria, Business Head, Kids Entertainment Cluster at Viacom18 said, “I think slowly and steadily we all have realized that we are great at conceptualizing,&amp;nbsp;developing and creating our own content. Therefore over the years, a lot of&amp;nbsp;local content has evolved in the genre. The dependence on international content that we&amp;nbsp;acquired from the West is going to dwindle and local IPs will evolve even more.  We will continue to grow as broadcast and local IPs and that’s the future.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Echoing&amp;nbsp;similar thoughts on the local IPs, Leena Lele Dutta, Business Head, SPN Kids genre added,  “what has worked for us was local characters, names and stories. This is the reason the channel has such&amp;nbsp;good viewership today. We intentionally moved away from alien characters as we would have needed a long time to establish them.” The channel completed a year recently. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Over the years, local animation has definitely come of age as Indian characters sit comfortably alongside global ones within the kids’ landscape. At Disney, our stories and characters remain region and platform agnostic,” said Devika Prabhu, Executive Director – Content and Communications, Media Networks, Disney India. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Talking about the growth in the genre, Nina mentioned, “I see a lot of growth this year, now that&amp;nbsp;GST and demonetization is behind us, the category will grow 12-15  per cent, both in terms of viewership and ad sales.”  Whereas Ashish Bhasin, Chairman &amp;amp; CEO - South Asia, Dentsu Aegis Network Dentsu Aegis Network,&amp;nbsp;feels  that the growth will be more or less in the line of overall television growth, which is expected to be around 10-12 per cent.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Challenges in the kids genre&amp;nbsp;space &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As per the BARC data, children,&amp;nbsp;as an audience i.e:&amp;nbsp;the age group  of 02-14 years, account&amp;nbsp;for 20 per cent of total TV impressions. This is the highest share across all age cuts. However, the biggest challenge the&amp;nbsp;industry is witnessing is that a lot of content which&amp;nbsp;kids consume is on GEC or a movie channel. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;87 per cent kids in 2-14 age group watch non-kids channels, while only 13  watch kids channels, according to a research report by BARC India titled ‘A Peek into Kids Viewership’.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Krishna Desai, Executive Director &amp;amp; Network Head - Kids, South Asia, Turner India, “Kids are increasingly exposed to a range of content online and offline. Their viewing habits are dynamic and ever-evolving.  While they are exposed to a vast range of other content, cartoons hold a special place in their hearts. However, the fact remains that due to the burgeoning phenomenon of Indian households primarily owning a single television set, since decades, the percentage of time spent by kids watching kids’ channels has flattened out to not more than 20 per cent.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the Production Front&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recently, Discovery Kids launched Little Singham in partnership with&amp;nbsp;Reliance Animation Studio. Also on completing a year,&amp;nbsp;Sony Yay announced their new character Kicko. Viacom18 will also be&amp;nbsp;launching their fifth IP. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaking about the production part of the industry, Shibasish Sarkar, COO, Reliance Entertainment explained, “What is lacking in the&amp;nbsp;Indian animation industry is its equation&amp;nbsp;with cartoons. When you talk about animation, people only&amp;nbsp;think of it in terms of&amp;nbsp;cartoons. Today animation is for all ages , you can’t define that it is only for children. When we started animation in the country, it was all about mythological characters such as,&amp;nbsp;Ram, Krishna and Arjun,   because all these characters were established in viewers'&amp;nbsp;minds. You really don’t need to spend money on these characters. But if we launch a&amp;nbsp;new character,&amp;nbsp;we also need to&amp;nbsp;establish them,&amp;nbsp;and you need to have some kind of engagement with kids. The problem is, we don't have that&amp;nbsp; kind of&amp;nbsp;funds available in India, because we are still growing and the industry is not that&amp;nbsp;mature.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;He further added, “Nobody is ready to put that much investment in,&amp;nbsp;but in the West, they first create characters, interact with&amp;nbsp;kids,&amp;nbsp;then convert it&amp;nbsp;into a&amp;nbsp;show. Now that we are maturing, we have to come out with&amp;nbsp;shows like Little Singham, where we can start connecting with the kids, but again Singham is an established brand.  Also we need to be very strong in pre-production. India is very weak in pre -roduction, as we do&amp;nbsp;not&amp;nbsp;have much talent in India. Also we have to create awareness about animation is.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Desai also mentioned that animation is not a quick and easy process; it involves thorough visualization and storytelling. “Currently, the major challenge which&amp;nbsp;India faces is a relatively low supply of key talent in animation, especially when it comes to local writers and storyboard artists. While there is incredible potential, there is a need for animation education and training, and the creation of a skilled workforce in India. With the right kind of funding and education, we can be confident of Indian animation standards being on par with global counterparts.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kids --the under indexed category &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Although it is&amp;nbsp;a robust category, the genre is still under leveraged. Uttam Pal Singh- Head of Discovery Kids feels it is more of an&amp;nbsp;industry call here. “We have&amp;nbsp;meetings with our sales team and with advertisers,&amp;nbsp;but what we&amp;nbsp;essentially understand&amp;nbsp;is that kids. as an audience,&amp;nbsp;are&amp;nbsp;becoming&amp;nbsp;stronger, the genre is growing. You cannot really ignore them and I&amp;nbsp;think things will improve.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The genre has&amp;nbsp;a&amp;nbsp;total of&amp;nbsp;7 percent of viewership on&amp;nbsp;TV,&amp;nbsp;but does not have more 50 per cent of Adex. The kids genre is not the only category which&amp;nbsp;is serving children, but the situation is getting better,” said Jaipuria. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disney's Prabhu refused to mention numbers,&amp;nbsp;but she said while advertising remains under-indexed for this genre, “we continue to witness a high double digit growth on Disney Channels on the back of great performance and partnerships.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Talking about the growth, Jaipuria shared, “Despite having headwinds, thanks to GST, we have still seen a fairly robust growth on the top line and ad revenue perspective. We have grown between 12-15 per cent which include the subscription revenue as well. Meanwhile, Dutta believed that ad revenue in the category has remained stable.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1524454742_WdcAMt_kids-story.gif</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/spotlight-news/spotlightnewsprint-price-sees-40hikeindustry-worried-89083.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>26/03/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Spotlight: Newsprint Price Sees 40% Hike, Industry Worried</news:title>
      <news:description>The print industry seems to be heading towards a possible&amp;nbsp;crisis with a price hike in newsprint because of the increasing raw material cost and China imposing a ban on imports of 24 types of rubbish including paper waste, in its campaign against environmental pollution.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newsprint, a low-cost non-archival paper consisting mainly of wood pulp, is most commonly used to print newspapers, publications and advertising material. There has been an almost 40 per cent spike in its price since the crisis began last year.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;China, the world’s largest paper recycler, produced about 63.3 million tons of waste paper pulp in 2016, according to the China Paper Association (CPA), with about 24 per cent of it produced from imported waste paper. “In the last six to nine months, the prices have increased. Also, the newsprint prices have gone through cyclicality over decades. However, the spike in price in the recent months is because of China,” said Pradeep Dwivedi, CEO, Sakal Media Group to exchange4media.&lt;br&gt;As the newsprint stocks with the publications are being used up, they are preparing to face the challenge and find the right measure to decimate the effect of the price hike. “Right now, some publishers can manage till the end of Q1 of the next financial year, and then there are some who have stock left only for one or two months, they will now have to order at the revised prices,” added Dwivedi.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;However, Paresh Nath, Editor and Owner of Delhi Press magazine, said that since the revised prices have already entered the market, its impact can partly be seen in the coming financial quarter. Similar views were also shared by Indranil Roy, CEO, Outlook India.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The print industry as a whole has not taken a call. Individual publications are taking their own measures. Some are cutting down the pages, some are increasing the retail price, some are increasing ad rates, etc.,” said I Venkat, Director, Eenadu, an Indian Telugu language daily newspaper.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adding fuel to the fire over the concern of India’s print industry, which was already recovering from the ill-effects of demonetisation and GST, is the union government’s recent decision to publish ads of tender notices digitally instead of newspapers. This is also expected to further cause loss to newspaper companies. "Paper prices have gone up by 15-18 per cent and it's expected to rise more. It is and will continue to negatively impact the industry. On top of that, GST is unfavourable to the quoted paper which we use,” said Roy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Most print companies have shown de-growth in revenues. Some have missed the projections way off, making the newspaper and magazine owners jittery,” said Jwalant Swaroop, former CEO of Sakal Media Group and Lokmat wrote in a column on exchange4media.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;While suggesting various coping methods that publishers might use, Dwivedi said, “The cost of marketing, distribution, salary cost and other components will also come under scrutiny.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Of all the stakeholders affected by the crisis,&amp;nbsp;according to a media report, shares of Indian paper companies are positively growing after manufacturers raised prices. To cope with the challenges, the print industry is expected to demand better rates from commercial advertisers as well as the government based on the tremendous growth shown in the latest Indian Readership Survey. “We now have IRS as a currency to show growth of the total readership. The value of the print media is still noticeable,” said Dwivedi adding that this is not a permanent crisis and can be handled like any other problem with innovative thinking.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“There have been years in the past when the prices were similar and publishers did balance the situation even at that point in time. Yes, it is a big problem. It is a problem that calls for innovative thinking but like any business challenge, it’s not so big that everything falls apart,” he said.  &lt;div&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:calibri, sans-serif;font-size:12.8px"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;Venkat is furious about the low cover prices of newspaper and magazines in India. He said, “Our cover prices are so less. Even in Sri Lanka, Bangladesh and Pakistan, it is around Rs. 14-15. Though their currency value is different, where are we compared to them? Thanks to one particular group, the prices are kept low because they don’t want to increase it. If one leading publication does that, pressure trickles down on everybody.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sharing similar thoughts on Indian readers’ reluctance to pay for news, Paresh Nath said, “I wish that cover prices should increase because they are already very low. Also, if the cover prices are low; the delivery cost is high. So in case, the cover price is increased, it will somehow give more incentive to the distributor to sell newspapers and magazines.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To calm down a panicked industry, Nath, who has had a very long association with the print industry, said, “It is still not doomsday and the newspaper industry can still survive by increasing the cover price and reducing the pages. These two things put together will help the industry weather the crisis.”</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1522034899_gJu0PZ_printspotlight.gif</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/spotlight-news/where's-the-chink-in-india's-creative-armour-&#13;
-88612.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>26/02/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Where's the chink in India's creative armour?&#13;
</news:title>
      <news:description>A spectacular and record-breaking innings across award shows last year, has made India a force to be reckoned with at the global advertising platform. At the Cannes Lions International Festival of Creativity alone, India bagged a record 40 metals in addition to 10 pencils at the D&amp;amp;AD awards, seven Clio awards and a whopping 49 metals at Spikes Asia. Not just this, India's leading (M)Ad Men, Piyush and Prasoon Pandey will receive the highest honour at Cannes this year, the Lion of St Mark, for their work and contribution to the industry. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yet, Indian creative agencies lag behind in the Gunn Report, an authoritative global index of creative excellence in Advertising. Only McCann Worldgroup India featured in the top 50 agencies list (ranked 32 worldwide.) In addition to McCann Worldgroup India, six other agencies from India made it to the top 50 APAC list. Taproot Dentsu, BBDO, Ogilvy and Mather, Leo Burnett, Law &amp;amp; Kenneth Saatchi &amp;amp; Saatchi along with Wieden+Kennedy appeared in the list, in that order, for their path-breaking campaigns from 2017.&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="http://cms.exchange4media.com/files/1519561554_uz1WGM_Top-creative-agencies-in-APAC-in-2017-from-India.jpg" class="img-responsive"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Award show entry barrier&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;While finding them in such global lists is always a matter of pride and celebration, Indian agencies not featuring in this list or any list for that matter should not be the only reflection of the creativity and calibre of agencies here, felt Kainaz Karmakar, Group Creative Director - ‎Ogilvy &amp;amp; Mather India. She said, "Our work is creatively sharp and relevant. A lot of our work is making a mark on the world and we must acknowledge that. Not just in creative awards but also in international effectiveness award shows. This report, like every report card must be looked at with a sense of balance." &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Finding a place in the Gunn Report is dependent on the number of awards an agency wins. Topping the Gunn Report therefore is all about playing the awards game. Law &amp;amp; Kenneth Saatchi &amp;amp; Saatchi (Publicis Groupe) that won accolades for the GiveHer5 campaign last year will not be participating in any award shows in 2018 as per the holding company's directive to divert funds to building the AI platform Marcel. "Playing this award is a very expensive game; with the entry factor and all. It's also about how significant India is in ad market globally. We are important from a strategic perspective but not from the top 10 global ad revenue market perspective because of our economy," pointed out Anil S Nair, CEO and Managing Partner, Law &amp;amp; Kenneth Saatchi &amp;amp; Saatchi.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="http://cms.exchange4media.com/files/1519561559_vRNXJb_Top-campaigns-from-India-in-2017.jpg" class="img-responsive"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;He further added, "We're the so-called under-valued ad market in terms of the value for population. So the fact is that we don't have the kind of resources to play up this awards game."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taproot Dentsu has emerged as the second most awarded agency from India in 2017 as per the Gunn Report. It is ranked at 20 in the APAC top agencies list. Agnello Dias, co-founder and CCO, Taproot Dentsu, concurred with Nair, when he said that, "Entering awards is tough. So if you can't enter awards, you cannot get a high score in the Gunn Report irrespective of what you do." &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Understanding India&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;While taking part in award shows is a real hurdle for agencies, there are other factors that dictate India's representation globally. "According to me, it's also about the constitution of the jury and their understanding of the work that needs to be awarded. Many times, we think a certain piece of work is good internally and we share it with our global counterparts; but we don't get the kind of acknowledgment we were hoping for. That's because of a cultural disconnect and also their understanding. Because our humour is very different than theirs. Even if you were to look at the Oscars, the benchmarks are really different," noted Nair. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;He added, "It's also that the market for all work produced in India is in India only. That's not the case for many other countries. What's produced in UK or US is exposed beyond that particular region."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Talent Woes&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pointing out that talent deficit is a concern for agencies, Prasoon Joshi, Chairman McCann Worldgroup Asia Pacific and CEO &amp;amp; CCO of McCann Worldgroup India, said, "There is a talent deficit at mid-level. The maximum churn has happened here with a lot more avenues open for the talent to explore so today we see a gap and an area of concern here. Industry is cognisant of this reality and has been making efforts to retain this talent and also groom younger talent." &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Improve idea execution&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Karmakar felt that India does need to sharpen some of its approaches. "We can sharpen our understanding of new-age media and push those boundaries harder. We can put our minds to how our executions can compete with the best in the world and become the best in the world," she said. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Execution, as Karmakar pointed out, is what India does not get right even when there is a great idea. Nair said, "Many times, our finesse of execution lets us down. People in the network have confessed that the idea was to do well but finally when it came to gold or silver consideration, the shortlist conversion, if you look at it from a mere marketing perspective, is very poor." &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Budgets fail us too. Nair further added, "We don't have the ability to pay for all technical teams across advertising. It's important have that level of detailing in our films." &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We shall overcome&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaking about India's global performance, Joshi said that while there is much left to be desired, "Internationally India's talent is well recognised today and I'm optimistic about the future of our talent." He further added, "Indian Advertising has come a long way and is uniquely addressing the complex demands and needs of the market and brands."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Both Nair and Karmakar said that while India does have to improve its quality of work and execution, one must not dwell on lists and rankings. "We have a long way to go and should look beyond if we can make our advertising better," said Nair. Karmakar was confident that "We can do all this, but we must do it with joy and without a sense of panic."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We must never turn into those parents who make a report card, the only measure of their child's success," she pointed out.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1519617729_4ZMZPN_Spotlight.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/spotlight-news/need-of-the-hourdiversify-your-digital-strategy-88278.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>05/02/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Need of the Hour: Diversify Your Digital Strategy</news:title>
      <news:description>The leading platforms of the digital ecosystem - Facebook and YouTube - have both made significant policy changes to their platforms over the last few weeks. These have served as a major wake-up call to brands and publishers. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The writing on the wall has never been more clear for publishers and brands - do not put all your eggs in one basket; in the case of digital advertising, two baskets. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook’s recent announcement to deprioritise posts from brands and publishers comes as rude shock to these two communities that have been heavily dependent on Facebook to reach users and drive traffic back to their own websites. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Youtube’s partner programme tweak puts upcoming content creators at a disadvantage now. They cannot monetise their content unless they meet the minimum subscriber and view hours threshold. YouTube’s change in policy does not disadvantage brands, but it is still a significant move for the advertising community that has been fretting over brand safety. New content creators who already find it tough on YouTube will now have to rake in a significant number of view hours (4000) and subscribers (1000) to see money in the bank accounts. YouTuber PewDiePie believes that while this is harsh to content creators, it does seem fair. “There are only so many ads on YouTube. So cutting off ad revenue from channels that are uploading other people’s content or movies makes sense to me,” he noted. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Facebook and Google duopoly that claims around 70 per cent of the global ad spends. Over the last few years organic reach of brands on Facebook has been consistently plummeting. “It was in the high 40% during 2011-12 and went down to 1% or less in 2014-15,” says Rahul Vengalil, Founder &amp;amp; Chief Executive Officer. Some say that in 2017 this number was down to zero. These were all sings that “that Facebook will be a completely paid platform,” said Gopa Kumar, EVP, Isobar India. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook’s message was clear to brands: Pay or Perish. And Mark Zuckerberg’s latest statement that Facebook will return the platform to its core purpose of making and maintaining friends is a veiled message to message to brands and publishers. “Facebook is not a benevolent distributor of branded content but a company looking at profiteering. It cannot afford to alienate its core audience by just showing them brand pages or ads and therefore this move to control the newsfeed was inevitable. Advertisers moved to Facebook for the easy reach, but anything that is easy and free doesn't last long,” says Rashmi Putcha, Co-Founder &amp;amp; Director, LIQVD ASIA. She is quick to add: The party is over. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What now? &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Agencies have been advising brands to look beyond the duopoly for a while now. “Facebook &amp;amp; YouTube are monetised platforms that want to earn revenues. They have been forced to tweak their rules because of media backlash &amp;amp; advertisers boycott. The digital fraternity needs to stop looking at these publishers for solutions,” observes Putcha.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even though brands and publishers may want to move away from the two technology giants, the reach of the two is unparalleled. “Brands cannot afford to move away from Facebook at this stage, due to the reach and the targeting that is possible no this platform. All the other social platforms will only compliment the activities on Facebook, or to get additional reach/engagment,” says Vengalil. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gopa Kumar, EVP, Isobar India, who advises advertisers to explore multiple platforms says that it will be hard to completely move away from Facebook. “Because there are limited ad units available, the bidding on these units will jack up prices, eventually resulting in brands pouring in more money into Facebook,” he says. “Brands will need to focus on shareable content rather than high quantity of content,” Kumar further adds. If brands do not crack the ‘sharable content’ formula, “it will have to be sponsored posts going forward,” he adds. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Putcha also notes that with organic reach likely to reduce even further, brands that desire a wide reach will need to spend more on ads and promotions to reach audiences. “Facebook &amp;amp; Instagram have bene testing ad units that will let businesses create a link between these platforms and WhatsApp. The more evolved brands might just be jolted by this new move (by FB) to re-look at their social media strategy which is increasingly becoming just another paid media platform and look at building their own communities which are meaningful and allow conversations between people of shared interests,” she says. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaking about platforms like WhatsApp for Business which has been launched in India, Instagram, etc, Kumar had a smart advice and warning for brands, “Enjoy it while its free; it will all start getting monetized.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What about Brand Safety&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;After the instance of YouTuber Logan Paul sharing a graphic and bad-in-taste video featuring a dead body hanging from a tree that began trending on YouTube, the video sharing platform decided to review popular videos manually before placing ads. Marketers seem to feel reassured with YouTube’s initiative to manually review video and impose a minimum threshold for monetising videos. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The update from YouTube seeks to ensure that brand ads won’t run on random, fly by night channels. But this is by no means even close to a solution for brand safety,” believes Putcha. &lt;br&gt;She says, “Along with aggressive measures of content review by both humans and machine learning algorithms, YouTube needs to enforce better targeting and segmentation measures. Smarter AI is the only real solution to solve the problem of safety but it is a mammoth task and will require collaborations with third party tech partners.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vengalil also feels that ensuring a minimum threshold is not enough to ensure brand safety deal with ad fraud. “What if the subscription is from Clicks Farms or Bots and not genuine users. YouTube needs to be open up its walled gardens to third party verification across Brand Safety, Ad Fraud &amp;amp; Viewability, wherein the impressions &amp;amp; delivery are independently verified by a third party,” he says. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not just this, the journey towards a cleaner ecosystem will need to include “better awareness among advertisers, agency folks; creating accepted tolerances &amp;amp; guidelines. And improve the understanding of ad:Tech solutions; and penalise defaulters &amp;amp; fraudsters,” notes Vengalil.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1517801833_kUkq0Z_Spotlight.gif</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/spotlight-news/digital-trendspotting-for-2018-87971.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>15/01/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Digital trendspotting for 2018</news:title>
      <news:description>Digital advertising is changing as rapidly as it is growing. The industry currently contributes only around 15 per cent to the total Advertising Industry in India and this is expected to reach 24 per cent of the entire market by 2020, according to the Dentsu Aegis Network-exchange4media Digital Report 2018.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;It is also estimated to grow with a CAGR of 32 per cent by 2020. Keeping up with this fast-paced industry means taking risks and crystal-gazing to finally hit the proverbial bull’s eye. As the industry hurtles towards the digital marketplace, new trends replace old ones and brands need to swiftly change gears to keep up with the emerging innovations and technologies. Here is a look at some of the trends brands need to adapt to in 2018:&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Business Transformation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Digital is a way of life, not a medium of communication or piece of technology. Digital marketers are increasing recommending brands to transform their entire value chains using digital. To this end, agencies are developing competencies to deliver what the new digital age demands.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Anil K Nair, CEO &amp;amp; Managing Partner, Digital Law &amp;amp; Kenneth Saatchi &amp;amp; Saatchi said that clients are going to be talking more about digital transformation than just digital communication. “Rather than doing superficial digital, more and more clients are beginning to realise that they may want to change their core to have a lasting impact,” he noted. Given that Indian businesses are still stuck with archaic systems and processes, “now is the right pivot point for these businesses to invest in new technology and processes,” he added.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hyper-Personalisation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;As one digital marketer rightly said to this reporter: Privacy is dead. For brands, there is an upside to this: hyper-personalised marketing. When you have the kind of granular data on consumers it would a waste to spend money on anything but pinpointed marketing. “Any non-personalised marketing techniques will become obsolete,” said Sudhir Nair, managing director, digital, Omnicom India. He added that non-personalised methods for even simple things like emailers, direct response campaigns will perish in 2018. He was confident that hyper-personalisation is the way forward in the digitised world.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Content &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Although content marketing makes for a small chunk of digital advertising, It is an entity that deserves its space in the world of advertising. “Content marketing is definitely taking money away from the television commercial,” said Arnab Mitra, founder and MD Liqvd Asia. Mitra said that 2018 will see a boom in the content marketing space, thus redefining the media landscape.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;The thumb rule that marketers can spend up to 10X of what they spend on content on media is now obsolete in the digital ecosystem. Marketers are willing to put in disproportionate amount of money in content marketing because they have the chance to go viral on digital media which would mean that media cost is negligible and people are distributing the content themselves. “Therefore, brands are focussed on creating good quality content which will get propagated on digital platforms by their own steam,” said Mitra.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Deshpande concurred with Mitra, and said that the appetite for content is definitely growing among brands. Anil Nair cautioned that content is like ‘Emperor’s New Clothes.’ “Too many people are trying too many new things, which is what any kind of evolutionary market will see,” he said. He advised that brands must look to create short-format snackable content and keep the brand’s involvement as subtle as possible, “because overt brand involvement will be rejected,” he added.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Regional Content&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Content on digital platforms is currently skewed towards the metro audience, this will see a dramatic shift in 2018. “There will be an exponential growth of vernacular content in 2018 coming from languages like Telugu, Tamil and Kannada. New markets untapped markets like Gujrati, Orissa, and Punjab will also emerge,” said Devendra Deshpande, Head, Content+ at Mindshare. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sudir noted that more regional content will lead to the emergence of content studios at the regional level. “Local content has not kept pace with the growing internet penetration. Indic content is becoming popular but the content is not being created from an Indic perspective,” he added. Sudir further said that this growth of regional Indic content may be bad news for the Indian print fraternity which has so far been cushioned from the digital explosion in India. “Unlike other countries, Indian print industry has been able to hold fort so, but that may not be the case going forward when we see more hard-core local micro-geo level content,” he said. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Voice&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts bet that voice will be the future of digital and not just advertising alone. “Voice will take over all digital formats, for example, voice search: people will search lesser and lesser by typing and more by speaking into devices. According to the latest statistics, 30 per cent of users in the US use voice search and 45 per cent of millennials use search,” said Shamsuddin Jasani, Managing Director, Isobar India.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;As per data from Google, 28 percent of search queries in India are done by voice and Hindi voice search queries are growing at over 400 percent year on year. “This 28% are urban internet savvy users who are comfortable using voice assistants like Siri,” said Jasani. He added, “It is not just Siri and Google Assistant, the beginning for voice has happened in 2017 with Alexa, Cortana, etc. And this movement towards voice will take off in 2018.”&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Sudhir Nair called voice an inclusive medium that should be given its due and not slighted because of the proliferation of video. Voice is an intuitive interface that can interact with consumers and sense consumer sentiment. “Mobile is still an external element unlike wearable devices that can read a consumer unobtrusively. While wearables and implantable devices may be a little farther away in the future, the interim medium will be voice,” felt Anil Nair.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Some of the other emerging trends are: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Augmented Reality:&amp;nbsp;VR costs are still prohibitive. Many smartphones are already AR enabled, because of the cost barrier, AR might overtake VR in the immediate future.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Photos:&amp;nbsp;Platforms like Snapchat and Instagram have brought back photographs. Photo stories are an interesting new medium that brands can utilise.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Micro-influencers:&amp;nbsp;Following some gaffes with celebrity influencers, brands began leveraging micro-influencers in 2017. These domain experts and have a meaningful reach and will see greater play in 2018 as compared to celebrity influencers.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Movie Launches on OTT: Movies that do not have the budgets for huge marketing campaigns but have a niche audience could launch primarily on OTT platforms.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1515983692_p0G4ws_Spotlight_Digital-ad_(6).gif</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/spotlight-news/spotlight2018-tv-trends-predict-15-per-cent-growth-87871.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>08/01/2018</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>SPOTLIGHT: 2018 TV trends predict 15 per cent growth</news:title>
      <news:description>Indian Television’s woes began in 2016 with demonetisation and hit a road block with GST in 2017. The predictions for the industry in 2018 seem nothing short of a generation leap. The industry had grown by 10-12 per cent in 2017 compared to 2016. With announcements of big mergers in 2017, ambitious digitisation plans, audience demand for varied fictional content and the rise of digital video consumption, 2018 is looking ahead to a 15 per cent growth, according to experts. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zee Unimedia COO, Ashish Sehgal&amp;nbsp;felt that January will be clouded by cricket and sports will score robust growth for TV this year. “Last year, a lot of growth came from FTA. However, the mainline GECs that had shown stagnation may grow again. They will have to produce more fresh content that has come to them because of the competition from FTA. This year you will see a fireback from GECs. We also didn’t see many blockbuster launches in 2017, but that will soon change and propel the Hindi TV movie category too,” he said.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TV advertising revenue to grow&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sehgal also said that the advertising industry may see a growth of 13-14 per cent in 2018. “There’ll be a 13-14 per cent growth in the advertising industry in 2018. On television, I’m expecting good double-digit growth, anywhere between 15-20 per cent. On digital, it looks like we’ll have a good growth this year,” he said.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The broadcasting industry de-grew by about 21 per cent battling 2016’s note ban compared to 2017. It lost an estimated Rs. 850 crore. As the dust around the big government decisions settles, 2018 is predicted to see a clear rise in advertising revenue. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pawan Jailkhani, Chief Revenue Officer, 9X Media, said that 2018 would likely witness three things like increased digitization on ground, massive fictional content creation and growth from advertising from the second half of the year. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“H2 will see a major jump in terms of advertising growth. Though first half will be decent but H2 will be much bigger. I think the year will see around 14-15 per cent growth. In terms of advertising, from a fiction or channel launches perspective, we’ll see abundant rise. There will be some uproar on FTA. If we’re going with FTA on larger level or not, the rethinking and consolidation about it will happen in 2018,” he said.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Categories that will spend big in 2018&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jailkhani agreed with Sehgal and said that sentiments will flare with six to eight upcoming state elections which will impact revenues and overall economy. “News channels will get huge benefits. Certain categories will be aggressive in the next year. Automobile predictions say that there will be 16 launches this year which will give a boost. Telecom seems to be in the mood to spend and will be generous this year. Digital as a medium will also further complement TV from the audience point of view,” he said. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The reach of television continues to grow with eight to 10 million homes being added to the already 180 million homes every year. Advertisers won’t be taking their hands off this pulse anytime soon. With the FMCG, automobile, and financial sector doing well, they will be in a position to spend more money, observed Rohit Gupta, President, Network Sales and International Business, Sony Pictures Networks. “Govt expenditure is expected to rise due to upcoming state elections. 2018 will be far better year and we should positively expect a healthy growth of 12-15 per cent,” he said.&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="http://e4mcms.exchange4media.com/files/1515381007_Xtrrwn_INFO-Box-2.jpg"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“FMCG is having a good run, primarily on television. Auto category has seen a good growth will continue to spend. Telecom wars will get stronger now that Jio will start monetizing on the services they were offering for free. The consolidation of Telecom industry will be a big push. If the Vodafone and Idea merger takes place, they will also pump in more money. Mobile handsets will also be one of the big spenders,” added Sehgal.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Chinese handsets have taken over. They are strong competitors to even Samsung and Apple in India and that run will continue this year too. Oppo, Vivo and now Gionee&amp;nbsp;will start advertising more,” he mentioned. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sehgal felt that e-commerce will see a similar trend as they won’t grow as much in 2018. “Another category, BFSI and retail will grow this year. Keeping this demonetization and GST affect aside, the growth we were seeing in 2015 in SME category will come back,” he said.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Focussed fictional content for TV&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the last one and half years, TV business was a tad&amp;nbsp;muted, not only in terms of advertising revenue but also with the slow of pace digitisation. Fiction and non-fiction shows haven’t enjoyed great success either. “I think fiction, which is a bread and butter for TV, has not done well in the last one year. 2017 was not that great in terms of content. If it was created, it didn't get the viewership,” asserted Jailkhani.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ZEEL premium channel’s, Business Cluster Head, Aparna Bhosle, experienced that for the English Entertainment channels, the year 2017 saw a considerable change in consumption patterns by the audience. Speaking about the English GEC particularly, she felt that viewers have become socially evolved and aren’t looking at English content just from a recreation point of view but also as a conversation starter. “At Zee, our endeavour has always been to give our viewers riveting and engaging content. With an exciting line-up of properties, our viewers were exposed to an extensive array of fresh and high-quality shows and movies. With an increase in the number of HD users and the fact that consumption of English entertainment is on a steady rise, last year, our focus was primarily to offer great content supported by dynamic marketing campaigns. In 2018, the aim is to further present quality content,” she said.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2018 should see this as&amp;nbsp;introduction of new advertisers to boost monetisation in the category. “The focus will continue to be what the category does best – capture the imagination of this young generation. For this, I see a further introduction of new homegrown shows and characters. Additionally, there will also be efforts towards building an ecosystem around the existing popular characters and shows beyond just TV. The shift from 4-14 to 2-14 years in 2017 has surely broadened the canvas for this category. 2018 may thus see differential content offerings within 2-14 years to cater to different age groups,” said Leena Lele Dutta, Business Head of Sony Pictures Networks, India - Kids Genre.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1515380815_vpl6jX_INFO-Box-1.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/spotlight-news/it's-digital-all-the-wayaiottrobotics....-87752.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>26/12/2017</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>It's digital all the way: AI, OTT, Robotics....</news:title>
      <news:description>Digital was the dominant narrative across sectors in India in 2017. Backed by the government’s decision to push India into a digital first economy, there were a number of developments that tilted the scale in its favour.&lt;br&gt;If we talk about media, marketing and advertising; from increasing thrust on OTT content, rising spends in digital marketing and AI targeted advertising, the digital push has been redefining these sectors in many ways.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rising Investments in Big Data and Artificial Intelligence&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Digital marketing space has been evolving constantly over past few years and 2017 was no exception. Marketers continued to explore newer ways to use technology to get those elusive 30 seconds of attention of their target customer. According to Pavan Chandra, Senior Sales Director – CX Applications at Oracle, “Artificial Intelligence (AI) and analytics have played a significant role in helping organizations identify the right target customers and understand their needs. Here comes the personalization, which dominated the marketing space during the previous year. The entire branding process has changed because customers are expecting personalization as the bare minimum from the organizations. If a company is customizing, that means that it is responding to their customers’ ever growing needs and expectations. Organisations, which did not acknowledge this change, lost out on customers and thus market share.”&lt;br&gt;“With around 25-30 per cent of the total revenues coming just from digital, there are huge investments being made in data and AI and agencies are getting future ready. Media transparency has become more important ever since YouTube’s brand safety fiasco and Facebook’s measurement errors came into light. Many brands have been changing how they think about digital and stepping up standards and governance. Havas Group is a pioneer of meta programmatic solutions. Together with MFG Labs, Havas launched the industry’s very first Meta-DSP in 2014 and in 2017, launched Client Trading Solution (CTS,) a game-changing programmatic solution that gives clients complete visibility and control over their campaigns, allowing full programmatic transparency. As an industry, we are redoubling our efforts to deliver a quality advertising environment, meet advertiser demands and create value for users,” added Anita Nayyar, CEO India &amp;amp; South Asia, Havas Media Group.&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="http://e4mcms.exchange4media.com/files/1514258671_hqOhLn_Graph-1-spotlight.jpg"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rise in Digital Content Consumption&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;The consumption of digital content witnessed considerable rise in 2017, right from popular TV shows, movies and music to original, digitally-led, personalized content relevant to the viewer’s specific interests and viewing preferences in the form of videos, web series and other digital programming options.&lt;br&gt;According to Manish Maheshwari, CEO, Network 18 Digital, “It has been a landmark year for the digital media sector, but if I had to choose three of the most impactful developments, it would be the increasing focus on the digital-first audience, the sector going a step closer to ‘mobile-only’ and the re-imagination of monetization models in the digital space. Brands were able to capture the profiles of their audiences more accurately than ever with effective tools at their disposal, leading to more accurate targeting and thereby better engagement. Secondly, the drastic reduction in mobile data pricing together with the rising affordability of smartphones bolstered the ongoing journey of ‘mobile first’ to ‘mobile-only,’ where content creators were propelled to create engaging content that is best consumed on the mobile device. Lastly, we saw an emerging pattern where monetization models were being revisited and re-imagined by going back to the one and only thumb rule of ‘content is king.’ Both in India and the world, publishers began going down the subscription and transaction route, adding to their existing yet dwindling revenue stream of advertising. The focus and investment on qualitative content is at an all time high as a result, as we embark on a new year.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="http://e4mcms.exchange4media.com/files/1514258661_MeSAiI_Graph-2-spotlight.jpg"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The year 2017 has been positive at various levels and when it comes to the digital sector specifically, there have been a few significant developments worth highlighting. Digital publishers and content creators were in need of an effective measurement system that could lend uniformity to the sector. This demand was met by BARC India, when they launched their indigenous digital measurement tool – EKAM, bringing in the much-required transparency for every stakeholder in the industry. The most relatable and ever-evolving aspect in the digital space continued to be the trend of web-series, but the launch of several new ‘digital-first’ shows in the past year widened the opportunities for brands to reach out to their respective TGs with fresh perspectives. Owing to cheaper data plans coupled with the mass adoption of 4G, the country saw an unprecedented growth in digital content consumption. This aided the advertising spends on digital as compared to the previous year, which has been a boon to both the content creators and brands across categories,” says Deepak Lamba, CEO, Worldwide Media.&lt;br&gt;The rollout of 3G and 4G broadband services, inexpensive smartphones along with cheaper data tariffs, is driving digital content consumption in Tier I and Tier II cities.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;The biggest contributor to the demand for online entertainment content, however, has been India’s young population that comprises of more than 65 per cent of Internet users which prefers watching content of their choice on their personal handheld devices.&lt;br&gt;Siddhartha Roy, CEO of Hungama.com, said, “Digital entertainment has witnessed a multifold increase in content consumption across both audio and video entertainment formats. This dramatic increase in the size of user community has been enabled by a rapidly expanding device and connectivity ecosystem. Video entertainment as a format has been a key consumption driver and Hungama Play’s extensive video content library, especially its selection of curated short format content, has been instrumental in driving high engagement rates on mobile devices. This has allowed brands to reach a sizeable and highly engaged audience that is tuned into their choice of entertainment on our digital platforms.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="http://e4mcms.exchange4media.com/files/1514258807_vG9sfd_Graph-3-spotlight.jpg"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Impact of Reliance Jio and&amp;nbsp;Demonetization&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;If we look at digital on the whole, the disruption led by Reliance Jio in the data space combined with the after effects of demonetization, kept redefining India’s digital transformation. Reliance Jio has been the biggest game changer which has enabled millions to latch on to the digital wave at an affordable price. And the biggest beneficiary of this is Prime Minister Narendra Modi’s Digital India campaign, which aims to spread internet literacy even in the remotest parts of the country. India adds 15,000 new internet users, everyday. ‘The Future of internet in India’ report the Nasscom prepared in association with Akamai Technologies Inc. says that 730 million internet users are expected in India by 2020 and 75 per cent of the new users will be from rural areas.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The e-commerce warfare&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another key development in the digital space in 2017 was the intense competition between e-commerce players. The merger talks between Snapdeal and Flipkart dominated headlines for quite some time and finally Snapdeal decided against the merger. Another significant development was the announcement by Reiance Jio of entering the e-commerce market. The company is already working with corner stores and consumer brands to create an operational model that will enable shoppers to buy at neighbourhood shops using digital coupons via its Jio Money platform. Even China based e-commerce giant Alibaba announced that it’s eyeing a pie of the growing e-commerce market in India.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to a report by financial services firm Morgan Stanley, online retail in India is estimated to grow over 1,200 per cent to $200 billion by 2026, up from $15 billion in 2016. That will be 12 per cent of India's overall retail market. “The number of India's online shoppers has crossed the 90 million mark this year, a growth of over eight times from 2013, when online shopping began to take roots here,” says a BCG report. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Crackdown on Fake news&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;The U.S. elections brought 'fake news' into the mainstream and with it, an understanding that we can be easily manipulated as people. Several of the major tech companies have taken some steps to remedy the situation. Google has partnered with nonpartisan organization, the International Fact-Checking Network, and Facebook is establishing better controls around political ads and increasing the transparency of the advertisers behind them. These new measures to control the use of the platforms are challenging for the tech giants, as they are burdensome and not failure proof.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1514258457_sek4lg_big_(38).jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/spotlight-news/the-worse-is-behind-the-broadcasting-space-as-it-bounces-back-87655.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>18/12/2017</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>The worse is behind the broadcasting space as it bounces back</news:title>
      <news:description>2017 has been no less than a roller coaster for the media and entertainment space. The same applies to broadcasting industry which battled the demonetization blues head on starting from last November when it de-grew as much as 21 per cent compared to last year losing an estimated Rs. 850 crore. As things started looking up from April onwards, it was struck by another economic hurdle GST. Despite its transitory impact, the broadcasting space saw a drop of 20–25 per cent in ad revenue in July as June saw postponement in advertising spends. Having said that, the industry is on a revival mode with experts expecting a positive first quarter in 2018.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;MK Anand, MD and CEO, Times Network explained the scenario in a nutshell, “Business has slowed down from earlier growth rates which were high. Advertising in broadcast specifically have been growing by 12 or 13 per cent. I think the whole year would have just scraped at zero plus/ minus a little bit. In the last six months (post GST,) there is a contraction. When you look at the Broadcast adex the drop is evident. It has sandbagged a little by an increase in low price volume from FTA GECs, Hindi movies, etc. If you take that out, the drop would be a little more than 1-2 per cent.” &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;He further pointed out that the headwinds of demonetisation and GST have been harsher on English business comparatively. “If Hindi GECs in the last six months have dropped by 2-3 per cent, English has dropped by about 5 per cent,” he said.&lt;br&gt;Though the industry was prepared for the new economic regime, it didn’t expect GST to be a bigger blow than demonetization. Joy Chakraborthy, President – Revenue, TV18 and CEO, Forbes India, added, “The launch of GST came with a new regime so a lot of wait and watch happened, followed by its own teething problems, changes in GST slabs, its process, etc. which in a way took away from the recovery of demonetization.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;He further mentioned the absence of government advertising. “Also, the absence of government advertising has been something due to DAVP deadlock, which kept broadcasters waiting given that GST was already kind of limiting,” he said.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In fact, Pitch Madison Report 2017 mentioned that television grew by 9 per cent to Rs. 18,831 crore and predicted that it will reach Rs. 21,296 crore in 2017. Publicis Groupe-run media agency Zenith forecasted a similar growth rate. Meanwhile GroupM’s 'This Year Next Year' (TYNY) report is expecting 8 per cent this year which is attributed to ‘Free To Air’ channels adding more inventory and 'pure HD' content gaining ground. The report also anticipated consolidation of niche channels. It matched the estimates of Pawan Jailkhani, Chief Revenue Officer, 9X Media. “TV is also in single digit. FMCG didn't show much traction. Icing on the cake were always categories like automobile, retail and finance,” he said.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anand also noticed a phenomenal growth in the HD space, especially in English, in spite of demonetisation and GST. He said, “The growth is in excess of 50 per cent.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GST seeping into festive mood&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sales of top FMCG players like Hindustan Unilever, Dabur, Marico and Emami were impacted by de-stocking ahead of GST implementation which in-turn affected the ad spends of broadcasters. To top it all, this seeped into the time crunched festive season to an extent. It condensed from six-eight weeks in previous years to four weeks this year.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For instance, ZEEL had mentioned that its advertisers were negatively impacted during transition which led to a temporary pull-back on their ad spends for the quarter ending 30 September, 2017. The network registered a Rs. 986.7 crore, a YoY growth of 2.9 per cent from Rs. 959.2 crore in the same quarter last year.&lt;br&gt;Mohan Nair, CEO at Mathrubhumi TV, mentioned that GST came in the way of channels achieving their targets during festive period. “On the regional front, the spenders were retail jewellers and retail consumer appliances dealers,” he said.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite all the obstacles, the broadcasting industry fetched impressive numbers during festive seasons. The four major Hindi GECs like Colors, Star Plus, SET and Zee registered revenues in the range of Rs. 1500-1700 crore between Navratri and Diwali, according to media reports, with Star and Colors reportedly clocking an increase of 20 per cent over previous festive months. Meanwhile SPN recorded more than that. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smaller players like 9XM and SAB Group saw a similar growth rate of 9-10 per cent and 15 per cent growth respectively this Diwali over last year.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Festive season witnessed lot of action from FMCG players, automobiles, consumer durables, jewellery and retail. E-commerce majors have increased TV ad spends by nearly 40 per cent this year. Automobile was pretty active with 50 per cent and a 160 per cent jump in ad spots was seen by four wheelers and two-wheelers, according to media reports.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paytm stole the show as it allocated Rs. 1000 crore for festive sales while ecommerce majors Flipkart and Amazon have collectively spent nearly Rs. 100 crore for promotions through television advertisements for their September sales.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rise of FTA channels &lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;The year saw the rise of Free-to-Air (FTA) channels. In some cases, it led viewership across genres like Hindi GEC and sports according to BARC. This definitely brought advertisers close to a fresh set of audience. “The accessibility of media with Free to Air channels and almost free data today lets marketers have access to this completely new set of consumers/markets who were earlier very difficult to reach,” said Shekhar Banerjee, Chief Operating Officer, Madison Media. According to estimates by the FICCI - KPMG Media and Entertainment Industry Report 2017, advertisers were expected to double their spends on FTA channels in 2017. “The FTA channels garnered an estimated Rs. 400-500 crore of the overall TV advertising pie in 2016; which is expected to rise to Rs. 800-1000 crore in 2017,” the report said. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Upbeat about 2018&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;The broadcasting industry is optimistic about a stable 2018 as there will be eight state elections which will improve sentiments and (hopefully) bring in advertising revenue. The industry is already showing signs of revival with November-December posting 10-11 per cent growth according to Jailkhani. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For Anand, the silver lining of 2017 is that from November 15 onwards there is ‘almost a distinct change in behaviour.’ He shared, “From our point of view daily booking, publishing and burn have been a hockey stick. December is substantially better, It’s on par with the months of January to May. If I was to keep that as a benchmark then turnaround is already happening.” He put industry numbers at 15-20 per cent for November and December vis-a-vis last November and December. “It is because of demonetisation drop last year. But vis-a-vis 2015 it may be on par,” he said. So, it’s a wait and watch on how the next two quarters will turn out. &lt;br&gt;Jailkhani sees the economy opening up and GST settling down. “Next two quarters have to do extremely well. I see a positive impact in the first quarter at least. Also, with elections in 2018, the overall sentiment will change,” he said. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;From sports’ perspective, Akshaya Kolhe, Director – Head of Sales for ESPN, South Asia said that 2018 will continue seeing sports play a crucial role for marketers to connect with people. He shared, “It starts with India’s cricket tour to South Africa, followed by two big events with the 11th season of IPL and FIFA World Cup which will be a big focus for marketers during the year. Apart from these, a multi-sport landscape continues to grow with Grand-slams, international football and home-grown leagues,” he said.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jailkhani signed off by saying “The worse is already behind us.”&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="http://e4mcms.exchange4media.com/files/1513531649_BuedKN_Info-1.jpg"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;img src="http://e4mcms.exchange4media.com/files/1513531646_WmSp9y_Info-2.jpg"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;With inputs from Venkata Susmita Biswas and Akshata Murthy&lt;/em&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1513565809_E2hMkP_big_(15).jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/spotlight-news/adex-takes-a-beatingindustry-hopes-for-revival-in-2018-87537.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>11/12/2017</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Adex takes a beating; industry hopes for revival in 2018</news:title>
      <news:description>It’s a nail biting finale as the end of 2017 inches closer and the suspense about growth statistics engulfs the Indian advertising industry. When it fell face down after demonetisation, it took it in its stride and began the new year of 2017 with optimism. They prayed hard for the year to close on a double-digit growth even after momentarily losing their balance on the GST highway.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the industry waits for the moment of truth at their destination, early indicators show that they registered the slowest growth this year since 2012. The numbers are still being crunched and the writing is not on the wall; but the 5.2 per cent growth in 2012 cast a big shadow even though it’s not that bad this year. The industry that was on a high in 2015 with as much as 17.6% growth has seen a gradual decline in the last couple of years. Hit by demonetisation bang in the middle of the festive season, 2016 registered a growth of 12.5% which has now dropped further in 2017.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some studies suggest that the industry grew by barely 10-11 per cent this year, a significant phase of low growth since the massive dip in 2012. The slow growth is due to demonetisation, implementation of the Goods and Services Tax regime. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Demonetization Blues&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;The industry may have secretly wished for a meteor strike as the dinosaur of demonetization raised its head. The first two quarters of 2017 witnessed slow growth owing to the immediate impact of the demonetisation initiative introduced by PM Narendra Modi. During this phase, a number of heavy spenders, including FMCG brands, tightened their purse strings and delayed promotional spending. Nearly 20-25 per cent of ad spends were affected because of the demonetisation of high value currency. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leading FMCG company, Hindustan Unilever Limited, registered a 3.8 per cent YOY decline in ad spends in the quarter that ended on December 31, 2017. Home-grown FMCG firm Dabur deferred ad spends and reported a 20 per cent YOY decline in ad spends. P&amp;amp;G India also registered a 12 per cent decline in ad spends during Q3FY17 when compared to Q3FY16. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the year came to an end, the FMCG industry saw a revival and an increase in ad spends. HUL increased ad and promotional spending by 20 per cent from Rs. 851 crore in Q2 FY17 to Rs. 1,023 crore Q2 FY18. The company spent Rs. 905 crore in first quarter of FY18 ending June 30.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Early estimates for 2017 had pegged the growth rate at around 13 per cent (Pitch-Madison Report 2016,) with hopes that the industry will inch closer to the Rs. 60,000 crore mark. The hopes of scaling the bean stalk were dashed but stability returned to the industry during the festive season. “In spite of the carry forward impact of demonetisation and GST disruption around July, the growth is not dramatically lower than previous years. It will be a great achievement if we touch double digit growth by the end of the year,” said Ashish Bhasin, ‎Chairman &amp;amp; CEO South Asia Dentsu Aegis Network.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Advertising expenditure during the festive season was estimated to be around Rs. 24,000 crore, accounting for nearly 30-40 per cent of the annual ad spends. “The latter part of the year saw good growth. So, my anticipation is that we will end the year on a double-digit growth,” said Bhasin. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As per forecasts by Zenith, a Publicis Groupe-run media agency, 2017 will see a growth of around 11.5 per cent and close at Rs. 53,918 crore.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Big Spenders in 2017&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There was an itch in the hands of gods as the FMCG and auto sectors, the two high spenders for the advertising industry, exercised caution in 2017. Amazon India, which has emerged as the second highest spender on advertising with a budget of around Rs. 800-1,000 crore (Pitch Madison Report 2016) continued to invest in promotional activities in 2017. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to reports, during the festive season Amazon, Flipkart and Snapdeal spent a cumulative Rs. 2,000 crore on advertising. Amazon India placed twice the number of ads on television as compared to Flipkart during the run-up to the festive season. In August and September, Amazon had 1,58,280 insertions compared to Flipkart's 77,060, as per BARC data. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smartphone brands flaunted their deep-pockets this year. The smartphone market, which is witnessing a boom due to cheap data rates, was on a spending spree. Smartphone brands took centre stage at all the sporting events, spending heavily on sponsorships and advertisements. Vivo spent more than Rs. 350 crore on marketing this year. The brand bagged the Indian Premier League (IPL) title sponsorship for two years after replacing PepsiCo and allocated Rs. 200 crore only for IPL promotions. According to reports, the player has also spent around Rs. 80-100 crore during the festive season, double of what they had spent last year. Together, OPPO and Vivo were estimated to have spent Rs. 2,200 crore on advertising in 2017. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rise of Free-to-Air Channels&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite the slow growth, the industry witnessed a number of watershed events, making 2017 a significant year for the world of advertising. The rise of Free-to-Air channels brought advertisers close to a fresh set of audience. “The accessibility of media with Free to Air channels and almost free data today lets marketers have access to this completely new set of consumers/markets who were earlier very difficult to reach,” said Banerjee. According to estimates by the FICCI - KPMG Media and Entertainment Industry Report 2017, advertisers were expected to double their spends on FTA channels in 2017. “The FTA channels garnered an estimated Rs. 400-500 crore of the overall TV advertising pie in 2016; which is expected to rise to Rs. 800-1000 crore in 2017,” the report said. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Flat Year Ahead? &lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Although the sector may have found the road to hell paved with good intentions in 2017, leaders are not that pessimistic. “We witnessed mid-year bumps with rollout of GST but all macroeconomic indicators suggest we are heading for a good year ahead,” said Shekhar Banerjee, Chief Operating Officer, Madison Media.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some forecasts say that&amp;nbsp;2018 looks bleak.&amp;nbsp;The Zenith study pegs&amp;nbsp;the growth at 8.4 per cent for 2018, dashing hopes for a double-digit growth.&amp;nbsp;The Forrester Predictions for 2018, forecast a flat year for advertising globally. The report notes that, “This is not an advertising budget crisis but simply changing priorities.” As per the predictions, CMOs will focus their efforts and monies on revitalizing customer experience, synchronising loyalty programs to customer expectations, understanding digital platform algorithms and advancing Martech to deliver individualised experiences at scale. This is because, “CMOs can no more defend underperforming media spends focused on customer acquisition, as churn rates escalate or stand idly by as digital platforms threaten to disintermediate their relationship with customers,” the report noted. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most industry insiders and analysts said that there is no reason to be so pessimistic. Banerjee said that the accessibility of media with FTA channels and year round sporting events will fuel a strong growth in Adex as we get into 2018. “Looking at the recent trends, we should expect lower sales promotion and BTL spends from marketers and higher ATL spends towards demand creation. There will be an increased focus towards performance marketing, even by CPG, given the growing strength of online grocery as a sales channel,” he added. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The advertising industry has pinned its hopes on digital as it’s driving impressive growth. "Earlier, all media would grow at similar rates but now different media are growing at dramatically different rates. For example, digital advertising will grow at 25-30 per cent while English print will be under pressure. In 2018, we can expect a growth of around 11-12 per cent and not as low as 8-9 per cent,” said Bhasin. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Indian Advertising Market&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Year&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Growth&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Yearly Ad Spend&amp;nbsp;2011&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;9.6%&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Rs 22, 433 cr&lt;br&gt;2012&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;5.2%  &lt;span style="white-space:pre"&gt;  &lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Rs 28, 854 cr&lt;br&gt;2013&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;11.3%  &lt;span style="white-space:pre"&gt;  &lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Rs 32,106 cr&lt;br&gt;2014&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;16.5%  &lt;span style="white-space:pre"&gt;  &lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Rs 37, 405 cr&lt;br&gt;2015&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;17.6%  &lt;span style="white-space:pre"&gt;  &lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Rs 43,991 cr&lt;br&gt;2016&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;12.5%  &lt;span style="white-space:pre"&gt;  &lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Rs 49, 480 cr&lt;br&gt;2017&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;13.5%  &lt;span style="white-space:pre"&gt;  &lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Rs 56, 152 cr&lt;br&gt;*Pitch-Madison Report&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Revised Estimates (*Zenith Media Report)&lt;br&gt;2017&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;11.5%  &lt;span style="white-space:pre"&gt;  &lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Rs 53, 918 cr</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1512964657_v9BrZM_big_(79).jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/spotlight-news/the-battle-that-print-industry-fought-in-2017-87432.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>04/12/2017</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>The battle that print industry fought in 2017</news:title>
      <news:description>Print journalism in India seems to persistently be in a race against time and technology. When news updates can be read on smartphones instantly in this day and age, newspapers are still being published at a 24-hour gap. “To search that new identity for itself, is the greatest challenge that the print media faces today,” said Union Minister Arun Jaitley.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;In urban areas, social media is becoming an effective source of news and yet, the print industry in India continues to grow. However, the growth rate is slowing down.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;While it can’t be denied that digital media has restricted the growth of Television, Radio and Print; it should be noted that the boom of digital media has impacted English publications more than the regional language publications.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;According to KMPG, regional language newspapers are expected to drive the sector growth as advertisers are now more interested in the medium. But, the rising digital content consumption is still perceived to be a long-term risk to the industry.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;In 2017, the print industry had to tide many troubled waters besides surviving the digital media wave. Demonetisation, implication of Goods and Services Tax (GST) and restrictions on press freedom has impacted the industry irrevocably.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Demonetisation&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;The print media majorly depends on advertisement and circulation revenue. The period arguably saw a fall in both.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;With demonetisation being announced on November 8, the sector saw one of the worst ever economic slowdowns. “From November 9, 2016 till end of February, 2017, the business came to a complete standstill,” said Sandeep Khosla, CEO of Mid-day. "Our major revenue comes from retail and realty and both were hit badly post demonetisation,” he added.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;“People were more interested to retain cash for buying necessary items. Purchasing printed matter is not the first priority for anyone,” said Paresh Nath, Publisher, Delhi Press.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;According to KPMG report, due to cancellation of Release Orders (ROs) from major advertisers, many English, Hindi and other regional newspapers were impacted and there was a consequent reduction in the number of pages during the November – December period. Q3’17 revenues of print-media companies reported margin de-growth of 3 to 5 per cent.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Circulation revenue of newspapers/magazines was also impacted due to note ban for a short period, as most of the hawkers and vendors generally deal in cash. Additionally, classified ads also reduced as even they relied on cash transactions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="http://e4mcms.exchange4media.com/files/1512355992_nE1B3L_Info%283%29.jpg"&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Goods and Services Tax&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;“People were just learning to deal with demonetisation and GST was announced, affecting the ad spend. The impact was equally bad,” said Varghese Chandy, vice president, Malayala Manorama. “We saw the retail trade being badly impacted post the economic reforms, lot of small time retailers were wiped out,” he added.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Under the new tax regime, newsprint was subjected to a heightened tax rate of 5 per cent as opposed to 3 per cent earlier. Print advertisements, which were earlier free from taxation, are also taxed at 5 per cent now.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Indranil Roy, CEO, Outlook Group, told exchange4media that demonetisation did not impact the group as much as the tax reform did. “I think the impact of the slowdown on advertising is a mix of demonetisation and GST. GST has a bigger impact on advertising,” Roy said.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Regional vs English language publications&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;In the quarter ending in September 2017, HT Media, the publisher of Hindustan Times and Mint, showed a decline in advertising revenue by 8.14 per cent as compared to the second quarter of the previous year. The ad revenue fell to Rs. 395 crore from Rs. 430 crore during the same period, last year.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;“Advertising revenue growth continues to be a challenge in our core Print business, with this quarter witnessing high level of uncertainty across industries on account of GST implementation,” said Shobhana Bhartia, Chairperson and Editorial Director, HT Media.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;On the other hand, Sudhir Agarwal, Managing Director, DB Corp Ltd (DBCL), said, “We are happy to report another quarter of noteworthy progress and implementation of several growth-oriented initiatives.”&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;DBCL which publishes Dainik Bhaskar, Divya Bhaskar, Dainik Divya Marathi and Saurashtra Samachar, showed a consolidated ad revenues growth by 6 per cent year-on-year at Rs. 396.6 crore as against Rs. 374 crore during Q2 last year. Its circulation revenue grew by 8 per cent YOY at Rs. 127.3 crore from Rs. 117.9 crore during Q2 last year.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Interestingly, the existing data on language wise ad revenue confirm the trend of how regional language newspapers are registering strong growth while English Publications are finding it hard to match the pace.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;In 2016, English newspapers’ ad revenue grew by 3.5 per cent and for Hindi and other regional language newspapers, it was 7.1 per cent and 8.7 per cent respectively.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;"With smaller towns and villages becoming more aware and educated, regional will continue to grow. It's the English newspaper which needs to worry and rethink their strategy, "said Vijay Darda, Chairman, Lokmat.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Circulation of print publications&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;In contrast to developed countries, India’s paid-for daily circulation is growing. Print industry in India is growing at 4.87 per cent in CAGR over a 10 year period. In 2016, the industry grew at 7.0 per cent.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Although the growth rate is positive, English language newspapers are under too much pressure with the rise in readers’ interest in digital content. However, the language newspapers are driving growth in viewership as well as advertising.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;With regional newspapers’ growth of 9.4 per cent, Hindi and English newspapers are growing at 8.3 per cent and 3.7 per cent respectively.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;However, the Audit Bureau of Circulation’s (ABC’s) data for the period of January-June 2017 and July-December 2017, shows a decline in circulation numbers of many member publications across languages.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;For the top 20 dailies across languages (member publications,) the growth rate of circulation is negative 0.04 per cent for that period. Amar Ujala, a leading Hindi Daily, showed a decline in circulation during Jan-June 2017; however, Virendra Pathania, Vice President Sales Promotion and Market Development for the group, told us that Amar Ujala showed “significant growth of 12 per cent in circulation in 2017.”&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Weekly news publications and magazines are in the same boat.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Although, it is difficult to attribute the negative growth rate of circulation figures to demonetisation and GST, they surely seem to have played a role.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;As Paresh Nath, Publisher of the Delhi Press, said, “Purchasing printed matter is not first priority for anyone. People were more interested (during the period of demonetisation) to retain cash for buying things of day to day needs than to spend on newspapers or magazines.”&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;On August 30, Ministry of Information and Broadcasting (I&amp;amp;B) entrusted the Press Information Bureau (PIB) with the task of verifying the circulation of newspapers. This was the first time that PIB had been tasked with verifying circulation of newspapers. Before this, the task was undertaken by the Registrar of Newspapers of India (RNI.)&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;According to media reports, the step is taken keeping in mind the 2019 General Elections so that the Directorate of Advertising and Visual Publicity (DAVP,) a body that decides allocation of government advertisements to newspapers, knows which newspapers to give ads to basis their real circulation numbers.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Censorship&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;The year 2017 witnessed many such incidents that were last witnessed during the Emergency period.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;On November 1, Rajasthan Patrika, a national daily, wrote a sharp front page editorial stating that it will not report any news related to Rajasthan Chief Minister Vasundhara Raje or her government officials until the controversial Criminal Laws (Rajasthan Amendment) Ordinance, that bars media from naming public servants and politicians as accused, is revoked.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;On National Press Day, November 16, symbolic of a free and responsible press in India, the national daily, left its editorial space blank to register its protest against the threat to freedom of press.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Similarly, newspapers in Tripura left their editorial spaces blank to protest the killing of a journalist, Sudip Datta Bhowmik, by a Tripura State Rifles personnel at the headquarters of 2nd battalion and in Manipur, major newspapers left its editorial blank to protest burning copies of Poknapham newspaper by members of BJP youth wing for allegedly publishing ‘disparaging’ content against the prime minister.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Additionally, Hindustan Times Editor, Bobby Ghosh, stepped down from his position in September amid rumours that his exit was preceded by Shobhana Bhartia’s, Chairperson HT Media, meeting with the prime minister.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Soon after Ghosh’s exit, Hindustan Times took down its hate tracker initiative, a microsite that aimed at being a “national database on crimes in the name of religion, caste and race.” This was initiated by Bobby Ghosh.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1512355782_Dfs5uO_Year-Ender-2.gif</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/spotlight-news/from-competition-to-collaboration-the-changing-dynamics-of-offline-and-online-retail-87348.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>27/11/2017</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>From competition to collaboration - The changing dynamics of offline and online retail</news:title>
      <news:description>In the last few years, the offline retail industry has increasingly come under stress with the rising popularity of online shopping platforms. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Led by big discounts, online retail players like Amazon, Flipkart, Snapdeal, Shopclues, etc. have managed to woo customers with their innovative and aggressive marketing mix. Moreover, the convenience of shopping from a remote location with competitive price points has added to their popularity. The numbers say it all. As per the latest study by Forrester Research, Indian online retail market is expected to reach $64 billion by 2021, growing at a five-year CAGR of 31.2 percent, making it the fastest growing online market in the world. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Morgan Stanley puts these figures differently. According to its latest estimates, India’s e-commerce market will grow at a 30 per cent compound annual growth rate for gross merchandise value worth $200 billion by 2026. Whatever be the case, the online retail market in India is poised to become one of the biggest drivers of the growth in the sector.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;With an internet user base of about 450 million, which is roughly 40 per cent of the population, India has become the second-largest user base in world, only behind China which has about 650 million or 48 per cent of the population. Led by the spurt in smartphone penetration, improved logistics infrastructure and convenient payment gateways, online shopping is set to maintain a robust growth in the time to come.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Offline Vs Online Retail&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="http://e4mcms.exchange4media.com/files/1511751959_1rfKB2_Graph-1-_-Source-eMarketer%281%29.jpg"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Looking at the growth and potential of the online retail market in India, the offline sector has been realigning to the changing market dynamics. In a way, it has been forced to change. While some experts have painted a gloomy picture of the future of offline retail, others have offered co-existence as the way forward for both.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If we look at offline retail sector closely, one of its biggest strengths has been its sheer size. With over 14 million retail outlets in India, many online players are now looking at co-creating newer possibilities by leveraging the power of offline retail. This may be the reason why the growth of online-to-offline (O2O) is currently gaining momentum. O2O is all about leveraging the digital and mobile medium to drive sales through the offline platforms. In other words, it is about establishing a link between the online discovery of products and offline transactions for the same.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaking about the battle for market control between offline and online and how the former is fast reinventing the game, Harish Bijoor, Brand-expert &amp;amp; Founder, Harish Bijoor Consults Inc. says, “The offline and online retail battle will be a continuous one. This is a see-saw battle. The weight is skewed towards offline as of now for sure. Even as online retail makes rampant strides, offline retailers will reinvent their game by being savvy. We have seen that happen. Every weakness of online will be the key strength point of offline retail. The elephant will therefore dance. Offline retailers in India, with the biggest brand names in early organized retail such as Shoppers Stop and the Future Group, are doing exactly this. And the one that is making the elephant dance is ecommerce for sure.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts also believe that the future of retail will eventually become extremely personalized and powered by data-driven insights. According to them, online and offline touch points will merge to deliver the most intuitive customer experience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sugham Dhall, Business Head, International Brand Luxury, Tata Cliq, says, “I see it settling with the convergence of online and offline. There is a new buzz word called the Omni channel. What Omni channel does is that it’s able to maximize footfalls, increase retail turnover and sales. We are enabling Omni channels for brands. We don’t see offline as competition, we see us as enablers to offline.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This point is also well argued by Manu Agarwal, Founder, Naaptol, who believes that the offline vs online debate will finally find a right mix through interdependence. “Omni channel is the need of the hour and thus most of the retail players are embracing it,” says Agarwal. He also vouches for the power of offline. “The Time Trade Retail 2017 Report also endorses that 70 per cent people plan to shop in stores in 2017. Even in our Focus Group Discussions, the customers are vocal about products being available in their cities and towns. We at Naaptol will soon getting into brick and mortar business,” he says.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="http://e4mcms.exchange4media.com/files/1511751966_ihkTO6_Graph-2-Source-Forrester-Research%281%29.jpg"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Re-imagining Offline&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;With new market forces realigning the retail sector in India, offline players have responded to the change and have started reimagining their approach. The power of the reimagined offline is validated by online players too, who are rushing to set up offline stores for better connect with customers. A good example of this is the way big smartphone players like Samsung, Oppo and Vivo are investing in setting up experiential stores to leverage the power of offline retail.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moreover, offline players have also adopted learnings from their online counterparts, especially in the domain of customer engagement and this is becoming its biggest strength too. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“In my opinion, the online players have acted as a catalyst for the market growth. At Vijay Sales, we have become more tuned to our guest’s needs; be it in giving the product demonstration, delivery scheduling and post purchase service which has helped us grow. I don’t see any challenge to offline players due to online presence,” adds Nilesh Gupta, Managing Partner - Vijay Sales.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;With offline retail 2.0 adapting to new demands, the perceived competition with its online counterpart is fast turning into a collaborative reality which will only strengthen in the time to come.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1511752050_gvBtid_Spotlight.gif</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/spotlight-news/happy-10th-birthday-viacom18the-rise-and-way-ahead...-87246.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>20/11/2017</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Happy 10th Birthday Viacom18: The rise and way ahead...</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p&gt;Reaching out to 80 countries through 44 TV channels, having five diverse lines of business that engage with 500 million consumers, Viacom18, a 50-50 joint venture between Reliance Industries-owned Network18 and Viacom Inc, has turned out to be one of the fastest success stories in India’s media and entertainment industry. It has reported to have a 40X growth in the top line during first 10 years of its existence in India. The company has its presence everywhere—TV, digital, cinema, merchandise and live.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Talking about its ‘phenomenal growth,’ Anupriya Acharya, Group CEO, Publicis Media India added, “This is especially commendable since they are a (relatively) late entrant and have only been around for about a decade.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sudhanshu Vats, Group CEO, Viacom 18, described them as ‘fantastic 10 years.’ “We have grown 40 times in top line in those 10 years. In the last five years, we have been PAT profitable as well. Most importantly we have built an organisation which has a heart, soul and mind,” said Vats who joined Viacom18 in April 2012 and steered the company into profitability across all lines.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Profitability comes from their strong dependence on advertising which has relatively reduced from 75 per cent five years back to 60 per cent. Vats further emphasised on that and said, “Our film business has also grown considerably. Our subscription revenues have grown. We have now added these new businesses which contribute about 3-5 per cent of our current portfolio. With our portfolio as well, we have managed to reduce our dependence on one channel and brought more channels overall. Moving ahead we would like to keep balancing the portfolio and would like to see 50 per cent coming from outside advertising. I see 10-15 per of our revenue cent coming from our new businesses between digital, consumer products and live and 12-15 per cent from Viacom18 Motion Pictures.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the company completes its glorious decade in India, we look at its successes and the reasons that helped it not just survive in this competitive market but thrive.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Launch of GEC Colors&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barely eight months in the business, Viacom18 launched a Hindi GEC called Colors which revolutionised the market with its right programming mix of popular reality shows. Led by Rajesh Kamat (now managing director, Emerald Media (KKR &amp;amp; Co’s Media platform,) it was introduced in the market with the tagline ‘Jasbaat Ke Rang.’ Buzz was created with huge investments in marketing campaigns with right targeting. Their target audience were housewives aged between 25 and 45, youth and male Indian population.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“2007/ 2008 saw the launch of multiple new GEC players; which meant that with the GEC space expanding, the existing players were also aggressively trying to defend their positions. Given the scenario, we felt if we were to have any chance of success, we would have to launch a multi- pronged attack using 3Ds – Differentiation, Disruption, Distribution,” said Kamat.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Explaining what made people switch to Colors leaving their loyalties behind, Kamat said in a time when escapist saas-bahu shows ruled the roost, they came in with differentiated social dramas like ‘Balika Vadhu’ and ‘Uttaran.’ “With ‘Khatron Ke Khiladi’ and ‘Bigg Boss,’ we disrupted the prime time which was then dominated by soaps and dramas. While we had the right content, we had to make equally sure that our content reached its audience. Back when we launched, those were the days of analogue distribution where the placement of channels really mattered. Hence Colors launched with a neighbourhood strategy, wherein we were tactically placed right before or right after a leading GEC channel,” he told e4m.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;With a good value proposition along with right distribution strategies, Colors escalated from 9th position to 3rd within three weeks of its launch. Since then it has disrupted the leadership ladder and is always one of the main contenders for the top spot in the viewership share. Ashish Bhasin, ‎Chairman &amp;amp; CEO South Asia, Dentsu Aegis Network, credited it to their understanding of the market. He said, “They obviously had a strategy and understanding of what the market needs were and executing and implementing it well. That was the key. Ultimately for any channel to succeed or fail the critical thing is the content. It’s easy to launch a channel with great content for the initial period and then figure out later on. What’s hard is to continuously sustain good quality content. I think they managed that pretty well. They got the consumer’s pulse and were able to deliver it right.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What worked in its favour were its experiments with formats whether it’s supernatural ‘Naagin,’ or the voyeuristic reality drama ‘Big Boss’ or star-studded thriller ‘24.’ There were times when it failed. The second season of ‘24’ and ‘Kavachh’ failed in TVR game, but the GEC always managed to be at the top of its game one way or the other.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Also from brand perspective Jagdeep Kapoor, Chairman and Managing Director Samsika Marketing Consultants, felt that Viacom18 through its strong brands like Colors has been able to fill a gap in market for aspirational entertainment. He said, “Colors, as an example, has been able to enter minds and hearts of Indian consumers through its programming and strategically move them away from occasional viewing (consumption) to regular viewing.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To conclude, Kamat said, “With the 3D’s we broke the monotony that was setting into the Hindi GEC space and came in with new content, new faces that viewers did not associate with any another channel or programme. This effort to be distinctive and fresh was appreciated by the viewers and the rest as they say is history.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://e4mcms.exchange4media.com/files/1511147208_CRE3R4_Info%281%29.jpg"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sharpening its regional presence&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Looking at the regional space, Viacom18 had foresight of its potential, back in 2013 when it initiated acquisition in Eenadu TV’s (ETV) regional GECs followed by extending Colors branding to its Marathi, Gujarati, Kannada, Bangla and Oriya counterparts. Kannada space did well for them which led them to launch the second GEC called Colors Super. Acharya praised its acquisition strategy. “The ETV channels gave Viacom18 an instant fillip in the regional entertainment space. Rebranding these channels to Colors only strengthened the brand and gave it further appeal. Regional markets, as we know, are the fastest growing today for both print and television,” she said.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The focus on this portfolio is only set to strengthen further with the launch of Colors Tamil early next year. With the market already packed by extremely popular Sun TV and other competitive players like Star Vijay, Zee Tamil and KTV among others, it will be interesting to see how Colors Tamil holds on its own. Vats agreed that Tamil is a challenging market but he promises the channel’s entry to be ‘very innovative and disruptive.’ He gives his word, “It will be big and new to that market. We are hopeful that the audience likes it,” he said.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Popularity of kid's channels&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even in kid’s cluster, Viacom18 scored with popular channels like Nick and Sonic which can be attributed to its popular shows like ‘Motu Patlu’ and ‘Shiva.’ The entertainment company leveraged the popularity of kid’s properties (‘Ninja Hattori,’ ‘Peppa Pig’ and ‘Motu Patlu’) to strengthen its consumer product business. Till last November, its kids cluster had a CAGR of 50 per cent in that business itself. Then Viacom18 tapped into animation industry with its maiden 3D animation theatrical ‘Motu Patlu King of Kings’ which reportedly made Rs. 4 crore.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tapping into digital&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Digital frontier has turned out to be a tricky game with huge investment on AVOD platform Voot’s content and marketing. Launched last year, its originals, with few exceptions, had lukewarm response. But interestingly enough, what worked for it were catch-up TV and exclusive show extension properties like ‘Unseen Undekha,’ ‘Cutless’ of ‘Bigg Boss,’ ‘MTV Splitsvilla’ and ‘Voot Kids.’ Voot claimed to have amassed 70 million views for ‘Bigg Boss’ in its first 10 days. Now Viacom18 is planning to take it behind pay-wall mid next year.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Successful cinematic foray&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Viacom18 Motion Pictures, one of the first studio-model-based motion picture businesses in India, has given Indian cinema some standout offerings like ‘Toilet-Ek Prem Katha,’ ‘Margarita With a Straw,’ ‘Queen,’ ‘Bhaag Milkha Bhaag,’ ‘Kahaani’ and ‘Gangs of Wasseypur’ among others. According to Rahul Kadbet, Head of Programming, Carnival Cinemas, the production house has mastered the art of filmmaking despite challenging its conventional norms. He credits the success to Neeraj Goswami, VP, Sales and Distribution. He said, “A dynamic and result-oriented professional in the business of distribution in the movies business, his vision towards the distribution strategy only made it possible to achieve this kind of success.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;With its recent entry into regional languages like Bengali, Marathi, Punjabi and down South, Vats informed us that the industry will see more movie productions in these markets.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Merchandising and more&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Looking at its merchandising business, Viacom18 Consumer Products with its 30+ brands across 14 brands has crossed Rs. 200 crore in retail sales in India according to media reports. Vats has aimed to make it the favoured house for consumer products in the country.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When it comes to IPs, Viacom18 has managed to reach a million consumers through impactful large format live properties such as Vh1 Supersonic, MTV VMAI, Nickelodeon KCA, Emerge, MTV Xtreme and Comedy Central Chuckle Festival among others. Vats shared that they are continuing to invest in creating new IPs across genres.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1511147482_eRlts7_big(5).gif</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/spotlight-news/are-marketers-ready-to-embrace-the-full-service-model-87140.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>13/11/2017</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Are marketers ready to embrace the full-service model?</news:title>
      <news:description>The rise of television gave us the all-powerful media buyers of today. They remained a core part of the advertising agency until the 1990’s when advertising agencies began to consolidate the media buying business into separate standalone entities. Now, with the digital ecosystem coming into place, it seems like the advertising world has tweaked the agency model to return to an era where all services are offered under one roof, be that creative, digital, PR, or even media buying. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This racy ride that the advertising industry undertook led to the creation of specialists and super-specialists. Marketers benefited from the specialists but are now forced to explain their briefs and business problems to multiple specialists to get the job done. The problem is that the specialists are now spread out. As hard as agencies try, marketers are still seeking solutions from multiple service providers with very few, rare clients who really leverage the full-service model. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The full-service model has made such a huge comeback in the recent years that every significant player in the ad world is offering full-service. In some cases, it is the agency itself that is offering full-service and in others it is the network as a whole that is consolidating the services under one umbrella. Agencies that do not want to be left behind are building and adding competencies every day. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But, “Hardly any significant player is buying full-service,” said Vikas Mehta, CEO, PointNine Lintas. “While the model seems extremely promising on paper, its market adoption has been excruciatingly slow in progress. You can count on your fingertips the number of clients who have one agency doing all the marketing duties for them. The problem is that the promise of full-service is a complex and difficult one to keep,” he said. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unless a few more kinks are straightened out, marketers claim&amp;nbsp;it will be hard for them&amp;nbsp;to truly embrace the full-service model.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Uniform Specialised Expertise &lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;The industry is constantly becoming more complex, creating the demand for specialists. Especially in the digital ecosystem, there are multiple areas that need specialised focus, such as social media, performance marketing, content, apps, design.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As an advocate of the unified agency approach, Amit Tiwari, VP Marketing, Havells, said that for a marketer to completely embrace the full-service model, it is important for the agency itself to have the specialisation and expertise in all the services that a marketer requires. “But the point is that very few agencies have the competence where they can provide best in class services across disciplines,” noted Sandeep Goyal, Founder, Mogae Media. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is a two-way street; once agencies up their expertise, the ball is in the marketer’s court. Tiwari felt that marketers themselves need to have the conviction towards leveraging this model. “A good number of marketers, around 30-40 per cent, have developed the conviction for this model. This conviction has to be supported by agencies improving their expertise because one cannot allow the business to be affected at the cost of adopting the full-service model,” he said. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Talent Acquisition&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;While one of the benefits of the full-service model is that clients can have a single touch point at the agency, talent is at the core of this model. Unless there are people who equally understand all the focus areas, implementation of this model will remain on paper. “Talent is the crux of the issue. Integration will remain notional until the talent issue is addressed by agencies,” said Vivek Sharma, Chief Marketing Officer, Pidilite Industries. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Advertising agencies are all about people and not products,” said Sudip Ghose, Senior Vice President –Sales, Marketing and Service, VIP Industries, adding that “very rarely will you even find talent who understand digital media and traditional media.” &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Digital Integration&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;For most marketers, the real struggle is to find an agency that understands both traditional and digital media. It is this sweet spot that agencies need to find, in order to win the trust of marketers. “Unlike the traditional media environment, in the digital environment, I have not found an agency that delivers the complete digital package,” said Karan Kumar, Head of Brand and Marketing, Fabindia. He says that though he is a proponent of full-service in the traditional medium, the digital medium remains one where he as a marketer gets his various services from multiple agencies. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Full-service Network and Full-service Agency&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Consolidation is taking place in the advertising world with networks either building or buying competencies. It still is not enough for marketers to choose a full-service network to work with. “If the best expertise lies within a network, I do not mind working with multiple agencies within a network. But that is not my top priority,” said Kumar. Marketers feel the same way about networks as they do about agencies. The ease of working with a single touch point is not as much as a priority as the performance of the business and achieving business goals. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sharma added, "The onus of integrating the brand’s offering and communication lies with the client. They are the ones who have to ensure that they maintain consistency in terms of positioning, values and persona, offering across all touch points in all mediums." &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Client Maturity&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not all clients are buying full-service and this also has to do with the type of clients. Mature clients with very high advertising budgets who have very strong marketing history and competencies choose to opt for specialised offerings and best available expertise. “They may choose to go with one agency that offers the best of two worlds, but that is not driven by the need for ease or integration,” explained Sharma. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mid-size clients who have an annual advertising budget of around Rs. 100-200 crore are a mixed bag and “may opt for the full-service agencies or specialised agencies depending on their maturity,” felt Sharma. The third bag of clients, Indian companies that are building their brand locally, “Who do not have the marketing experience, maturity and competencies may choose to go with a full-service agency for their comfort as they begin their marketing journey,” said Sharma. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“As clients mature and their needs become complex, they will choose to go for specialised agencies,” added Sharma. Echoing his thoughts, Ghose also said that complex requirements demand specialists and therefore the future will belong to specialists. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Way Forward&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;This phase of consolidation of services under one umbrella will create the opportunity for clients to come on board for multiple service even though they may not start out with more than one or two services to begin with. “It is not likely that all clients will use all the 26 Dentsu Aegis Network (DAN) agencies. It is more like there are a number of doors and windows to enter the house of DAN. A client may enter through any of the routes available and over a period of time, the effort is to provide as many marketing communication services as we can,” said Ashish Bhasin, Chairman &amp;amp; CEO South Asia Dentsu Aegis Network. He said that the one Profit &amp;amp; Loss model that that DAN follows has immensely helped the network serve clients better.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Agencies and networks recognise the need for experts and specialists in every field and said that the full-service of today is not the same as it was thirty years ago. Explaining how it all comes together, Anita Nayyar, ‎CEO India &amp;amp; South Asia - ‎Havas Media Group, said, “The unbundling of services will stay as expertise functions within the full-service model. In the realm of the agencies there will be one brand custodian who will deliver to the client and take the services from the unbundled offerings within the agency.”</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1510544826_NwxLMe_big_(15).gif</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/spotlight-news/it-was-a-happy-diwaliad-spends-report-15-20increase-over-last-year-experts-87040.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>06/11/2017</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>It was a happy Diwali, ad spends report 15-20% increase over last year : Experts</news:title>
      <news:description>Following a good spell during the festive season, the advertising industry has witnessed a recovery with an increase in ad spends across sectors. Industry experts said that there has been a 15-20 per cent increase in ad spends this year over last year. This much-needed recovery and increase in spends will help the advertising industry experience an overall growth of around 10-12 per cent over&amp;nbsp;last year. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apprehensions about this festive season were high ahead of the first big festival of the season - Ganesh Chaturthi. The implementation of the Goods and Services Tax, RERA, residual impact of demonetisation and a short festive season were expected to hamper&amp;nbsp;performance this season. But the industry seems to have settled down,&amp;nbsp;according to&amp;nbsp;experts. If not for these hurdles, the growth could have been much higher, said Vivek Bhargava, CEO, DAN Performance Group. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The growth of advertising expenditure until July was around 4 per cent. “We have now revised our own estimates for the year to about 10 per cent on the conservative side. But this means that last quarter should see growth of 16-17&amp;nbsp;per cent,” said Ashish Bhasin, Chairman &amp;amp; CEO South Asia Dentsu Aegis Network. Following an increase in ad spends during the festive season the “industry is recovering,” Bhasin added. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even though the going was tough, traditional media like TV and OOH tasted success and registered satisfactory growth during the festive season. The broadcast industry is struggling with 7-8 per cent growth this season. Select broadcasters such as&amp;nbsp;Sony Pictures Network and Disney India have seen healthy growth. “SPN recorded an impressive growth of more than 20 per cent,” said Rohit Gupta, President, Network Sales, Sony Pictures Networks India. He credits this growth to the high performance of the network’s main and FTA channels, like SET, MAX, Sony SAB and Pal and not to the industry. “April onwards, we had a consistent high growth. We saw spending from across all categories whether it’s automobile, consumer goods, mobile handset, telecom or FMCG,” he said.&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="http://e4mcms.exchange4media.com/files/1509936357_x5zn7I_Spot-Light-Infographic-%28Revised%29.jpg"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Similarly, Abhishek Maheshwari, VP &amp;amp; Head, Media Networks &amp;amp; Interactive, Disney India, said that Disney India has seen a growth of 25-30 per cent over regular months on the back of brands who want to make their presence felt in the festive season. The categories mostly included Auto (two and four-wheeler,) consumer goods, mobile manufacturers, FMCG, e-commerce and paints. He observed, “Post the lull the companies saw post demonetisation and GST, there was good buoyancy this festive season where companies stepped out to spend aggressively to gain the lost momentum and market shares.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The implementation of GST, RERA and a short festive season did not bode well for the OOH sector. “Though all these might prove to be great steps in hindsight, as of now, it has forced every business to relook at their structures forcing a halt in marketing activities,” said Alok Gupta, Director, Graphisads.&amp;nbsp;Despite the low growth of the OOH sector, Gupta is now positive. “However, things have started to look up now as companies have settled down and with govt taking booster steps such as Bank Recapitalisation, one really looks forward to a steep growth curve. &lt;em&gt;Acche din&lt;/em&gt; might just be around the corner!” he said.&amp;nbsp; In fact, as an indicator of the &lt;em&gt;Acche din&lt;/em&gt;, one of the leading media buyers bought a significant chunk of the OOH inventory for the festive season, out of fear that OOH inventory may fall short. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The radio sector saw a healthy performance this season. Festival revenues of one of India’s leading radio channels, Radio One, were up by 25 per cent during September and October over July and August. “November will ascertain if the upswing is a consistent one as sales at the clients' end generally seem to be depressed due to GST issues and lowered demand,” said Vineet Singh Hukmani, MD and CEO,&amp;nbsp;94.3 Radio One. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brands made use of the festive season to build their image and not just focus on sales related communication. “We see many clients using this time to build their share of voice and market share to get an edge over competition,” said Hukmani. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A similar trend was seen on the digital medium as well, with brands taking the content marketing route to promote their brands. “This time there have been more long format videos and content marketing as opposed to traditional spends on Search, Facebook, etc.” said Bhargava. He added that this strategy works for the digital medium in particular because of targeted advertising. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Of the various media, digital has seen better performance and has become the go-to medium for brands this festive season. The dependence on the digital platform for advertising is surely increasing given the reach that the medium offers. “The reach on digital has become substantial. If you take something like Facebook alone, you can reach around 200 million people. An ad on the YouTube Homepage can reach around 120 million people. In comparison, a full-page ad in a leading newspaper will reach hardly 20 million people,” said Bhargava. Given the benefits the digital medium offers, digital advertising saw a flurry of activity from e-commerce brands, followed by smartphone manufacturers, automotive and BFSI. The growth of the digital advertising sector is higher than that of the overall advertising sector. Bhargava is confident that the digital advertising market as a whole will breach the Rs. 10,000 crore mark this year showing a growth of 40 per cent over last year.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1509936305_w5ixch_spotlight.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/spotlight-news/spotlightwe-are-in-the-third-wave-of-digital-disruptionnorm-johnston&#13;
-86936.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>30/10/2017</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Spotlight: We are in the third wave of digital disruption: Norm Johnston&#13;
</news:title>
      <news:description>Speaking at the recently held&amp;nbsp;17th edition of the exchange4media conclave, Norm Johnston, Global CEO Mindshare FAST &amp;amp; Global Chief Digital Officer at Mindshare, said, "We are in the third wave of digital disruption."&amp;nbsp;According to Johnston, the Internet of Things (IoT) will&amp;nbsp;have far reaching impact&amp;nbsp;on marketing and advertising with one major advantage being availability of data.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;"A challenge that we see with a lot of companies, particularly creative agencies, is that they tend to think TV first. There are simple things that you need to keep in mind when making ads and these challenges will be even more pronounced with the third wave of digital disruption," he said, while adding that a lot of creative agencies struggle to&amp;nbsp;create&amp;nbsp;deep, meaningful experiences.&lt;br&gt;He also touched upon the topic of brand safety, something that has been much discussed this year. Speaking about it, Johnston&amp;nbsp;noted that brand safety and ad fraud have always been around but due to increasing spends on digital, companies are now beginning to understand their importance. "You can never completely remove these issues but you can try your best to minimise them," he said. He also said that Google and Facebook need to be more transparent and stop thinking that they "can grade their homework."&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The changing role of media companies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;There is no question that new technologies like AI are changing the very nature of media buying. With automation increasing, there is the possibility that many roles that are now done manually would be redundant. Johnston believes that 'mundane' roles in the media buying process could be delegated to AI.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;"I think our role will now increasingly become implicit rather than explicit, which will be to convince the AI to recommend our clients to users. And this is extremely complicated but this is how increasingly, people will be buying and searching," he said.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AR + VR to be bigger than TV&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;According to Johnston, Augmented Reality (AR) would be the dominant technology in the future and would further enable the internet to reach out from devices into the real world. He predicted that the combined AR and VR (Virtual Reality) market would be bigger than TV by 2020. Further, the increasing penetration of AR would also help in humanising the internet.&lt;br&gt;He gave the example of how China utilised VR on Single's Day as an example of the kind of innovation that is possible with these technologies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The importance of metrics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;"I think, at least with social media, we have now come to an understanding of what the actual impact of a 'Like' is and it is not very impactful. Most people who like a brand are people who are going to buy the brand anyway. What is impactful is your friends&amp;nbsp;sharing things to you. We know that this has an influence on your buying decision. The question about metrics has been around forever. The thing with digital is that you can measure so much," said Johnston.&lt;br&gt;Comparing digital to TV, he pointed out that the metrics used on TV are quite basic and come&amp;nbsp;with several&amp;nbsp;flaws. On the digital front, he stated that the industry is improving in two respects. Firstly, in linking digital exposure to actual sales and, secondly, in media attribution.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Voice search, the next big thing?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;40 per cent of search&amp;nbsp;in the US is&amp;nbsp;done by voice, a statistic, which Johnston feels points to a&amp;nbsp;major trend on the internet, namely that&amp;nbsp;people are more comfortable talking to their phones.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two thirds of all search will be done by voice, he stated. "Of the 52 billion devices connected to the internet by 2020, only 5 per cent will have a keyboard. In most cases, you will be talking to Alexa, Google or Siri, which will have a huge impact on a lot of things. Firstly, the creative side, how do you create an experience for when a person is talking to the device and not typing. It will change how we optimise for search. There is a difference between&amp;nbsp;how people phrase words and&amp;nbsp;how they&amp;nbsp;type&amp;nbsp;or speak," he said.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Live sports,&amp;nbsp;the&amp;nbsp;game&amp;nbsp;changer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;The moment the big live sporting events move to an OTT player, it will be game&amp;nbsp;over for TV, predicted Johnston. He gave the example of how in the US, sales of antennae is&amp;nbsp;increasing. The reason behind it, he explains, is that most people are subscribing to OTT services but only want their TV to watch sports&amp;nbsp;events.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;In the next 10 years, the likes of Google or Amazon will bid for these rights and with their deep pockets they will be able to do it, he said.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1509331288_Jfbcf6_conclave17norm.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/spotlight-news/are-advertisers-bullish-with-festive-ad-spends-this-year-86568.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>03/10/2017</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Are advertisers bullish with festive ad spends this year?</news:title>
      <news:description>One month into the crucial festive season that sees nearly 30-40% of overall ad spends, industry insiders say that advertising spends are on the right track. According to early predictions, ad spends during the 2017 festive season were estimated to grow by 15-20% over last year. A total of Rs 24,000 cr is expected to be spent over the two-month period. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="http://e4mcms.exchange4media.com/files/1507000157_zGFi98_Spot-Light-Infographic-4.jpg"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Noting that the trend for ad spends is following early predictions, Ashish Bhasin, ‎Chairman &amp;amp; CEO South Asia, Dentsu Aegis Network, said, “October is likely going to be a good month. There will be a 15-20% increase in ad spends compared to last year because the base is lower due to the impact of demonetisation in the second half of the festive season last year.” &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;While many called the implementation of GST and demonetisation a double whammy for the advertising industry, ad spends have not been heavily impacted, said some experts. “Even though the industry had apprehensions post GST and demonetisation, we predict that ad spends will be in the range of 15-18% higher than the last festive season,” said Krishna Kumar Revanur, Branch Head – South, iProspect India. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;MK Anand, MD and CEO, Times Network, is also optimistic about the festive season, “If September is an indication, there is good growth in festive months. Over a subdued Q2, I think Q3 will have high growth. Between 35-50% is my estimate. But one must bear in mind that Q2 is a low base. And Q3 last year was demonetisation announcement.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CMO of a leading fashion apparel retailer said that the festive spirit among consumers is strong, reflecting in high ad spends from the retailer. “Ad spends from our end are in the double digit and maybe higher than 15% over last year’s spends,” he said. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Digital Growth Robust &lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Digital advertising will drive growth this year, experts felt. Industry consensus is that digital ad spends will make up for the lack of other spends by other mediums. The fierce competition between Amazon and India has already seen a huge ad blitz this festive season.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to reports, e-commerce giants Flipkart and Amazon have spent a cumulative Rs 100 cr on advertising for their respective annual sale events - Big Billion Days and Great Indian Festival. According to Red Seer Management Consulting, the gross GMV for the e-tailing industry during the five-day sale as a whole was expected to reach up to Rs 10,000 cr or USD 1.7 bn, up from USD 1.05 bn recorded in 2016 festive season. Kumar said that all trends point to a robust digital growth this festive season, be that in terms of traffic, revenue or sales. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AD Revenue&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Advertising revenue has been healthy during September. Sony Pictures Network (SPN) has witnessed satisfactory performance from all its channels which helped grow revenues substantially. Kaun Banega Crorepati saw a complete sell-out of its ad inventory, said Rohit Gupta, President – Network Sales &amp;amp; International business, SPN. “We got good response from sponsors. That helped us grow our revenues substantially during this festive season especially in September. This year has been good for us. We are growing substantially from April to September as a network and otherwise. We are continuing the trend of growing double than the market (way beyond double digit). September has been an excellent month on the back of all the big properties.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anand has seen significant growth in September compared to August, though it has not yet returned to normal for the network. He said, “I see this picking up further in the coming months as the impact of the major reform steps settles down. Diwali should hopefully further improve the situation.” &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At this mid-way point during the festive season, the sentiment seems positive in some corners of the industry. Bhasin said that the industry seems to be improving during the festive season, but that it was too early to call as the real test will be after Diwali. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Negative Sentiment&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some feel that the spending is not as high as expected. According to Pawan Jailkhani, Chief Revenue Officer, 9X Media, September saw some recovery compared to July-August but it’s around 7-8%. “Brands are taking strategies genre wise. They will campaign in selected genres. That’s killing the market. I am not seeing a major recovery, mostly single-digit growth.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On festive season spending he adds, “E-commerce has to spend because it’s a festive season and consumer spending goes up. Brands have to be present across mediums. But the problem is the spends aren’t much. There are some genres which show much better CPRPs and deliver more growth than the non-CPRP driven channels like English.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On that note he isn’t expecting more than 7-8% hike in festive spending over last year for the industry. “Overall economy is in a bad shape. Festive is not the indication of the health of the industry. We won’t be able to perform as per the projections.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPN has seen decent spending from the telecom and automobile categories. “Spending from handset, e-commerce and consumer goods is relatively low compared to last year,” said Gupta.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;He also observed that with the festive season being crunched to four weeks the spending is not as buoyant as it has been in the past. “This year, a lot of categories are not firing.”</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1507000157_zGFi98_Spot-Light-Infographic-4.jpg</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/spotlight-news/will-ipl-2018-ensure-steep-hike-in-team-revenues-86470.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>25/09/2017</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Will IPL 2018 ensure steep hike in team revenues?</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="text-align:justify"&gt;Ten seasons down the line, Indian&amp;nbsp;Premier League (IPL) has established itself as the most thrilling and popular&amp;nbsp;sporting league in the world, offering brands an opportunity to aggressively&amp;nbsp;market and advertise their products. It is also one of the most preferred&amp;nbsp;platforms to launch new products and strengthen the brand recall of existing&amp;nbsp;ones. IPL as a platform is raking in big moolah. This in turn is good news for&amp;nbsp;team owners who can benefit from the overall value of the sporting league.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify"&gt;If we look closely, IPL has a robust revenue&amp;nbsp;distribution model in place where the&amp;nbsp;BCCI&amp;nbsp;collects revenue from&amp;nbsp;distributors and shares it with the teams. Given the quantum jump in&amp;nbsp;broadcasting revenue this year, IPL teams are set to reap the benefits of this&amp;nbsp;surge. Just to add some perspective, this year, IPL title sponsor Vivo coughed&amp;nbsp;up Rs 2,200 crore for a five-year deal, while Star India paid a staggering Rs&amp;nbsp;16,347.5 crore to bag the media rights of the game making this league among the&amp;nbsp;most expensive sporting leagues in the world.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;img src="http://exchange4media.com/storyimages/86470_1.jpg" style="width:597px;height:543px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Impact on IPL team revenues&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify"&gt;Talking about the impact of IPL’s&amp;nbsp;overall revenue surge, it is a given that the teams are going to profit&amp;nbsp;immensely. IPL in its tenth year is already worth Rs 34,000 crore and has&amp;nbsp;posted a 26% increase in its overall business from Rs 27,000 crore last year.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify"&gt;It is well known that for all IPL&amp;nbsp;teams, sponsors are the real source of income. Teams have sponsors for&amp;nbsp;everything from main sponsor, jersey sponsor and even a sleeve sponsor. The&amp;nbsp;cumulative ad revenue for IPL from 2018-2022 is pegged at Rs 10,000 crore, which&amp;nbsp;is much higher than IPL’s revenue in 2017, which was Rs 1,300 crore. This&amp;nbsp;growth in ad revenue will be primarily driven by the new ad rates which are&amp;nbsp;expected to go up way further. Some media agency chiefs are even expecting a&amp;nbsp;10-second TV ad spot rate to climb to Rs 15-17 lakh from Rs 6 lakh in 2017.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;img src="http://exchange4media.com/storyimages/86470_2.jpg" style="width:443px;height:181px"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:justify"&gt;If we look at team revenues, Kings XI&amp;nbsp;Punjab earned Rs 26.5 crore from sponsorship revenues in 2016, which according&amp;nbsp;to reports went up to Rs 30 crore in 2017, and is expected to go much higher in&amp;nbsp;next season. While Mumbai Indians earned Rs 70 crore in sponsorship last year,&amp;nbsp;it aimed at a 10-12% increase in sponsorship revenues in 2017 and with IPL now&amp;nbsp;becoming cash rich than ever before, the expectation can be as high as 30% next&amp;nbsp;year.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify"&gt;It is&amp;nbsp;important to state that in 2014-15, KKR posted 30% growth in revenues and 54% when&amp;nbsp;the overall worth of the league was way below its current estimates.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Revenue growth of 25-30%&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify"&gt;GMR-owned Delhi Daredevils is already&amp;nbsp;aiming at a 20% increase in sponsorship revenues. According to industry&amp;nbsp;estimates, in case of teams such as Delhi Daredevils and Kings XI Punjab, thecost of sponsoring the jersey front ranges between Rs 10 crore and Rs 12 crore,&amp;nbsp;while price of advertising at the back is Rs 5-6 crore. While the cost of&amp;nbsp;sponsoring the fronts of jerseys for teams such as KKR and Mumbai Indians&amp;nbsp;ranges between Rs 8 crore and Rs 22 crore; backs of jerseys are priced at&amp;nbsp;around Rs 10-12 crore. This is expected to go higher by at least 20-25% as IPL&amp;nbsp;enters a new phase of growth with Star India having bagged its distribution&amp;nbsp;rights.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify"&gt;Speaking about how IPL teams will&amp;nbsp;benefit from the spike in IPL revenue, Saurabh Uboweja, CEO and Chief Brand&amp;nbsp;Strategist, Brands of Desire says, “Two of the leading sources of income for&amp;nbsp;IPL teams are BCCI's contribution from the sale of media rights and sponsorship&amp;nbsp;rights..&amp;nbsp;The recent sale of both these rights combined for BCCI means&amp;nbsp;an additional income of not less than Rs 3,600 crore every year. BCCI is likely&amp;nbsp;to share at least 30% of that every year with IPL teams. IPL teams can expect&amp;nbsp;to at least double their revenues from the coming season onwards, which means&amp;nbsp;all teams will be profitable in a single shot.”&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-align:justify"&gt;On an&amp;nbsp;average, team sponsorship revenues are between Rs 30-40 crore and ticket sales&amp;nbsp;account for around Rs 25-35 crore. Central pool revenues are in the Rs 75-90&amp;nbsp;crore range for franchises.&amp;nbsp;According to some estimates, franchises are&amp;nbsp;expected to clock 20-25% increase in overall revenue from 2018 onwards. However,&amp;nbsp;all these predictions also depend on the upcoming BCCI-IPL meet which is taking&amp;nbsp;place in a week’s time, and if there are no new conditions announced, the teams&amp;nbsp;will definitely have lot more to expect from IPL 2018.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1506313395_eVvycv_86470.gif</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/spotlight-news/healthy-onam-ad-spends-spell-hope-for-navratri-and-diwali-70566.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>18/09/2017</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Healthy Onam ad spends spell hope for Navratri and Diwali</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;p style="text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  Onam celebrations in Kerala have set the tone for the upcoming festive season in India. The advertising industry in God's Own Country has weathered the impact of the much talked about Goods and Services Tax (GST). Industry insiders say that they have noticed an overall increase in ad spends this year. At the national level, ad spends are expected to increase by 15–20%. At the regional level, the Kerala advertising industry has noticed an increase of 10%.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  The usual suspects—smartphones, electronic goods, automotive and textiles categories witnessed high sales. These sectors also spent a significant fraction of their annual ad budgets on the Onam season.&amp;nbsp;“Samsung, Sony and automobile players like Hero, Hyundai, Hero and Maruti were big this time. Oppo and Vivo from the telecom sector invested a lot in advertising,” said Kamal Krishnan, National Head – Media Solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  “It was a fairly good Onam,” said Varghese Chandy, Sr VP Marketing, Malayala Manorama. However, he added, “To make a comparison we have to compare the July to September quarter as Onam falls on different days.”&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  Smartphone brands like Oppo and Vivo and jewellers like Bhima Jewellers were some of the companies that spent the most this season. “About 50–60% of ad revenues were from the FMCG, automobile, textile, jewellery and telecom industries. There was a 25–30% growth in ad revenues compared to last year. Jewellery sector did spend adequately but the other sectors were much louder this time,” said Kamal Krishnan PS, National Head – Brand Solutions (Print).&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &lt;img src="http://www.exchange4media.com/storyimages/70566_1.jpg" style="max-width:100%;height:auto;vertical-align:middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &lt;strong&gt;Ad spends by medium&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  Advertising on television saw a growth of about 30–40%. The total ad spends on TV was around Rs 130–150 cr during the Onam window with about 60–65% of this spend coming from national brands.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  Unnikrishnan, VP Sales, Asianet News said, “As far as news is concerned, electronic brands like LG, dealers like Gopu Nandilath, Pittapally, etc. spent good money. And Onam for us was good, rather better than last year.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  Advertising in print was dominated by local brands. About 60% of the overall advertising was from the local brands of Kerala. “Local players had a larger play during Onam this year in comparison to previous years. For example, print impact jackets were taken mostly by local brands,” said Sanchayeeta Verma, Managing Partner, Maxus South India &amp;amp; South Asia.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  All in all, it was a happy Onam for the advertising industry in Kerala. Raju Menon, Director-Operations, Maitri Advertising said, “I have not seen anyone complaining about sales. Overall, this year people who came to shops have actually purchased and gone. Last year, there were more inquiries and fewer sales. People of Kerala had a very good Onam this year as there was no scarcity of food items, vegetables were plenty and the government was able to control the open market prices.”&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  While many shared a highly positive response to Onam this year, some said that the festival this year was just above average. Gopalakrishnan Nair, Sr VP &amp;amp; Principal Partner, DDB Mudra Group, said, “There was a mixed response. Retail business has done well. The ad spends were slightly lesser as Onam was about 10 days earlier compared to last year and due to GST and demonetisation. Onam was not all that good this time; it was just above average.”&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  The fact that the jewellery sector did not spend much this came as a shock to many. Bhima, a brand from this sector, was active during Onam while the rest were silent. Gayatri Suhas, Managing Director of Bhima Jewellers, said, “Sales were the usual this time of the year. Buying jewellery is a tradition in Indian society and this cannot be broken.”&lt;/p&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1505979059_PADZmP_big_70566.gif</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/spotlight-news/spotlighthow-well-can-branded-content-solve-strategic-business-problems-70462.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>11/09/2017</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Spotlight: How well can Branded Content solve strategic business problems?</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  Even with technology taking huge leaps with each passing day, here is something even the best of ad-blockers still cannot block - branded content. There is no ‘Skip Ad’ option and consumers are voluntarily watching the content with very little or no push from the marketers themselves. This is especially true if the content is in digital video format. The numbers speak for themselves: the digital video market is expected to be worth $1.6 billion by 2022 (Media Partners Asia) the size of the digital advertising market in India is Rs 76.9 billion, the digital sector is growing at a rate of 28%, and the total number of internet users in India has surpassed 400 million in 2017, more than half of these are on Facebook (KPMG India FICCI Indian Media and Entertainment Industry Report 2017).&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &lt;strong&gt;Digital advertising (Industry Size in INR Billion)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &lt;img src="http://www.exchange4media.com/storyimages/70462_1.jpg" style="vertical-align:middle;margin-left:5px;margin-right:5px;border:1px solid #000"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &lt;strong&gt;Media Sector Growth in 2016 over 2015&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &lt;img src="http://www.exchange4media.com/storyimages/70462_2.jpg" style="vertical-align:middle;margin-left:5px;margin-right:5px;border:1px solid #000"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &lt;strong&gt;Internet Users in India (in millions)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &lt;img src="http://www.exchange4media.com/storyimages/70462_3.jpg" style="vertical-align:middle;margin-left:5px;margin-right:5px;border:1px solid #000"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  Undoubtedly, snackable content has many takers and can successfully engage with viewers, but the question the industry is trying to answer is whether branded content is well-poised to solve strategic business problems.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  The ‘viral fever’ that brands were suffering from seems to be finally dying down. Brands are now looking at branded content with objectives that go beyond the mandate of merely going viral on the internet. Marketers now look at branded content as a means to an end. “Branded content is not brand new in India anymore; we have all experimented with this medium. I am now looking for people who can demonstrate how they will get their content across but organically also show me how their content is helping in the achievement of my business goals,” said the CMO of a leading telecom company, who did not wish to be named. “In fact, a marketer does not want to do content, and is rather looking for a solution to a business problem,” observed Devendra Deshpande, Head Content Plus, Mindshare India.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  Finding business solutions is what will take branded content to the next level, some feel. “I don’t know what branded content is solving,” said Anil S Nair, CEO and Managing Partner, Law and Kenneth Saatchi &amp;amp; Saatchi. According to him branded content also needs to be held to the same scrutiny that traditional advertising agencies are subjected to. “We as a team will be judged by what impact we have made for the client’s business. Currently branded content agencies don’t have that pressure. The moment there is a performance link people will get far more responsible,” he noted.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  Content creators say branded content can address a variety of objectives: for smaller brands it could be about building brand awareness, larger brands may look for brand positioning, internet brands may look to drive up user traffic. “But brands should not look at quantitative metrics alone, they should look at qualitative metrics,” said Ashwin Suresh, Founder, Pocket Aces. Noting that branded content has helped brands increase user traffic and in one case even drove up bookings on a hospitality website, he said, “Content marketing can solve a lot of objectives, but what it cannot solve is direct sales.” That he says is up to the brand. “There are few instances where we can drive sales, but largely we can get people to the website and then it is up to the brand to convert them,” he says.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  The objectives of increasing mind share and creating awareness are best achieved through branded content. Pravin Shah, Founder &amp;amp; CEO, Six Inches Communications, agrees with Suresh. “Some brands ask us about the ROI of branded content and our response is: you cannot expect ROI-lead generation from an awareness campaign.” Branded content is purely about creating awareness; the brand is not selling, but participating with the consumer, Shah said. And that is why a young brand like Brand Factory is leveraging both branded content alongside traditional advertising to achieve different brand objectives. “My marketing mix is skewed towards television advertising currently because the objective of the TVC is to drive business,” says Roch D'Souza, CMO, Brand Factory. He adds that the digital/branded content journey of Brand Factory is focussed on the brand objective rather than driving sales.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  The difference in results is deeply rooted also in the approach of a branded content creator versus that of a traditional agency or ad production house. In the words of Mandheer Singh, CMO, BigBazaar, an agency understands the brand and what it represents whereas a content creator offers an interpretation of a brand.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  Noting that the craft of storytelling is the same across TVCs and branded video content, Sachin Dingankar, Head of Marketing at Zydus Wellness, said, “Some are able to bridge the divide of being able to deliver a 30 seconder and deliver long form content or a movie even. Yet communication agencies are taking time to understand how the medium has changed. And that’s where I think agencies have some distance to cover,” he said.&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  That said, it is not hard to find the sweet spot that will deliver results and drive up engagement. “Consumer research and insighting lends itself to a direction. And once I have that strategic direction, we get the right content partner for that campaign,” said Deshpande. As an agency, Mindshare collaborates with multiple content creators, picking and choosing the most appropriate creators and mediums for the task at hand. According to KV Sridhar (aka Pops), founder, hypercollective, “If you understand the brand and the audience, you can create any content.” He said that once you have a well-defined brand story you can collaborate with content creators to develop content that fits well with the brand and stays true to the brand positioning across mediums.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &lt;strong&gt;Twitter Users in India (in millions)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &lt;img src="http://www.exchange4media.com/storyimages/70462_4.jpg" style="vertical-align:middle;margin-left:5px;margin-right:5px;border:1px solid #000"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &lt;strong&gt;Facebook Top Countries&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &lt;img src="http://www.exchange4media.com/storyimages/70462_5.jpg" style="vertical-align:middle;margin-left:5px;margin-right:5px;border:1px solid #000"&gt;</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1505285091_bulvDr_70462.gif</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/spotlight-news/and-the-ipl-media-rights-go-to-70370.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>04/09/2017</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>And the IPL media rights go to…</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  With two dozen companies bidding for the broadcast and digital rights of the next five years of the Indian Premier League (IPL), the market is abuzz with speculations. According to our estimates, the rights could fetch cricket body Board of Control for Cricket in India (BCCI) around Rs 15,000 crore looking at IPL’s brand value. There are also talks about an international digital firm wanting to form a consortium with an Indian television channel but the concerned parties have refused to comment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  In its tenth year, the property is worth Rs 34,000 crore ($5.3 billion) and has posted a 26 per cent increase in its overall business from Rs 27,000 crore ($4.2 billion) last year. The league has seen a three-year CAGR (compound annual growth rate) of 13.9 per cent according to Duff &amp;amp; Phelps, a global valuation and corporate finance advisory.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  The same advisory estimated that the TV rights could fetch the BCCI close $1.8 billion (Rs 11,540 crore) for five years.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &lt;strong&gt;The bidding story&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  Besides broadcaster majors Star India, Sony Pictures Network and Discovery Communications, new entrants in the digital category include Reliance Jio Digital, Amazon Seller Service, Yupp TV, Airtel, Twitter, ESPN Digital Media, Times Internet, Facebook, Yahoo, BAMTech and DAZN/Perform group, among others. A relatively new entrant in sports broadcasting space, Discovery Communications’ DSPORT is rumoured to be bullish about its bidding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &lt;img src="http://www.exchange4media.com/storyimages/70370_1.jpg" style="max-width:100%;height:auto;vertical-align:centre;border:1px solid #000"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  BCCI has made few key changes in the process. IPL media rights are divided into three categories: television rights for the Indian subcontinent, digital rights and five international media rights (in Middle East, Africa, Europe, the US and rest of the world).&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &lt;img src="http://www.exchange4media.com/storyimages/70370_2.jpg" style="max-width:100%;height:auto;vertical-align:centre;border:1px solid #000"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  BCCI from its last deal with Sony reportedly fetched Rs 6,700 crore across the ten-year period. It has to be noted that in 2008, the Singapore-based World Sports Group bagged the IPL television rights for a ten-year period with a $918 million bid. It simultaneously signed a deal with Multi Screen Media Pvt. Ltd. (MSM) that Sony would be the official broadcaster.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  Sony Pictures Network earned reasonably well over the decade starting from Rs 300 crore in the first season to Rs 1300 crore in the tenth season.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  When it comes to digital rights, most of the above mentioned players will make an aggressive bid for it. According to Duff &amp;amp; Phelps, the internet and mobile rights could land in the region of $210 million (approximate Rs 1344 crore). In February 2015, Star India had got the internet and mobile rights for three years for Rs 302.2 crore. In 2015, its OTT platform Hotstar netted advertising revenue of around Rs 50 crore, followed by Rs 65 crore in 2016 and Rs 150 crore in 2017, according to media reports.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  This year, Hotstar had signed up five marquee sponsors: Vivo, Maruti Suzuki, Reliance Jio, Dream 11, and AMFI. The sponsorship deals with Vivo and Maruti Suzuki are reported to be of Rs 20 crore each.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &lt;img src="http://www.exchange4media.com/storyimages/70370_3.jpg" style="max-width:100%;height:auto;vertical-align:centre;border:1px solid #000"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &lt;strong&gt;Bringing IPL to this stature&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  Vinit Karnik, Business Head - Entertainment, Sports &amp;amp; Live Events at GroupM, points out that IPL’s fixed timing has worked to its favour and kept the brand relevant. He says, “For the first time in the country you have a sporting league with a fixed calendar which makes the life of a marketer easy as he can plan launches, communication and campaigns around IPL.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  Then comes its positioning as an entertainment segment with a dosage of cricket through its campaigns like ‘Manoranjan ka Baap’, ‘Jumping Japang’ to ‘10 Saal Aapke Naam’ &amp;nbsp;according to Neeraj Vyas, Senior EVP &amp;amp; Business Head – Hindi Movies and Music Cluster at SONY SAB, SPN. &amp;nbsp;He says, “From an advertiser’s perspective, brands want to be around IPL because it cuts across all geographies and builds a reach faster than anything else. That is its biggest advantage.” The same entertainment quotient brought in women audience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &lt;img src="http://www.exchange4media.com/storyimages/70370_4.jpg" style="max-width:100%;height:auto;vertical-align:centre;border:1px solid #000"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  A mention has to be made of its cumulative reach which grew from 102 million in season 1 to 411 million in season 10, according to SPN. This has to be attributed to the distribution of Hindi movie channel Sony MAX. Vyas points out, “Sixty-nine per cent of the numbers has come from Max this year.”&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  Despite the property hit by so many controversies from the betting fiasco that led to the ban of Chennai Super Kings and Rajasthan Royals for two seasons to the rigging bidding deals by Lalit Modi, IPL’s brand image hasn’t been tainted. N Chandramouli, CEO of TRA, explains, “The audience didn’t change. They felt the game is safe, as the owners have cheated.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;p style="text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &lt;strong&gt;Brand power&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  So, it’s no surprise that all the above factors have made IPL the favourite for brands to leverage at a premium cost in the tenth season. Amazon India, Vodafone, Pepsi, Maruti Suzuki and Parle rolled out their campaigns especially for the league. Rohit Gupta, President – Network Sales &amp;amp; International business, SPN, shares that around 35–40 brands across categories come in every year and that the 10 years have seen major launches with the best creatives. “Brands are spending Rs 40–50 crore over two months. There is pressure on creative agencies to bring out the best. An ecosystem has developed around IPL.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  Siddharth Banerjee, EVP-Marketing, Vodafone India, points out that the league has provided a platform to innovate. Vodafone India happens to be the only Indian brand to associate with the property since its inception. The brand reserves one third of their marketing budget for IPL. It has successfully reaped the fruit of its 10-year labour, given the ‘multiplicity of communications it offers’. He shares, “The 10-year-long association with IPL has created a winning formula for Vodafone and given us a positive ROI. We have always aligned our communication goals around IPL with our key business objectives.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  YES Bank which has associated with the IPL in the past reportedly saw a media value of Rs 58.12 crore delivered for the bank, courtesy the first 20 matches of the 2017 season. Rajat Mehta, Senior President, Marketing and Corporate Communication, YES Bank shares, “YES Bank has further leveraged IPL content rights to attain global leadership within the BFSI segment not only in India but across the world. This year, we used our video and digital rights to achieve 235 million impressions by reaching over 30 million fans; our video views were at a staggering 52 million.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  New categories were born out of IPL, including the Indian handset category with the likes of Karbonn and Micromax. There was even participation from digital wallets like PayTM and Freecharge. Gupta shares, “Three to four years back, there was ecommerce category. Amazon was the first one to come into IPL.” Last year, the handset category contributed to 20 per cent of IPL’s advertising revenues, the highest among all categories.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  Will Yang, Brand Director, Oppo India, had shared earlier that IPL has helped it generate increased brand awareness, putting it ahead in ‘top of the mind recall’ brands. “Our association and investment during the IPL period has helped us in connecting with not just current customers but potential consumers as well,” he said. The Chinese handset firm was IPL’s presenting sponsor last year.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  IPL’s infectious brand energy and success pulled in FMCG majors like Hindustan Unilever, Godrej and Reckitt Benckiser and invariably Chinese mobile handset players like Vivo, OPPO, Gionee and Lenovo-owned Motorola.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  Looking at the above historical viewership data, advertising revenue and active participation by brands over the course of 10 years, the league is only set to grow at least for the next five years, according to Karnik, who believes the ‘property has proved its merit over the last 10 years.’</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1504704050_2jgHSh_70370.gif</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>https://www.exchange4media.com/spotlight-news/magazine-journalismexistential-threat-or-re-imagined-future-70276.html</loc>
    <news:news>
      <news:genres>PressRelease</news:genres>
      <news:publication_date>28/08/2017</news:publication_date>
      <news:title>Magazine journalism: Existential threat or re-imagined future?</news:title>
      <news:description>&lt;br&gt;Traditional journalism has never been beset with an existential threat that it faces now. Thanks to the growing popularity of online media, news is increasingly getting generated by the minute and consumed within a similar span. In such a situation traditional media outlets, especially print publications, have come under great stress.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;The speed of news generation and news consumption that digital media facilitates makes newspapers and magazines at best a repository of second-hand information. Many feel that print journalism, especially magazine journalism, is becoming increasingly tough to practice and some have even started writing obituary pieces about this format of journalism.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &lt;img src="http://www.exchange4media.com/storyimages/70276_1.jpg" style="float:left;margin-left:5px;margin-right:5px;border:1px solid #000"&gt; Such is the gravity of this existential threat to magazine journalism that recently Union Minister for Finance, Defence Corporate Affairs went on record to describe it in these words, “Magazine journalism in India is today probably the most difficult one. Thanks to technology, the definition of news has itself changed. News these days is whatever the camera is ready to capture or alternatively what digital media is able to get attracted to. Print journalism both in terms of technology and timing faces that radical challenge. Even for daily newspapers, one really cannot read in the newspapers what one has seen several times over on TV the previous evening or read it on the smartphones.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &lt;strong&gt;What do the numbers say?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;According to Pitch Madison Report 2017, print grew at 7% in 2016, with dailies registering a growth of 8% while magazines saw negative growth. Demonetization resulted in leading print advertisers holding back on spends in the last quarter. In 2017, the print advertising market is expected to grow by 9.5% to come close to Rs 20,000 crore, with dailies and regional publications leading the growth.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &lt;img src="http://www.exchange4media.com/storyimages/70276_2.jpg" style="vertical-align:middle;margin-left:5px;margin-right:5px;border:1px solid #000"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;The report further states that in terms of category contribution, FMCG is the largest contributor to the print pie, with a contribution of 15%. Automobiles are the second largest contributor at 14%, followed by Education (10%). Contribution of E-commerce comes way down with just 3%. The E-commerce category has dropped significantly by 15% to come down to Rs 621 crore in 2016. In terms of Volume, Hindi publications continue to be ahead of English publications contributing 35% of the total volume while the latter contribute only 26%. But in terms of growth of volume, English publications have grown by 8% while Hindi publications grew by only 3%. Kannada, Bengali and Punjabi publications show substantial increase in volume, while Gujarati and Tamil publications show a decline of 6%.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &lt;img src="http://www.exchange4media.com/storyimages/70276_3.jpg" style="vertical-align:middle;margin-left:5px;margin-right:5px;border:1px solid #000"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &lt;strong&gt;Re-imagining magazine journalism&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;Despite the negative growth registered by magazines, industry players are hopeful that the format will get redefined and re-imagined and witness another golden era in the time to come. According to Raj Chengappa, Group Editorial Director (Publishing), India Today Group and President, Editors Guild of India, “The biggest challenge is how the technology has made news available anywhere and anytime. The most popular platform is emerging to be the smartphone. However, it has its own limitations. If you look at most of the news items on the net, it follows the cookie cutter approach as one item looks like the other. There is no discrimination between news items. While print is all about display, size of the headlines, the picture that we use and even the graphics. Also, there is too much of news and the scope of having credible news has diminished and people are getting confused by all this. What people are looking for is relevant and credible news.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &lt;img src="http://www.exchange4media.com/storyimages/70276_4.jpg" style="float:left;margin-left:5px;margin-right:5px;border:1px solid #000"&gt; Stating that magazine journalism is all about curated content and distilled information, Chengappa further adds, “What magazines do is to take complex information, distill it and bring clarity. So, the clarity which print magazines can bring out has better writing, better display, better visuals and it is an art by itself. &amp;nbsp;While there is huge explosion of news, most people are seeking clarity about what they read and want curated news. So what you are seeing now is the revival in the interest of magazines as they are great storytellers. The role of magazines now is growing again. People are coming back to understanding good writing. In fact, the India Today magazine has been re-imagined with that approach.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &lt;strong&gt;Double whammy of demonetization &amp;amp; GST&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;The bigger challenge which the entire media industry, especially the print industry, is facing for the last 8–10 months is mostly linked to the external economic environment. The double whammy of demonetization and GST has adversely affected ad spends and print is more affected than TV or digital.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &lt;img src="http://www.exchange4media.com/storyimages/70276_5.jpg" style="float:left;margin-left:5px;margin-right:5px;border:1px solid #000"&gt; Speaking about the challenges for magazine publishers, Anant Nath, Editor, Caravan and Executive Director, Delhi Press stated, “Magazines that are highly dependent on consumer product advertising have been more adversely hit. For magazines, the other big challenge is that of distribution. In my opinion, to say people are reading online and therefore print is declining is only part of the problem; it is like looking at the issue from a purely myopic perspective.”&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;Nath believes that readers are willing to buy print publications if they are available at a convenience to them. “If a print product is readily available at their doorstep or at a point of purchase which is accessible and convenient, then readers are more than willing to buy. The problem with magazines is that we as an industry have not been able to somehow ensure as effective distribution as we should have. Therefore, we are still counting on the reader to make some efforts to buy a magazine while there needs to be active involvement from the publishers’ end.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &lt;strong&gt;The way forward&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;While it may be challenging for magazine publishers to woo readers in this digitally connected world, the good news is that the reader is still passionately consuming print content in the form of magazines. Some media veterans argue that magazine journalism has the advantage of connecting deeply with the consumers which TV and digital lack. However, they also suggest that in order to keep the readership intact, the distribution approach needs to be reworked to make print publications, especially magazines, conveniently available for readers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &lt;img src="http://www.exchange4media.com/storyimages/70276_6.jpg" style="float:left;margin-left:5px;margin-right:5px;border:1px solid #000"&gt; “I think magazine journalism has the advantage of engaging the reader in an in-depth way. This is not the case with TV and digital and this in itself is a big plus that the magazine publishers can leverage. However, what is critical is how you ultimately present those stories to the readers and how you adjust to the demands of new marketing,” stated Alok Mehta, veteran journalist and former Editor-in-Chief, Outlook Hindi .&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
  &lt;img src="http://www.exchange4media.com/storyimages/70276_7.jpg" style="float:left;margin-left:5px;margin-right:5px;border:1px solid #000"&gt; According to Maneck Davar, Chairman and Managing Director, Spenta Multimedia, India's largest custom magazine publisher, consumer magazines are going through a lot of stress. Davar believes that the overall dip in advertising revenues and readership numbers is causing such a situation. “There are a number of reasons for this situation and mainly because the younger generation is not reading magazines as they prefer digital content. &amp;nbsp;Also, globally most magazines have online subscription while in India it’s very difficult to follow that model. On the positive side, the loyalty that print publications enjoy is way better than digital media and that can become its biggest advantage.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;There is no denying that the ease of access has made digital news more popular. It is convenient to consumer news on mobile or laptop. &amp;nbsp;But will the long format and analytical journalism of magazines be taken over by this populist platform?&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;br&gt;While explaining the innate difference between digital and print, Nath says that magazine journalism has its distinct flavour which cannot be replaced by any other platform. He also believes that the various formats of media will eventually co-exist without any existential threat. “In most cases, online reading is more geared towards news and current affairs and breaking news. The articles that we publish in our magazines are far more in-depth and for engaged reading. For people who want to read such articles, mobile is not the ideal format. Also, online as a medium has too many distractions and it does not offer a much focused reading experience. Moreover, India with its sheer population numbers offers good scope for growth and sustainability of print. So, print will always have an important space. It will co-exist with the online space and all the media will finally find equilibrium,” stated Nath.</news:description>
      <news:keywords>advertising news, marketing, ooh, television, digital, print, radio, media</news:keywords>
      <news:publication>
        <news:name>Exchange4Media</news:name>
        <news:language>en</news:language>
      </news:publication>
    </news:news>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://storage.googleapis.com/news-photo/1505469981_Mgrtp0_big_70276.gif</image:loc>
    </image:image>
  </url>
</urlset>
