<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>www.exchange4media.com (Fullstory)</title>
    <description>News Marketing India advertising Indian brands tv media newspapers</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright @ 2008 Exchange4media Media Private Limited. All rights reserved</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://www.exchange4media.com/cms/CMS_UploadFile/fullstory/91483.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <item>
      <title>Turkish Airlines, Warner Bros. and The LEGO® Movie franchise launch in-flight safety video</title>
      <author>exchange4media News Service</author>
      <pubDate>06/08/2018</pubDate>
      <description>Turkish Airlines has launched a new animated safety video, complete with familiar LEGO® mini-figures in surprising new roles. The custom-animated safety video for Turkish Airlines was created by the teams who assembled “The LEGO Movie”, “The LEGO Batman Movie”, “The LEGO NINJAGO® Movie” and the highly anticipated sequel “The LEGO Movie 2” due in cinemas beginning February 2019, which reunites the heroes of the first film in an all new action-packed adventure. In partnership with Warner Bros. and featuring the popular characters from The LEGO Movie franchise, the safety video will be shown on all flights starting today and will also debut online.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The safety video, which is the first LEGO safety video ever made, demonstrates step-by-step safety procedures to passengers in a fun, unique style – complete with sensible airline-approved humor, celebrity cameos and an unforgettable song and dance number. Turkish Airlines is proud to have one of the youngest fleets in the world and strives to achieve the best in aviation safety standards. Whether frequent travellers or first-time fliers, the video aims to inform and entertain passengers, alongside an extensive selection of movies, TV shows, music and games available in different languages on the in-flight entertainment system. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The safety video will kick off the “biggest partnership with the smallest cast ever assembled”, hinting there is much more to come from the Turkish Airlines and LEGO Movie franchise alliance. Leading up to the worldwide release of “The LEGO Movie 2”, Turkish Airlines will roll-out a global TV campaign, film themed wrapped airplanes, in-flight and in-airport activations and even a second safety video. A partnership sure to entertain and delight!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;M. İlker Aycı, Turkish Airlines Chairman of the Board and the Executive Committee commented; “As a leading global airline with an emphasis on safety, we are excited to partner with Warner Bros. and The LEGO Movie franchise for this video. We are both brands that are enjoyed around the world, bringing together generations and cultures everywhere. We hope that our passengers can enjoy this new video, which has something for everyone.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Blair Rich, President, Worldwide Marketing, Warner Bros. Pictures Group and Warner Bros. Home Entertainment said; “We are thrilled to be working with Turkish Airlines again and “widening their world” to include that of our colorful LEGO Movie universe. The partnership showcases the best of two different brands converging in a clever and imaginative way, connecting to consumers and entertaining them.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The LEGO Movie franchise-inspired safety video was brought to life by a 16-strong production team consisting of 2 concept artists, 3 layout artists, 7 animators and 4 lighting technicians. Lasting more than 950 days from beginning to end, the specialists used 2,938,840 LEGO bricks to animate the LEGO action. A total of 9,658,631 CPU hours (Central Processing Units) were used to generate 973 versions of animation. 30 different versions of the new safety video were created, both in English and Turkish, to cover the safety particulars of the 15 different airplane models in the Turkish Airlines fleet.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;See the video here:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/C2hCN6cVuqM" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;</description>
      <storyimages>https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/article/article_large_image/1533564223_1YsiFR_lego_turkish.jpg</storyimages>
      <guid>91483</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
