<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>www.exchange4media.com (Fullstory)</title>
    <description>News Marketing India advertising Indian brands tv media newspapers</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright @ 2008 Exchange4media Media Private Limited. All rights reserved</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://www.exchange4media.com/cms/CMS_UploadFile/fullstory/91806.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <item>
      <title>Experts from Balaji Telefilms, Cipla Health &amp; ICICI Bank to speak at Content JAM</title>
      <author>exchange4media News Service</author>
      <pubDate>29/08/2018</pubDate>
      <description>Content marketing is about helping clients and brands create a memorable, meaningful story that resonates with their audience. The Indian Content Marketing Awards (ICMA 2018) by Audacity recognises and encourages the best content marketing efforts of the year with a stunning showcase of talent, expertise, inspiration and insight for brand marketers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The third edition of the Audacity e4m Indian Content Marketing Awards 2018 (ICMA) and second edition of Content JAM, a content marketing conference, is set to take place on September 7.&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/1535510619_CwzGDq_Content-jam-logo-lokmat-Revised-01-%281%29.jpg" style="width:300px;height:192px;float:right"&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the e4m Content JAM conference, leading global and Indian experts of content marketing will discuss on the theme ‘Content First: Storytelling in the Digital Age'. As technology levels the playing field for the marketing haves and have-nots, content is the only game changer for a company in achieving its marketing and business objectives. In a world, where digital is breaking silos, content is mission critical for organisations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sunil Lulla, Group CEO, Balaji Telefilms Ltd will be seen in a Fireside Chat at Content Jam. His topic of discussion is ‘Primetime vs. My Time’. For a long time now, content creators have been preparing for content-on-the-go and for an audience that wants it now. How have newer forms of technology changed this conversation?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lulla thrives on driving brands and businesses to market-place leadership. With over 35 years of experience in building JWT, GREY, MTV, SONY, TIMES, Indya, Diageo, Lulla is now the Group Chief Executive Officer of Balaji Telefilms Ltd. An active votary for the media industry’s growth, Lulla is an active voice in industry forums. He is equally passionate about running as he is about chasing dreams.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joining him at the next speaker session will be Anantha Nayak, CEO, Cipla Health Ltd. Nayak has over two decades of experience in the FMCG sector, across diverse functions, geographies and consumer segments. An alumnus of IIM Calcutta &amp;amp; UDCT Mumbai, he started his career in P&amp;amp;G and has worked mainly in the beauty care category. Most of his career, he was based in Singapore, apart from having stayed in Thailand for couple of years.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nayak has diverse experience in launching new brands, turning around businesses and managing wide portfolio of countries and brands. He led the launch of Olay and Whisper Choice sanitary napkins in India.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In late 2013, he relocated from Singapore to India along with his family, to start up a consumer healthcare business for Cipla.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;He is a Chemical Engineer and has an MBA from IIM, Calcutta. He is an amateur athlete and has run several marathons in different countries. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Industry expert Sujit Ganguli, Chief Marketing Officer, ICICI Bank, will also be speaking at this year’s Content JAM. At ICICI Bank, he is responsible for the company's marketing, public relations, Internet business and service quality. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Under Ganguli’s leadership, the insurance player has come out with various campaigns on tax planning, rural awareness and child insurance plans, retirement solutions, popular communications such as the 'Jeete Raho' campaign and the 'Retirement - The world's best job' campaign.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ganguli, a physics graduate from Fergusson College, Pune and an IIM Bangalore alumnus, began his career with Hindustan Lever as area sales manager and later became, senior product manager for Deluxe Green Label Coffee and Lipton Taaza Tea. He was also a part of the core team at Reliance Infocomm which launched Reliance India Mobile.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can find more details about Content JAM here –&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://e4mevents.com/content-marketing-awards-icma-2018/"&gt;https://e4mevents.com/content-marketing-awards-icma-2018/&lt;/a&gt;</description>
      <storyimages>https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/article/article_large_image/1535511459_yefS8U_ICMA_2018_Speakers.jpg</storyimages>
      <guid>91806</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
