<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>www.exchange4media.com (Fullstory)</title>
    <description>News Marketing India advertising Indian brands tv media newspapers</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright @ 2008 Exchange4media Media Private Limited. All rights reserved</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://www.exchange4media.com/cms/CMS_UploadFile/fullstory/91835.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <item>
      <title>Interbrand appoints Pitchfork Partners as its communication partner</title>
      <author>exchange4media News Service</author>
      <pubDate>30/08/2018</pubDate>
      <description>Brand consultancy Interbrand has appointed Pitchfork Partners as its strategic communication consultant. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The decision has been taken with an intent to strengthen Interbrand’s reputation as a highly sought-after employer and a strong partner to brands, the company said in a statement. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gonzalo Brujo, Interbrand’s Global Growth Officer and part of the network’s global leadership team, congratulated the India team and said, “Interbrand India is our youngest but the fastest growing office. Their growth in the five-year period has been exemplary and we are delighted that the world’s leading brand consultancy is now India’s leading too!”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ashish Mishra, Managing Director, Interbrand India, said, “Pitchfork Partners shares our beliefs and values. We are delighted to partner with it. We started our journey in India half a decade ago and have already built relationships with a third of India’s 40 most valuable brands. What’s truly satisfying is that we have been chosen as partners for majority of the country’s leading branding assignments of the decade. We see a huge opportunity for sustained growth and Pitchfork has the credentials to help us.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jaideep Shergill, Co-Founder, Pitchfork Partners, said: “We are excited to partner with Interbrand. The company has a wide body of work in India and we are committed to helping it achieve its business goals through strategic and insights-driven communication.”</description>
      <storyimages>https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/article/article_large_image/1535609603_HAhOB1_interbrand_final.jpg</storyimages>
      <guid>91835</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
