<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>www.exchange4media.com (Fullstory)</title>
    <description>News Marketing India advertising Indian brands tv media newspapers</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright @ 2008 Exchange4media Media Private Limited. All rights reserved</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://www.exchange4media.com/cms/CMS_UploadFile/fullstory/91847.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <item>
      <title>Sahir Khan launches sports communication consultancy - farm communications </title>
      <author>exchange4media News Service</author>
      <pubDate>30/08/2018</pubDate>
      <description>With an experience of almost 18 years in the field of communications, Sahir Khan announced the introduction of a new age sports communication consultancy – farm communications. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commenting on the launch, Sahir Khan, Founder, farm communications said, “With a deep passion for Sports and a profound understanding of this industry, I am thrilled to introduce farm communications. We at farm communications strongly believe, all form of sport in India deserve equal and adequate recognition and needs to be brought to the forefront. farm’s key endeavour is to place India to the forth at global sports arena.”&lt;br&gt;  &lt;br&gt;With a tag line, ‘we produce fresh ideas’, farm is a new-age consultancy that aims to bring fresh perspective in a cluttered and saturated agency world.  farm is a team of handpicked sports aficionados and communication specialists with an immense passion for sports. “We aim to bring in our experience to help brands connect with their customers, communities &amp;amp; colleagues through sports,” said Khan.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Khan has spent a major part of his career working with Perfect Relations spearheading the sports practice. During his career stint of 18 years, Khan has worked closely with sports brands, imminent sports personalities and corporates promoting sports.  He has been instrumental in promoting Motorsports racing in India for JK Tyres, launch of Bhaichung Bhutia Football Schools (BBFS), Chennai Super Kings and devising launch strategy for ISL teams to name a few. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In addition, Khan has successfully handled PR campaigns for big ticket international events like World scrabble championship 2009, Lusofonia Games 2014, India’s first ever F1 event - Power Boat Racing world championship 2004, first Indian International sports summit 2010 to name a few. His recent successful project was India’s first World Squash Open championship 2017, held in Mumbai.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I have been fortunate enough to be able to contribute to the India’s Sports growth story in a small way and hope to continue this endeavour through farm,” Khan concluded.</description>
      <storyimages>https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/article/article_large_image/1535622323_zEEMUl_farm_communications_sports.jpg</storyimages>
      <guid>91847</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
