<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>www.exchange4media.com (Fullstory)</title>
    <description>News Marketing India advertising Indian brands tv media newspapers</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright @ 2008 Exchange4media Media Private Limited. All rights reserved</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://www.exchange4media.com/cms/CMS_UploadFile/fullstory/91849.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <item>
      <title>Zee Anmol continues to dominate U+R Hindi GEC market: BARC Week 34</title>
      <author>exchange4media News Service</author>
      <pubDate>30/08/2018</pubDate>
      <description>Zee Anmol continued to lead the top position in the U+R market in Week 34 of Broadcast Audience Research Council (BARC) India data. The channel registered 805 million impressions. Star Utsav and Star Bharat bagged second and third position with 672 million impressions and 653 million impressions respectively.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colors’ ‘Naagin-3’ continued to lead the list of top five programmes with 15.5 million impressions, followed by Zee Anmol’s ‘Kumkum Bhagya’ on second spot with 12.5 million impressions. Zee TV’s ‘Kundali Bhagya’ and ‘Kumkum Bhagya’ bagged third and fourth spot with 12.2 and 11.2 million impressions respectively.  Star Plus’ ‘Yeh Rishta Kya Kehlata hai’ bagged fifth slot with 10.9 million impressions. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hindi GEC Urban&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Star Plus continues to maintain its leadership position in Urban GEC market with 442 million impressions. Colors stood at number two with 417 million impressions. Zee TV, Sony Sab and Sony Entertainment Television bagged the third, fourth and fifth spots with 356 million, 352 million and 349 million impressions, respectively.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colors’ ‘Naagin 3’ leads the top five programmes in week 34. The show registered 10.7 million impressions followed by Star Plus’ ‘Yeh Rishta Kya Kehlata Hai’ at second spot with 8.0 million impressions and Colors’ ‘Dance Deewane’ on third with 7.4 million impressions. Zee TV's ‘Kundali Bhagya’ stood on number four with 7.3 million impressions and Sab TV’s ‘Taarak Mehta Ka Ooltah Chashma’ on fifth spot with 6.9 million impressions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hindi GEC Rural&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zee Anmol garnered first position with 646 million impressions followed by Star Utsav on second position with 480 million impressions and Sony Pal on third position with 416 million impressions. Rishtey and Dangal TV bagged fourth and fifth position with 392 million impressions and 390 million impressions respectively.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zee Anmol’s ‘Kumkum Bhagya’ bagged the first spot with 10.4 million impressions followed by Star Utsav’s ‘Rabba Ve’ on second spot with 6.5 million impressions and Zee Anmol’s ‘Mahek’ on third with 6.25 million impressions. Sony Pal’s ‘Taarak Mehta Ka Ooltah Chashma’ and Dangal TV’s ‘Mahima Shanidev Ki’ bagged fourth and fifth spot with 6.24 and 4.9 million impressions respectively.</description>
      <storyimages>https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/article/article_large_image/1533203864_YKXhma_barcbiglogo.jpg</storyimages>
      <guid>91849</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
