<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>www.exchange4media.com (Fullstory)</title>
    <description>News Marketing India advertising Indian brands tv media newspapers</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright @ 2008 Exchange4media Media Private Limited. All rights reserved</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://www.exchange4media.com/cms/CMS_UploadFile/fullstory/91846.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <item>
      <title>BANG BANG gears up for 2020</title>
      <author>exchange4media News Service</author>
      <pubDate>30/08/2018</pubDate>
      <description>Launched in 2006 by Roopak Saluja, production company BANG BANG&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;has produced popular spots for brands such as IKEA, Google, Pepsi, L’Oréal, Sony, Unilever, Indigo, Netflix and dozens of others with Ogilvy, JWT, Lowe Lintas, Dentsu Taproot, Wieden + Kennedy and BBH.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;BANG BANG launched its new avatar earlier this year, working with Dentsu India to deliver IKEA’s iconic India launch campaign, being rolled out across media over the coming months. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To announce its #Production2020 mission and evolution, BANG BANG released this high-octane video last week across social media channels. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/UwVxJux-sBs" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaking on the evolution, Roopak Saluja, Founder &amp;amp; Managing Director, BANG BANG (and Group CEO of The 120 Media Collective) said, “It’s hard to overstate the extent of flux our industry has seen in recent years. But wait, there’s more coming. The world needs a recalibrated production model to cater to the needs of 2020. We at BANG BANG have been ramping up to this reality for years and are delivering it here and now in 2018, with commercials at the core but augmented capabilities, backed by a vast body of work, across content, photography, digital, interactive, gaming and more. The one constant is storytelling but there are now a thousand ways to get there.”</description>
      <storyimages>https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/article/article_large_image/1535622285_0ow95H_Bang-Bang_image.jpg</storyimages>
      <guid>91846</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
