<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>www.exchange4media.com (Fullstory)</title>
    <description>News Marketing India advertising Indian brands tv media newspapers</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright @ 2008 Exchange4media Media Private Limited. All rights reserved</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://www.exchange4media.com/cms/CMS_UploadFile/fullstory/91848.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <item>
      <title>White Rivers Media wins Gatsby India’s account for third consecutive year</title>
      <author>exchange4media News Service</author>
      <pubDate>30/08/2018</pubDate>
      <description>Mandom Group’s grooming brand in Asia Gatsby has associated with White Rivers Media for the third time in row. As part of the mandate, White Rivers Media will continue to manage their digital and social media presence across India. The account will be managed by their head office in Mumbai&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since the first year of Gatsby’s association, White Rivers Media has studied their target audience well and accommodated these insights into content, the agency said in a statement. Engaging content on the page is exclusively targeted towards young urban men, which has resulted in an impressive engagement rate, the statement said. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This collaboration aspires to explore different permutation and combinations of engaging content, media spends and ad models to optimise their reach. The agency also plans to strike conversations in the community and sense the sentiment for various messages. These insights will help Gatsby enhance brand management, evolve in their own space and stay ahead of their competitors. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commenting on this win, Shrenik Gandhi, Chief Executive Officer and Founder, White Rivers Digital Media, says, “We have been working closely with team Gatsby for past two years and I am looking forward to a great next year with the brand. While a good portion of our time this year shall be invested in building the brand in the 'traditional digital' manner, special efforts are being taken to capture the new age digital audience via innovative and category first digital activations. I take this opportunity to thank team Gatsby India on the continued trust they have on us.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Talking about the association, Puneet Motiani, Director at Gardenia CosmocarePvt. Ltd. (sole exclusive agents for Gatsby brand in India), said, “The essence of Gatsby lies in its youth. White Rivers Media consists of young blood who thoroughly understand the brand’s persona. A good sense of product market as well as a keen ear to the ground greatly assists in selecting the right target audience and engaging them in a fun and constructive manner allowing for meaningful brand interactions which in turn results in positive and improved consumer experiences.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;He added, “The contests on Facebook, Instagram and Twitter are anything but dull, keeping the audience rightfully engaged through self-expression. The partnership is both, proactive as well as participative due to which high content quality is maintained with a consistent voice and tone. We look forward to working with White Rivers Media Team for many years to come.”</description>
      <storyimages>https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/article/article_large_image/1535626123_5XIBty_white_rivers_collage.jpg</storyimages>
      <guid>91848</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
