<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>www.exchange4media.com (Fullstory)</title>
    <description>News Marketing India advertising Indian brands tv media newspapers</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright @ 2008 Exchange4media Media Private Limited. All rights reserved</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://www.exchange4media.com/cms/CMS_UploadFile/fullstory/91850.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <item>
      <title>Post Office creates Jason Derulo's 'Goodbye' lyric video for Warner Bros. Records</title>
      <author>exchange4media News Service</author>
      <pubDate>30/08/2018</pubDate>
      <description>Mumbai-based Post Office, a venture by Supari Studios, in association with Warner Bros. Records, recently released the official lyric video for the song, ‘Goodbye’ by Jason Derulo. The track enlists a number of artists, with Jason Derulo being accompanied by David Guetta, Nicki Minaj and Willy William. The video has already been viewed over 2 million times, and has generated a buzz with a global audience. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the past, Post Office has worked on creating lyric videos for Dua Lipa’s New Rules (which has garnered more than 3 million views till date), Adam Lambert's Two Fux and Nike's Da Da Ding.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/d-mZwL4Bh6E" rel="nofollow" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to Post Office, the brief received for the video was to have a tropical carnival theme mixed with a chill island vibe,&amp;nbsp;and so they created multiple layouts that would bring out the desired look and feel of love and fun and relaxation. It was ensured that the words of the song were readable at all points through the use of strong, bright fonts centered on the screen, which also lent an upbeat energy to the video.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Subtle animations in the many elements in the backgrounds, as well as beat-matched visual effects were used to add to the dynamic appeal of the video, mentioned a statement issued by the studio.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aditya Tawde, Director, Head of Post Office, says “The idea behind this lyric video was to show the Trinidadian carnival culture mixed with the Tropical Ibiza vibe to create a celebratory environment for the viewer. The moment we got this brief and heard the song, we immediately thought of the vibrant celebration and festive mood.” &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Visually, the goal was to make this film look colourful and capture the grand moments of the Trinidadian festivals amalgamated with Ibiza party life. The biggest challenge was to make the lyrics more legible with overpowering background visuals, which eventually we had to dim down. What really makes this video amazing is to see the visuals coming alive which go along with the melody of the song.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mohit Bhasin, Executive Producer, Post Office, adds “It's always interesting to work with Warner Bros. Records. As a brand, they have a very clear idea of what will work for their audiences. Once we locked on the visual style, it was sheer madness trying to put the whole film together for the release of the track. The end product looks good, WBR was quite pleased with the film too, and that pretty much is the definition of a 'project well done' for us!”</description>
      <storyimages>https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/article/article_large_image/1535627412_QekcyX_Post_Office_Studio.jpg</storyimages>
      <guid>91850</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
