<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>www.exchange4media.com (Fullstory)</title>
    <description>News Marketing India advertising Indian brands tv media newspapers</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright @ 2008 Exchange4media Media Private Limited. All rights reserved</copyright>
    <atom:link href="http://www.e4m.in/cms/CMS_UploadFile/fullstory/91858.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <item>
      <title>#HappyBdayPMModi: From humble beginnings to creating Brand NaMo</title>
      <author>exchange4media News Service</author>
      <pubDate>18/09/2018</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;From helping his father sell tea at a stall near Vadnagar railway station in Gujarat to creating brand NaMo, PM&amp;nbsp;Narendra Modi&amp;rsquo;s incredible journey through his humble beginnings to the Office of Prime Minister has certainly made him the poster boy of Indian&amp;nbsp;advertising. As PM Modi celebrated his 68th birthday on September 17 in Varanasi, wishes came pouring in from politicians, business leaders, sportsmen and film stars across the country.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Starting from the state of Gujarat to various other parts of the country, brand NaMo&amp;rsquo;s mystique clearly symbolises one of his famous quotes, &amp;lsquo;Hard work never brings fatigue, it brings satisfaction&amp;rsquo;.&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Reminiscing his birthday celebrations, exchange4media takes you through brand Modi and his evolving online image, which has contributed successfully in narrating a story of grit, determination and strong leadership, along with setting trends across the globe.&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
With our Prime Minister turning 68, #HappyBdayPMModi has been one of the top trending hash tags on&amp;nbsp;Twitter&amp;nbsp;throughout Monday. Like every year Modi started his day by seeking blessings from his 98 year old mother, Heeraben, followed by an interaction with school students discussing the key aspects of learning in life. Later in the day, a giant 568 kg ladoo was unveiled by Union Minister Prakash Javedekar and his colleague Mukhtar A Naqvi, who also released the book &amp;lsquo;The Making of a Legend&amp;rsquo; in New Delhi. Late in the afternoon, a coffee-table book titled &amp;lsquo;Narendra Modi: A Charismatic &amp;amp; Visionary Statesman&amp;rsquo; was dedicated to India&amp;rsquo;s 14th PM, Modi. The 672-page book offers its readers a look into his everyday routine beginning at the crack of the dawn with his morning tea and exercise till the nightfall when he retires for the day.&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Several public figures and brands also took to Twitter to greet Prime Minister Modi.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-lang="en"&gt;&#13;
&lt;p dir="ltr" lang="en"&gt;Happy Birthday to our PM, Narendra Modi ji! Wishing him good health and happiness always.&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/narendramodi?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;@narendramodi&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&amp;mdash; Rahul Gandhi (@RahulGandhi) &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/RahulGandhi/status/1041557321699282944?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;September 17, 2018&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#13;
&lt;script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-lang="en"&gt;&#13;
&lt;p dir="ltr" lang="en"&gt;.&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/narendramodi?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;@narendramodi&lt;/a&gt; A very happy birthday to Hon&amp;rsquo;ble Prime Minister. I wish him long and healthy life.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&amp;mdash; Arvind Kejriwal (@ArvindKejriwal) &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/ArvindKejriwal/status/1041512666806804480?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;September 17, 2018&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#13;
&lt;script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-lang="en"&gt;&#13;
&lt;p dir="ltr" lang="en"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Amul?src=hash&amp;amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;#Amul&lt;/a&gt; wishes the Hon. PM Narendra Modi a very happy birthday. &lt;a href="https://t.co/aOogZgGfRR"&gt;pic.twitter.com/aOogZgGfRR&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&amp;mdash; Amul.coop (@Amul_Coop) &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/Amul_Coop/status/1041396226279845889?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;September 16, 2018&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#13;
&lt;script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;strong&gt;Modi&amp;rsquo;s vision - Digital India&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
With Modi addressing rallies one after the other, his powerful oratory skills, soon struck a chord with the masses letting his party BJP win by a whopping 282 seats out of 543 in the Lok Sabha Polls, thus crowning him as the Prime Minister of India on May 26, 2014. Since then, a new young India is seen rising with every passing day. Remember, through his speeches Modi made sure to reach out to the aspirational-middle class educated young Indians. Meanwhile, Modi&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Digital India&amp;rsquo; vision has been a frontrunner in India&amp;rsquo;s marathon towards connecting all Indians and thereby establishing a digital empowered society. Among some of his top 10 quotes trending on social media Modi once said, &amp;ldquo;E-governance is easy governance, effective governance, and also economic governance. E-governance paves the way for good governance&amp;rdquo;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;img alt="" src="https://storage.googleapis.com/story-images/92119.jpg" style="width: 600px; height: 324px;" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;strong&gt;Consumer Insight: Schemes under Modi&amp;rsquo;s regime&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-lang="en"&gt;&#13;
&lt;p dir="ltr" lang="en"&gt;Birthday greetings to our Prime Minister &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/narendramodi?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;@narendramodi&lt;/a&gt;. Wish him a long life and many years of dedicated service to the people of the country &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/PresidentKovind?src=hash&amp;amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;#PresidentKovind&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&amp;mdash; President of India (@rashtrapatibhvn) &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/rashtrapatibhvn/status/1041499478350618629?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;September 17, 2018&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#13;
&lt;script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-lang="en"&gt;&#13;
&lt;p dir="ltr" lang="en"&gt;Warm birthday compliments to the dynamic &amp;amp; illustrious Prime Minister of India, Shri Narendra Modi ji. I wish him good health and a long life. May he continue to render for many more years his exceptional services to the nation and guide the country to its glory. &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/narendramodi?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;@narendramodi&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&amp;mdash; Arun Jaitley (@arunjaitley) &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/arunjaitley/status/1041492552128651264?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;September 17, 2018&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#13;
&lt;script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
After declaring note ban, the next big economic move made by Modi Government, certainly witnessed serpentine queue outside ATMs leading to heated debates across the globe on the after effects of demonetisation. The Modi-led-BJP Govt then termed it as a slew of measures taken to curb black money, promote digitisation and attain a less-cash economy if not a cashless one. Even if Modi&amp;rsquo;s push for a cashless economy might seem to be a distant dream now, it looks as if with the growing popularity of brand Modi there&amp;rsquo;s still hope for a cashless future going ahead under Modi&amp;rsquo;s regime. From rolling out schemes like GST,&amp;nbsp;Jan Dhan Yojana, Insolvency and Bankruptcy Code,&amp;nbsp;Modi Govt has rolled out nine key economic policies that define NaMo&amp;rsquo;s tenure so far. He is also famously known for the&amp;nbsp;campaign&amp;nbsp;Swachh Bharat Abhiyan&amp;nbsp;that aims to clean up the streets, roads and infrastructure of India&amp;#39;s cities, smaller towns, and rural areas. He also made&amp;nbsp;linking Aadhaar card mandatory to get benefits of all government services.&amp;nbsp;For good or bad, these policies each delineate the direction of Modi Govt&amp;rsquo;s economic thinking, thereby stating how brand Modi rules despite the cracks.&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;strong&gt;Brand Modi love&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Last year around December, Twitter was also abuzz with prominent CEOs showering praises on Modi&amp;rsquo;s reformist government, as India jumped 30 places into the list, breaking into the top 100 of World Bank&amp;rsquo;s Ease of Doing Business ranking. With &amp;lsquo;Make in India&amp;rsquo; another signature initiative of his, Modi vowed to turn India into a rising &amp;lsquo;New India&amp;rsquo; offering great potential for global investors. Not only this, he was also featured among the 10 most powerful people in the world as per U.S magazine Forbes&amp;rsquo; 2018 list. He was also featured on the cover of the world&amp;rsquo;s most prestigious TIME magazine.&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;strong&gt;Fashion Icon&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Also famously known as the &amp;lsquo;King of Governance, Prime Minister Modi has not taken a single leave till date. Along with re-defining India&amp;rsquo;s future, Modi has made sure that he scores a 100/100 on the fashion score board as well. From bandh-gala suits, Nehru jackets, traditional turbans, pashmina shawl to his signature half-sleeves kurta and churidars, Modi continues to inspire many by his impeccable fashion sense.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
From practising Yoga and making it a global phenomenon to being the first Indian PM to click selfies, brand NaMo continues to break barriers and set trends.&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;strong&gt;Brand NaMo&amp;rsquo;S positioning&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
&lt;br /&gt;&#13;
Brand NaMo has efficiently focused on a single minded proposition clearly positioning itself as a synonym for &amp;lsquo;Development&amp;rsquo;. With this as his vision for Brand India, shouldn&amp;rsquo;t the saffron party be confident of a bigger win in the upcoming 2019 Lok Sabha polls?&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/fEcmWS8UTLM" width="560"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <storyimages>91858-92119.jpg</storyimages>
      <guid>91858</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
