<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>www.exchange4media.com (Fullstory)</title>
    <description>News Marketing India advertising Indian brands tv media newspapers</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright @ 2008 Exchange4media Media Private Limited. All rights reserved</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://www.exchange4media.com/cms/CMS_UploadFile/fullstory/91862.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <item>
      <title>BARC Week 34: Santoor Sandal &amp; Turmeric continues to lead Top 10 brands</title>
      <author>exchange4media News Service</author>
      <pubDate>31/08/2018</pubDate>
      <description>In the BARC Top 10 Brands for Week 34 (August 18-24), Santoor Sandal and Turmeric continued to lead the category with 14,085 insertions. Amazon.In, Harpic and PolicyBazaar.com bagged second, third and fourth spot with 12,873, 11,992 and 11,891 insertions respectively.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social Message - Star Network stood at number five with 11,138 insertions, while Lizol took the sixth spot with 10,169 insertions. Trivago fell on number seventh from third spot this week with 9927 insertions whereas Colgate Dental Cream fell on number eight from fifth with 9280 insertions. Lalitha Jewellery and Wipe garnered ninth and tenth slot with 9199 and 8974 insertions respectively.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the same week, in BARC Top 10 Advertisers, FMCG brands Hindustan Lever and Reckitt Benckiser continued to reign with 1,58,242 and 86,768 insertions respectively. ITC Ltd maintained its third spot with 45,703 insertions. Cadbury India bagged the&amp;nbsp;fourth spot with 28,107 insertions, while Wipro climbed up at fifth position from seventh with 25,650 insertions. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Procter &amp;amp; Gamble and Colgate Palmolive India stood at number six and seven with 25,017 and 23,943 insertions respectively.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brooke Bond Lipton India bagged eighth spot with 22,977 insertions, while Godrej Sara Lee grabbed ninth spot with 22,025 insertions. SBS Biotech slipped to number ten with 21,959 insertions.</description>
      <storyimages>https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/article/article_large_image/1531389250_ASB25b_barcbiglogo.jpg</storyimages>
      <guid>91862</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
