<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>www.exchange4media.com (Fullstory)</title>
    <description>News Marketing India advertising Indian brands tv media newspapers</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright @ 2008 Exchange4media Media Private Limited. All rights reserved</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://www.exchange4media.com/cms/CMS_UploadFile/fullstory/91867.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <item>
      <title>NP Singh elected new IBF President</title>
      <author>Nishant Saxena</author>
      <pubDate>31/08/2018</pubDate>
      <description>NP Singh, CEO &amp;amp; MD&amp;nbsp;of&amp;nbsp;Sony Pictures Networks, has been elected as the new President of the Indian Broadcasting Foundation (IBF), at their 19th Annual General Meeting. He will&amp;nbsp;succeed&amp;nbsp;Punit Goenka, Managing Director, Zee Entertainment Enterprises Limited.&amp;nbsp;Goenka's term has come to an end. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Also,&amp;nbsp;Prasar Bharati&amp;nbsp;CEO Shashi Shekhar Vempati has been&amp;nbsp;elected as the&amp;nbsp;Director of IBF&amp;nbsp;Board.&amp;nbsp;All other&amp;nbsp;office-bearers of the Foundation have been re-elected.&amp;nbsp;However, appointed member Girish Srivastava, Secretary General, IBF, has stepped down from his position.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Singh has over 30 years of rich and varied professional experience. He joined the Sony Group (then MSM) in June 1999 as its Chief Financial Officer and was promoted as its Chief Operating Officer in 2004. In 2014, he was appointed as the CEO.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;He&amp;nbsp;has held several leadership positions across finance and operations verticals in organisations such as Modi Xerox, Spice Telecom, ModiCorp and Hindustan Copper Limited.&amp;nbsp;A Masters from Delhi School of Economics, Singh holds a Bachelor's degree in Commerce from Delhi University. He is a Fellow Member of the Institute of Cost Accountants of India.</description>
      <storyimages>https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/article/article_large_image/1535707378_86Y5CX_NP-Singh.jpg</storyimages>
      <guid>91867</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
