<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>www.exchange4media.com (Fullstory)</title>
    <description>News Marketing India advertising Indian brands tv media newspapers</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright @ 2008 Exchange4media Media Private Limited. All rights reserved</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://www.exchange4media.com/cms/CMS_UploadFile/fullstory/91875.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <item>
      <title>Varun Dhawan is the new brand ambassador for Resiquick Adhesive</title>
      <author>exchange4media News Service</author>
      <pubDate>02/09/2018</pubDate>
      <description>Resiquick, the new instant adhesive&amp;nbsp;brand from Astral Adhesives, has launched a new campaign developed by Lowe Lintas Ahmedabad. Varun Dhawan is the brand ambassador for Resiquick, promoting the adhesive brand in a multi-film campaign.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaking on the campaign, Kairav Engineer, VP – Business Development, Astral Poly Technik said, “Our association with Varun Dhawan for the instant adhesive range is in sync with our brand ethos and identity, which is to innovate and introduce newer products that surprise and delight both, our trade and consumer. It is for the first time in the segment that a brand ambassador is signed on for a Cyanoacrylate-based instant adhesive product, and we are confident that Varun is a perfect fit with his on-screen and off-screen persona”.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The multi-film campaign shows how using a glue that spills can land people in tricky and sticky situations. Varun Dhawan introduces the audience to the hero of the film - Resiquick adhesive, pronouncing its unique benefit of '1 drop at a time' for ease of use and the strong bond it provides with the tagline 'sirf chipkao nahi, jodo'.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commenting on the campaign idea, Sagar Kapoor, Executive Director, Lowe Lintas said, “The Resiquick tube is of superior design. It delivers one drop at a time hence is not clumsy to use. It also has a cap that can be reused, unlike most others in the category. So we decided to focus on the real benefit. Of course, delivered in an engaging and entertaining way. We were fortunate to get Varun Dhawan to help us do that. He lands the cheeky yet honest message of Resiquick. Sirf chipkao nahi, jodo!”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The films are&amp;nbsp;currently live on and offline. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/1PTDKqdwTU4" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/yfE-3CVNnA0" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&lt;iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/v0ZwltzEIBo" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;</description>
      <storyimages>https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/article/article_large_image/1535770174_9RNt1j_Resiquik1_(1).jpg</storyimages>
      <guid>91875</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
