<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>www.exchange4media.com (Fullstory)</title>
    <description>News Marketing India advertising Indian brands tv media newspapers</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright @ 2008 Exchange4media Media Private Limited. All rights reserved</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://www.exchange4media.com/cms/CMS_UploadFile/fullstory/91870.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <item>
      <title>Ogilvy India working on creative mandate for Vodafone Idea Limited </title>
      <author>Venkata Susmita Biswas</author>
      <pubDate>01/09/2018</pubDate>
      <description>exchange4media has reliably learnt that Ogilvy India is the agency on record for Vodafone-Idea Limited (VIL). While VIL did not respond to exchange4media's request for a confirmation, Ogilvy India declined to comment on the matter.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The merged entity that became operational on Friday is expected to come out with a fresh marketing campaign introducing the company to consumers in the next two weeks.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.vodafoneidea.com/"&gt;website &lt;/a&gt;of the new company is now live. The website sports two colours prominently: grey and orange. The colour palette seems to have been arrived at by mixing the colours of Vodafone and Idea Cellular: a rich red and bright yellow.    &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src="https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/1535780577_GmdpSv_voda-idea-sit_%281%29.jpg" style="width:450px;height:332px;vertical-align:middle"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The announcement of the merger noted that both Vodafone and Idea brands, which operate in different markets, will continue to function as separate brands under VIL. The marketing communication is expected to establish VIL as the parent company that nests Vodafone and Idea.</description>
      <storyimages>https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/article/article_large_image/1535698640_WO2sGX_vodaideabig.jpg</storyimages>
      <guid>91870</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
