<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>www.exchange4media.com (Fullstory)</title>
    <description>News Marketing India advertising Indian brands tv media newspapers</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright @ 2008 Exchange4media Media Private Limited. All rights reserved</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://www.exchange4media.com/cms/CMS_UploadFile/fullstory/92150.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <item>
      <title>Realme awards national strategic communication mandate to Grapes Digital </title>
      <author>exchange4media News Service</author>
      <pubDate>19/09/2018</pubDate>
      <description>Grapes Digital, the full-fledged marketing agency has bagged the strategic communication mandate for Realme, following a successful multi agency pitch.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The agency has been entrusted with the task to activate and manage the entire communication strategy and reputation of Realme and elevate the brand's presence to greater heights.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Realme is an emerging smartphone brand that specializes in providing high quality smartphones for the youth. Its latest device, Realme 2 created a new sales record last week by selling 200,000 units in 5 minutes on Flipkart&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The team from Grapes Digital will work in tandem with Realme to get a grasp of the brand philosophy and deliver in alignment with their business goals.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaking on the win, Himanshu Arya, Founder, Grapes Digital, said, “We are excited and geared up to manage the brand communication for Realme. The brand has established itself as a serious player in the budget smartphone market and has won recognition for its ‘Power’ and ‘Style’ product proposition. We are looking forward to creating unique media positioning and driving the brand forward with cutting-edge communication solutions.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaking on the association from Realme, Francis Wong, Brand Director, Realme India said, “We have Grapes Digital as our communication partner on board and we’re hopeful that they will be able to refine our positioning across all channels. The agency showed a lot of potential and we believe that they will deliver seamless communication efficiencies.”</description>
      <storyimages>https://cms.exchange4media.com/files/article/article_large_image/1537350949_wRThEg_collage2_(1).jpg</storyimages>
      <guid>92150</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
